<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726210000 +0000" stop="20250726213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The High Graders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When his tailor is killed in an accident at a supposedly worthless gold mine, Paladin discovers that the man was murdered and his heirs are being swindled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726213000 +0000" stop="20250726220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Randall is rooked out of his bounty by crafty criminal Hunt Willis and his accomplice. Not one to accept defeat, Josh turns detective to rout the outlaws, his investigation dogged by the suspicious sheriff, a cousin to Willis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726220000 +0000" stop="20250727000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Playing The Ponies, Flatfoot Stooges, Snitch In Time, Up In Daisy's Penthouse, A Bird In The Head, Dizzy Detectives</sub-title>
    <desc>"A horse is a Stooges, of course, of course.  , Moe, Larry and Curly take care of the horses.  , The Stooges are carpenters who become policemen.  A mysterious burglar disguised as a gorilla has the cops baffled and Mr. Dill, the head of the citizens league, threatening the police chief's job.  The boys go on the case and pose as night watchmen at an antiques store.  They confront the crook, who turns out to be a real gorilla owned by Dill.  After defeating Dill and some other bad guys in a wild fight, the gorilla drinks some nitroglycerin and blows up. , The Stooges are carpenters who are re-staining some furniture they've delivered to a boarding house.  The plot gets complicated when the boys confront some crooks who are hiding out there.  They defeat the bad guys with the help of the varnished furniture, which sticks the head crook to a chair. , The Stooges escape from jail to prevent their newly rich dad from marrying Daisy, a gold-digger after his money.  Shemp looks like dad, so he impersonates him and marries Daisy.  What the Stooges don't know is that Daisy is in cahoots with some crooks, and they plan to bump off her new husband.  The boys foil the crook's plan and take Pa home to Ma. , The maniacal masters of madcap are back, digitally remastered, repackaged and hilarious as ever. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727000000 +0000" stop="20250727023000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Earth Girls Are Easy</sub-title>
    <desc>"A teenager helps three aliens enter the dating scene in the 1980s."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727023000 +0000" stop="20250727030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>He Meets His Match, The Grisly Ghoul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman and Robin track a female student who joined Joker's gang, but Joker poisons her perfume to cover his tracks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727030000 +0000" stop="20250727040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Mudd's Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise picks up intergalactic conman Harry Mudd and three incredibly beautiful women hiding a dark secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727040000 +0000" stop="20250727043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Olsen's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Jimmy inherits millions overnight, he becomes the target of swindlers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727043000 +0000" stop="20250727050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Clark Kent Outlaw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Clarl Kent pretends to join a gang of diamond thieves in an undercover scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727050000 +0000" stop="20250727060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>My Friend, Mr. Nobody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Penny "imagines" a new companion, which is a disembodied life force living below the surface. Dr Smith accidentally injures Penny leading to the creature taking his anger out on the entire planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727060000 +0000" stop="20250727070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Shape Of Doom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In a race to keep a ship carrying the president out of danger, Nelson and Crane battle a whale that has swallowed an atomic bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727070000 +0000" stop="20250727080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Chase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Inspector Kobick forces the Earthlings to help him deal with a ring of counterfeiters by holding some of their number hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727080000 +0000" stop="20250727090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In an Iron Curtain country, Tony and Doug pose as scientists to investigate a primitive enemy time-tunnel in 1956.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727090000 +0000" stop="20250727100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent's friend stands trial for an invader who vaporized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727100000 +0000" stop="20250727110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Unwelcome Neighbor</sub-title>
    <desc>"A widower and his son move into a nearby valley and refuse friendly advice from Adams and Nakoma, with disastrous consequences."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727110000 +0000" stop="20250727113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cattail Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin visits the Grand Teton Mountains in the U.S. and the wilderness north of Canada to show us the territorial fight, the rescue of a baby moose and to see the sandhill cranes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727113000 +0000" stop="20250727120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>The Philmont Trail</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim make a fascinating climb up the Philmont Trail with a troop of Explorer Scouts at the famous Boy Scout ranch near Cimarron in northern New Mexico."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727120000 +0000" stop="20250727123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Kalahari region of southern Africa, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler study the life and habits of the graceful and cunning leopard by establishing a camp near a hidden leopard den."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727123000 +0000" stop="20250727130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim continue their investigation into the home life of the leopard."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727130000 +0000" stop="20250727133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of Eagles</sub-title>
    <desc>"A valley in the mountain country of the western United States is the territory of the Golden Eagle, America’s largest and most powerful bird of prey.  Marlin and Jim locate an eyrie (nest) of this magnificent bird, and build a blind high on a rocky cliff so they can photograph its nesting habits. Humor and drama are interwoven as the young eagle, in his search for food, follows a skunk into his den…and later finds out that a fast dive at a sitting duck results in his first unwanted bath.  His territory is invaded by a forest fire, and the hunting is made easier as the other animals of the valley flee the flames.  He is trapped by man in a scientific experiment, but later released to continue his life in the “Valley of Eagles.”"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727133000 +0000" stop="20250727140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Giant Armadillo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan journey to Guyana, South America in search of one of the world’s rarest wild animals, the giant armadillo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727140000 +0000" stop="20250727143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Dough Re Mi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg, wanting to make a record, books a recording studio and plans on singing a song with his siblings. However, when Peter's voice begins to change, his hopes of recording are dashed. That is until Greg gets a new idea that just may accommodate Peter's changing voice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727143000 +0000" stop="20250727150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Jan's Aunt Jenny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan discovers her Aunt Jenny looked exactly like her when she was young. She wants a current picture of her aunt to see how she might look in the future, and she's troubled by her discovery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727150000 +0000" stop="20250727153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The Not Making Of The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie goes against Howard and, to get a girl, campaigns for Adlai Stevenson in the 1956 Presidential race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727153000 +0000" stop="20250727160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, Come All Ye Bums</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The gang works to raise money for Frank's annual hobo Christmas dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727160000 +0000" stop="20250727163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes suspicious when a record promoter comes to town to gather material for a folk music album.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727163000 +0000" stop="20250727170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Equal Rights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy and Ethel demand equal rights for women. Okay, say Ricky and Fred at the restaurant: separate checks for the four of them. Thus begins Lucy and Ethel's careers as restaurant dishwashers. So they plot revenge: they'll scare their husbands by claiming to have been robbed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727170000 +0000" stop="20250727173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>June's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June's birthday has Wally and Beaver fighting over what to buy with the $5 dollars that Ward gave them. Wally buys her a wallet while Beaver buys an ugly blouse that June kindly thanks him for, but she has a hard time bringing herself to wear it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727173000 +0000" stop="20250727180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tire Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants to raise chinchillas and begins building a cage in the garage. However, when Beaver changes his mind, Ward tries his best to get Wally and Beaver to clean up the mess. Things get worse when Ward unknowingly runs over some of the wood and nails left laying around with the car, causing the boys to try to patch a flat tire before Ward finds out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727180000 +0000" stop="20250727183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Play The Rams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro gets a date with the Drydales’ new maid, Linda, but she is only interested in the fact that he has a color television set. Instead of paying attention to Jethro, she watches a football game the first night and an ice hockey game the next. Jethro attempts trying out the games, but isn’t very successful at football and doesn’t like the hockey gear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727183000 +0000" stop="20250727190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Shorty Kellems Moves West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Shorty Kellems heads to Hollywood after selling his hotel, silver mine, house and land. Besides the thousand he has for that, he also has two hundred big ones, since the bills are bigger than the ones Jed has. Drysdale is told Shorty's “big” money makes Jed's look like nothing. Drysdale thinks Shorty has $200 million and is desperate to get his money in the bank. He promises Shorty a wild Hollywood party if he deposits the money. Drysdale comes through with the "orgy," and Shorty decides to put his money in the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727190000 +0000" stop="20250727193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Sweepstakes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan has the winning ticket for a South American sweepstakes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727193000 +0000" stop="20250727200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Quick Before It Sinks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Professor thinks that the island is sinking, which causes the castaways to panic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727200000 +0000" stop="20250727203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama And The Big Wheel  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Iola buys a lottery ticket with Mama's change at the store, Mama doesn't care enough to keep the ticket—until Iola wins a chance to spin the lottery wheel for $2 million.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727203000 +0000" stop="20250727210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>More Power To You  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama refuses to pay the electric bill she is disputing, the electric company turns the power off—and the timing couldn't be worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727210000 +0000" stop="20250727220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Farnsworth's Fling / Three In A Bed / I Remember Helen / Merrill, Melanie &amp; Melanesia / Gopher Farnsworth Smith (part 1)  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The crew is in Australia to work on one of the cruise lines ships based there. And a wealthy man named Fransworth has decided to invite his whole family for a reunion. But in actuality he wants to see who among them he should keep in his will.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727220000 +0000" stop="20250727223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Barney's Morale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's overzealous policing enrages the people of Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727223000 +0000" stop="20250727230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Kirk Kirkand- Classic Scifi Tv Props</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727230000 +0000" stop="20250727233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moon Is Not Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the camp facing prohibition and a severe medical supply shortage during another heat wave, Hawkeye resolves to lift morale by importing a racy new movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250727233000 +0000" stop="20250728000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Run For The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Olympic runner assigned to the 4077th fails to materialize, Father Mulcahy must save the camp's honor in a high-stakes footrace against the 8063rd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728000000 +0000" stop="20250728003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Sings The Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria comes home from work one evening in a total apathetic mood. When Archie tries to find out what's wrong with her, she snaps at him and storms off. Later, Edith gets to the bottom of Gloria's mood when she confides in Edith that she thinks that she has temporarily fallen out of love with Mike (something that Edith confesses happened to her and her feelings for Archie). Meanwhile, Archie and Mike prepare for a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728003000 +0000" stop="20250728010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Pay The 20 Dollars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie stops by Jefferson Cleaners to pick up some dry cleaning and pays with a twenty dollar bill. Later, a furious George shows up at the Bunker's front door claiming the bill Archie passed to him was counterfeit. This leads to two separate arguments: one between Archie and George and the other between Edith and Louise. Louise and Edith quickly make up and soon put a plan into motion that would clear up the entire mess between George and Archie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728010000 +0000" stop="20250728013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike's graduation day is coming up fast and Mike is a nervous wreck as he studies for his exams. Surprisingly, Archie begins acting nicely to Mike, since Archie has high hopes that once Mike graduates, he will finally move out of the house and begin repaying Archie the room and board that he owes him. However, as Mike's test results come in, Archie's in for a shock as Mike is offered a fellowship to get his masters degree thus, the Stivics are going to live for one more year with the Bunkers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728013000 +0000" stop="20250728020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Lionel The Live-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Lionel has a fight with his parents and moves into the Bunker's house for a night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728020000 +0000" stop="20250728023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 10/19/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728023000 +0000" stop="20250728030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/22/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728030000 +0000" stop="20250728033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Curse Of The Petrie People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura is given and accidentally destroys a hideous brooch that tells the story of the Petrie family. Will she be able to reconstruct the pin before her mother-in-law's next visit?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728033000 +0000" stop="20250728040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bottom Of Mel Cooley's Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's parents give Laura a Petrie family heirloom: a hideous brooch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728040000 +0000" stop="20250728043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph cuts a record to sweet talk Alice after insulting her mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728043000 +0000" stop="20250728053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>No Time Like The Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A scientist uses time travel in the attempt to prevent past tragedies, both in world history and in his own life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728053000 +0000" stop="20250728060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Bull In A China Shop</sub-title>
    <desc>"A handsome homicide detective is befriended by four old ladies who invite him for tea and proceed to play out a variation of Arsenic and Old Lace for his benefit."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728060000 +0000" stop="20250728070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After completing a mission, Paris is undercover as an American businessman and still in disguise when he is kidnapped by Latin American revolutionaries led by terrorist Robert Siomney. They ask for the release of three prisoners in return for Paris' life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728070000 +0000" stop="20250728080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Corner Of Hell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>On the run from Gerard, Kimble stumbles onto private property belonging to a family of moonshiners. When Gerard gives chase on foot, he too is caught by the backwoods family, and is accused of attacking one of the girls in the family. Kimble has to decide</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728080000 +0000" stop="20250728090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Tender Killing Care</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Spence Johnson's elderly father, who had complained of medical neglect and improper care in a nursing home, dies Spence hires his friend Harry O to help prove he was killed by negligence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728090000 +0000" stop="20250728093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728093000 +0000" stop="20250728100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728100000 +0000" stop="20250728103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Rap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed naively thinks the system can help a young serial car thief who continually skirts responsibility for his actions with the help of his rich father's lawyer. In the meantime, he and Malloy help a woman track down the drug dealer responsible for her boyfriend's fatal overdose, and pull over a stubborn elderly woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728103000 +0000" stop="20250728110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harbor Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy needs to sell two tickets to the ballet after his date cancels, but he quickly regrets putting a notice on the station's bulletin board. While patrolling the harbor and surrounding area, he and Reed investigate a marine fuel dealer accused of forgery, pull over a driver with a suspicious box on the roof of his car, question a suspicious young couple, deal with an astrologer who is driving recklessly and encounter a drunken cook shooting a rifle from the crow's nest of a docked ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728110000 +0000" stop="20250728120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Air Guitar Bill</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill enters an air guitar competition."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728120000 +0000" stop="20250728123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry Hides Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver is staying at the Mondellos, Larry sneaks a peak at his sister's diary and his mother discovers him and yells at him right in front of Beaver. This prompts Larry to run away to Beaver's house, where Beaver secretly hides him in his bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728123000 +0000" stop="20250728130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Pet Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pet fair at school has Beaver feeling left out because he doesn't have a pet, but he tells everyone he does, a parrot. Meanwhile, Ward tries to find a pet for Beaver and buys him a hamster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728130000 +0000" stop="20250728140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Positive Negative</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A respected retired general is blackmailed into declining an offer to clean up the city of San Carlos, which is being tarnished by the operations of mobster George Emory. When Emory turns up dead, the general is the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728140000 +0000" stop="20250728150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.j.  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When radio disk jockey, and Michelle's new boyfriend, Arthur Saxon is accused of murdering a rival, Matlock agrees to defend him. Michelle swears he's the kindest, most gentle man she's ever known, but Matlock soon learns otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728150000 +0000" stop="20250728160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Tragic story of an alcoholic teen who accidentally kills a little girl while she is drinking and driving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728160000 +0000" stop="20250728170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Waltons find out Sheriff Ep is a decorated war hero and John-Boy wants to write about it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728170000 +0000" stop="20250728180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Nina's Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nina Sharky hatches a plan to get away from her tight-fisted father and fortune-hunting husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728180000 +0000" stop="20250728190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Old Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Two men whom Ben once worked with during a gold claim arrive in Virigina City  on opposite sides of the law. Naturally, Ben is caught in the middle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728190000 +0000" stop="20250728193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hangman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict is blamed for a brutal crime despite his claims of rehabilitation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728193000 +0000" stop="20250728200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Of Hate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is out for vengeance when Mark is used as a pawn in a bank robbery scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728200000 +0000" stop="20250728210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jonas Murdock Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Out of meat and low on food, the wagon train must not kill any wildlife or all will face the wrath of local indians. The one holdout is Jonas Murdoch, who has always lived outside the rules and doesn't consider a rabbit an issue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728210000 +0000" stop="20250728220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young OD victim is brought into the ER. A man fakes back pain to get a free ride to the hospital. John gets peeved at all the frivolous calls the squad goes on while real emergency victims need help. A man is shocked after kicking in his TV screen. The ambulance carrying the paramedics and a heart attack victim is involved in a traffic accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728220000 +0000" stop="20250728223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>U.n., The Night And The Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A United Nations delegation tours the 4077th—a Swede, a Hindu and a British officer— and each leaves a lasting effect on the men and women of the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728223000 +0000" stop="20250728230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Bedfellows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th faces a sleepless night as Charles's snoring keeps B.J. and Hawkeye from counting sheep. Meanwhile, Colonel Potter discovers that his son-in-law, Bob Wilson, has had an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728230000 +0000" stop="20250728233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Say No More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A military strategist refuses to accept responsibility for the war games that have mortally wounded his own son. And Margaret develops laryngitis, as she is about to meet her hero, Dr. Chesler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250728233000 +0000" stop="20250729000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Friends And Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter must deal with an old Army friend who is getting his own soldiers killed through his incompetency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729000000 +0000" stop="20250729003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Gentleman Crook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An infamous con artist, held temporarily in Mayberry, manages to enchant everyone except Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729003000 +0000" stop="20250729010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to help Barney express his lovestruck feelings for Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729010000 +0000" stop="20250729013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Gorilla</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly and Jethro both want a gorilla to help out around the house, so Jed asks Drysdale to get them one. Drysdale hires a man dressed as a gorilla to scare the Clampetts, but it fails. They put their new gorilla, Herby, to work doing chores and dress him in old clothes. Mr. Kelly, the man in the gorilla suit, wants out of the deal and gives his suit to Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729013000 +0000" stop="20250729020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Oh My Aching Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph hurts his back at a bowling tournament the night before his physical exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729020000 +0000" stop="20250729023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Major Bonacelli</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Italian officer who studied under Klink helps Hogan photograph an air base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729023000 +0000" stop="20250729030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Dear Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's men plan to surprise him for his birthday by blowing up an ammunition dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729030000 +0000" stop="20250729033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Dust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After selling the rope for a hanging, a conscienceless peddler tries to sell the condemned man's father a bag of "magic dust."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729033000 +0000" stop="20250729043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lover's Leap</sub-title>
    <desc>"The victim of a swindle finds his troubles multiplying when he's accused of murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729043500 +0000" stop="20250729050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729050500 +0000" stop="20250729053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Disappearing Trick</sub-title>
    <desc>"Walter Richmond is a gullible tennis player with a nose for snooping. He meets a woman named Laura Gild and tries to learn everything about her. His curiosity does not pay off when she and her supposedly dead husband scam him for money."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729053500 +0000" stop="20250729060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of M.j.h.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A small-time crook cooks up a scheme for getting rich quick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729060500 +0000" stop="20250729070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cold Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman is kidnapped, drugged and interrogated, her father an ex-spy for the Soviets during the Cold War. A defector now in America, the man hires Mannix to find his daughter in this case of international espionage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729070500 +0000" stop="20250729080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Target In The Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank struggles to prove his friend did not commit murder, but someone (the real killer) is working equally hard to thwart him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729080500 +0000" stop="20250729090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend dupes Betty into caring for her son while she secretly tries to straighten out her life of crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729090000 +0000" stop="20250729093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729093000 +0000" stop="20250729100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729100000 +0000" stop="20250729103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Rampart Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an elusive purse snatcher whose latest victim was visiting her husband's grave. In the meantime, they deal with an annoying former cop turned security guard, encounter a desperate old man attempting to break into a car, help a cantankerous elderly woman who is being evicted, mediate a near-violent dispute over five dollars, track down a runaway baby carriage and search for an armed suspect who just robbed a cocktail lounge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729103000 +0000" stop="20250729110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Foothill Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy, Reed and Sgt. MacDonald go horseback as part of the search for suspects responsible for a break-in at a large ranch. Meanwhile, Sgt. MacDonald offers a reward for the return of his favorite boots, Officer Wells starts a collection for a couple who claims their baby needs brain surgery and the station is attacked by a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729110000 +0000" stop="20250729120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Childhood Classics</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill teaches Toony about the classic children's TV we watched in our youth, from Kukla to Captain Kangaroo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729120000 +0000" stop="20250729123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An upcoming test in history, Wally's weakest subject, has Wally studying all weekend and has Larry and Eddie coming up with a plan that will give them good grades on the test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729123000 +0000" stop="20250729130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Library Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows Beaver to check out a book on his library card but when Beaver loses the book he becomes convinced that Ward will be put in jail, thanks to Eddie Haskell's wiseguy comments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729130000 +0000" stop="20250729140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crafty Kidnapper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alex Tanner and his wife, Patricia, inherent her father's global media empire, things get messy when an obnoxious newspaper man is found dead and the couple's toddler is kidnapped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729140000 +0000" stop="20250729150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Police Officer Jim Shanley is found dead, Sergeant Jerry Reese is charged with the crime. Everyone thinks he's guilty, especially Shanley's partner. In defending Reese, Matlock begins to realize that an old cop buddy of his isn't the man he used to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729150000 +0000" stop="20250729160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Your Own Kind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A sniper fells a girl involved in an interracial romance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729160000 +0000" stop="20250729170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy won the right to accompany news reporters to a news event - the Hindenburg</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729170000 +0000" stop="20250729180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Marry Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Cathcart tries to find a woman for his big brother because family custom dictates that the oldest marries first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729180000 +0000" stop="20250729190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Abner Willoughby's Return</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Former miner Abner Willoughby returns to Virginia City in search of money he buried somewhere in the area years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729190000 +0000" stop="20250729193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Woman From Hog Ridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas shoots a horse thief who turns out to be a member of the Boyle clan, and now Ma Boyle is after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729193000 +0000" stop="20250729200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Seven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Seven condemned murderers escape and take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729200000 +0000" stop="20250729210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Amos Gibbon Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After an argument with Major Adams, Flint leaves the wagon train and cozies up to a bar at a nearby town. What he doesn't know is the locals are shanghaiing strangers for slave labor in a mine and no one on the train knows where he went.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729210000 +0000" stop="20250729220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>905-wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny and Roy answer a pre-dawn call at a small grocery store for a man down, bleeding. Searching the back of the store, Johnny is confronted with a Bengal tiger. A big brush fire threatens a suburban canyon area with lots of domesticated animals and things get dicey all around for the fire department and the Animal Control guys. Rampart becomes a veterinary surgical center for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729220000 +0000" stop="20250729223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give And Take</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded GI learns a painful lesson when he forms a recovery room friendship with the enemy soldier he's critically wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729223000 +0000" stop="20250729230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As Time Goes By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and Hawkeye work on a time capsule to commemorate their time in Korea; Rizzo and B.J. goof around with a fake hand grenade; Klinger becomes smitten with a young, pretty Korean war criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729230000 +0000" stop="20250729233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot Episode</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital (M.A.S.H) unit in Korea, two army doctors by the names of Hawkeye Pierce and Trapper John McIntyre receive some exciting news in the mail. Their Korean house boy, Ho-John got accepted into Hawkeye's old college. Hawkeye and Trapper decide to hold a party filled with music, dancing, and alcohol to raise money for Ho-John's plane trip to the U.S. They achieve this by raffling off a weekend pass with a nurse, Lieutenant Dish for R&amp;R in Tokyo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250729233000 +0000" stop="20250730000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>To Market, To Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After black marketers hijack the 4077th's supply of hydrocortisone, Hawkeye and Trapper concoct a deal with local black marketer, Charlie Lee, to get some more. The catch: Henry's antique oak desk, which they must trade in order to get the medicine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730000000 +0000" stop="20250730003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Housekeepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie go to great lengths to show Aunt Bee what a mess they'd be without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730003000 +0000" stop="20250730010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a handsome new doctor arrives in town, his friendship with Ellie arouses suspicion in Aunt Bee and Barney and jealousy in Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730010000 +0000" stop="20250730013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Come Back, Little Herby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Clampetts don’t have success with the gorilla they took out of the zoo, they decide to get Herby back. They contact Drysdale who tells Mr. Kelly, but he refuses to do it. Mr. Kelly tells Drysdale he’ll return on his own terms and has Drysdale buy him designer clothes and expensive food. Herby returns to the mansion and starts living the life of luxury, dancing and dining with Elly by the pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730013000 +0000" stop="20250730020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is baby-sitting to pay for a phone but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730020000 +0000" stop="20250730023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730023000 +0000" stop="20250730030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a Luftwaffe codebook, but must organize a special mission when Newkirk drops it down a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730030000 +0000" stop="20250730033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Back There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While discussing time travel among friends in 1961, a man suddenly finds himself in 1865—on the date of Lincoln's assassination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730033000 +0000" stop="20250730043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Elusive Element</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A promoter's plan to frame his wife and business partner for embezzlement fails, but they're arrested anyway for his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730043500 +0000" stop="20250730050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730050500 +0000" stop="20250730053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Figures</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bookkeeper decides to come out of anonymity by committing a crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730053500 +0000" stop="20250730060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Death Sentence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman finds a bomb in her car, it convinces her that her husband loves her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730060500 +0000" stop="20250730070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Step In Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is told a murder of a woman he recently witnessed happened a year before. The sheriff insists that maybe the gumshoe is suffering hallucinations. Joe is befuddled until the victim's sister hires him to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730070500 +0000" stop="20250730080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Proxy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man hires Cannon! The man's will requires than an investigator look into his death, so Christopher Grant hires Cannon to see if any of the man's scheming relatives might have helped him to an early exit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730080500 +0000" stop="20250730090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Scapegoat, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer plans to botch the defense of a murder suspect in order to protect the real killer - his own son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730090000 +0000" stop="20250730093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730093000 +0000" stop="20250730100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730100000 +0000" stop="20250730103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>West Valley Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy has his eye on an attractive woman he's seeing all over town walking a scotty dog, which eventually turns out to be bad news for her. Meanwhile, he and Reed assist a police helicopter track down a young man riding his dirt bike in the hills illegally during fire season, search for an armed suspect who held up a movie theater before escaping on a motorcycle and coordinate with the police helicopter in a futile search for two armed robbery suspects who fatally shot a night watchman inside a department store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730103000 +0000" stop="20250730110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Venice Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have to break the news to a young model that her press agent lied when he said there would be nothing wrong with having a nude photo shoot on a busy public beach. Later, they discover a man stealing from a phone booth, assist in the chase of a stolen dune buggy, try help an attractive woman whose safety is put in grave danger by an obscene phone caller, deal with a wino who dies while eating at a diner and pull over a woman towing a large jack-o-lantern.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730110000 +0000" stop="20250730120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Land Of Enchantment</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit New Mexico on the next stop of Toon in With Me's "Trekkin' All 50" tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730120000 +0000" stop="20250730123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Election</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie nominates Wally for class president but Wally has no interest in the position; that is until Ward gives him some encouragement. Wally quickly gets wrapped up in the election and his friends see a change in him—a change that prompts them to vote against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730123000 +0000" stop="20250730130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An old acquaintance of Ward's stops by and offers to paint the trim on the house. However, June and Ward are both apprehensive about the prospect of an alcoholic coming in contact with Wally and Beaver, despite the fact that he says he's cleaned himself up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730130000 +0000" stop="20250730140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Final Fadeout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After an unscrupulous television star decides not to continue with his hit show, the producer is in hot water. It's not surprising that a murder soon occurs, but nothing goes as expected after that.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730140000 +0000" stop="20250730150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730150000 +0000" stop="20250730160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Good Cop, Bad Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil defends Parker after he is falsely accused of police brutality by a drug dealer. The prosecution's main witness - the man's girlfriend, who was once engaged to Parker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730160000 +0000" stop="20250730170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heartbreaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Curtis Willard's sister left her husband to pursue a singing career.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730170000 +0000" stop="20250730180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>A Man A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws threaten to kill one person every day until Matt gets out of town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730180000 +0000" stop="20250730190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Small World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a banker discriminates against midget George Marshall by denying him a job, Marshall, desperate to support his infant daughter, decides to rob the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730190000 +0000" stop="20250730193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pitchman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark finds gold on their property, a fast-talking salesman who tried to sell Lucas a new lightning rod offers instead to buy the ranch's mineral rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730193000 +0000" stop="20250730200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Micah is badly injured by an escaping prisoner, Lucas tracks the prisoner back to his home town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730200000 +0000" stop="20250730210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Trial For Murder: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When an esteemed member of the wagon train is found dead, Adams needs to prevent mob rule and make sure a lawful trial takes place. The accused is not well liked and found passed out with the rifle used in the murder. But is he the killer?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730210000 +0000" stop="20250730220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Stewardess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John falls for a stewardess and shows his stuff when a passenger has a heart attack; later, he tries to date her. The firefighters respond to a motorcycle accident and a chemical fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730220000 +0000" stop="20250730223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Lightweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper and Hawkeye seek to keep a new nurse from being transferred by Hot Lips, and they vie for her affection. Henry Blake, challenged by another commander to a boxing tournament, makes Trapper fight a big, intimidating soldier in exchange for keeping the nurse at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730223000 +0000" stop="20250730230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Chief Surgeon Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Burns complains about Hawkeye Pierce's disrespect, and when Henry appoints Hawkeye chief surgeon, it's to Burns' shock. The rest of the 4077th "coronates" Hawk while Frank and Hot Lips complain to General Barker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730230000 +0000" stop="20250730233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Baker arrives at the camp with his "moose." Hawkeye decides to find a way of getting her away from Baker. He tries ordering him to release her, tries buying her and then resorts to cheating at cards. He releases her but she won't go, so he tries to teach her how to be independent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250730233000 +0000" stop="20250731000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yankee Doodle Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is designated as the setting for the making of an army film on Mobile Army Surgical Hospital units. Hawkeye is chosen as the star while Margaret and Frank compose a screenplay. Hawkeye objects to the piece of propaganda that filmmaker Lt. Bricker is producing and, having exposed the original film, reshoots a new one his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731000000 +0000" stop="20250731003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Plaque For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Pike (Dick Elliott) and the townspeople are shocked to discover that the last living descendant of Revolutionary War hero Nathan Tibbs is Mayberry's town drunk, Otis Campbell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731003000 +0000" stop="20250731010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A by-the-book courthouse inspector condemns Andy and Barney's lack of proper procedure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731010000 +0000" stop="20250731013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed In Politics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is feuding with the Beverly Hills Smog Commission because they tell her she has to stop making her lye soap. Commissioner Tinsley visits the mansion, ordering Granny to quit her soap making, and when she sees him, she threatens him with her shotgun. Jed and Granny visit Drysdale’s office for some help, where Jane tells them they should try to defeat Tinsley on Election Day, and Jed mistakes this as being told he should run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731013000 +0000" stop="20250731020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731020000 +0000" stop="20250731023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Klink Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer for a German suicide squad train bound for the Russian front in order to steal key documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731023000 +0000" stop="20250731030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gasoline War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men plan to destroy a gasoline station that has just been built in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731030000 +0000" stop="20250731033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Invaders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman in an isolated farmhouse is troubled by the appearance of tiny aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731033000 +0000" stop="20250731043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Greek Goddess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is hired by a sculptor charged with murdering the overbearing mother of his model.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731043500 +0000" stop="20250731050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731050500 +0000" stop="20250731053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Festive Season</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man believes that his sister murdered his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731053500 +0000" stop="20250731060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Listen, Listen</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three women have been strangled. Police arrest a stocking salesman as the killer. Mr. Morgan knows who the real culprit is: he has seen the next murder in a dream. He tries to tell people, but no one listens. His wife ignores him as well, which is unfortunate because she is the strangler's next victim."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731060500 +0000" stop="20250731070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Wine From These Grapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An investigation leads Joe Mannix to his hometown, Summer Grove, where he works on a murder case involving the death of a worker during a labor dispute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731070500 +0000" stop="20250731080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Night Flight To Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires Cannon to find out who is using trained dogs to kill the man he served with in Vietnam, and why. It might have something to do with the unit's commanding officer, permanently disabled, perhaps by his own men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731080500 +0000" stop="20250731090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Ransom In Diamond, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The manager of a jewelry-store steals a fortune in order to get a ransom for his kidnapped wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731090000 +0000" stop="20250731093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731093000 +0000" stop="20250731100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731100000 +0000" stop="20250731103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Today's patrol begins with a traffic stop of a high-society cat burglar who's just finished serving a four-year prison term, and Malloy senses the guy is about to return to his old ways. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a standoff with a wounded robbery suspect who fatally shot a convenience store worker, examine an abandoned vehicle, investigate the theft of a book from a library and deal with a distraught unemployed man who takes his young daughter hostage in his home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731103000 +0000" stop="20250731110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Van Nuys Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy returns from vacation sporting a mustache, but finds it difficult getting his colleagues to accept his new look. On patrol, he and Reed respond to a small plane crash by a drunkard that critically injures his young son, investigate the theft of valuable stamps from a mansion, search for a jewelry store armed robber with the aid of a talented witness, deal with a very unlucky purse snatcher and interrogate an evasive department store shoplifter with a big surprise in her purse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731110000 +0000" stop="20250731120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toon Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ship ahoy! Bill and Toony enjoy a luxury cruise, waterslides and all."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731120000 +0000" stop="20250731123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Dance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Beaver and Larry are forced into attending dancing school by their parents and after one lesson, they find that they absolutely detest it, like they knew they would. This prompts them to skip class next time and they hide out behind a barn until it's time to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731123000 +0000" stop="20250731130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry's Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry is furious when Beaver leaves him out when he joins a club called the Bloody Five. To get revenge, Larry makes up a story that he is starting his own club and that people are waiting in line to join. This prompts Beaver to resign from the Bloody Five and he tries to join Larry's bogus club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731130000 +0000" stop="20250731140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Restless Redhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman claims she was menaced by a car driven by a hooded assailant, whom she shot at with a revolver. When the police find a body in a car wreck with a bullet wound, she is wanted for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731140000 +0000" stop="20250731150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Brennan</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock vies with a formidable district attorney while defending a client accused of killing a city councilwoman, discovering a secret hiding in the man's past that is affecting his judgment in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731150000 +0000" stop="20250731160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Maybelle Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Maybelle's new phone sex business is a great success - until one her girls decides to moonlight as a prostitute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731160000 +0000" stop="20250731170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma is in the hospital and Grandpa wants to bring her home</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731170000 +0000" stop="20250731180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Do-badder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of drifters plot to ambush a prospector who's on his way to Dodge after striking big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731180000 +0000" stop="20250731190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Danger Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is forced to confront a former gunnery officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731190000 +0000" stop="20250731193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Baranca</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an outlaw leader lures Marshal Torrance out of town, Lucas is the only one who can stop him from lynching a local man who killed one of the members of his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731193000 +0000" stop="20250731200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Martinet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A former army captain comes to North Fork to kill the man who shot down his son in a gunfight—Lucas McCain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731200000 +0000" stop="20250731210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Trial For Murder: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When the deceased's wife arrives, the people on the wagon train learn that the murdered man has a dark past, and this could be a case of Cain and Abel—or perhaps someone in the dead-man's past came home-to-roost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731210000 +0000" stop="20250731220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Engine Cram</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fireman is injured in a practice drill. Roy and John think they have a buyer for the old fire engine. A man suffers a back injury while riding a motorcycle. A mother pressures Dr. Morton to give her son a prescription. A man having a heart attack walks into the station. DeSoto and Gage rescue a man who has fallen off a cliff on Catalina Island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731220000 +0000" stop="20250731223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731223000 +0000" stop="20250731230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731230000 +0000" stop="20250731233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250731233000 +0000" stop="20250801000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801000000 +0000" stop="20250801003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Saves A Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie encourages and helps a female farmhand to express her femininity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801003000 +0000" stop="20250801010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Forecloses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Grumpy businessman Ben Weaver insists that Andy foreclose on a down-on-his-luck neighbor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801010000 +0000" stop="20250801013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Hair-raising Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor blows the whistle on Granny's mountain-medicine practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801013000 +0000" stop="20250801020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Ralph Kramden, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton invests in Ralph's stock when Ralph wants twenty dollars. When Ralph thinks he is named in a millionaire's will, arguments arise. It turns out Ralph was simply left a pet bird named Fortune, and much of the money was left to the butler and maid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801020000 +0000" stop="20250801023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Unfair Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan kidnaps Burkhalter's sister in order to exchange her for a captured Allied agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801023000 +0000" stop="20250801030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801030000 +0000" stop="20250801033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For Your Thoughts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gaining telepathic abilities when his coin lands on its edge, a mild-mannered bank clerk learns about the difference between other people's plans and fantasies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801033000 +0000" stop="20250801043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Skeleton's Closet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends the ex-wife of an author who is murdered after having written a lurid expose´ on small town secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801043500 +0000" stop="20250801050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801050500 +0000" stop="20250801053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Post Mortem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that a winning sweepstakes ticket is in the suit her husband was buried in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801053500 +0000" stop="20250801060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crocodile Case</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his lover's husband to have her for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801060500 +0000" stop="20250801070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Woman In The Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After inheriting the original manuscript of the first chapter of Marx's "The Capital," Lisa Ralph turns up murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801070500 +0000" stop="20250801080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Come Watch Me Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A mob killer murders Cannon's client. But the killer is someone Cannon will never suspect, and that leaves him unprepared when he is accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801080500 +0000" stop="20250801090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Prime Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby believes that a parolee who served time for hit-and-run charges is connected to a year-old robbery case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801090000 +0000" stop="20250801093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801093000 +0000" stop="20250801100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801100000 +0000" stop="20250801103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While assisting in a tactics training course, Malloy and Reed meet Officer Wells' new partner, an overconfident probationary officer who seems destined to put himself and his colleagues in danger. On patrol, they deal with an unconventional bank robber, come to the aid of a motor officer who is injured during a traffic stop and investigate a credible bomb threat at a grocery store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801103000 +0000" stop="20250801110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Capture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The captain has ordered top priority be given to ending a rash of burglaries in the area, and all signs point to career criminal Reno West. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed use their creativity to neutralize a vicious guard dog at the home of an unresponsive diabetic man, investigate the theft of a jade figurine from a mansion and respond to a domestic dispute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801110000 +0000" stop="20250801120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill, P.i.</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill trains to be a private detective, with a little help from TV history and a real-life private eye!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801120000 +0000" stop="20250801123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally lends his school sweater to Frances and quickly finds getting it back is going to be difficult because the girl keeps making up excuses. Things reach a boiling point when Ward and June overhear Frances bragging to her friends how Wally is chasing after her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801123000 +0000" stop="20250801130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Hypnotist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing someone being hypnotized in a movie, Beaver sets out to do the same. He tries hypnotism on Eddie—who pretends Beaver has hypnotized him—and Beaver gets scared when Eddie won't snap out of the trance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801130000 +0000" stop="20250801140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sleepwalker's Niece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When his stepbrother is found dead, a man is charged with murder and is accused of using his sleepwalking as a cover-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801140000 +0000" stop="20250801150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The P.i.  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A private investigator's daughter shoots some photos that get the wrong man accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801150000 +0000" stop="20250801160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Round</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Forbes is delighted when his fiancée Angela comes to see him, but is disappointed when he realizes that they have very different plans for the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801160000 +0000" stop="20250801170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hiding Place</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A Baldwin relative visits and John-Boy wants to interview her about events in Europe</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801170000 +0000" stop="20250801180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cody's Code</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded outlaw jeopardizes Cody Durham's courtship with Rose Loring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801180000 +0000" stop="20250801190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Jackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Candy faces unexpected troubles when he's left a great deal of money by an old friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801190000 +0000" stop="20250801193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Milly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A new store owner upsets the town by demanding that all credit accounts be paid off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801193000 +0000" stop="20250801200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Cold Cash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The widow of a bandit killed by Lucas plots a grotesque revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801200000 +0000" stop="20250801210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Countess Baranof Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Baranof is desperate to get to Alaska to claim her family fortune, and with no horses she applies her considerable charms on Flint. But she's not the one Flint should worry about, as her bodyguard has a more sinister agenda.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801210000 +0000" stop="20250801220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Election</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John become candidates for a welfare committee. A man gets his arm stuck in an appliance drain while his brother aspirates on a can tab. A delirious child causes problems at the hospital. A sculptress’ model is stuck inside a plaster cast. A construction worker is trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801220000 +0000" stop="20250801223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801223000 +0000" stop="20250801230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801230000 +0000" stop="20250801233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250801233000 +0000" stop="20250802000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802000000 +0000" stop="20250802003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Sam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is suspicious of Mayberry's mysterious new farmer (William Schallert).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802003000 +0000" stop="20250802010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Gets His Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict vows revenge on the man who sent him back to prison: none other than Deputy Barney Fife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802010000 +0000" stop="20250802013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Joins The Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed, who took a job as a garbage man to do something to keep busy, gets a job at the O.K. Oil Company on the Board of Directors after Drysdale talks him into it. He decides to help the company get more oil and money. The clan brings oil from their backyard to donate more oil, and to make some profit for O.K. Oil, they start an airline with the O.K. plane, complete with Jethro as the pilot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802013000 +0000" stop="20250802020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Safety Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph has an accident on his way to receiving his Safest Bus Driver Award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802020000 +0000" stop="20250802023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802023000 +0000" stop="20250802030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802030000 +0000" stop="20250802033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flight 33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial aircraft mysteriously travels back through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802033000 +0000" stop="20250802043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Potted Planter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A jealous husband is teased into a tizzy after being led on by his sister's lies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802043500 +0000" stop="20250802050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802050500 +0000" stop="20250802053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Faith Of Aaron Menefee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's belief in a faith healer leads to an interesting situation for both of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802053500 +0000" stop="20250802060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Place</sub-title>
    <desc>"A bank teller schemes the perfect plan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802060500 +0000" stop="20250802070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Days Beyond Recall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix receives a visit from Jane Haley after her alcoholic brother disappears without a trace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802070500 +0000" stop="20250802080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Alibi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon tries to extract reporter Peggy Angel from a clever frame. Who is the real murderer, and why frame this particular person?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802080500 +0000" stop="20250802090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Uninvited Peril</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty searches for a couple's missing son, unaware that he's a psycho and escaped from a mental hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802090000 +0000" stop="20250802093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Sneaky Ways Of A Woman Who Is Both Beautiful And Smart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Janet Craig, rebuffed as a physician by the local males, sets out to win them over as a woman—and a good cook.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
