<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021170000 +0000" stop="20241021180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Stark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam, the son of one of Dodge City's revered citizens returns. But upon arriving someone takes a shot at him. The man who shot him, Stark, is a bounty hunter. It seems that Adam was in jail in Texas and broke out, and Stark aims to bring him back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021180000 +0000" stop="20241021190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The War Comes To Washoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Adam's differences in politics lead to unrest in the house. When Joe is picked to go to a convention on the statehood of Nevada, will his relationship with a admitted Confederate's daughter weigh his decision?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021190000 +0000" stop="20241021193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Treasure Of Canyon Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In a ghost town, Lucas, Mark and Micah tangle with the Newman family and learn the secret of the town's 20-year-old mystery of a lost gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021193000 +0000" stop="20241021200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Day At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in an explosion, Lucas fights despair as he prepares for a meeting with a gun-toting enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021200000 +0000" stop="20241021210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Shadrack Bennington Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Shadrack Bennington has been a cavalier of the open road, not wanting to be tied down until he joins the wagon train, heading for San Francisco and a future even he couldn't anticipate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021210000 +0000" stop="20241021220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Hang-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A jewel thief is trapped in an air-conditioning duct. Two battered men continue their brawl in the hospital. A man ruins his cast by going surfing. Dr. Brackett treats a woman with a neurological disorder. Radioactivity impedes the rescue of a lab worker. Johnny misses the end of an 'Adam-12' episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021220000 +0000" stop="20241021223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021223000 +0000" stop="20241021230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021230000 +0000" stop="20241021233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021233000 +0000" stop="20241022000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022000000 +0000" stop="20241022003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022003000 +0000" stop="20241022010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Bankrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Myers is about to get evicted by the city council when he discovers an old bond that the city of Mayberry issued 100 years ago. Mayberry now owes him $350,000 and can't pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022010000 +0000" stop="20241022013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is very excited about graduating from the sixth grade. But in order to prevent embarrassment, Mrs. Potts gets help from Drysdale and Diana to get Jethro to miss his sixth grade graduation. She schemes to turn Jed and Jethro’s watches back 45 minutes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022013000 +0000" stop="20241022020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Never Take Your Wife To A Convention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The only thing Oliver learns at a farming convention is how to get a hangover. He and Lisa meet up with Charlie, a former gangster-turned-farmer, and Wanda, his floozy dancer wife. The more Charlie talks about his farm, the more Oliver's convinced that his shady days are not in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022020000 +0000" stop="20241022023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022023000 +0000" stop="20241022030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022030000 +0000" stop="20241022033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022033000 +0000" stop="20241022043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hasty Honeymooner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas Tolliver arrives in California from Oklahoma to meet the woman he was matched up with by a computer dating service. The woman, Miliicent Barton, is supposedly a rich widow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022043500 +0000" stop="20241022050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022050500 +0000" stop="20241022060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Triumph  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When two missionaries arrive at a remote medical mission in the Indian jungle, jealousy leads to murder and a coverup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022060500 +0000" stop="20241022070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Day Filled With Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When a basketball star disappears, his family hires Mannix to hunt him down—before the syndicate does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022070500 +0000" stop="20241022080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Medicine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates a doctors claim that he is innocent of a death he was charged with concerning a patient he was treating that had slipped into a diabetic coma. Cannon becomes involved in a medical malpractice suit when a young resident physician is charged with making the wrong diagnosis on a woman in an apparent diabetic coma who dies after his treatment. Hired by the hospital facing a two million dollar suit, Cannon hears testimony of the accused Dr. Jeff Reston, played by guest star David Birney, that the woman he treated wore a diabetic's bracelet. She was, in fact, suffering from hypoglycemia. But the bracelet disappeared and none of the nurses attending with Reston can back up his story. Reston then gives Cannon a motive for a possible conspiracy against him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022080500 +0000" stop="20241022090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Marathon Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the death of a heavily-insured man that is believed to be an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022090000 +0000" stop="20241022093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hideout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews rushes to the scene when a woman kills a wanted thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022093000 +0000" stop="20241022100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022100000 +0000" stop="20241022103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022103000 +0000" stop="20241022110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022110000 +0000" stop="20241022120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Our Worst Nightmares</sub-title>
    <desc>"A wicked fish gives Bill, Toony, Quizzer, Simon Shock, and Teddy bad dreams!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022120000 +0000" stop="20241022123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Most Interesting Character</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers assigns Beaver's class to write a short essay about the most interesting character they know. While Judy writes about her dad, Beaver debates over whom he should write about. Beaver finally decides to write about Ward, but Beaver isn't sure if Ward is interesting enough.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022123000 +0000" stop="20241022130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Date Committee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally becomes the chairman of the blind date committee for an upcoming dance. However, Wally quickly wants to resign from the position when he can't find anyone to go with the new girl, Jill Bartlett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022130000 +0000" stop="20241022140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Watery Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lorna Thomas is a has-been actress who once gave up her baby for adoption and lived to regret it. George Clark discovers that his wife might be Lorna's long-lost daughter and begins to see dollar signs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022140000 +0000" stop="20241022150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022150000 +0000" stop="20241022160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>First Deadly Sin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial rapist stalks Sparta.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022160000 +0000" stop="20241022170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason helps Verdie research her family tree</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022170000 +0000" stop="20241022180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sam Mctavish, M.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of the first woman doctor in Dodge City, Dr. Sam McTavish, riles Doc Adams. However, she soon wins his confidence and that of his patients, and the two physicians make a startling medical discovery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022180000 +0000" stop="20241022190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss picks up a mail order bride for a friend, but problems arise when the bride decides she has fallen in love with Hoss and has no interest in her husband to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022190000 +0000" stop="20241022193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Two ex-Confederate officers seek revenge on Lucas. McCain was a lieutenant in the 8th Indiana, which defeated the 12th Cavalry 15 years earlier at the Battle of Fort Donaldson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022193000 +0000" stop="20241022200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Assault</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman can't talk his way out of an assault charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022200000 +0000" stop="20241022210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Wagons Ho!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While preparing to return to St. Joseph, the men read the story "Wagon Ho" written and printed by Samuel T. Evans about his trip as a naive young Irishman headed west and his experiences and adventure on the trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022210000 +0000" stop="20241022220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Crash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy bring in a football player who was tackled too hard. A burglar has a heart attack. John wants Roy to apologize for calling him "some kind of nut." Dr. Early treats a hypochondriac. A babysitter brings in a child who has swallowed some pills. Roy and John rescue the occupants of a light plane that crashed in a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022220000 +0000" stop="20241022223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022223000 +0000" stop="20241022230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022230000 +0000" stop="20241022233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022233000 +0000" stop="20241023000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023000000 +0000" stop="20241023003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney On The Rebound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After a tiff with Thelma Lou, Barney is victimized by a scheming young couple.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023003000 +0000" stop="20241023010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023010000 +0000" stop="20241023013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Homer Noodleman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts leave Hooterville after spending Thanksgiving there. They return to their mansion, telling Drysdale and Jane about the boy Elly started dating. When Drysdale hears of this, he decides to get a country boy to come and court Elly. He employs Dash Riprock to play country boy Homer Noodleman. After the Clampetts are introduced to Homer, Granny wants to meet his father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023013000 +0000" stop="20241023020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Computer Age</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate Ralph Monroe joins a computer dating service to meet a husband. Oliver thinks it's a great idea since computers are always right. Lisa thinks they can't possibly take the place of romance, so she challenges Oliver to test their match-up on the electric brain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023020000 +0000" stop="20241023023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everyone Has A Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plot to destroy an ammunition train is foiled by Burkhalter's brother-in-law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023023000 +0000" stop="20241023030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses an incredibly original ruse to get Schultz a weeklong furlough in Heidelberg. While there, Schultz is to deliver needed radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023030000 +0000" stop="20241023033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023033000 +0000" stop="20241023043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The 12th Wildcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Burt Payne coaches and owns 10% of a professional football team. His rich wife, Ellen, owns the remainder. Knowing that he's washed up and needing some quick cash, Burt tries to sell his share of the team to a group of investors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023043500 +0000" stop="20241023050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023050500 +0000" stop="20241023060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From Purgatory  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>In a Brooklyn slum, an aspiring author joins a gang of hoodlums to collect material for a book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023060500 +0000" stop="20241023070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Voices In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A former championship diver, now disabled, believes she is going to be murdered after receiving death threats.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023070500 +0000" stop="20241023080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Iceman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon reopens an investigation when he discovers a convicted man may be innocent, but then refuses parole. Robert Foxworth is the villain. He plays a murderer, an ex-Green Beret who served in Vietnam with overtones of CIA activity. The murdered man was Cannon's friend, and that brings him into the case. When the convicted murderer turns down a parole, Cannon becomes very curious."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023080500 +0000" stop="20241023090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A blind girl is Barnaby's only lead in his search for a missing coed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023090000 +0000" stop="20241023093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's March</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews investigates when a local beautician is blamed for a crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023093000 +0000" stop="20241023100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023100000 +0000" stop="20241023103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023103000 +0000" stop="20241023110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023110000 +0000" stop="20241023120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Murder Mystery...</sub-title>
    <desc>"Someone has killed Mr. Quizzer! Can you solve the mystery? (Don't worry, it's just a game.)"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023120000 +0000" stop="20241023123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Bath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June allow Wally to babysit Beaver one evening while they attend a party. However, things go awry when Beaver gets ready to take a bath. He accidentally lets the bathtub overflow, causing the water to leak onto the bathroom floor and into the downstairs ceiling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023123000 +0000" stop="20241023130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A new school year has the bus service being extended to those students living in town. However, after not even a week, Beaver gets suspended from riding the bus after getting into a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023130000 +0000" stop="20241023140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Garrulous Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry Benton is a hard-luck guy. He gets in an argument in a poker game and knocks Mike Granger out cold. Then he is informed him that Granger is dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023140000 +0000" stop="20241023150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Crook</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Wally McDaniels, a fellow choir member, after he is arrested for killing the man who had turned him in to the police for stealing rare books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023150000 +0000" stop="20241023160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Just A Country Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to Los Angeles to arrest an arsonist. When the man is murdered to keep him from talking Bubba teams up with a pretty insurance investigator to solve the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023160000 +0000" stop="20241023170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023170000 +0000" stop="20241023180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gentry's Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A baron gives Matt trouble when Matt wants the man's sons in jail for a crime they committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023180000 +0000" stop="20241023190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Beginning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe befriends a young man, Billy Horne, a white man captured and raised by the Shoshones. Meanwhile, Milton Tanner goes after a third of the Ponderosa. Seeing that his new friends are in trouble, Billy takes matters into his own hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023190000 +0000" stop="20241023193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Short Rope For A Tall Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are in another town to sell a bull to Joe Lovering. While there, Mark buys two horses from Mr. Schneider. Neither Mark nor his father knows that the horses have been illegally bought and resold to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023193000 +0000" stop="20241023200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Bibs Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor-turned-gunfighter's reputation hangs on one lucky shot—and a lot of gall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023200000 +0000" stop="20241023210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Horace Best Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Adams' "distant" cousin Horace arrives hoping to be a wagon master. His trading skills allow him to steal the crew and vendors from Adams, but when Adams confronts him with the decisions he must make on the trail, there are second thoughts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023210000 +0000" stop="20241023220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Decision (a.k.a. Problem)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John rescue a man whose engine has fallen on him during his car repair work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023220000 +0000" stop="20241023223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023223000 +0000" stop="20241023230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023230000 +0000" stop="20241023233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023233000 +0000" stop="20241024000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024000000 +0000" stop="20241024003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Crime-free Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are honored for achieving the lowest crime-rate in the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024003000 +0000" stop="20241024010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy learns a great deal about Thelma Lou's cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024010000 +0000" stop="20241024013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot-rod Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro wants a new car, embarrassed by the truck. He buys two new cars for two different images he is trying. But Jed tells him to just get a few new parts for the truck. Granny, who is celebrating her birthday, believes that they are planning to replace her. But she learns the truth, and wants the truck to stay the way it was. Jethro ends up getting a whole new front for the truck, and when Jed tells him to fix it, he gets a whole new back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024013000 +0000" stop="20241024020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Liberation Movement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lisa hears a women's liberation speaker, she demands that Oliver share the household chores while she runs the farm. While he meets with nothing but red tape while trying to build a tool shed, Lisa gets the permit and completes the building with ease. A skeptical Oliver is in disbelief that his wife is so successful at "men's work".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024020000 +0000" stop="20241024023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reverend Kommandant Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan sneaks a French pilot's girl into camp and gets Klink to marry them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024023000 +0000" stop="20241024030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Escape-proof Camp I've Ever Escaped From</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Klink's "no escape" record is jeopardized when Malcom Flood, a British escape artist, lands in Stalag 13 and intends to continue his impressive escape record, a plan likely to endanger Hogan's scheduled rendezvous with an OSS agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024030000 +0000" stop="20241024033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024033000 +0000" stop="20241024043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wrathful Wraith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Louise Self finds herself in the unfortunate position of having to stand trial for the murder of her husband twice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024043500 +0000" stop="20241024050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is terrified of falling asleep for fear he might die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024050500 +0000" stop="20241024060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Consider Her Ways  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A physician tries to stop her hallucinatory vision of an all-female society from becoming a reality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024060500 +0000" stop="20241024070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Color Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A witness against a crime boss is murdered just before he can reveal the syndicate's plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024070500 +0000" stop="20241024080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024080500 +0000" stop="20241024090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Circle Of Treachery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>As a thief awaits trial, his accomplice puts out a contract on the only witness to the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024090000 +0000" stop="20241024093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Slain Cabby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews uses taxi drivers as bait for criminals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024093000 +0000" stop="20241024100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024100000 +0000" stop="20241024103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024103000 +0000" stop="20241024110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024110000 +0000" stop="20241024120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Monster Bash!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony throw a spooktacular Halloween Party with the help of a special expert!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024120000 +0000" stop="20241024123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After leaving the cap off the ink, Beaver is grounded to the house for a whole day after spilled ink ruins some of Ward's papers. However, Larry and Beaver sneak out to the movies and when Beaver wins a bike, he must find a way to keep it a secret from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024123000 +0000" stop="20241024130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's class holds a "Most Beautiful Baby" contest in which each student is supposed to bring in a baby picture. To make the deadline, June picks out a cute picture of Beaver at the last minute and sends it to Miss Landers, not realizing that the cute picture may cause Beaver embarrassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024130000 +0000" stop="20241024140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blushing Pearls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mitsuo Kamuri has been seeing a great deal of Grover Nichols, son of wealthy businessman Hudson Nichols. Nichols doesn't approve of his son's relationship and when Mitsuo is "caught" with a string of valuable pearls belonging to Mrs. Nichols, he agrees to absolve her if she stops seeing his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024140000 +0000" stop="20241024150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Murder Game  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to spend the weekend as part of a murder mystery with Cliff, Leanne and three people who each paid $10,000 for the privilege of matching wits with the famous Ben Matlock. When the pretend victim turns up dead, Matlock and his team must determine which of the three paying customers is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024150000 +0000" stop="20241024160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>No Other Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet tries to keep Eugene from giving up when his father faces the death penalty. And the police search for three suspects in connection to a robbery/murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024160000 +0000" stop="20241024170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg; Doctors doubt her ability to walk ever again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024170000 +0000" stop="20241024180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snow Train: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A train that Matt, Doc and Festus are riding is stopped by Indians who request two passengers be turned over to their custody for selling them poisonous whiskey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024180000 +0000" stop="20241024190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Ones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mexican freedom fighters loyal to Benito Juárez take over the Ponderosa, gravely wound Little Joe and force Ben to guide them to a wagon train loaded with gold being smuggled to California by Emperor Maximilian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024190000 +0000" stop="20241024193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024193000 +0000" stop="20241024200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024200000 +0000" stop="20241024210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Albert Farnsworth Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Arrogant British Colonel Albert Farnsworth causes an indian attack that results in the capture of a young girl by the Cheyenne and the mortal wounding of his long time aide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024210000 +0000" stop="20241024220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The station adopts a stray dog, which they name Boot. The firemen rescue a boy from a hole; he turns out to be an abused child. Roy and John rescue another boy whose head is stuck in a basement window. Dr. Early extracts a child's arm from a steering wheel. At a brush fire, Boot helps locate an injured hiker, and then leaves with a hook and ladder truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024220000 +0000" stop="20241024223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024223000 +0000" stop="20241024230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024230000 +0000" stop="20241024233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024233000 +0000" stop="20241025000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025000000 +0000" stop="20241025003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Brief Encounter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Aunt Bee falls for traveling handyman Henry Wheeler, Andy soon learns that Wheeler is not as nice as he appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025003000 +0000" stop="20241025010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Andy's big-city fishing buddies invites him to join the Esquire Club, an exclusive Raleigh men's organization. Barney also is asked to join but tries a little too hard to fit in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025010000 +0000" stop="20241025013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale And Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts and Miss Jane return from spending Christmas in Hooterville to learn that Drysdale has driven after them, along with Fairchild, Elly’s bear. Back in the hills, Drysdale gets arrested for vagrancy and bootlegging in a place called Ripley. When they learn, the people at the bank couldn’t be happier that their boss has been locked up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025013000 +0000" stop="20241025020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Charlie, Homer, And Natasha</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver won't take Lisa to New York for a big party, but the issue isn't over. She conspires with Eb to invent new invisible friends, hoping the scheme will end with a trip to the city to visit a psychiatrist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025020000 +0000" stop="20241025023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan blackmails General Burkhalter to keep Klink from being transferred to the Russian front for failing to keep Hogan from blowing up a radio tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025023000 +0000" stop="20241025030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Colonel Klink's Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink suffers at the hands of a tough sergeant sent to discipline prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025030000 +0000" stop="20241025033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025033000 +0000" stop="20241025043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Runaway Racer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Test driver Pete Griston cracks up a vehicle owned by Pappy Ryan. Pappy accuses Havey Rettig of tampering with the car and files charges against Rettig and Griston. Then Rettig is killed and Griston is found standing groggily over the body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025043500 +0000" stop="20241025050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025050500 +0000" stop="20241025060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Crimson Witness  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Ernest Mullett is a playboy who loses his job, wife and girlfriend to his hated, overachieving brother, Farnum Mullett. Ernest's hatred turns to murder when he decides to reenact the biblical story of Cain and Abel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025060500 +0000" stop="20241025070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The wife of a money man for the mob is killed during a hit-and-run accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025070500 +0000" stop="20241025080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Died Twice</sub-title>
    <desc>"With the help of his former police partner, Frank is asked by his former captain to reopen a case of a corrupt cop who has reappeared after being declared dead years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025080500 +0000" stop="20241025090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A rapist threatens to get more violent with Betty's friend if she tells the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025090000 +0000" stop="20241025093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Insulin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Two hoodlums attempt to murder their former cellmate by withholding his insulin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025093000 +0000" stop="20241025100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025100000 +0000" stop="20241025103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Million Dollar Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a run-in with a suspected professional jewel thief and fear she will walk due to lack of evidence. They also find themselves in competition with a millionaire vigilante, who provides assistance with apprehending a drunk driver and ending a shootout, but seems destined to soon overstep the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025103000 +0000" stop="20241025110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandmothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a hype who robbed a hand-made craft store run by elderly women, only to later return the money after robbing an antique store. In the meantime, they engage in a high-speed pursuit, and pull over a priest in possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025110000 +0000" stop="20241025120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Creepy Carnival</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025120000 +0000" stop="20241025123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward saves an old pedometer from being thrown out and gives it to Beaver, but not before telling him a story about when he was a kid he would walk 20 miles a day. Taking the story literally, Beaver makes a bet with Whitey that he, too, can walk 20 miles in a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025123000 +0000" stop="20241025130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Borrowed Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver spend the day at the lake, which is where they encounter two kids who let them borrow their boat. However, little do Larry and Beaver know, the boat is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025130000 +0000" stop="20241025140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Startled Stallion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy rancher John Brant forecloses on Jo Ann Blanchard's mortgage and takes possession of her prized stallion. Jo Ann goes to Mason for help in getting the horse back but soon needs his aid in getting her off a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025140000 +0000" stop="20241025150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Brennan  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock vies with a formidable district attorney while defending a client accused of killing a city councilwoman, discovering a secret hiding in the man's past that is affecting his judgment in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025150000 +0000" stop="20241025160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Turning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea thinks Virgil needs a new line of work after seeing the aftermath of a deadly shooting at a roadhouse. Virgil finds himself in danger when they arrest the man who committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025160000 +0000" stop="20241025170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Return - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to Walton's Mountain to write about the failing economy and lack of jobs</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025170000 +0000" stop="20241025180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snow Train: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A train that Matt, Doc and Festus are riding is stopped by Indians who request two passengers be turned over to their custody for selling them poisonous whiskey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025180000 +0000" stop="20241025190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Gallagher's Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss helps out two young girls, whose father has just died, by taking them on a journey to their Aunt's place. Unbeknownst to Hoss, one of the girls carries a stolen bag of money and he soon finds out that there are others who are interested in both the money and the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025190000 +0000" stop="20241025193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025193000 +0000" stop="20241025200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025200000 +0000" stop="20241025210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Allison Justis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When someone yells horse thief, Flint shoots a man only to find he is the husband of a childhood friend. Flint learns the man is mayor and highly respected. The question of whether he killed an innocent man bothers him and the man's son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025210000 +0000" stop="20241025220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A photo shoot at the station gets John excited. A country doctor helps Roy and John when they can't reach Rampart on a call. The paramedics rescue a man drowning in a swimming pool and two stuntmen trapped on a waterfall at a movie studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025220000 +0000" stop="20241025223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025223000 +0000" stop="20241025230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025230000 +0000" stop="20241025233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025233000 +0000" stop="20241026000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026000000 +0000" stop="20241026003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pickle Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's canning time again, and Aunt Bee has put up another batch of pickles. After realizing the only thing they're good for is killing flies brave enough to land on them, Andy and Barney decide to substitute store-bought for her homemade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026003000 +0000" stop="20241026010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets an offer to become the sheriff of Greendale, and Andy tries to discourage him. Unsure how to handle matters, Andy gets the idea to let Barney be sheriff of Mayberry for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026010000 +0000" stop="20241026013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Problem Bear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale has come down with the flu after spending so many nights outside while on the way to Hooterville. Granny wants to help him with her Possum Ridge Penicillin, also known as White Lightening. She leaves Drysdale a jug of it, but he puts it to the side and takes a sleeping pill. However, Elly’s bear Fairchild has taken up drinking Granny’s moonshine and climbs into his room as Drysdale is sleeping and drinks the entire jug.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026013000 +0000" stop="20241026020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Lisa's Vegetable Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>According to Oliver, every farm wife should be growing her own vegetables so Lisa starts her own garden. Armed with useless pamphlets from Mr. Kimball and a flask of perfume, Lisa begins work. It's hardly a money-saving proposition after she buys a tractor, farm supplies, and hires Alf and Ralph as her housekeepers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026020000 +0000" stop="20241026023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Top Secret Top Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a top-secret document from Klink's coat to save him from being arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026023000 +0000" stop="20241026030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026030000 +0000" stop="20241026033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Dom Deluise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Dom Deluise. Originally aired on 10/20/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026033000 +0000" stop="20241026043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Police Sergeant Dave Wolfe warns Joe Oliver to stay away from his kid sister, Susan. Now Susan's been beaten up in her apartment, Oliver has been shot to death and Dave is being charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026043500 +0000" stop="20241026050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>And When The Sky Was Opened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When three U.S. astronauts return to Earth after the first flight into space, they begin being erased from history one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026050500 +0000" stop="20241026060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Woodbine Twineth  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Nell Snyder is worried about the bizarre activities of her niece, who claims acquaintance with the "minute people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026060500 +0000" stop="20241026070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Overkill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix gets involved with the case of a serial killer after his friend becomes the latest victim. But not all is as it seems when he discovers the killer may not be responsible for every murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026070500 +0000" stop="20241026080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Touch Of Venom</sub-title>
    <desc>"A group of terrorists have drugged Cannon with a poison, giving him 72 hours to give them a defector and receive the antidote or die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026080500 +0000" stop="20241026090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On Campus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the supposed suicide of a college professor who had been the victim of his student's pranks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026090000 +0000" stop="20241026093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Curse Of Chester W. Farnsworth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe is convinced that the Shady Rest is haunted by a guest who visited 50 years ago, Chester W. Farnsworth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026093000 +0000" stop="20241026100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>That Was The Night That Was</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate Bradley's Shady Rest is patronized by a guest who gives every indication of being from outer space.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026100000 +0000" stop="20241026103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Critter Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke is sick, and Elly calls the "critter doctor" from the zoo. When Jed finds out he is a "college boy," he thinks it is a possible beau for Elly May, not knowing he is a graduate and an older man. Granny is against this doctor coming, and she mistakes a young salesman who is selling bug repellents for the doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026103000 +0000" stop="20241026110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Silver Dollar City Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the first day of the Silver Dollar City Fair, and Granny is working on getting Elly May a husband before Elverna Bradshaw’s daughter gets married. The two women continue to fight and argue, challenging one another more and more. But with the excitement of the fair, Elly enters a few contests, and Granny arranges plots to brag about Elly May.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026110000 +0000" stop="20241026113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Shiver Me Timbers!, Dizzy Divers, Puppet Love</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye is attracted to an old weather-beaten ship bearing a sign "Ghost Ship - Beware" and he explores it with Olive Oyl and Wimpy as his unwilling companions., Bluto attempts to get to sunken treasure before Popeye can., Popeye wants to propose Olive, but he doesn't have the courage to express his feelings. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026113000 +0000" stop="20241026120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Flying Sorceress, Bottles, Advance And Be Mechanized</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom steals a witch's flying broom so he can scare the wits out of Jerry., An old pharmacist falls asleep in his apothecary and dreams about all of the bottles coming to life with some of them good and some not so good., Tom is a space security guard and he uses his cat robot to chase Jerry's mouse robot as it attempts to sneak some cheese out of the Mining Facility."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026120000 +0000" stop="20241026130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Round Trip To Mars, Chilly's Cold War, Swing Your Partner, Phantom Of The Horse Opera, Coming Out Party, The Sleeping Princess, Woody's Magic Touch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody sabotagues Professor Dingledong's Mars rocket so that it won't take off and pretends to be a martian., Chilly Willy is cold and hungry and takes shelter in the home of Colonel Pot Shot where Smedley is the caretaker., Homer drags his horse out of bed to drive his buggy to the barn dance. In anger, Hank breaks up the dance and forces Homer to pull the buggy home., An outlaw disguises himself as a ghost to scare Woody away., Inspector Willoughby repeatedly foils Crash's attempts to escape Sing Song prison., A fairy curses a princess when she's not invited to a royal ceremony., Woody must trick a witch in order to transform the king's son back into a human again."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026130000 +0000" stop="20241026140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Abominable Snow Rabbit, Big Game Haunt, Hyde And Go Tweet, Shishkabugs, The Phantom Ship, The Haunted Mouse, Bewitched Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and Daffy decide to tunnel underground over to Palm Springs. Wrong directions end them up in the Himalayas where they run into trouble with the Abominable Snowman... , Cool Cat gets chased by Colonel Rimfire into a haunted house. They find a ghost who just wants to be friends, but out of fright they run. , Sylvester is sleeping on the ledge outside the office of Dr. Jekyll (whom we see in his office drinking the potion that turns him into a monster). , Yosemite Sam is working as a king's chef when he is asked to prepare a dish made from rabbit. When Bugs Bunny comes over to borrow carrots, Sam decides that Bugs would be perfect for the recipe. , Beans and his stowaway nephews, Ham and Ex, search for a lost treasure on a haunted ship in the frozen North. , A hungry cat goes to a restaurant in search of food. A ghost mouse sees the cat's arrival as an opportunity to get back at all the cats from his life. , Bugs enters the fairytale world to go save Hanzel and Grettel from the witch. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026140000 +0000" stop="20241026150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Infernal Machine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A federal judge is threatened by a bomb-throwing clockmaker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026150000 +0000" stop="20241026160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jose Morales Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Hawkes is leading three wagons through indian territory. They run into trouble with Mexician bandits lead by Lee Marvin. When the two groups must band together to fight off an indian attack, certain biases and assumptions are thrown away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026160000 +0000" stop="20241026170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Jubal Tanner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria sells land to an old friend who has deeply sentimental reasons for owning it, despite the fact that her own sons are part of a plan to flood that land with waters from a dam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026170000 +0000" stop="20241026180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Luke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E08</episode-num>
    <desc>As Luke Dangerfield lies shot and dying, he requests that his protégé, Austin, brings him to Dodge so he can see his estranged daughter one last time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026180000 +0000" stop="20241026190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is seriously injured on a cattle drive and Ben takes him to a nearby town in search of a doctor. To his dismay, Ben finds out that the only doctor available is in jail, waiting to be hung for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026190000 +0000" stop="20241026193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026193000 +0000" stop="20241026200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026200000 +0000" stop="20241026210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Backshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Jefferson aids Rowdy after his horse takes a spill. Sam is a wanted man and asks Rowdy to turn him in but give the $5,000 reward to his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026210000 +0000" stop="20241026213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Episode In Laredo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kovak is reserving the entire hotel in Laredo, Texas for Sam Tuttle, a famous unbeatable gunfighter. After Paladin is forced to kill Kovak, Tuttle must challenge Paladin in order to keep his reputation intact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026213000 +0000" stop="20241026220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Dead End</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher hires Randall to bring back a line rider charged with grand theft. The accused man's father accompanies Randall on the trek to the remote shack where the thief is thought to be hiding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026220000 +0000" stop="20241027000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Hugs And Mugs, Punchy Cowpunchers, Pest Man Wins, Commotion On The Ocean, Hot Ice, Tooth Will Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges run a furniture store and come into possession of a stolen pearl necklace.  Three crooked dames convince the boys that the necklace is theirs, and when the real thieves arrive, the Stooges fight to defend the girl's property.  The Stooges defeat the bad guys and the girls decide to go honest and return the necklace to its rightful owner. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are three soldiers assigned to go undercover and spy on an outlaw gang that's terrorizing a nearby town.  The bad guys have the Arizona Kid locked up, so the boys set about rescuing him with the help of beautiful Nell, his girl.  They free the kid, and he rides to summon help.  The Stooges, with the help of Nell, manage to subdue the bad guys before the kid arrives with the cavalry. , The Stooges graduate from dental school and go out west to open a practice.  Everything goes well until Shemp "cures" an outlaw's toothache from the instructions in a carpentry book, and the boys must leave on the run. , The Stooges are pest exterminators who drum up business by planting vermin in a ritzy mansion where a party is going on.  The boys are hired, but must dress as guests to work unobserved.  They disrupt the party and a wild pie fight ensues.  [Basically a remake of "Ants in the Pantry".  ] , The Stooges are would-be reporters, who are tricked into becoming stowaways by "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that Borscht has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , The Stooges apply for job as 'Yard Men' at Scotland Yard, thinking they'll become detectives, but instead wind up as gardeners.  When they accidentally see a memo about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The bad guys want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027000000 +0000" stop="20241027023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Invaders From Mars</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young boy learns that space aliens are taking over the minds of earthlings."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027023000 +0000" stop="20241027050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Crystal</sub-title>
    <desc>"On another planet in the distant past, a Gelfling embarks on a quest to find the missing shard of a magical crystal, and to restore order to his world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027050000 +0000" stop="20241027060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Horror In The Heights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hindu Rakshasa terrorizes a Jewish neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027060000 +0000" stop="20241027070000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Trevi Collection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch desires to control the world of high fashion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027070000 +0000" stop="20241027080000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Chopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on revenge, a headless motorcycle rider murders those who wronged him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027080000 +0000" stop="20241027090000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Primal Scream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Defrosted ancient cell samples discovered in the Arctic grow into savage prehistoric primates and go on a rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027090000 +0000" stop="20241027100000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The first based on a Native American legend, a Diablero shaman spirit murders for jewels to pay back his debt and be released from his Earthly bonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027100000 +0000" stop="20241027110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>36 Hours</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt race to find the landing device before astronauts perish in the re-entry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027110000 +0000" stop="20241027113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Distraction   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack spies on Kelly, trying to hear who'll she'll take to the dance, she sets up a prank to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027113000 +0000" stop="20241027120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Woman   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Trying to cheer Screech up so he'll complete their science project, Zack pretends to know a girl who is interested in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027120000 +0000" stop="20241027123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a freak accident, Screech can predict the future, an ability Zack uses to his advantage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027123000 +0000" stop="20241027130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Lisa Card   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Lisa splurges with her dad's credit card, she asks the Bayside gang to help get the money back before her dad discovers the shopping spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027130000 +0000" stop="20241027133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Masquerade Ball   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and Slater bet on who can kiss Tori first, and their best chance will come at a masquerade ball. Lisa has a secret admirer, Screech, but she thinks it's Zack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027133000 +0000" stop="20241027140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Weekend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang wins a mystery weekend at a mansion where they will all play a part in a murder mystery. The trouble begins when the game goes awry and Zack is left as the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027140000 +0000" stop="20241027150000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie's Cartoon BOO-Nanza</title>
    <sub-title>House Of Svengoolie's Cartoon Boo-nanza</sub-title>
    <desc>"A collection of Halloween themed cartoons hosted by the The Sven Squad."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027150000 +0000" stop="20241027153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Fonsillectomy</sub-title>
    <desc>Fonzie has to have his tonsils removed and will miss a big Halloween party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027153000 +0000" stop="20241027160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Shirley's Operation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Learning that her appendix is about to burst but not wanting to lose her part in "Alice in Wonderland," Shirley hides while the rest of the play's actors try to find her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027160000 +0000" stop="20241027163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Farmer Takes A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeff Pruitt, a farmer from the hills, comes to Mayberry in search of a wife. He enlists Barney and Andy's help and ends up picking Thelma Lou!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027163000 +0000" stop="20241027170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Thinks Ricky Is Trying To Murder Her</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy is deeply engrossed in a brand-new whodunit, called "The Mockingbird Mystery," and is, understandably, a nail-biting wreck. Having become deeply paranoid that she is in for an imminent doom, Lucy begins to believe that Ricky is trying to murder her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027170000 +0000" stop="20241027173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While his class is reciting a poem about trees, Beaver remembers a tree that Ward had given him for his birthday when they lived at their old house. Wanting "his" tree back, Beaver and Larry go to Beaver's old home and promptly dig it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027173000 +0000" stop="20241027180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Comes To Dinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a surprise when June invites Miss Landers over for dinner and Larry convinces him that something bad might happen. This leads Beaver to become a nervous wreck as he tries to make sure his parents don't do anything to embarrass him. Meanwhile, Larry charges a quarter to anyone who wants to spy on Miss Landers eating dinner at the Cleavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027180000 +0000" stop="20241027183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jane Finds Elly A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny continues her search to get a man for Elly, though fears her mission might be harder with Elly having entered the cake-baking contest. Back at the mansion, Jethro becomes restless in Beverly Hills and decides to join his family in the hills, especially after hearing about the fair going on. Miss Jane comes along, being told by Drysdale to keep her watch on the family and not to let Elly get serious about a man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027183000 +0000" stop="20241027190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Another Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Maria comes to Beverly Hills, making Mrs. Drysdale very excited. But she wants to keep the countess away from the hillbillies. However, it's spring tonic time, and Granny passes it around the neighborhood, including at Countess Maria's house. She falls in love with the brew and visits the Clampetts. They become friends instantly. She starts falling for Jed, and has plans to marry her 6th husband, hoping it is an American.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027190000 +0000" stop="20241027193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous Hollywood producer crash-lands on the island. When he insults Ginger, the castaways stage a "Hamlet" musical play to restore her confidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027193000 +0000" stop="20241027200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch doctor makes voodoo dolls from the castaways' personal affects, which he has stolen from their huts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027200000 +0000" stop="20241027203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Cries Uncle  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The sudden appearance of Carl's nomadic brother, Roy, excites everyone but Mama. Although she seems upset that Roy is popular with the rest of the family, she finally admits her affection for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027203000 +0000" stop="20241027210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Aunt Fran  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Aunt Fran is temporarily given the responsibility of writing an advice column in the local newspaper. Unfortunately, she doesn't have any good advice and comes to rely on Mama to supply material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027210000 +0000" stop="20241027220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Promoter / Judges / Family Plan / Forever Engaged / May The Best Man Win (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 1. A "Marriage-A-Thon" cruise has 25 engaged couples competing for prizes before a mass wedding."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027220000 +0000" stop="20241027223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Keeper Of The Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie joins a secret club that meets in Jubal Foster's barn. When Jubal burns his own barn down, he attempts to blame the group of boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027223000 +0000" stop="20241027230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Rich Correll- Horror/sci-fi Movie Props And Costumes</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rich Correll built a successful career as a comedy actor, director, and producer, but a lifelong passion for horror inspired him to collect some of the Hollywood’s most iconic horror, sci-fi, and fantasy props and costumes. With Rich at her side, Lisa tours Icons of Darkness, a museum where Rich displays hundreds of his favorite pieces for the public to enjoy, like the original raptor from Jurassic Park (1993) and the coveted, highly valuable original Xenomorph costume from Alien (1979). His collection celebrates movie history from the Universal Monster classics to the fun and futuristic hits like Back To The Future. Hollywood memorabilia appraiser and expert, Joe Moe, assigns the highest ever value in Collector’s Call history to Rich’s collection and brings a remnant of Rich’s childhood to offer in trade for an equally rare artifact from Jurassic Park."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027230000 +0000" stop="20241027233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027233000 +0000" stop="20241028000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028000000 +0000" stop="20241028003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria's Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Gloria are having a discussion over who will take care of Joey, just in case there comes a time when both of them are unable to care for the little tyke before his 18th birthday. Mike has serious reservations over allowing in-laws Archie and Edith to get custody of Joey, particularly due to what he perceives as Archie's bad influences. Gloria is having a hard time convincing Mike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028003000 +0000" stop="20241028010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Edith Bunker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith saves a man's life and becomes the toast of the town,but Archie isn't happy standing in the shadow of her limelight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028010000 +0000" stop="20241028013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Secret Passion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith discovers Archie once had a brief encounter with an old high school friend she's invited to dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028013000 +0000" stop="20241028020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie enters Joey in a newspaper's beautiful baby contest, against the express wishes of Mike and Gloria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028020000 +0000" stop="20241028023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Alice Ghostley And Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Alice Ghostley and Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/23/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028023000 +0000" stop="20241028030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Diahann Carroll (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Diahann Carroll. Originally aired on 10/27/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028030000 +0000" stop="20241028033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Uhny Uftz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Did Rob see a UFO?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028033000 +0000" stop="20241028040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Long Night's Journey Into Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura tries to spend the night alone while her family is on a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028040000 +0000" stop="20241028043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is baby-sitting to pay for a phone but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028043000 +0000" stop="20241028050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What You Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A two-bit thug thinks he's found the key to a better life in an old sidewalk salesman who has the uncanny ability to tell people what they need the most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028050000 +0000" stop="20241028060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>An Unlocked Window  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Three nurses care for a patient in a creaky old manor where more than a few nurses have been killed in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028060000 +0000" stop="20241028070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Glass Tightrope</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Working as a stock clerk in a department store, Kimble witnesses his boss, Martin Rowland, accidentally kill a business associate in the parking lot after hours. When Kimble learns that a local vagrant found near the crime scene is the prime suspect, Kimb</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028070000 +0000" stop="20241028080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Code</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincente Bravo, dictator of Nueva Tierra, is planning an invasion against a neighboring democracy, San Cristobal. The United Peoples' Republic is sending Nikor Janos with a coded invasion plan to help Bravo and set him up as puppet dictator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028080000 +0000" stop="20241028083000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The 7th Green</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Highway Patrol exposes a ruthless man who operates a professional hideout for criminals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028083000 +0000" stop="20241028090000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028090000 +0000" stop="20241028093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
