<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322060500 +0000" stop="20250322070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Huntdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is stuck in a farm town with an injured foot, and a group of citizens who seem to be keeping a deadly secret from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322070500 +0000" stop="20250322080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322080500 +0000" stop="20250322090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gold Record For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to preserve his reputation for genius, a rock star kills the ghost writer who always complained for never getting credit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322090000 +0000" stop="20250322093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Honeymoon Hotel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe decides to turn the Shady Rest into a honeymoon haven, after being made a Justice of the Peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322093000 +0000" stop="20250322100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Shoplifter At The Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>With the sheriff on vacation for a few days, Sam Drucker, as Justice of the Peace, sends habitual shoplifter Eustace Pockle to jail—at the Shady Rest!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322100000 +0000" stop="20250322103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Shoplifter At The Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>With the sheriff on vacation for a few days, Sam Drucker, as Justice of the Peace, sends habitual shoplifter Eustace Pockle to jail—at the Shady Rest!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322103000 +0000" stop="20250322110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>His Royal Highness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale invites a king to stay with the Drysdales, paying the Clampetts to stay away. Drysdale plans to set King Alexander up with Elly May and tells Jed the King is visiting them. However, nobody knows that the King is actually broke and working as a servant. Drysdale sets Elly May up with His Majesty, but Mrs. Drysdale, who does not know about the set up of Elly and Alexander, hopes to set up her niece, Doreen, with the King.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322110000 +0000" stop="20250322113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>For Better Or Nurse, Mess Production, Crystal Brawl</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Olive takes a job as a nurse in a hospital, Popeye and Bluto try to impress her., Popeye and Bluto, two rival factory workers, fight each other for privilege of saving Olive Oyl., When Bluto takes Olive to the fair, Popeye disguises himself as a fortune teller to get her attention."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322113000 +0000" stop="20250322120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Heavenly Puss, Stork's Holiday, Fine Feathered Friend</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom arrives in heaven only to find out that in order to enter he must first go back and apologize to Jerry., The stork has problems with anti-aircraft guns when trying to deliver babies in World War II Germany., Jerry pretends to be a chick so the mother hen protects him from Tom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322120000 +0000" stop="20250322130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rock-a-bye Gator, Paw's Night Out, Mouse Trappers, Tomcat Combat, Dig That Dog, Salmon Loafer, Feudin, Fightin-n-fussin</sub-title>
    <desc>"While all the other gators are hibernating, Gabby Gator tries to trap and eat Woody while his guard is down., Paw comes home from a night out and tries to enter the house without waking Maw., Papa Panda unsuccessfully tries to catch a mouse in the house., Philbert the tomcat tries to eat Woody, but Humane Officer Willoughby protects Woody., A man's new, little puppy grows into a giant dog with a digging problem., Chilly steals fish from Smedley's salmon cannery., Woody fights with a hillbilly couple who want to make him their dinner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322130000 +0000" stop="20250322140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>To Hare Is Human, Hop, Look &amp; Listen, An Itch In Time, Slick Hare, The Impatient Patient, Bunker Hill Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wile E. Coyote relies upon a supercomputer to try and capture Bugs Bunny. , A grasshopper casually introduces himself and then gets chased by some crows. , Elmer threatens to give his dog a bath if he doesn't stop scratching, but the poor pooch is the victim of a hungry flea., Elmer Fudd finds Bugs in the kitchen and decides to use him in the meal. , Daffy has the hiccups and goes to Dr. Jerkyl to see if he can help stop them. , The historic Revolutionary War battle at Bagel Heights is fought between Bugs and Yosemite. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322140000 +0000" stop="20250322150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Samurai</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The U.S. State Department is about to return a valuable samurai sword to its rightful owner, a Japanese prince, when it is stolen by an group of sword-wielding assailants. Jim and Artemus must locate the sword and return it to the prince before he leaves the next afternoon, or risk damaging U.S.-Japan relations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322150000 +0000" stop="20250322160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain Sam Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"Tough and headstrong female ferryboat captain Samantha Stewart is asked by her son Johnny and his bride to accompany them on the wagon train to California, where they will board a ship for a Pacific voyage. But actually, Johnny is not telling his proud mother that her doctor has told him that she must stay with a dry climate on land or she will die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322160000 +0000" stop="20250322170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Into The Widow's Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Heath’s boyhood sweetheart comes to town in a traveling show. When her drunken husband turns up murdered, Heath is arrested by the new district attorney, who is out to show that the Barkleys can’t get away with murder despite their wealth and reputation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322170000 +0000" stop="20250322173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cooter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cooter brings Mr. Ben Sissell, a gambler, a drink. A kid accuses Ben of dealing off the bottom of the deck, and draws. The third man at the table, Pate, shoots the kid."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322173000 +0000" stop="20250322180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Killer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Charles Bronson guest stars as a cowardly gunslinger who only goes after old men or young kids who aren't very experienced with guns. But, when Matt Dillon gives him an ultimatum, he shows his true colors."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322180000 +0000" stop="20250322190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Something Hurt, Something Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights' friendship with a neighboring rancher is threatened when their mentally unstable daughter accuses Joe of attacking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322190000 +0000" stop="20250322193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>One Went To Denver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas welcomes his old friend, Tom Birch, who once saved his life, unaware that the man is now a bank robber who is on the run with his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322193000 +0000" stop="20250322200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Wait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Maury, released from Yuma prison, arrives in North Fork intent on getting even with Marshal Torrance, who helped send him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322200000 +0000" stop="20250322210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Geisha</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hey Soos is knocked unconscious by a wild stallion, he awakes in a kimono with a geisha kneeling nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322210000 +0000" stop="20250322213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Lady On The Wall</sub-title>
    <desc>"Paladin stops in the small town of Bonanza on his way through and finds himself accused of stealing a painting of a young, beautiful woman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322213000 +0000" stop="20250322220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Corner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A bounty hunter is not a hero in his own hometown, as Josh learns when he honors a dying friend's request to return his body to Cameron and the townspeople rush to judgment, believing Josh killed him for the reward money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322220000 +0000" stop="20250323000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Back To The Woods, How High Is Up, Three Pests In A Mess, Hula-la-la, Goof On The Roof, Pies And Guys</sub-title>
    <desc>"Set in colonial times, the Stooges are convicted criminals who are banished from England to the American colonies.  When they arrive, they find that the colonists are starving because the local Indians won't let them on their hunting grounds.  The Stooges go hunting any, and after a wild chase, are captured by the Indians.  They escape and another wild chase ensues. , The Stooges are the 'Minute Menders', three tinkers who live under their car.  The boys decide to drum up some business by punching holes in the unattended lunch boxes of some workmen.  When they're caught in the act, they escape and accidentally get hired as riveters on a new building, working on the 97th floor.  Their ineptitude and lousy workmanship screw up construction of the building and they must parachute off the building to escape the wrath of the boss. , A professor attempts to win a bet by turning the Stooges into gentlemen.  After some lessons in etiquette, the boys make their society debut at a fancy party.  They soon revert to their old habits and a wild pie fight ensues. , The Stooges are three inventors trying to a get a patent on their preposterous fly catching invention.  When they learn they'll have to catch 100,000 flies to earn enough to get a patent, some crooks overhear and think the boys are the $100,000 sweepstakes winners.  When the crooks give chase, the Stooges hide in a sporting goods store where Curly shoots a dummy, which they mistake for a real person.  The boys decide to bury the "body" in a pet cemetery, but the cemetery owner arrives from a costume party with his partners, all dressed as spooks, and they proceed to scare the devil out of the Stooges. , The boys run into trouble with the local witch doctor who wants to add their heads to his collection., The Stooges are entrusted with taking care of their friend's house while he goes off to get married.  At first they only wreck the place a little bit, but when they try to install a television antenna, total destruction ensues.  When their friend returns with his bride, she's so shocked she walks out on him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323000000 +0000" stop="20250323023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Creature From The Black Lagoon</sub-title>
    <desc>"A scientific expedition searching for fossils along the Amazon River discover a prehistoric Gill-Man in the legendary Black Lagoon. The explorers capture the mysterious creature, but it breaks free. The Gill-Man returns to kidnap the lovely Kay, fiancée of one of the expedition, with whom it has fallen in love."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323023000 +0000" stop="20250323030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sport Of Penguins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Penguin steals a supposedly priceless parasol and leaves an exploding umbrella for the Dynamic Duo. Meanwhile, he teams with Lola Lasagne, fashion icon, to steal the real parasol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323030000 +0000" stop="20250323040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Let That Be Your Last Battlefield</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise finds itself host to two alien beings from the same planet, who share an intense and self-destructive hatred for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323040000 +0000" stop="20250323050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Primal Scream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Defrosted ancient cell samples discovered in the Arctic grow into savage prehistoric primates and go on a rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323050000 +0000" stop="20250323060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Two Weeks In Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Two aliens, who are actually intergalactic bank robbers, transform themselves into earthlings. They revive a man named Zumdish who operates a tour agency and they pretend to be his clients. When the Robinson's are absent, Dr. Smith turns the ship into a hotel, but he doesn't realize how dangerous his guests are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323060000 +0000" stop="20250323070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Time Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An attempt to turn Admiral Nelson into a human time bomb almost succeeds in creating war between Russia and the United States.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323070000 +0000" stop="20250323080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant scientist and his assistant hunt the Earthlings using a sound detector from which there is no escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323080000 +0000" stop="20250323090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Pirates Of Deadman's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1805, the travelers try to escape from a pirate's Barbary Coast lair before it is shelled by U.S. warships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323090000 +0000" stop="20250323100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Genesis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>David Vincent discovers the aliens have taken over a sea lab for sinister purposes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323100000 +0000" stop="20250323110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Hand</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matthew and Walt go to Las Vegas to investigate rigged games."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323110000 +0000" stop="20250323113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Snow White And The Seven Dorks   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang puts together a hip-hop version of 'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs,' and Zack and Jessie get caught in a serious situation when Lisa catches them rehearsing the final scene—the KISS!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323113000 +0000" stop="20250323120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Dance (part 1)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Kelly gets a job working at The Max but may have to tell Zack it's over between them when she falls for her boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323120000 +0000" stop="20250323123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Aftermath (part 2)   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack seeks revenge after catching Kelly with Jeff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323123000 +0000" stop="20250323130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 1   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie meets her new stepbrother, Eric, soon discovering that he possesses a dark side.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323130000 +0000" stop="20250323133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 2   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie's new stepbrother, Eric, runs afoul of the gang and even takes Mr. Belding's car apart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323133000 +0000" stop="20250323140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fake Ids   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack falls for a college girl, he lies about his age and makes fake IDs so he, Slater and Screech can sneak into an 18-and-over dance club. While there, they see Kelly's boyfriend dancing with another girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323140000 +0000" stop="20250323143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Greg Gets Grounded</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby mentions to Mike and Carol that Greg nearly crashed his car through careless driving. This leads to the suspension of Greg's driving privileges for a week—and on the eve of a big date with his girlfriend, Rachel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323143000 +0000" stop="20250323150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>To Move Or Not To Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>With constant complaints about the size of the house bombarding Mike and Carol, Mike puts the house up for sale and looks into buying a new one. It isn't long after that that the house appears to be haunted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323150000 +0000" stop="20250323153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>R.o.t.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie is named R.O.T.C. squad leader but has trouble controlling his squad. After several warnings to obey his commands, he puts them all on report.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323153000 +0000" stop="20250323160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Day Blind Dates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley unwittingly double-date with two criminals intent on robbing the bank next to the Pizza Bowl, the girls find themselves being held as hostages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323160000 +0000" stop="20250323163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Education Of Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. is back in Mayberry to get his diploma. He is so determined that Andy convinces Helen to allow him to attend class, but Ernest T. isn't exactly classroom material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323163000 +0000" stop="20250323170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Off To Florida</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucy misplaces two train tickets to Florida, she and Ethel consult the classified section, hoping to share a ride with someone driving south. They team up with a peculiar middle-aged woman, Mrs. Grundy, who's bent on getting to Florida in record time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323170000 +0000" stop="20250323173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Monkey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a pet and Ward and June object to his latest one, a mouse. They tell him they can have a sensible pet, so when Beaver and Larry see an ad at the market giving away a free monkey, Beaver jumps at the chance and Ward and June find their house the new home for Stanley, the Monkey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323173000 +0000" stop="20250323180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Finds A Wallet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry find a wallet that contains $89 while on their way to the grocery store to pick up some groceries for June. Surprisingly, Beaver and Larry decide to turn it in at the police station and Beaver finds himself waiting an agonizing week to see if he can keep the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323180000 +0000" stop="20250323183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Super Hawg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale acquires a baby hippopotamus, which the Clampetts see and mistake for a giant hog. However, Elly May knows the difference, realizing that this is a hippo. Granny is desperate to become the owner of this "hawg," knowing how much meat this critter will provide. Drysdale agrees to sell it to the Clampetts, but Granny thinks the price is too high.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323183000 +0000" stop="20250323190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly, The Working Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly gets a job as a secretary at Mr. Drysdale’s bank to ensure proper treatment of the girls working there. But Granny makes her look like a flapper and teaches her wiggle walking, eye rolling and lap setting. Drysdale throws her out, but after he realizes it is his largest depositor’s daughter, brings her back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323190000 +0000" stop="20250323193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan discovers a special tree sap that can be used to make pancake syrup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323193000 +0000" stop="20250323200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gold Strike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Howell discovers a gold mine on the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323200000 +0000" stop="20250323203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Mania  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Naomi's partner in a women's tag team wrestling match is accidentally knocked unconscious by Mama, the pair have no choice but to battle the "Masked Mabels."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323203000 +0000" stop="20250323210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gift Horse  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama's anger over Iola's being upset by the family selling her handicraft at a garage sale leads to Iola inadvertently being given the money collected at the sale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323210000 +0000" stop="20250323220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Bugged</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl refuses to wear clothes; a blind woman thinks a man's attention is pity; a divorced man thinks his cabin is wiretapped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323220000 +0000" stop="20250323223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An old beau of Aunt Bee comes to town to court her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323223000 +0000" stop="20250323230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Bozo The Clown- Tom Holbrook</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bozo the Clown collector Tommy Holbrook has literally written the book on Bozo collectibles. Appraiser Kate Martin will price Tommy's collection of Bozo costumes, Spin-A-Wheel and vintage makeup kit. And new Bozo owner David Arquette drops by to thank Tommy for preserving the Bozo legend."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323230000 +0000" stop="20250323233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Korean Surgeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Syn Paik, a North Korean surgeon, arrives with some wounded, he is passed off as a South Korean by Hawkeye and B.J., but to no avail. Hot Lips and Frank try to convince Potter that Paik is a spy. Paik, Hawkeye and B.J. agree that it would be in the interest of all for him to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250323233000 +0000" stop="20250324000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye Get Your Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After 24 hours of surgery, Hawkeye and Potter venture off to a Korean hospital to lend a hand. Hawkeye is appalled to learn that he must carry a gun. After helping the Koreans, they are shelled on the way back. They scramble from the jeep before it is shelled, and Potter urges Hawkeye to shoot in self-defense, against Hawkeye's will, and he does—into the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324000000 +0000" stop="20250324003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Discovers Women's Lib</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria has been reading books on women's lib and encourages Edith to try a little liberation herself. However, Mike won't take any of her ideas, which leads to huge fight in which Gloria demands that Mike recognize her as an equal partner in their marriage. When Mike refuses to do so, Gloria storms out of the house and moves in with a friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324003000 +0000" stop="20250324010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The First And Last Supper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is all set to go to the Mets game; however, Edith has different plans for the evening after she accepted an invitation to go to dinner with the Jeffersons. When Archie discovers this, he comes up with the excuse that Edith sprained her ankle, thus he turns down the invitation, but this is all in vain, when Lionel suggests Louise bring the dinner over to their house. Meanwhile, Archie discovers that George refuses to break bread with "whitey."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324010000 +0000" stop="20250324013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Saga Of Cousin Oscar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is furious with his houseguest, Cousin Oscar. It seems when they were kids, Oscar bullied Archie and now Oscar is taking full advantage of his visit at the Bunkers. Archie wants to throw him out, but Oscar makes an exit of his own when he turns up dead. This leaves Archie left with the funeral arrangements which drives him up the wall after looking over the costs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324013000 +0000" stop="20250324020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Poses In The Nude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike's artist friend, Szabo, is coming to the Bunker's house for a visit. Archie is a bit perplexed for two reasons. First, he is Hungarian. The other is that he sketches models in the nude. Szabo gets a great idea that Gloria should pose in the nude for him (an idea Gloria is all for). However, Archie is dead set against it and Mike doesn't seem to have any problems with it. That is, until Archie's nagging leads to him having second thoughts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324020000 +0000" stop="20250324023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Petula Clarke And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Moving Day, a young elevator operator has a crush on Carol, who plays it up to make Harvey jealous. Then, in As the Stomach Turns, Carol's soap opera alter ego inherits money from her late, great uncle, but problems arise when her family stops by for a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324023000 +0000" stop="20250324030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Alan King</sub-title>
    <desc>In Sleep No More My Lady, Carol comes home from work, just as Tim gets up to leave, and the two must coordinate in their small apartment. Then, in The Reunion, Carol reunites with a high school friend and tries to convince her she's happy. Finally, in The Session, Carol visits a psychiatrist for the first time and meets a preoccupied analyst.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324030000 +0000" stop="20250324033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stacey Petrie: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's brother returns with exciting and odd news.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324033000 +0000" stop="20250324040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stacey Petrie: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's brother meets his fiancée but things don't go as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324040000 +0000" stop="20250324043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Alice And The Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and Nortons visit the Wedemeyers and the wives believe their husbands are neglecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324043000 +0000" stop="20250324050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324050000 +0000" stop="20250324060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Butterfly  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Bill and Janet Nelson are besieged by the understanding that a troubled neighborhood boy is planning to slay them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324060000 +0000" stop="20250324070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Orpheus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF must stop the faceless killer Stravos in two days' time; only his superior, Bergman, can contact him but even Bergman doesn't know who he really is. Jim plays a U.S. agent and heroin addict who kills another agent and is forced to defect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324070000 +0000" stop="20250324080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Man On A String</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While walking on the road late at night, Kimble comes to the aid of Lucey Russell after her car has broken down. As gratitude, she provides him with a place to stay for the night. But the next morning, the police find the dead body of Lars Adams, a marrie</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324080000 +0000" stop="20250324090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Reasons To Kill (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Framed for murder, Harry battles for his freedom and his life as he tries to unravel a deadly web of corruption."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324090000 +0000" stop="20250324093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324093000 +0000" stop="20250324100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324100000 +0000" stop="20250324103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a difficult night ahead of them when they get stuck with an old patrol car that it is riddled with problems. On patrol, they deal with a female car thief, chase down a prowler with a sympathetic story, pull over a motorist who points out an ironic detail, investigate suspicious activity at a warehouse and pursue an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324103000 +0000" stop="20250324110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Ground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>During a seemingly routine traffic stop, Malloy and Reed are ambushed and kidnapped by two men who are on the run after a foiled robbery attempt. Their only hope is a young woman who is led to believe that Malloy and Reed killed her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324110000 +0000" stop="20250324120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Simply Sylvester</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate everyone's favorite black and white tuxedo cat, Syvlester."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324120000 +0000" stop="20250324123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's Day Composition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver must write a composition about his mother but soon finds himself the only one with a seemingly "boring" mother while Richard, Larry and Judy have colorful mothers. Beaver decides to make his mother colorful, too, even if it means making up things.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324123000 +0000" stop="20250324130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Violet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver finds himself in a most uncomfortable situation when Fred Rutherford practically plays matchmaker and pairs Beaver up with his daughter, Violet. Fred organizes a picnic and invites the Cleavers, which is where the situation culminates into Beaver getting kissed by Violet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324130000 +0000" stop="20250324140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Skeleton's Closet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends the ex-wife of an author who is murdered after having written a lurid expose´ on small town secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324140000 +0000" stop="20250324150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thoroughbred  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the manager of a thoroughbred farm is murdered, her father begs Matlock to represent the mentally handicapped man accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324150000 +0000" stop="20250324160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>My Name Is Hank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A young refugee claims to be the son of a Sparta cop who died in the war. But quickly becomes a suspect in a murder/robbery after he accepts a ride with the criminals who actually committed the crime. Gillespie looks into his story, while Virgil and the boys track down the shooter. Meanwhile, the young man’s presence triggers a surprisingly bitter reaction from Parker, who views him as a painful reminder of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324160000 +0000" stop="20250324170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Theft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The disappearance of some valuable silver pieces throws suspicion on one of the Waltons</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324170000 +0000" stop="20250324173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doc's Revenge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Clem Maddow rides into Dodge. Doc syas to Chester "I'm going kill a man.""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324173000 +0000" stop="20250324180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Preacher</sub-title>
    <desc>"Seth, a newcomer to Dodge is bullied by Keeler, a boxer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324180000 +0000" stop="20250324190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Horse Of A Different Hue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Ben's oldest friends must make sure Joe loses a horse race in order to protect a family member from being killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324190000 +0000" stop="20250324193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark McCain is eager to help lawman Jay Jefferson, who has arrived in North Fork intent on killing an outlaw for the reward, whether he is the right man or not.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324193000 +0000" stop="20250324200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When escaped convicts hold up the general store in North Fork and take Marshal Torrance hostage, Lucas comes to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324200000 +0000" stop="20250324210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Betsy Blee Smith Story</sub-title>
    <desc>"Despite the advice of some Coop decides to visit former girlfriend Eloise Blee, but finds Eloise gone, and instead winds up being talked into posing as her twin sister Betsy's missing husband and father of her baby daughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324210000 +0000" stop="20250324220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Hypochondri-cap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley convinces himself he has arthritis. A man gets his hand caught in his garage door opener. A woman passes out and has an auto accident. The doctors treat a woman infected from plastic surgery gone awry. The station responds to a two-alarm fire at an oil refinery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324220000 +0000" stop="20250324223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Colonel Potter goes to Tokyo on R&amp;R, his horse develops colic. Klinger becomes chronically depressed, and Hot Lips gets appendicitis. The horse is flushed out with a hose, Hawkeye and B.J. perform an appendectomy on Hot Lips, and all are well when Potter returns, except Klinger. Potter offers Klinger a discharge for severe depression, and Klinger gets very excited, which loses him the discharge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324223000 +0000" stop="20250324230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Exorcism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Potter orders Radar to move a Korean spirit post believed to ward off evil spirits, things mysteriously begin to go wrong. When an old Korean man is brought into camp for medical attention, he refuses surgery unless the spirits in the camp are exorcised. A priestess is brought in, who exhibits her dance and her bells and chants. All is well, and Radar returns the spirit post to its original position.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324230000 +0000" stop="20250324233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawk's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hawkeye bemoans the young age of the wounded, he appears to develop problems. Sleepwalking and bad dreams, according to Sidney Freedman, are taking Hawkeye back to a simple time, but the horrors of war continue to intrude. After Sidney's assurances that he is as sane as can be, Hawkeye's life once again seems to settle down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250324233000 +0000" stop="20250325000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Unforgettable Characters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets accepted into the "Famous Las Vegas Writers School," and begins to write his impressions of the camp. It happens to be Frank's birthday, so Hawkeye and B.J. stage a fight with each other to make Frank happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325000000 +0000" stop="20250325003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Bloodhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's attempts to train an old mutt named Blue as a police dog coincide with a manhunt for an escaped criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325003000 +0000" stop="20250325010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In The Middle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Thelma Lou have an argument. They reconcile quickly, but it leads to other arguments between Andy and Barney, Thelma Lou and Helen, Andy and Helen, and another between Barney and Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325010000 +0000" stop="20250325013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick arrives with his daughter, Essiebelle. He found love letters Jethro wrote to his daughter, a beauty contest winner. He plans to get Jethro and Essiebelle married so he can get his paws in the Clampett fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325013000 +0000" stop="20250325020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Lies, Lies, Lies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries to convince his friends that a movie star has invited them all to a barbecue at her house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325020000 +0000" stop="20250325023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Colonel Klink Please Stand Up Against The Wall?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When Carter, in disguise as the camp kommandant, is seen near one of Hogan's operations, Klink is threatened with a treason charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325023000 +0000" stop="20250325030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to capture LeBeau, but not before he lets him complete his mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325030000 +0000" stop="20250325033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Betty White</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama cleans out the attic, and Eunice finds out what happened to her childhood bunny. Then, in Counterfeit Bill, Carol tries to get rid of a fake twenty dollar bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325033000 +0000" stop="20250325043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Singing Skirt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Big Barn is a legal gambling casino run by George Anclitis. Things are going well until George's second banana, Slim Marcus, botches a crooked card game and is exposed for cheating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325043500 +0000" stop="20250325050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Escape Clause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hypochondriac exchanges his soul for immortality and indestructibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325050500 +0000" stop="20250325053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Insomnia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A man seeks an end to the insomnia that is ruining his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325053500 +0000" stop="20250325060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Can Take Care Of Myself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man and his girlfriend run afoul of a gangster, they find their lives in danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325060500 +0000" stop="20250325070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin For A Clown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is on the middle of a fence when it comes to an intense child custody case, in which he is working for the mother while seeing the father dash attempts on his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325070500 +0000" stop="20250325080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Daddy's Little Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon helps fake the murder of a mobster in order to allow the man to testify against his boss."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325080500 +0000" stop="20250325090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Friends Till Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Betty's is now smuggling heroin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325090000 +0000" stop="20250325093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325093000 +0000" stop="20250325100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325100000 +0000" stop="20250325103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Nightwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he can haggle another $12.50 off a used car, but malloy warns him that he's pushing his luck. On patrol, they test a suspected drunk driver who hit a light pole, investigate a home invasion that results in a man fatally shooting his ex-son-in-</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325103000 +0000" stop="20250325110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While off duty following shooting re-qualification, Reed fires his weapon at a would-be unarmed mugger whose armed accomplish drives off. When the would-be suspect later dies, the unfortunate circumstances leave Reed facing a possible suspension and murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325110000 +0000" stop="20250325120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Dance Fever</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill prepares for a very special audition!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325120000 +0000" stop="20250325123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Spot Removers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>For an upcoming dance, Wally is ready to wear a grey suit but when Beaver brings his new friend, Richard, over to the house, he accidentally spills oil on it, leaving a big stain. This leads Richard and Beaver to try to bleach the stain out with disastrous results. Beaver finds himself with another problem, when later Eddie discovers what Beaver is hiding from Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325123000 +0000" stop="20250325130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Model</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver sends his picture in to a modeling agency and they reply with a letter stating they will place his photo in a modeling directory. Soon after Beaver receives another letter this time asking for $30 and when Beaver ignores it, the company threatens legal action."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325130000 +0000" stop="20250325140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Potted Planter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A jealous husband is teased into a tizzy after being led on by his sister's lies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325140000 +0000" stop="20250325150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Model  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock has finally had a breakthrough in the case he was struggling with, but after being hit by a car, he needs to put the case together from scratch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325150000 +0000" stop="20250325160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>King's Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The F.B.I. tries to talk an ex-boxer into testifying against a mobster he once worked for, but the fighter sees the situation as an opportunity for blackmail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325160000 +0000" stop="20250325170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Roots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant worker and his young son stay with the Waltons, causing the son to want his father to give up life on the road</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325170000 +0000" stop="20250325173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>How To Die For Nothing</sub-title>
    <desc>"Zach and Bulow, up with a cattle drive, are raising a ruckus."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325173000 +0000" stop="20250325180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Dutch George</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt's Childhood hero, Dutch George is now the leader of a notorious gang of horse thieves he must now stop."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325180000 +0000" stop="20250325190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Time To Step Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When an older cowhand is relieved of his stressful duties for easier jobs, he gets angry and joins a gang as revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325190000 +0000" stop="20250325193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark manages to capture a hawk, but then falls into danger from a rattlesnake. When a stranger comes to his rescue, the grateful Mark invites the man home, unaware that he is on the run from the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325193000 +0000" stop="20250325200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Three-legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rambunctious teenager wrecks a schoolroom, Lucas McCain, as a member of the North Fork school board, asks the boy's reluctant uncle to pay for the damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325200000 +0000" stop="20250325210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Katy Piper Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie Wooster and Barnaby West have the task of escorting Dr. Katy Piper and her daughters to join up with the Chris Hale wagon train. Barnaby shoots and kills a masked bandit who hijacks the Piper wagon. The bandit turns out to be a teenage boy, and though Barnaby is cleared of any wrongdoing, a sense of guilt weighs heavily on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325210000 +0000" stop="20250325220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Limelight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man with a history of heart trouble becomes agitated when his daughter is trapped under a backhoe. A boy shoots himself with a pellet gun. Another paramedic appears on the news and in the paper, making John jealous. A babysitter has an anxiety attack. Gage and DeSoto rescue Brice from a fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325220000 +0000" stop="20250325223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325223000 +0000" stop="20250325230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325230000 +0000" stop="20250325233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250325233000 +0000" stop="20250326000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326000000 +0000" stop="20250326003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Uniform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred the grocery store clerk repeatedly sweeps trash into the street, even after Barney writes him a citation. Fred threatens that if he ever sees Barney out of uniform, he'll pound him, causing Barney to leave his uniform on at all times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326003000 +0000" stop="20250326010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie finds a lost wallet containing $50, and just as he's waited the seven-day period to claim the money as his own, the owner steps forward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326010000 +0000" stop="20250326013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Lingers On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick returns to the Clampett mansion looking to get rich off Jed's money. He tries to get a job at the bank guarding Jed's money, only to get a few million dollars. But Granny has her doubts about the freeloader, though he seems to be proving her wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326013000 +0000" stop="20250326020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Crazy Legs Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter plans to use Gomer to win the inter-squad competition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326020000 +0000" stop="20250326023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to kidnap Burkhalter to trade him for an underground agent but ends up with Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326023000 +0000" stop="20250326030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Who Stole My Copy Of Mein Kampf?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to eliminate a beautiful allied defector who is giving Klink an award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326030000 +0000" stop="20250326033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Boy Meets Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary who makes ordering lunch an ordeal. Then, in Boy Meets Girl, Harvey tries to pick up Carol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326033000 +0000" stop="20250326043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fanciful Frail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Things keep going from awful to good grief for poor Ethel Andrews. First she's left at the altar by her fiancee, Bruce Strickland, who also lets her take the blame for a $50,000 securities theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326043500 +0000" stop="20250326050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326050500 +0000" stop="20250326053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One Grave Too Many</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is ridden with guilt after he takes a wallet from a heart attack victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326053500 +0000" stop="20250326060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Party Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman shares a party line with two nosy neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326060500 +0000" stop="20250326070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Catalogue Of Sins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate when a psychiatrist is blackmailed after files are lifted from his office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326070500 +0000" stop="20250326080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Conspirators</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon travels to a small town in Texas to investigate a young girl's suspicious death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326080500 +0000" stop="20250326090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Rendezvous With Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to find the son of a South American ruler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326090000 +0000" stop="20250326093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326093000 +0000" stop="20250326100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326100000 +0000" stop="20250326103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>A Fool And His Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy wins $10,000 in a contest to name a new woman's shampoo, resulting in a lot of unwanted advice on how to use the money. On patrol, he and reed deal with a loud music complaint that has a romantic sub-context, encounter a sniper perched atop a parki</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326103000 +0000" stop="20250326110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of A 415</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed return a young runaway to his home while responding to a domestic disturbance call at the same address, discovering a dysfunctional situation that appears to be escalating toward a tragic conclusion. In the meantime, they search for a female drug pusher who mistakes a stranger for a fellow pusher, investigate a man attempting to force his way into a truck and encounter a wino riding a stolen bike at night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326110000 +0000" stop="20250326120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>2nd Annual Toonaween</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate Toon In With Me's second annual Toonaween!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326120000 +0000" stop="20250326123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Businessman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally gets a job selling Igloo ice cream and quickly finds himself giving credit to everyone, including Eddie. However, as the day approaches that his money is to be collected, Wally scrambles to get those who owe him money, to pay up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326123000 +0000" stop="20250326130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Ivanhoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Assigned to read one more book before the end of the school year, Ward suggests Ivanhoe, and Beaver reads it and takes the ideas of knighthood and chivalry to heart. He begins defending girls and begins charging his friends to make them knights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326130000 +0000" stop="20250326140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Witless Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge is accused of murdering a government witness who planned to expose him as a crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326140000 +0000" stop="20250326150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cult  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A concerned father travels from Chicago to Atlanta to reclaim his son from a cult. When the cult leader is found dead, Matlock takes the case on behalf of the father's defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326150000 +0000" stop="20250326160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Epitaph For A Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A longtime friend of the Chief makes threats against a doctor he believes is responsible for his wife's death .When the doctor is killed he becomes the prime suspect. But Gillespie doubts his guilt - even after he confesses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326160000 +0000" stop="20250326170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Chicken Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A local "Robin Hood"" who steals from the ""haves"" and gives to the ""have-nots"" causes a crisis of conscience for John-Boy "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326170000 +0000" stop="20250326173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Prairie Happy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Chester and Matt are out riding when they get shot at by a boy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326173000 +0000" stop="20250326180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chester's Mail Order Bride</sub-title>
    <desc>"Chester's drinking a lot at the Long Branch. A buffalo hunter, Nate takes his picture of a girl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326180000 +0000" stop="20250326190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursued: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights help a family of persecuted Mormons escape with their lives after they are burned our of their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326190000 +0000" stop="20250326193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The McCains try to be tolerant of their embittered neighbor, Abel MacDonald, who tells Lucas to keep off his land and won't allow his son to become friends with Mark. However, McCain decides he's gone too far when he won't allow his injured boy to get medical treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326193000 +0000" stop="20250326200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfounded rumor causes North Fork's outspoken feminist schoolteacher to be attacked by a mob of angry townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326200000 +0000" stop="20250326210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian Girl Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>"A white renegade rides into the wagon train camp with an Indian girl tied to a rope and forced to walk without food or water. He says that he is bringing her back to the tribe where she will be tortured and killed for killing the chief's son. Hawks, in charge of a smaller group until Hale and Coop meet them with the rest of the train, decides to forcibly take the girl from her sadistic captor and keep her with his group, even knowing that this may lead to an attack from the chief's tribe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326210000 +0000" stop="20250326220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>All Night Long</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Gage tries to create his own television game show. An elderly musician experiences heart trouble. When a car runs a stop sign, three injuries result. A tightrope walker gets stuck between two buildings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326220000 +0000" stop="20250326223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326223000 +0000" stop="20250326230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326230000 +0000" stop="20250326233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250326233000 +0000" stop="20250327000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327000000 +0000" stop="20250327003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Sheriff Taylor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers moving to Raleigh for another job. An upset Barney tries to demonstrate to Andy just how bad Mayberry would be without him, creating more harm than good in his effort to get Andy to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327003000 +0000" stop="20250327010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pageant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets the lead role in the Centennial Pageant as Lady Mayberry. She is, however, not up to the challenge, and Andy must find a way to tell her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327010000 +0000" stop="20250327013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Race For Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May enters a Beverly Hills beauty contest, Queen of Beverly Hills, and the Drysdales and Miss Jane try to make sure that she'll win. And when Granny hears it is a race, she is set on entering, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327013000 +0000" stop="20250327020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The Carrier</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter is quarantined with the German measles. He enjoys his time away from Gomer, who visits him in the hospital and soon ends up his roommate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327020000 +0000" stop="20250327023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Hannibal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and the daughter of a German general try to photograph her father's plans designed to prolong the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327023000 +0000" stop="20250327030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>My Favorite Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A baroness is asked by Klink to get secrets out of Hogan, and he complies by giving her a British agent with phony invasion plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327030000 +0000" stop="20250327033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Fruitcake, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball is thrown out of the house for playing poker. Then, in The Fruitcake, Carol tries to avoid a nervous breakdown, despite her husband's annoying behavior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327033000 +0000" stop="20250327043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crying Cherub</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A valuable Matisse painting is stolen from a museum. When the thief is found murdered, museum employee June Sinclair and her boyfriend, David Lambert, are charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327043500 +0000" stop="20250327050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327050500 +0000" stop="20250327053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cell 227</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An innocent man faces death in the gas chamber for the death of a girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327053500 +0000" stop="20250327060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Schartz-metterklume Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a governess at the Wellington household has surprising results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327060500 +0000" stop="20250327070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Turn Every Stone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A million-dollar libel suit against a crusading publisher may be tied to the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327070500 +0000" stop="20250327080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin Corner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon gets hired to be a bodyguard for a courier of securities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327080500 +0000" stop="20250327090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple murders young men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327090000 +0000" stop="20250327093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327093000 +0000" stop="20250327100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - Dr-33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Crosby plays a hippie whose wife has been persuaded—by other hippies—to pass bad checks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327100000 +0000" stop="20250327103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Keeping Tabs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are stunned to discover that the driver who led them on a high-speed chase is the son of Sgt. MacDonald, and Malloy takes it upon himself to help his boss figure out why the young man is acting out. In the meantime, they investigate a possible burglary in progress at an apartment building, mediate a dispute at a park over an elderly woman feeding ducks, respond to a call of two armed men fighting over a woman and deal with a wino who is attempting to direct traffic at a busy intersection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327103000 +0000" stop="20250327110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Rap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed naively thinks the system can help a young serial car thief who continually skirts responsibility for his actions with the help of his rich father's lawyer. In the meantime, he and Malloy help a woman track down the drug dealer responsible for her boyfriend's fatal overdose, and pull over a stubborn elderly woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327110000 +0000" stop="20250327120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1991</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327120000 +0000" stop="20250327123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has joined an all-male club at school and learns that they are putting on a play. He's not too happy when he learns that the part he's supposed to play is that of a chorus girl. Later, Beaver and Gilbert make matters worse when they stumble upon Wally's costume, a dress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327123000 +0000" stop="20250327130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Day Of School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>The last day of school has each one of Miss Landers' students bringing her a gift. June orders some nice handkerchiefs for the gift and a slip for herself. Beaver mistakes the slip as the gift for Miss Landers and debates on whether or not to give her this very "personal" gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327130000 +0000" stop="20250327140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nebulous Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A scam to swindle elderly relatives and a pang of conscience leads to a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327140000 +0000" stop="20250327150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Priest  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends when a mobster is accused of murdering a priest. It doesn't take long before Matlock suspects that the Church is covering something up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327150000 +0000" stop="20250327160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his wife and her lover after he catches them together, then flees to a remote cabin with his daughter who does not know what he has done. The chief and the boys hope to talk him into surrendering without resorting to violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327160000 +0000" stop="20250327170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>As the Waltons prepare their entries for the local fair, an old suitor of Olivia's visits</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327170000 +0000" stop="20250327173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar</sub-title>
    <desc>"Augie Shart and Gene Tyler a couple of drunks try to hang Weed Pindle from Texas once they find he fought for the Union."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327173000 +0000" stop="20250327180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cara</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc tends Cara, who slashed her forearm, to make it look like a suicide attempt. She asks for Matt. They haven't seen each other in twelve years since Yuma. Cara wants to stay awhile. Kitty doesn't want to hear about Matt's old flame."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327180000 +0000" stop="20250327190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursued: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights help a family of persecuted Mormons escape with their lives after they are burned our of their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327190000 +0000" stop="20250327193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When his employer begins to suspect him of embezzlement, bookkeeper Asa Manning decides to hire a professional gunman to take care of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327193000 +0000" stop="20250327200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Although a drought has forced local cowhands to seek work on a railroad construction project, railroad executives are afraid that their workers will desert them if they believe an old man's claim that he has found a way to make rain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327200000 +0000" stop="20250327210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop tells Bill the story of the Earp brothers and the Silver Lady, a woman who was encased in a coffin of sliver coins that melted around her after the stagecoach she was riding on and guarded by Morgan Earp had an accident and burned."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327210000 +0000" stop="20250327220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Steel Inferno, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A careless worker sparks an explosive fire in a high-rise building. Station 110 leads a full alarm response, assisted by Squad 51. A triage team from Rampart Hospital, led by Dr. Brackett, sets up in a nearby garage. Several workmen and two women including the fiancee of a paramedic remain trapped on the 16th floor. A Coast Guard helicopter assists in rooftop evacuation; Dixie and Dr. Early take charge of the many patients at Rampart. A paramedic is injured attempting a rescue, while Gage and DeSoto extricate themselves from a broken elevator. An explosion on the 21st floor injures a fire captain, necessitating a dangerous rescue down an elevator shaft."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327220000 +0000" stop="20250327223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327223000 +0000" stop="20250327230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327230000 +0000" stop="20250327233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250327233000 +0000" stop="20250328000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328000000 +0000" stop="20250328003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darling Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Darlings come to Mayberry looking for a boy whom they could engage to Charlene's new baby. Opie becomes the prime target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328003000 +0000" stop="20250328010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328010000 +0000" stop="20250328013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is looking for a beau for his gorgeous daughter, so Drysdale and Jane set Elly up with Fred Penrod, a young accountant at the bank. However, no one can seem to get his name straight. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns to plant a paw-paw tree in the back yard, really to look for the Clampett fortune he still believes is buried in the back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328013000 +0000" stop="20250328020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Caution: Low Overhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter sets out to expose a fraud by proving to Gomer that the man who sold him a cheap watch is a crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328020000 +0000" stop="20250328023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Watch The Trains Go By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for Burkhalter's sister to keep Klink occupied, so he can leave camp and blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328023000 +0000" stop="20250328030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Old Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses the car of an SS man who's just married Klink's old girlfriend and is honeymooning in Paris, where Hogan needs to pass radios to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328030000 +0000" stop="20250328033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Glen Campbell</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Guinea Pig, Carol searches for a cure for Swine Flu before her lover turns into a pig. Then, in A Star is Born, Carol and the gang parody the classic film. Next, in The Other Woman, Carol distracts her friend so she won't see her husband is cheating. Finally, in Take a Letter, Carol tries to take dictation from her boss, but the company's faulty products keep getting in the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328033000 +0000" stop="20250328043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nimble Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is sought out by land tycoon Adam Thompson, who suspects one of his nephews of rifling the house safe. The twist? The land tycoon's next in command is found dead, after it's found out that he was the one stealing the secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328043500 +0000" stop="20250328050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is terrified of falling asleep for fear he might die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328050500 +0000" stop="20250328053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of Credit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A researcher comes to a small-town bank to find out what happened at a robbery years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328053500 +0000" stop="20250328060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Escape To Sonoita</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Two kidnappers find a tanker in the middle of the desert and decide to make their escape in it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328060500 +0000" stop="20250328070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Run, Sheep, Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to determine which cops are tied in with a vice ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328070500 +0000" stop="20250328080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Perfect Fit For A Frame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon gets hired to protect a girl but when her supposed pursuer is found dead he finds himself charged with murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328080500 +0000" stop="20250328090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Woman In Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a plastic surgeon accidentally kills his patient, he remodels his nurse to look exactly like her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328090000 +0000" stop="20250328093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328093000 +0000" stop="20250328100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328100000 +0000" stop="20250328103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harbor Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy needs to sell two tickets to the ballet after his date cancels, but he quickly regrets putting a notice on the station's bulletin board. While patrolling the harbor and surrounding area, he and Reed investigate a marine fuel dealer accused of forgery, pull over a driver with a suspicious box on the roof of his car, question a suspicious young couple, deal with an astrologer who is driving recklessly and encounter a drunken cook shooting a rifle from the crow's nest of a docked ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328103000 +0000" stop="20250328110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Rampart Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an elusive purse snatcher whose latest victim was visiting her husband's grave. In the meantime, they deal with an annoying former cop turned security guard, encounter a desperate old man attempting to break into a car, help a cantankerous elderly woman who is being evicted, mediate a near-violent dispute over five dollars, track down a runaway baby carriage and search for an armed suspect who just robbed a cocktail lounge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328110000 +0000" stop="20250328120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Diners, Drive-ins &amp; Drive-thrus</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony cook up the idea to open their own restaurant while exploring the tasty past of diners, drive-ins, and drive-thrus."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328120000 +0000" stop="20250328123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Team</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While coaching Beaver's football team, Wally makes up a secret play and Beaver just happens to mention it to Penny who inadvertently passes it on to the opposing team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328123000 +0000" stop="20250328130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Won't Eat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is determined not to eat brussels sprouts and adamantly refuses to eat them when June serves them for dinner. In order to go to a football game, Ward makes Beaver promise that he will eat brussels sprouts the next time they are served. Beaver quickly finds himself confronted with the "deadly" vegetables when the Cleavers go out to eat at a posh restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328130000 +0000" stop="20250328140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Verdict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason loses a case when Janice Barton is convicted of murdering her aunt and subsequently sentenced to death. After the verdict, Mason continues investigating to find the real killer among the old lady's heirs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328140000 +0000" stop="20250328150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Boy  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Hating his mother's new boyfriend, Tony Morgen kills the man and frames his mother. Matlock takes the case to prove the woman's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328150000 +0000" stop="20250328160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hello In There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba refuses to believe that a former teammate embezzled funds from the bank where he worked. And sets out to prove that his friend was framed and murdered. Harriet hopes that art therapy can help the man's traumatized son, who becomes a target himself when the killer realizes he witnessed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328160000 +0000" stop="20250328170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Braggart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When a grownup Hobie Shanks visits the Waltons, John Boy seems to be the only one put off by his outlandish claims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328170000 +0000" stop="20250328173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Amber</sub-title>
    <desc>"Peak Fletcher says his sister Sarah Amber stole a calf. She was set up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328173000 +0000" stop="20250328180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Unknown Grave</sub-title>
    <desc>"On a stage heading for Dodge Sheriff Darcy has a heart attack while guarding a murderer, Blackie."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328180000 +0000" stop="20250328190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>To Bloom For Thee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is unaware that his fiancée is a troubled woman with a hidden, dark past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328190000 +0000" stop="20250328193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain gives blood to save a dying man and is surprised by Marshal Torrance's odd behavior toward the man. Then three men arrive from a nearby town and demand custody of the stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328193000 +0000" stop="20250328200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger At Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's finding the body of a murder victim starts Lucas, his friend, Artemus, and Marshal Torrance on a search for the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328200000 +0000" stop="20250328210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jarbo Pierce Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"The series' final episode begins and ends with the two characters who stayed with it from beginning to end, as Charlie tells Hawks about his earlier days working for trading post operator Jarbo Pierce. Jarbo, once a wild, hard-drinking man, had become a minister, though he could still take on any man who tried to fight him. When his younger brother Adam arrived at the post Jarbo found himself at odds with him as Adam preferred the wilder ways of life and didn't understand Jarbo's concerns for the Indians he traded with, and began working with a man who wanted to use ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328210000 +0000" stop="20250328220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Steel Inferno, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A careless worker sparks an explosive fire in a high-rise building. Station 110 leads a full alarm response, assisted by Squad 51. A triage team from Rampart Hospital, led by Dr. Brackett, sets up in a nearby garage. Several workmen and two women including the fiancee of a paramedic remain trapped on the 16th floor. A Coast Guard helicopter assists in rooftop evacuation; Dixie and Dr. Early take charge of the many patients at Rampart. A paramedic is injured attempting a rescue, while Gage and DeSoto extricate themselves from a broken elevator. An explosion on the 21st floor injures a fire captain, necessitating a dangerous rescue down an elevator shaft."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328220000 +0000" stop="20250328223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328223000 +0000" stop="20250328230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328230000 +0000" stop="20250328233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328233000 +0000" stop="20250329000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329000000 +0000" stop="20250329003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329003000 +0000" stop="20250329010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329010000 +0000" stop="20250329013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Son Of Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May and her new beau, Fred Penron, are getting rather serious. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns, this time with his son, Dub. He plans to set Dub up with Elly, to once again try to get some of Jed's money. Jed and Jethro try to hide this from Granny because the Cricks really rile her up. She sees the Cricks, but Jed tries to convince her that she is having visions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329013000 +0000" stop="20250329020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Girl-shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Warren is truly shy around women except when he is sleepwalking. When he sleepwalks he turns into a lothario of the first order—and his new conquest is Helen!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329020000 +0000" stop="20250329023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Klink's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets himself sent to the hospital so he can get information from a wounded agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329023000 +0000" stop="20250329030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Purchasing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and crew are ordered to deliver airdropped ammo to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329030000 +0000" stop="20250329033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Wrong Number / Saturday Night / Recital, The / Vacuum Salesman</sub-title>
    <desc>In Wrong Number, Carol questions a strange phone call for her husband. Then, in Saturday Night, Carol tries to get invited to a party next door. Next, in The Recital, four talentless musicians perform a showcase. Finally, in Vacuum Salesman, Tim has an emotional breakdown while trying to sell a vacuum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329033000 +0000" stop="20250329043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Madcap Modiste</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of the biggest names in fashion is poisoned after embarrassing her husband on TV.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329043500 +0000" stop="20250329050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329050500 +0000" stop="20250329053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hooked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A man schemes with a young woman to get rid of his wealthy wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329053500 +0000" stop="20250329060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Greatly Beloved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A newcomer refuses to allow his garden to be used for a church activity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329060500 +0000" stop="20250329070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Then The Drink Takes The Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates why a man who is against the evils of drink is spending a load of cash and time at an alcoholic retreat in Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329070500 +0000" stop="20250329080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329080500 +0000" stop="20250329090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Image In A Cracked Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune hunter marries rich women and makes off with their valuables.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329090000 +0000" stop="20250329093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Cannonball Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe's latest plan for decommissioning the Hooterville Cannonball falls on the holidays, as the gang are decorating the train for the annual Christmas Eve caroling run.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
