<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525000000 +0000" stop="20250525023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Mummy</sub-title>
    <desc>"In 1895, British archaeologists find and open the tomb of Egyptian Princess Ananka with nefarious consequences."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525023000 +0000" stop="20250525030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Fine Feathered Finks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After plotting his next caper from prison, the Penguin disguises himself as an umbrella shop owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525030000 +0000" stop="20250525040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Savage Curtain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk and Spock meet Abraham Lincoln and Surak of Vulcan and must do battle with some of history's most terrible villains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525040000 +0000" stop="20250525050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Sentry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A lizard-man creature kills subterranean workers who have stolen its eggs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525050000 +0000" stop="20250525060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Flaming Planet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith disposes of a plant that has grown out of control, but once outside the plant manages to attach itself to the Jupiter 2. The plant apparently believes that Dr. Smith is its mother, meanwhile the ship is attacked by a brave space warrior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525060000 +0000" stop="20250525070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The X Factor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson and the Seaview crew battle enemy agents in a daring attempt to save a kidnapped U.S. scientist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525070000 +0000" stop="20250525080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Lodestone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A new giant inspector comes up with a way to track a metal unique to Earth. The Spindrift crew initially manages to get rid of all of it... until they realize that Dan has a metal pin in his leg made of the material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525080000 +0000" stop="20250525090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>One Way To The Moon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug materialize on the first manned flight to Mars, where their added weight forces a change in flight plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525090000 +0000" stop="20250525100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>David rushes to help when people are frozen to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525100000 +0000" stop="20250525110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>36 Hours</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt race to find the landing device before astronauts perish in the re-entry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525110000 +0000" stop="20250525113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Mamas And The Papas   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>As a class project, the Bayside gang pairs up for mock weddings, but problems arise when Lisa becomes allergic to Screech, her mock husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525113000 +0000" stop="20250525120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitters   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Kelly breaks her arm, the gang helps take care of her baby brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525120000 +0000" stop="20250525123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Pinned To The Mat   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Confident of Bayside's winning streak, Zack bets on a wrestling match, only to find that Slater's quit the team and has been replaced with Screech!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525123000 +0000" stop="20250525130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty And The Screech   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After discovering she is failing in science class, Kelly is tutored by Screech, and soon develops a crush on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525130000 +0000" stop="20250525133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Zack Tapes   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack uses his subliminal advertising course to get Kelly to go with him to the Sweetheart Dance. But when his plan backfires, the whole school vies for his affection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525133000 +0000" stop="20250525140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Friendship Business   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang starts a business selling friendship bracelets, but Zack's tough work schedule tests the limits of their friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525140000 +0000" stop="20250525143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Try, Try Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan becomes convinced she's got no talent after failing to make it into a ballet recital. As a result, she drops out of ballet and tries (the considerably louder) tap dancing instead. Meanwhile, Mike sets out to make a family dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525143000 +0000" stop="20250525150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Popularity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan competes in a popularity contest at school. With Peter as her campaign manager and the rest of the family pitching in, she's got a great chance of winning - if she can stop making promises to her classmates that she can't possibly keep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525150000 +0000" stop="20250525153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Open House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie and Potsie plan to host a poker night at the Cunningham house as Howard and Marion will be out of town. However, their plans change when three young women stop by after their car breaks down, and Potsie invites them to stay the night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525153000 +0000" stop="20250525160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Monastery Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne is allowed to stay at a convent for a couple of weeks, but she soon gets on the Mother Superior's bad side when she has trouble keeping a vow of silence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525160000 +0000" stop="20250525163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Cow Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The mayor calls in an investigator from the state capital to help solve a string of cow thefts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525163000 +0000" stop="20250525170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>In Palm Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy and Ricky and Ethel and Fred are bored with each other so the gals head off to Palm Springs for a break. Rock Hudson guests as himself and has a hand in getting the couples back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525170000 +0000" stop="20250525173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Caddie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver has gotten a job as a caddy and is quickly running around the golf course chasing balls. However, all innocence is broken when one of the guys, Beaver is caddying for cheats in order to win a bet. Soon, Beaver begins wrestling with his conscience over whether or not to tell anyone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525173000 +0000" stop="20250525180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with the news that he applied to appear on a local television show called 'Teen Forum' and has been accepted. Beaver gets out of classes for the taping and all his classmates are treated to being able to watch him on TV during class. However, what Beaver, his friends and family don't know is that the show tapes each episode a week in advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525180000 +0000" stop="20250525183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Something For The Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts, Drysdale and Jane are heading to their castle in England. Their plane ride isn’t the easiest, especially for Drysdale and another passenger. Jethro smuggles Elly’s turkey, buzzard, on board, and Drysdale is attacked by it in the bathroom, as well as another man who has the misfortune of being seated near the clan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525183000 +0000" stop="20250525190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Possum Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to keep the Clampetts in Beverly Hills by telling them there is going to be a Possum Day held there. Granny decides to run for Possum Queen in Beverly Hills, and Drysdale convinces her that she is running against Mrs. Drysdale. Meanwhile, Drysdale is desperate to actually get a Possum Day to happen for the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525190000 +0000" stop="20250525193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Music Hath Charm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing Gilligan drumming, Ms. Howell is inspired to form an island orchestra. Unfortunately, the drumming has also attracted the attention of a neighboring island's tribe, who are convinced that a war is about to start.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525193000 +0000" stop="20250525200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>New Neighbor Sam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways overhear gangsters discussing buried treasure and threatening their lives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525200000 +0000" stop="20250525220000 +0000">
    <title>Return to Mayberry</title>
    <desc>"Reprising their roles in the original 'Andy Griffith Show,' Andy returns to Mayberry to run again for sheriff, only to discover his former deputy, Barney, has also entered the race.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525220000 +0000" stop="20250525223000 +0000">
    <title>Mayberry R.F.D.</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Get Married  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Andy and Helen marry, and Aunt Bee becomes Sam's housekeeper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525223000 +0000" stop="20250525230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Lego- Chris Lee</sub-title>
    <desc>"The name Christopher Lee has become synonymous with LEGO. As a collector, builder and LEGO Masters champion, he pretty much knows about, built or has collected it all. Today, he's invited us to his home where we'll check out his phenomenal collection which includes the iconic Galaxy Explorer, his beloved Airport Shuttle, not to mention his truly one-of-a-kind Prototype Factory Bricks. Our expert Aaron Fike, who owns a few LEGO stores himself, will be tasked with trying to appraise Christopher's collection and then come up with a LEGO trade worthy enough to convince our collector to "LEGO" of one his favorite collectibles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525230000 +0000" stop="20250525233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Iron Guts Kelly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>General 'Iron Guts' Kelly arrives for an inspection, and ends up dying in Margaret's tent. Hawkeye and Trapper help the General's aide smuggle him out of camp. The next day he is reported killed at the front, as that is where he would have wanted to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250525233000 +0000" stop="20250526000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>O.r.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The O.R. is filled with more wounded than the unit can handle. Hawkeye does heart massage on a soldier, which saves his life, but he dies four hours later. Sidney Freedman drops in during the deluge, and is dragged into the fray by Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526000000 +0000" stop="20250526003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Locket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith's antique locket is missing and Archie sees it as a way to collect from the insurance company to buy a new television set. Confident of getting the insurance money, Archie orders a new color set, only to have an insurance adjuster arrive at the house to question the claim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526003000 +0000" stop="20250526010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie In The Hospital</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie has been suffering from a terrible pain in his back and has become a terrible pain to Edith, who has been waiting on him hand and foot. When the doctor takes a look at him, he orders Archie to be admitted to the hospital for tests. This is where Archie befriends the other patient in his room, but because of a partition, Archie doesn't realize the man is black.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526010000 +0000" stop="20250526013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, Say Can You See</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie begins to realize that he's not as young as he used to be when he finds that he may need glasses. To make matters worse, middle-aged Archie can only envy the eternally youthful outlook of his friend and contemporary, Bill Mulheron. He is especially impressed that the toned, flashily garbed Bill has managed to attract a sexy young bedmate named Tina. However, Archie soon discovers all is not as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526013000 +0000" stop="20250526020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Goes Too Far</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is searching the house for a magazine to prove to Mike that he was right concerning a debate that they are having. However, Archie oversteps his boundaries and searches Mike's room where he discovers a poem that Mike once wrote. This leads to a huge argument concerning privacy and Mike storms out to Lionel's while Gloria and Edith storm out and have a slumber party at the apartment of one of Gloria's friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526020000 +0000" stop="20250526023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 03/23/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526023000 +0000" stop="20250526030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Barbara Eden And Jonathan Winters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Barbara Eden and Jonathan Winters. Originally aired on 12/04/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526030000 +0000" stop="20250526033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Farewell To Writing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob goes to a secluded cabin to write his novel, but drives himself crazy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526033000 +0000" stop="20250526040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Uhny Uftz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Did Rob see a UFO?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526040000 +0000" stop="20250526043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526043000 +0000" stop="20250526050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Martian Please Stand Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Troopers follow the tracks from a frozen pond into a diner. Inside they find a soda jerk, a bus driver and his seven passengers. The bus driver is certain only six people boarded his bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526050000 +0000" stop="20250526060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Last Seen Wearing Blue Jeans  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A 17-year-old girl is inadvertently driven to Mexico by a dangerous car thief, who is unaware she is sleeping in the back seat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526060000 +0000" stop="20250526070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>My Friend, My Enemy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A communist agent, Karl Maur, spots Paris on vacation, knocks him out and turns him over to Dr. Tabor, who is a brain specialist and mind control expert. Unable to break Paris, Tabor blanks out Paris' memories and uses an implanted electrode to program his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526070000 +0000" stop="20250526080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Detour On A Road Going Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a hotel steward in Wyoming, Kimble is forced to run after learning that another hotel employee has stolen hotel funds, and Kimble becomes the suspect. Kimble escapes on a tour bus containing a bickering couple called the Langners, a visit</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526080000 +0000" stop="20250526090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Elegy For A Cop</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell assumes an undercover identity to avenge the murder of his close friend, police lieutenant Manny Quinlan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526090000 +0000" stop="20250526093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526093000 +0000" stop="20250526100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526100000 +0000" stop="20250526103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 123 -- Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed feels a strong sense of accomplishment when he stumbles upon a large stash of narcotics as he secures a residence after executing a traffic warrant with Malloy and Officer Ed Wells. He's in for a rude awakening at the trial, however, when he's cross examined by the defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526103000 +0000" stop="20250526110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 143 -- Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin their shift responding to a disgruntled tenant who is holding his landlord at knife point. Later, they investigate a rash of property theft from multiple homes in a quiet neighborhood, stake out an apparent bag of laundry left on the side of the road and search for a runaway boy who gets himself into a life-threatening situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526110000 +0000" stop="20250526120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill &amp; Toony Start A Podcast</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill have a podcast! Maybe. All they need is a title. And something to talk about."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526120000 +0000" stop="20250526123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Box Office Attraction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward have noticed the Wally has been spending quite a bit of his time at the movie theater but it's not to see the movies. He's been eyeing the pretty young lady who works in the box office. Thanks to Eddie, Wally works up enough courage to ask her out but quickly sees another side to the young lady that is a bit too mature for Wally's taste.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526123000 +0000" stop="20250526130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Scholarship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is let down when he learns that he didn't get the sports scholarship from State University. However, he does learn that Lumpy did get one and this leads him to throw a party in Lumpy's honor. However, half way through the party, Fred calls with some unfortunate news for Lumpy, the scholarship is no longer available due to Lumpy's grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526130000 +0000" stop="20250526140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blonde Bonanza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady promoter is killed after a crooked modeling deal, his intended victim is suspected of his murder—but the truth in this case is more than skin deep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526140000 +0000" stop="20250526150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Sisters  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When he is accused of murdering his wealthy wife, an old acquaintance hires Matlock to defend him. The more digging Matlock does, the more he begins to suspect other family members.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526150000 +0000" stop="20250526160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For An Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The father of a man Gerard prosecuted kidnaps the DA's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526160000 +0000" stop="20250526170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Song</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason writes a song to sing with Bobby Bigalow's band</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526170000 +0000" stop="20250526173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Love Of A Woman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc's nurse from the war, Abbie, comes to Dodge. So does Coney who's out to kill Matt for putting him in jail for 5 years. Coney gets sick and Abbie takes care of him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526173000 +0000" stop="20250526180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Jay Hawkers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dolph Quince (Jack Elam) sends Phil Jacks (Ken Curtis) into Dodge to bring Marshall Dillon out to their herd to help with Jayhawkers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526180000 +0000" stop="20250526190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Ben Cartwright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After an attempt on his life Ben lays low, allowing even his close friends to believe him to be gone in an effort to thwart the plans of a scheming politician.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526190000 +0000" stop="20250526193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Jealous Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Fay Owens, old friends of Micah, are the McCain's new neighbors. Jake quickly develops an unreasoning jealousy of Lucas with Fay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526193000 +0000" stop="20250526200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Conscience</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>No one's more surprised than Micah when newcomer Leota Carraway claims he's her long-lost husband and the father of her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526200000 +0000" stop="20250526210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Jamison Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint, at a grave, sees a man stabbed in the back with a note saying, "Deliver to Beauty Jamison." As that is the daughter of the man interred he pays a visit and sees a woman trying to continue a legacy with the locals trying to break her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526210000 +0000" stop="20250526220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen are puzzled by Boot's strange behavior. Meanwhile, paramedics rescue a woman whose sports car is pinned under a gas truck and investigate a series of unusual incidents in the home of a woman attempting to cook a meal for her boyfriend and his mother. An unconscious man is brought in to the hospital suffering from internal bleeding. Dr. Early deals with the victim of a curse. An explosion in a hospital lab endangers a number of workers and important records.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526220000 +0000" stop="20250526223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Springtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When spring arrives, Klinger gets word from home that his sweetheart back in Toledo wants to marry him. Henry arranges for Father Mulcahy to do this over short wave radio. Radar falls in love with a nurse, while a grateful patient won't leave Hawkeye alone, and even threatens Major Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526223000 +0000" stop="20250526230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Check-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper gets an ulcer and a ticket home. Unfortunately, his going-away party is spoiled by a new Army regulation, which forces him to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526230000 +0000" stop="20250526233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250526233000 +0000" stop="20250527000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527000000 +0000" stop="20250527003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manicurist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful manicurist from the city comes to Floyd's to set up shop. She makes all the wives in town extremely nervous as she manicures their husbands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527003000 +0000" stop="20250527010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Brief Encounter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Aunt Bee falls for traveling handyman Henry Wheeler, Andy soon learns that Wheeler is not as nice as he appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527010000 +0000" stop="20250527013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed And The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>It is time for spring tonic, and the Countess Maria returns to meet with her good friends the Clampetts, as well as get some tonic. And after the Clampetts learn Maria is single again, having lost her husband at a party, Granny sees this as the time for Jed to make his move on the Countess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527013000 +0000" stop="20250527020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton buy a T.V. set together and constantly fight over what to watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527020000 +0000" stop="20250527023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Old Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses the car of an SS man who's just married Klink's old girlfriend and is honeymooning in Paris, where Hogan needs to pass radios to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527023000 +0000" stop="20250527030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Klink's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets himself sent to the hospital so he can get information from a wounded agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527030000 +0000" stop="20250527033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Where Is Everybody?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds himself in a town strangely devoid of people. What's more, he can't recall his own identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527033000 +0000" stop="20250527043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Traveling Treasure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>His fishing trip ruined, Mason is on the case when a deep-sea fisherman aboard a rented boat is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527043500 +0000" stop="20250527050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527050500 +0000" stop="20250527053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Salvage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan, an underworld kingpin, hatches a plan to punish a singer who killed his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527053500 +0000" stop="20250527060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a terrible accident leaves a man completely paralyzed, people who encounter him think he is dead, though he is very much alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527060500 +0000" stop="20250527070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For The Peep-show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The uncle of a young woman has disappeared after giving her $300,000 dollars in cash for safekeeping. Mannix must find out where the money comes from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527070500 +0000" stop="20250527080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Electric Coffin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A search for a missing girl leads Frank into a case of murder and a romantic triangle when Cannon is hired by the child's mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527080500 +0000" stop="20250527090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man abducts Betty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527090000 +0000" stop="20250527093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527093000 +0000" stop="20250527100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527100000 +0000" stop="20250527103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 142 -- As High As You Are</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy and Reed's patrol begins, an uneventful traffic stop becomes more interesting when something catches Malloy's eye. Later, they discover an unusual situation responding to a break-in at a hospital supply warehouse, which becomes even more odd when the warehouse owner and a group of revenge-seeking thugs show up at the scene. The shift ends in a fitting way when they are called to an apartment where a baby has been left unattended with a pet lion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527103000 +0000" stop="20250527110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 43 -- Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and several civilians are taken hostage after he is shot and seriously injured by robbers while stopping for lunch at Duke's Longhorn Café.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527110000 +0000" stop="20250527120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Steamboat</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527120000 +0000" stop="20250527123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all set to go with Eddie and Wally to hook up a AM/FM car radio in Eddie's car but June stops him and insists he go to the grocery store to pick up the items he had promised. This leads Beaver to give June the cold shoulder treatment while playing up to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527123000 +0000" stop="20250527130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for a couple of days and leave Uncle Billy to stay with Wally and Beaver. Beaver quickly realizes Billy runs a much looser ship than Ward and June and feels as if he can get away with more things. However, he's soon in for a rude awakening when he helps Gilbert sneak into the movies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527130000 +0000" stop="20250527140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ruinous Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a land development deal goes sour, Mason defends engineer Adam Conrad, accused of a murder committed in an old house that has something sinister hidden underneath it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527140000 +0000" stop="20250527150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cop  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Detective Joe Peters has been accused of taking bribes and murdering a fence; he also is suspected in the death of a fellow cop. Matlock takes the case and finds himself investigating the police force.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527150000 +0000" stop="20250527160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Littlest Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lonnie makes a heartbreaking discovery about a woman he dated in high school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527160000 +0000" stop="20250527170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy falls for a poet who is visiting his college</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527170000 +0000" stop="20250527173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kitty's Rebellion</sub-title>
    <desc>"An old friend of the family comes to Dodge looking for Kitty, but when he finds out she's a saloon owner, he's dismayed. Intent on defending her honor wherever she is insulted, he nearly gets himself killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527173000 +0000" stop="20250527180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sky</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Chester is teaching Miss Kitty guitar playing and singing technics, the cowpokes at the Long Branch are making quite a fuss over Frog mouth Kate. Kate has a fondness for a younger man almost half her age (Billy Daunt)."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527180000 +0000" stop="20250527190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Star Crossed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Candy falls in love with Tisha Sterling, a young woman being blackmailed by a man named Passmore, a marshal from another town who pretends to be her cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527190000 +0000" stop="20250527193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Reckoning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is torn by conflicting emotions when he meets the town's new preacher—a former outlaw whom he vowed to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527193000 +0000" stop="20250527200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Town Slept</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The town of North Fork becomes a haven for outlaws when suave Ben Judson smooth-talks his way into the marshal's job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527200000 +0000" stop="20250527210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Ellen Thomas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen is an orphan traveling west to join family; members of the train reject her due to her surly disposition. Her only friend is Sally Mayhew, another girl traveling west with her family dying of consumption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527210000 +0000" stop="20250527220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Rip-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John are accused of stealing money from a victim. A premature delivery and a blinded man result from a car crash. A perilous rescue involves a plane that might explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527220000 +0000" stop="20250527223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life With Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail from home worries Henry that Lorraine may be seeing other men. Father Mulcahy presides over a Jewish circumcision ceremony for the Korean-born son of a US GI.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527223000 +0000" stop="20250527230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Alcoholics Unanimous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry's departure to Tokyo leaves Major Burns in charge of the 4077th. He declares total prohibition of alcohol, which leads to a near riot in the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527230000 +0000" stop="20250527233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>There Is Nothing Like A Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses are evacuated when the threat of an enemy parachute drop arises. Hawkeye and Trapper try to enliven everyone's spirits while they are gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250527233000 +0000" stop="20250528000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Ribs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sick and tired of having liver and fish for an 11-day stretch, Hawkeye, driven near to insanity, starts a riot in the mess tent. He and Trapper then orders spare ribs and sauce from his favorite barbecue joint—in Chicago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528000000 +0000" stop="20250528003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528003000 +0000" stop="20250528010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Luck Of Newton Monroe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant peddler comes to town (Don Rickles) and sells Barney, Floyd and Goober defective goods. After he disregards Andy's warning, he finds himself in the Mayberry jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528010000 +0000" stop="20250528013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Big Daddy, Jed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Beatnik Sheldon Epps returns with his friends from the Parthenon West Coffee House, asking Jed for money so they can keep their hangout. Drysdale is hoping to close the place down. But his plans fail when Jed befriends the hippies and supports them, providing music and lights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528013000 +0000" stop="20250528020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Here Comes The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's advice to a lodge brother on how to be head of the household has his wife (Alice's sister) in tears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528020000 +0000" stop="20250528023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon interferes as Hogan tries to help a defecting scientist, whom they were ordered to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528023000 +0000" stop="20250528030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cupid Comes To Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps Klink fall in love with General Burkhalter's sister to get his mind off not being promoted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528030000 +0000" stop="20250528033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A street salesman cleverly eludes Death. But if he lives, a little girl must die in his place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528033000 +0000" stop="20250528043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Posthumous Painter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Artist Jack Culross fakes his own suicide and sees the sales of his paintings go through the roof. His only oversight was forgetting to inform his wife of the scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528043500 +0000" stop="20250528050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A neo-Nazi psycho has planted a bomb somewhere in L.A. Friday and Gannon have to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528050500 +0000" stop="20250528053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Our Cook's A Treasure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A real estate agent becomes obsessed with the idea that his new cook is a serial killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528053500 +0000" stop="20250528060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A gambling addict cannot resist the lure of $200,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528060500 +0000" stop="20250528070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A blind crook and Mannix are both on the trail of some valuable stolen jewels.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528070500 +0000" stop="20250528080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer has blamed his crime on a innocent cop and Cannon is out to prove who the real killer is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528080500 +0000" stop="20250528090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A former gangster goes into hiding to finish an indictment he'd been writing about the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528090000 +0000" stop="20250528093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528093000 +0000" stop="20250528100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528100000 +0000" stop="20250528103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 34 -- Astro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed become envious of officer wells, who has been given a coveted assignment in the newly established astro helicopter division. Out on patrol, they require assistance saving a wealthy elderly couple who get locked in their heavily fortified basement safe, and then use air support to track down robbery suspects who escape on a motorcycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528103000 +0000" stop="20250528110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 14 -- S.w.a.t.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are the first to respond to a downtown rooftop sniper who has been indiscriminately shooting at anyone he can find with his scoped rifle. After risking their lives to get civilians out of his line of sight, they become lead participants in the S.W.A.T. team's attempt to neutralize the suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528110000 +0000" stop="20250528120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Cartoon Mascots</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony prepares for a very special audition!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528120000 +0000" stop="20250528123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prep School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward are excited when they learn that Aunt Martha has made arrangements to send Beaver to a prep school in New England. However, Beaver quickly realizes he will miss his friends as they are all entering Mayfield High School next year. This puts Beaver in a delicate position: how to tell Aunt Martha he doesn't want to go without hurting her feelings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528123000 +0000" stop="20250528130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And The Fraternity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has his mind pretty much made up about going to Ward's alma mater, State University, and he's even considering joining Ward's old fraternity. However, both Eddie and Wally think twice when they hear from a college student that that's the worst fraternity on campus, but Ward has already sent out his letter of recommendation for both of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528130000 +0000" stop="20250528140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Jealous Journalist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The drowning death of a newspaper executive during a fishing trip sets off all kinds of repercussions at the newspaper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528140000 +0000" stop="20250528150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Angel  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to take the case of free-spirited rock star Angel. The musician has been accused of killing her manager, and due to an alcohol-induced blackout can't even offer an alibi for the night of the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528150000 +0000" stop="20250528160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Landlord</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A drug dealing slumlord is murdered by his accomplices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528160000 +0000" stop="20250528170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Venture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>John takes on a loan to improve the business and he gets a big order</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528170000 +0000" stop="20250528173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Quits</sub-title>
    <desc>"When another doctor shows up in Dodge promising lower doctor's fees and miracle cures, Doc gets angry and many Dodge citizens think Doc Adams has quit as Dodge's doctor."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528173000 +0000" stop="20250528180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Bear</sub-title>
    <desc>"Joe Plummer is mad and jealous because his boss Mike Blocker is marrying Tilda. So he tries to frame Blocker for murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528180000 +0000" stop="20250528190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Trouble Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A Cartwright cattle drive stops in the town of River Bend. There they help Lilah Holden, an old friend of Candy's, out of a jam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528190000 +0000" stop="20250528193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Milly's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran returns with tales of heroism and the fate of Milly's brother in the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528193000 +0000" stop="20250528200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A head wound wipes out Lucas' memory, leaving him with only one clue: he's wearing an outlaw's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528200000 +0000" stop="20250528210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Richardson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When the wagon horses start to die of a disease, Adams is forced to send two feuding men to buy new horses with his emergency money. Two horses return, but with only one man, leading Adams to wonder whether he made a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528210000 +0000" stop="20250528220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Audit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>John is audited by the IRS. A man hit on the head wants to be treated by a doctor, not the paramedics. A child is rescued from a locked car. A pregnant girl has difficulty breathing. A professional medical con man shows up at Rampart. A construction worker is trapped when part of the building his crew is working on collapses, and he wants Roy to remove his leg before the rest of the building falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528220000 +0000" stop="20250528223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Full Rich Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye records a letter to his dad, detailing the exploits of a mad Turkish soldier who calls Hawkeye a "damn good Joe," the unfortunate loss of the corpse of a Luxembourg soldier (who turns out not to be dead), Lt. Henri-Batiste LeClerc and a gun-happy officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528223000 +0000" stop="20250528230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Dogs And Servicemen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A local dog bites Radar, and the camp conducts a search to find the pooch so that Radar doesn't have to undergo a series of painful rabies vaccinations. Hawkeye defies Frank, to take care of a GI who's suffering from a case of hysterical paralysis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528230000 +0000" stop="20250528233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Charles Lamb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A Greek Colonel thanks the 4077th by giving them food and drink for an Easter celebration. But the feast is foiled when softhearted Radar saves the main course from the spit—a lamb, which Radar tricks Henry into giving a medical discharge and sends home to Ottumwa, Iowa. Thus, Hawkeye and Trapper invent the famed Spam Lamb!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250528233000 +0000" stop="20250529000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp is under fire and is swamped with wounded. They are being attacked by their own artillery in a frightening "friendly fire" incident. After Trapper and Margaret get trapped in the supply tent together, Frank's jealousy of Trapper drives him to propose to Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529000000 +0000" stop="20250529003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Farmer Takes A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeff Pruitt, a farmer from the hills, comes to Mayberry in search of a wife. He enlists Barney and Andy's help and ends up picking Thelma Lou!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529003000 +0000" stop="20250529010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529010000 +0000" stop="20250529013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cool School Is Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly and Jethro join the beatniks at the Parthenon West, and Granny tries to get them out. But her attempts fail, and she becomes a beatnik herself, after inventing "The Tater Digger,” a new dance. Jed is all for the young ones expressing themselves, but once he sees Granny dressed the way she is and acting the way she is, he changes his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529013000 +0000" stop="20250529020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Golfer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to learn how to play golf to impress his boss, and, of course, the situation turns into a disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529020000 +0000" stop="20250529023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flame Grows Higher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a POW is caught at the processing location after Stalag 13, Hogan suspects there is a traitor in the underground. Newkirk and LeBeau help him find out who it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529023000 +0000" stop="20250529030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Request Permission To Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving a "Dear John" letter, Carter asks Hogan if he can escape and get back to his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529030000 +0000" stop="20250529033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Denton On Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A has-been, drunk gunslinger finds his fast-draw abilities magically restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529033000 +0000" stop="20250529043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Injured Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a test driver deliberately crashes a race car equipped with an experimental engine, claims the collision paralyzed him and then ends up murdered, Mason defends the investor behind the engine's creation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529043500 +0000" stop="20250529050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapping</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon help an employee rescue her kidnapped boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529050500 +0000" stop="20250529053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of Mr. Pelham</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Albert Pelham is slowly being replaced at home and at work by a double.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529053500 +0000" stop="20250529060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When the husband of an unhappy marriage disappears, the neighbors suspect foul play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529060500 +0000" stop="20250529070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Memory: Zero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Maggie escapes from a deadly accident by a hair. The felon is a militant taxi driver. Mannix has the suspicion that he has already committed murder once, that of his colleague, Maggie's boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529070500 +0000" stop="20250529080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Lonely Place To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A syndicate boss may just be next in line to be murdered when Cannon investigates a case involving a triple homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529080500 +0000" stop="20250529090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of Guilt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks for a member of Chicano street-gang who is the only witness to a millionaire's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529090000 +0000" stop="20250529093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529093000 +0000" stop="20250529100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529100000 +0000" stop="20250529103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 64 -- Bottom Of The Bottle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see the same drunk twice in one night, respond to a bar fight and engage in a high-speed pursuit with good samaritans who make a bad decision. They also search for a biker who tries to coerce a woman to repay a debt by riddling her apartment with buckshot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529103000 +0000" stop="20250529110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 54 -- Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed hope to find an impostor as they investigate a boxing promoter's accusation that a police detective stole $350 from him. In the meantime, they deal with a disgruntled wife who is in the process of destroying her own car in the middle of a downtown street, investigate a gun theft from a pawn shop, drive up on a home burglary in progress and obtain critical information while interrogating a suspected car thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529110000 +0000" stop="20250529120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Animation Irl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cartoons come to life in the real world with special guests Rob Paulsen and Randy Rogel of the Animaniacs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529120000 +0000" stop="20250529123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie has been seeing one particular girl, Cindy Andrews, and she wants to give Eddie a birthday gift, so she decides to knit a sweater. She uses Wally as a model and he begins spending so much time at Cindy's he arrouses the suspicions of Julie, Eddie, Lumpy, Beaver and his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529123000 +0000" stop="20250529130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Book Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been assigned to write a book report on 'The Three Musketeers.' However he's waited right down to the wire to get reading and quickly realizes that he'll never get finished. So, he decides to watch the movie that's going to be on TV and write his book report based on the movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529130000 +0000" stop="20250529140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Thermal Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Attorney Ken Kramer comes to the aid of an alleged thief accused of stealing a $50,000 necklace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529140000 +0000" stop="20250529150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Professor  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Professor Erskine Tate wakes from a drunken stupor behind the wheel of his car. He doesn't know how he got there or what happened. When he's accused of having hit a mailman during a drunken joyride, he goes to a former student, Matlock, for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529150000 +0000" stop="20250529160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fool For Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor plots to eliminate his wife -- and his mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529160000 +0000" stop="20250529170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The reverend and teacher get married</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529170000 +0000" stop="20250529173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Coward</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gambler Ed Eby has a grudge against the Marshall and starts talking about how "big" someone would be if they were to kill Matt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529173000 +0000" stop="20250529180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The F.u.</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Onie Becker is shot down on the streets of Dodge after quarreling with Al Clovis in a poker game, everyone thinks Al Clovis committed the shooting. The plot thickens after Matt and Chester pursue Clovis on a train headed out of Dodge."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529180000 +0000" stop="20250529190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Commitment At Angelus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After Joe's friend, Steve, is killed in an accident, he takes over organizing a strike at the mine that the deceased had begun. As tensions rise, the miners threaten to disrupt the whole enterprise if their demands are not met.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529190000 +0000" stop="20250529193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Executioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A former neighbor of the McCain's is released from jail after serving his sentence for stage coach robbery, but the money was never found. Lucas agrees to let the man work for him, but the new work hand holds a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529193000 +0000" stop="20250529200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Lou Mallory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Mallory has arrived in North Fork and quickly purchases land, which includes the hotel and Milly Scott's store. She pays higher prices than the sellers feel their properties are worth. Everyone is happy until they find out that Lou really is an astute businesswoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529200000 +0000" stop="20250529210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kitty Angel Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty Angel finds herself not welcome on the wagon train because of her past. When Flint returns to the train toting a sick indian baby, she has everyone's prejudices to deal with as well as the baby's life-threatening illness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529210000 +0000" stop="20250529220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Frequency</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Johnny's policeman friend is injured in a car crash, the paramedics can't reach the hospital because another squad is using the biophone. A child with a mysterious malady turns out to be drunk. Roy and John assist at the hospital when the victims of a motorcycle gang war are brought in for treatment. An artist becomes trapped in his own sculpture. A father and son are trapped in a collapse at a construction site.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529220000 +0000" stop="20250529223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bulletin Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Camp activities include Henry's nervous delivery of a sex lecture, with Hawkeye and Trapper heckling, a Shirley Temple movie and a cookout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529223000 +0000" stop="20250529230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Consultant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Borelli visits the 4077th to demonstrate his artery transplant technique. Unfortunately, being so close to the front at the 4077th causes Borelli's drinking problem to interfere at the worst time—when a patient needs the transplant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529230000 +0000" stop="20250529233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>House Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye hits Major Burns and Houlihan is a witness. Despite Hawkeye and Trapper's claims that it wasn't intentional, Frank makes allegations against Hawkeye, and he is put in house arrest facing court martial. A female colonel is sent to inspect the nurses. When she cries "Rape!" when Burns visits her tent, Houlihan recants her story, and Burns, not Hawkeye, ends up under house arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250529233000 +0000" stop="20250530000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Aid Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye, Houlihan and Klinger go to an aid station at the front. Working closely together under heavy fire and unsanitary medical conditions, the three return to camp with new found respect for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530000000 +0000" stop="20250530003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bailey's Bad Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich kid Ronald Bailey is jailed when he blatantly defies the law. As Bailey waits for his influential father to bail him out, Andy teaches him the lesson of self-responsibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530003000 +0000" stop="20250530010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves pretend to be Hollywood producers in order to rob the Mayberry Bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530010000 +0000" stop="20250530013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bank Battle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to get the Clampetts interested in a hobby to occupy their time and to stop Jed from traveling around the neighborhood with a fix-it wagon. He shows Jed all types of hobbies, like collecting stamps and building a boat in a bottle. Jethro gets a hobby with these offers—getting the boat out of the bottle!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530013000 +0000" stop="20250530020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman's Work Is Never Done</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of Ralph's endless domestic complaints, Alice takes a job and leaves a maid to take care of the housework.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530020000 +0000" stop="20250530023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Gives A Birthday Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hijacks a German bomber, and plans to use it to destroy an oil refinery and foil a German general who knows about the his operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530023000 +0000" stop="20250530030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Schultz Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink and two other prison camp kommandants are arrested for conspiring against General Burkhalter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530030000 +0000" stop="20250530033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteen-millimeter Shrine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging former movie star lives and dreams in the past, constantly watching her old movies alone in isolation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530033000 +0000" stop="20250530043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Left-handed Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Health club instructor Ward Nichols wants to marry the daughter of his employer, but his estranged wife is pressuring him for money and claiming to be pregnant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530043500 +0000" stop="20250530050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530050500 +0000" stop="20250530053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Claus And The Tenth Avenue Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal fresh out of prison takes a job as Santa Claus for the holiday season.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530053500 +0000" stop="20250530060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cheney Vase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A dishonest ex-museum curator uses a forged letter to get close to an elderly woman and her priceless vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530060500 +0000" stop="20250530070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When investigating a case of hit-and-run, Mannix gets caught amid the fronts of a mafia war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530070500 +0000" stop="20250530080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>No Pockets In A Shroud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When an heir of a millionaire who prefers to live like a hermit is discovered to be missing, Cannon in hired to investigate and uncovers a mysterious case of murder and embezzlement. But the case is hampered by the hermit's attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530080500 +0000" stop="20250530090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Due to circumstantial evidence, Betty's old flame is a prime suspect in a restaurant tycoon's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530090000 +0000" stop="20250530093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530093000 +0000" stop="20250530100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530100000 +0000" stop="20250530103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 24 -- A Rare Occasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy spends a weekend afternoon attending a barbecue at Reed's home, where Reed lets him hold his newborn son for the first time and tries to set him up with his wife's friend. However, their relaxation is interrupted when they have to deal with a young neighbor who overdoses on drugs and becomes the target of his dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530103000 +0000" stop="20250530110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 124 -- Airport</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are rendered powerless when a drunken man with no flight experience decides to take a solo flight in a stolen airplane at a busy airport. Later, they try to locate a 17-year-old runaway living in a condemned home with a much older man, engage in a shootout with a convenience store robber and search for a booby-trapped bank safe that has been stolen with a tow truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530110000 +0000" stop="20250530120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>New Wave Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530120000 +0000" stop="20250530123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Poor Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward is given two tickets to a baseball game and is faced with an impossible decision. Should he take Wally or Beaver? Beaver lets him off the hook when he announces he has plans with Gilbert. However, when they fall through, Beaver changes his mind about the game and becomes convinced because he's the youngest he gets the short stick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530123000 +0000" stop="20250530130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Don Juan Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Beaver with a major dilemma. He has two girls who ask him to go with them. However, he has a little problem, he accepted the first invitation but now wants out of it when he's asked by the second girl. This leads him to take some of Eddie's poor advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530130000 +0000" stop="20250530140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Venom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is hired to look into the death of his client's son, which occurred two years earlier. It is revealed that several people may have had reason to want the man out of the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530140000 +0000" stop="20250530150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Claus  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a down-on-his luck Santa Claus (Tom McCabe) is accused of killing his avaricious landlord, Matlock finds himself defending the very unlikeable man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530150000 +0000" stop="20250530160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Love, Honor, And Obey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Parkers investigation into a purse snatching reveals an abused woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530160000 +0000" stop="20250530170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy's dean asks him to take care of a 16-year-old genius college student for a weekend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530170000 +0000" stop="20250530173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Wind</sub-title>
    <desc>"Men at the Long Branch believe one of the "saloon girls" brings them luck at Blackjack. Matt's suspicious and tries to run her and the dealer out of Dodge when men start killing each other over her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530173000 +0000" stop="20250530180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Fawn</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt rescues a white woman (who was let go by the Cheyene) and a child from buffalo hunters then has to protect her from her Boston husband."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530180000 +0000" stop="20250530190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Dream To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Bitter, alcoholic Josh Carter makes life miserable for his wife, Sarah, and their children—until Hoss helps him mend his ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530190000 +0000" stop="20250530193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530193000 +0000" stop="20250530200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530200000 +0000" stop="20250530210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Flint Mccullough Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint, in love with a Mormon girl he can't marry, joins the Confederate Army. When he finds out that he won't be seeing any action on the battlefield, it may be too late for him and the girl he loves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530210000 +0000" stop="20250530220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Engine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John buy an old fire engine, and Station 51 gets a new engine. A woman overdoses on LSD and Roy tries to talk her down, leading the two paramedics on a chase to the top of a building. Brackett treats a resilient gunshot victim. A politician suffers a heart attack and the station responds to a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530220000 +0000" stop="20250530223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530223000 +0000" stop="20250530230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530230000 +0000" stop="20250530233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530233000 +0000" stop="20250531000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Abyssinia, Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry finally gets his discharge. While he is tying things up, Burns prepares for his new command. Henry bids a tearful adieu, but not before Klinger turns up in an outrageous tropical outfit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531000000 +0000" stop="20250531010000 +0000">
    <title>Me-TV Special Presentation</title>
    <sub-title>The Andy Griffith Show Reunion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cast members from "The Andy Griffith Show" gather to reminisce about the classic 1960s TV series."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531010000 +0000" stop="20250531013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Versus Automation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts befriend Leroy Lester, an unappreciated accountant being replaced at the bank by a computer, and give him the rest, relaxation and vacation he deserves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531013000 +0000" stop="20250531020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Life And Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ralph thinks he's dying and sells the story to a magazine, he discovers it was a dog who was sick instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531020000 +0000" stop="20250531023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds In The Rough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A German officer threatens to expose Hogan unless he is paid a million dollars in diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531023000 +0000" stop="20250531030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531030000 +0000" stop="20250531033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531033000 +0000" stop="20250531043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Brazen Bequest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Cromwell, the president-elect of Euclid College, worries that some less than stellar moments from his past will be exposed when Maisie Freitag arrives at the college.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531043500 +0000" stop="20250531050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531050500 +0000" stop="20250531053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Bullet For Baldwin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Benjamin Stepp turns into a cold-blooded murderer after being fired from his job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531053500 +0000" stop="20250531060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Switch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man buys an alibi so he can murder his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531060500 +0000" stop="20250531070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mannix tracks down an assassin, he is shot and seriously injured. Having a breakdown, Mannix is diagnosed with psychosomatic blindness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531070500 +0000" stop="20250531080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Stone Cold Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The reopening of the cold case of a salesgirl reveals that a bicycle she sold may be a clue to her death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531080500 +0000" stop="20250531090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dangerous Gambit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigation a fatal automobile accident, Barnaby uncovers a complex scheme to defraud a bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531090000 +0000" stop="20250531093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Days At Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Norman Curtis, the railroad president, sends his basset hound to the Shady Rest for a change of scenery.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
