<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214190000 +0000" stop="20260214200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Gift Of Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights stand up to vigilantes who are trying to keep families from leaving the flat lands for the high country during a terrible drought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214200000 +0000" stop="20260214203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Young Man's Fancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The pangs of first love are painful for Mark: the object of his affections has eyes for another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214203000 +0000" stop="20260214210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Promoter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark attempt to reform a con man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214210000 +0000" stop="20260214220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>The Calf Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy comes to like one of two calf woman, but when a member of a buffalo hunt is killed by her for attacking her younger sister, Rowdy is threatened by his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214220000 +0000" stop="20260214223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Road To Wickenburg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin wakes up after being drugged, beaten and robbed in the town of Blue Bell by five men, one of whom is the town's sheriff. They took his money, gun, bullets, horse and saddle. All he has left is his two-shot derringer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214223000 +0000" stop="20260214230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Cure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Emily Kendrick hires Josh to keep her beloved, Harry, from drinking himself to death. Kendrick has matrimony on her mind and with the arrival of Harry's brother for the wedding, she wants to make sure all goes as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260214230000 +0000" stop="20260215010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Haters, Sitter Downers, He Cooked His Goose, Cuckoo On A Choo Choo, Musty Musketeers, Uncivil War Birds</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges join the "Women Haters" club and vow to have nothing to do with the fair sex.  Larry marries a girl anyway and attempts to hide the fact from Moe and Curly as they take a train trip. , Marriage isn't all bliss as Larry, Moe and Curly find out when they set up house with Corabell, Florabell, and Dorabell. You could call them the Dumbbells. , The Stooges are civil war soldiers who are constantly changing uniforms to avoid the opposing armies.  Eventually they decide to be loyal to the south, but remain disguised as Union soldiers.  Curly is detected as a spy, but Moe and Larry prevent his execution.  The boys escape with a secret map and marry their three southern belles. , Larry is a pet dealer who's seeing Moe's wife while at the same time trying to steal Shemp's fiancee.  When Moe's become suspicious, Larry attempts to frame Shemp as the boyfriend.  He gets Shemp a job as a door-to-door pajama salesman and sends him to Moe's apartment, and then tells both Moe and Shemp's fiancee to go there and catch him in the act.  Larry's plan backfires when Shemp catches him and lets Moe deliver some punishment. , Larry and Shemp are living in a stolen railroad car.  Larry wants to marry his girlfriend, but she won't consent until Shemp marries her sister.  Shemp however, is constantly drunk and in love with "Carry", an imaginary giant canary.  Moe is an investigator from the railroad, sent to discover how the car was stolen from a moving train.  Moe is also in love with Shemp's girl.  Shemp winds up with both women, but still prefers his imaginary canary. , Set in the middle ages, the Stooges wish to marry their sweethearts, but the King won't give his consent until Princess Alicia gets married.  The princess is abducted by Mergatroyd, an evil magician who plans to marry her and become ruler of the country.  The Stooges help the princess escape and then defeat the magician and his henchmen in a sword fight "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215010000 +0000" stop="20260215033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Dracula ('31)</sub-title>
    <desc>""There are far worse things awaiting man than death." This horror classic stands as the most famous and celebrated film version of the popular vampire story. Bela Lugosi delivers a star-making performance as the titular villain--his erudite, refined Dracula is at once alluring and terrifying, while director Tod Browning creates an effectively haunted and chilled atmosphere. "Dracula" is an immeasurably important and influential film for its genre, and an invaluable touchstone in Universal's impressive and definitive horror film canon."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215033000 +0000" stop="20260215060000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Dinoshark</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215060000 +0000" stop="20260215070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Android Machine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Will and Dr. Smith discover an android-making machine. Smith uses it to create his own personal android, but soon the owner of the machine comes looking for payment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215070000 +0000" stop="20260215080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Doomsday Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview encounters terrifying extragalactic creatures who plan to use the sub's power to populate Earth with their kind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215080000 +0000" stop="20260215090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Framed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings help a tramp who is framed for murder by a photographer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215090000 +0000" stop="20260215100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Crack Of Doom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Landing on Krakatoa in 1883, the time travelers try to convince a British scientist that the volcano is about to explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215100000 +0000" stop="20260215110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Quantity: Unknown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To regain a metallic cylinder, the aliens will stop at nothing -- even murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215110000 +0000" stop="20260215120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Quest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams and Nakoma are told by Mad Jack,he's spoken with an Army Corporal. The Corporal said he was sent by the Govt. to help with issues regarding the animals. Adams is suspicious and thinks it may be a lie and the Corporal a bounty hunter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215120000 +0000" stop="20260215123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tusker Territory</sub-title>
    <desc>"Of all the behemoths that once roamed the earth, only the elephant is left for us to marvel about.  And marvel we should for here’s an animal that weights 10 tons, yet leaves an imprint only a half-inch deep when walking on soft sand…can eat 200 pounds of hay a day, drink 50 gallons of water at one go, grow to be 13 feet tall at the shoulder, yet can use its trunk so delicately it can pick a flower off the ground without crushing it.  But many questions about this animal remain unanswered.  By literally living with a family of elephants in Bechuanaland, Africa, we observe their fascinating life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215123000 +0000" stop="20260215130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Mastermind Of The Sea</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim with experts from the Seaquarium in Miami set out to capture a porpoise and study its mysterious progress of learning – the hop-skip around the world to see porpoises in far away places as Port Elizabeth, in South Africa; Coolangatta in Australia; and Whaler’s Cove, in Hawaii."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215130000 +0000" stop="20260215133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Animals That Time Forgot</sub-title>
    <desc>"In remote corners of the wild kingdom remaining untouched by forces of change there also remain animals that span the bridge of time back into prehistoric eras…like the Komodo Dragons off the coast of Java; marsupials that are rare and birds that appear as if they just flew out of the still streaming marshlands of the Mesozoic era."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215133000 +0000" stop="20260215140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Strangest Of All</sub-title>
    <desc>"A few of the many bizarre and strange animal behaviors that abound in the wild kingdom, the strangest of all are revealed in this episode."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215140000 +0000" stop="20260215143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Winter Comes To Yellowstone</sub-title>
    <desc>"All roads are closed, but by helicopter and snow plane Marlin and Jim travel though the park to uncover a fascinating story of animal life in winter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215143000 +0000" stop="20260215150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>South Through The Sonora</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim travel by jeep at the hottest time of the year to the rugged Sonora Desert in Arizona on a reptile collecting expedition."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215150000 +0000" stop="20260215153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Private Ear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter eavesdrops in on his siblings' private conversations with the help of Mike's tape recorder, causing no small amount of family discord. Marcia and Greg teach Peter a lesson with the help of - you guessed it - the same trusty tape recorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215153000 +0000" stop="20260215160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Her Sister's Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of being in Marcia's shadow, Jan is determined to do something that Marcia never did. She tries the pompom squad, and then an essay writing contest, where she wins first prize - or does she?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215160000 +0000" stop="20260215163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cabin In Beverly Hills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed puts up the cabin for Granny's birthday, which Mrs. Drysdale is not happy about. During the celebrating, a sociology student stops by and sees the Clampetts. She thinks they are Drysdale's servants and works to liberate them from what she believes to be a life of servitude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215163000 +0000" stop="20260215170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Foils A Home Wrecker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to save the cabin for the Clampetts, but his wife calls a professional home wrecker to tear down the mountain shack. Meanwhile, Ginny Jennings and her sociology professor come back to visit the Clampetts and see that they are still occupying the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215170000 +0000" stop="20260215173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy learns a great deal about Thelma Lou's cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215173000 +0000" stop="20260215180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Golf Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Championship golfer Jimmy Demaret visits the Ricardos when Lucy and Ethel arrive at a bizarre scheme for combating their "golf widowship." The girls install a basketball court in the Ricardo living room and pretend to be as deeply absorbed in the game as their husbands are in the fairways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215180000 +0000" stop="20260215183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Autobiography</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been given an assignment in which he must write a autobiography for class but isn't sure about his abilities at writing. So, he convinces a girl, who likes him, to write it for him. When she discovers that he is merely using her, she writes an outrageous life story and hands it in, causing embarrassment for Beaver when the teacher reads it in class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215183000 +0000" stop="20260215190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his heart set on taking a swing at being a paper boy again but another kid beats him to it. This leads Beaver to think about using sabatoge to get the new paper boy fired. However, the boy may just do that himself when the service becomes terrible leading Beaver to confront him only to discover he is a she.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215190000 +0000" stop="20260215200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>The Killing Kind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie calls Angels' Jill, Kelly and Sabrina together and tells them of the murder of the daughter of an old friend - a young investigative reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215200000 +0000" stop="20260215210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Between Friends</sub-title>
    <desc>"A prominent lawyer's murder casts suspicion on a disgruntled employee at his firm."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215210000 +0000" stop="20260215220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Funny Girl, The / Butch &amp; Sundance</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kay Penny's gift of humor that people consider most precious in life, restores the voice of little Pip in "The Funny Girl" on Fantasy Island. B111 Cummings and Alex Fairly have enough excitement to last ten lifetimes. As they leave Fantasy Island with their adventure dream fulfilled, "Butch and Sundance" are happy to return to reality."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215220000 +0000" stop="20260215230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Burl Of My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Vicki is infatuated with Gopher; a publisher falls for an author's niece; two passengers try to cheat each other in a treasure hunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215230000 +0000" stop="20260215233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Andy's big-city fishing buddies invites him to join the Esquire Club, an exclusive Raleigh men's organization. Barney also is asked to join but tries a little too hard to fit in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260215233000 +0000" stop="20260216000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Janay Smith- Sports &amp; Celebrities</sub-title>
    <desc>"Janay Smith is giving us a small glimpse at the world largest, private, game worn sports collection, a collection she inherited after her sports crazed, lawyer father left her, when he passed. Some of this spectacular collection is at the Smithsonian, but today, she'll show us Hank Aaron's jersey, and the game ticket from the day he broke Babe Ruth's home-run record. We'll see Muhammad Ali's trunks and training robe, Kobe Bryant's #8 autographed jersey, and Jim Brown's MVP trophy. Historian and African American material culture expert, Philip Merrill, will evaluate this collection with a number never heard before on "Collector's Call," and then attempt a trade Janay with a big-time big league offer. But will she play ball?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216000000 +0000" stop="20260216003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216003000 +0000" stop="20260216010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216010000 +0000" stop="20260216013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie, The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike &amp; Gloria get one of Mike's students to babysit Joey. Archie feels that the babysitters are too radical and takes care of babysitting himself along with his poker foursome.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216013000 +0000" stop="20260216020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Vs. The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the TV broken, Edith decides to buy a new one for Archie for their 30th wedding anniversary. But when the clerk won't let Edith buy a TV without Archie's signature because she's a woman, she goes to the bank for a loan. There too, she can not borrow money because she is just a housewife with no job, making Edith furious. Helpless, Edith goes home and asks Archie for $500, but she won't tell him why (surprise). During their conversation, Edith discovers that Archie may be sexist also.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216020000 +0000" stop="20260216023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Waitress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith finally confronts the waitress who tempted Archie's fidelity after Harry unwittingly hires her to work at Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216023000 +0000" stop="20260216030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Bogus Bills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is arrested for passing phony $10 bills she got from Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216030000 +0000" stop="20260216033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>I Wish I Were Gus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Alda arrives at his favorite uncle's funeral to rekindle a family feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216033000 +0000" stop="20260216040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Standard Deviation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert gives Ray and Debra an IQ test as part of his assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216040000 +0000" stop="20260216043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret Life Of Buddy And Sally</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob thinks Sally and Buddy are having an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216043000 +0000" stop="20260216050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Bird In The Head Hurts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura wonder about Richie when he claims a woodpecker is attacking him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216050000 +0000" stop="20260216053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Loudspeaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph writes a speech because he thinks he's going to be Raccoon of the Year—but it turns out Norton receives the honor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216053000 +0000" stop="20260216060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Piano In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man discovers that the piano he bought his wife for her birthday possesses magical properties—the music it plays makes people reveal their true essence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216060000 +0000" stop="20260216070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Trap  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A woman plots to slay her rich husband and marry one of his employees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216070000 +0000" stop="20260216080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Bag Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Syndicate is bribing a major politician, codenamed "C6," through their operatives Harry Fife and his chief killer, Jenkins. The IMF must find out who C6 is and get the evidence against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216080000 +0000" stop="20260216090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Stroke Of Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Keller, a promising art student, tests his new rifle by firing a random shot which instantly kills his mentor, the town minister, who happens to be driving on a road right in the line of fire. Kimble happens to be in the car after the minister gives</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216090000 +0000" stop="20260216100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>For The Love Of Money</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell tries to unravel the mystery of a mentally disturbed young man who's convinced that he's murdered his own brother twice!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216100000 +0000" stop="20260216103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216103000 +0000" stop="20260216110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216110000 +0000" stop="20260216113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 155 -- I.a.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Tony Johnson finds out he has been accused of a shakedown just after saving Malloy's life during a shootout. Reed and Malloy set out to find a bar girl named Ginger who Johnson says will prove his innocence, but her story leaves Malloy with an uneasy feeling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216113000 +0000" stop="20260216120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 66 -- The Vandals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy have a gun pulled on them after stopping a car that turns out to be stolen, but the contents of the trunk link the two suspects to an even more sinister crime. Afterward, a recently widowed father and his teenage daughter report that their home has just been toilet papered, which ends up being a prelude for a much more serious incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216120000 +0000" stop="20260216130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>It's 65!</sub-title>
    <desc>"What a transformation 60 years brings! Bill gives Toony a taste of life in 1965."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216130000 +0000" stop="20260216133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie, The Businessman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie get jobs at the Mayfield Dairy thanks to Ward pulling some strings. They soon unknowingly find themselves involved in a plot started by the foreman and his assistant, who are secretly stealing the merchandise. When Ward learns of the plot, he warns Wally who in turn tries to warn Eddie, but Eddie doesn't buy it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216133000 +0000" stop="20260216140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Football Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is scheduled to receive a football award at a father-son dinner being held in the school gym. While talking with his friends, Beaver learns that none of them are planning on wearing a jacket and a tie so when June and Ward insist that he wear one, he adamantly refuses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216140000 +0000" stop="20260216150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Poison Pen-pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A casual pen pal relationship leads to insider information and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216150000 +0000" stop="20260216160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Judge  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock accepts the pro bono case of Kevin Meredith, a young man accused of murdering his lover, who, as Matlock discovers, had a shocking secret. In order to capture the real killer, Matlock must end a long-time friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216160000 +0000" stop="20260216170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Devil And Mr. Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young son of a businessman escapes from his kidnappers, "The Devil" and "Mr. Frog," Five-O must recover the $300,000 ransom money that the desperate father paid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216170000 +0000" stop="20260216180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Substitute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Miss Hunter is called away unexpectedly, a substitute teacher with ways of her own takes over</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216180000 +0000" stop="20260216190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Wishbone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt goes after three bandits who robbed a stagecoach and killed the driver and guard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216190000 +0000" stop="20260216200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Jackknife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Searching for missing Ponderosa cattle, Adam Cartwright stops to aid injured rancher Matt Grant. What Adam doesn't know is that Grant is part of the very gang of rustlers responsible for the missing cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216200000 +0000" stop="20260216203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Illustrator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas encourages a drunken artist charged with murder to use his talents to identify the true killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216203000 +0000" stop="20260216210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Knife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark try to persuade a persecuted young mute to return stolen money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216210000 +0000" stop="20260216220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mark Hanford Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jack Hanford built his wealth with the intention of passing it on to his son. However, the son turns it all down to honor his Cheyenne heritage when his mother dies. To make matters worse, in his son's eyes, Hanford had sent for a woman he briefly knew to replace his mother before she had died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216220000 +0000" stop="20260216230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Simple Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Swamped with paperwork, the paramedics are continually distracted by emergencies: a girl trapped in an overturned car, a beautician who has taken too many diet pills, an elderly man and workers stuck on a blazing ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216230000 +0000" stop="20260216233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260216233000 +0000" stop="20260217000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217000000 +0000" stop="20260217003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217003000 +0000" stop="20260217010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217010000 +0000" stop="20260217013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pickle Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's canning time again, and Aunt Bee has put up another batch of pickles. After realizing the only thing they're good for is killing flies brave enough to land on them, Andy and Barney decide to substitute store-bought for her homemade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217013000 +0000" stop="20260217020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets an offer to become the sheriff of Greendale, and Andy tries to discourage him. Unsure how to handle matters, Andy gets the idea to let Barney be sheriff of Mayberry for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217020000 +0000" stop="20260217023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Look, Don't Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a waitress, catches Ray's eye, he has a lot of explaining to do.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217023000 +0000" stop="20260217030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Frank The Writer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank submits his writing to Ray's editor hoping to get his own column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217030000 +0000" stop="20260217033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a counterfeiting operation that has been set up in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217033000 +0000" stop="20260217040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One In Every Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A prisoner offers the Nazis information on Hogan's operation in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217040000 +0000" stop="20260217043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Sammy Davis Jr.</sub-title>
    <desc>In Backstage, Carol reunites with an old friend and her old prejudices come back. Then, in No Frills Airline, Tim receives horrible airplane service all because he didn't pay an extra fee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217043000 +0000" stop="20260217053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fancy Figures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Ellis is sent to jail for stealing the sum of $300,000. Ellis is later exonerated thanks to evidence discovered by his wife and the real thief, Charles Brewster, is arrested for the theft. Brewster manages to get out of jail on bail but later turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217053500 +0000" stop="20260217060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Rites Of Jeff Myrtlebank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man comes back to life at his own funeral and soon begins to act very strangely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217060500 +0000" stop="20260217070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Beard  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After receiving a wig and a beard, shy Wally Mills acquires a fresh personality, a girlfriend and an abundance of problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217070500 +0000" stop="20260217080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Color Her Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend and colleague of Joe Mannix has been murdered. The lawyer of the arrested suspect asks Mannix to find an important witness for the defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217080500 +0000" stop="20260217090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Kelly's Song</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The man who arranged the death of an embezzler cannot find the loot. But Cannon might, when he investigates on behalf of the man framed for the murder. But Cannon's client might be closer to the case than he lets on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217090500 +0000" stop="20260217100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man returns from prison and learns that his partner in a ten-year-old kidnapping never gave back the abducted child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217100000 +0000" stop="20260217103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217103000 +0000" stop="20260217110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217110000 +0000" stop="20260217113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Man Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed, who is an optimist and still has faith in the human race, is subjected to ridicule from Officer Wells after he is swindled twice. On patrol, he and Malloy come to the aid of a woman whose baby has been kidnapped by a heavily armed man seeking a large ransom. Afterward, wells once again questions Reed's judgment during the search for an intoxicated sniper at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217113000 +0000" stop="20260217120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 165 -- Once A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The search for a stabbing suspect leads to a bitter ex-cop who has just moved into the area. Afterward, Malloy and Reed deal with a naive and frustrated starlet who shoots up a telephone booth and loses her suitcase containing a live rattle snake. The officers then become involved in shootout at a train station that leads to another unfortunate run-in with the ex-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217120000 +0000" stop="20260217130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Black History In Visual Art</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217130000 +0000" stop="20260217133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Double Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's new girlfriend, Carolyn, can't go out to the movies on Saturday night because she has to watch her little sister, Susan. Carolyn suggests that Beaver take Susan out to the movies and that they all double date. Not wanting to let Wally down, Beaver decides to go along, despite being nervous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217133000 +0000" stop="20260217140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Joins Record Club</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver wants to join a record club and asks Ward for the money to join. Fed up with Beaver constantly asking for money, Ward decides to put him on an allowance. However, Beaver is so thrilled with his records he disreguards the bills for them and quickly finds himself swamped with records, a rising bill and not enough allowance to pay for everything."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217140000 +0000" stop="20260217150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mystified Miner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason tries to clear his young, beautiful client after a twisting and wheeling plot of murder, kidnapping and embezzlement unfolds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217150000 +0000" stop="20260217160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Affair (aka The Maid)  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents a maid accused of killing her employer at the request of the man's widow. The request is a little odd, but it seems the widow wants everyone to know exactly what kind of man her husband was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217160000 +0000" stop="20260217170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker's Wild, Man, Wild!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Two young men play an increasingly dangerous and deadly game for the attentions of a beautiful but spoiled heiress, who plays them off against each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217170000 +0000" stop="20260217180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Bequest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The promise of inherited money is behind some happy moments and unusual conflicts for the Walton Family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217180000 +0000" stop="20260217190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sanctuary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank robber takes refuge in a church, holding the pastor and two women hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217190000 +0000" stop="20260217200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Wooing Of Abigail Jones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to keep peace on the ranch, Hoss and Joe try to help ranch hand Hank Meyers woo the the plain-looking schoolteacher, Abigail Jones. When their first plan backfires, they convince Adam to get involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217200000 +0000" stop="20260217203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bertie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A lively old lady arrives in town hot on the trail of a notorious bandit—and the reward money for capturing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217203000 +0000" stop="20260217210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Six Years And A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor seeks revenge on the man he blames for ruining his practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217210000 +0000" stop="20260217220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bernal Sierra Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Revolutionary Bernal Sierra joins the train finding the wife of his dead friend married to Casey Reardon, who sold guns to the Mexican revolutionaries. Bernal is suspicious of Casey, his brothers and Perdita over missing gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217220000 +0000" stop="20260217230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Tee Vee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The paramedics rescue a man from a manhole fire. Chet and John blow up the station's TV. Dr. Morton treats a man with a bleeding peptic ulcer. An aquarium is delivered to Dr. Brackett, who suffers a toxic reaction to a catfish bite. A man accidentally glues his eyes shut. A gas explosion and mudslide trap a man in his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217230000 +0000" stop="20260217233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260217233000 +0000" stop="20260218000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218000000 +0000" stop="20260218003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218003000 +0000" stop="20260218010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218010000 +0000" stop="20260218013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Keeper Of The Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie joins a secret club that meets in Jubal Foster's barn. When Jubal burns his own barn down, he attempts to blame the group of boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218013000 +0000" stop="20260218020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bailey's Bad Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich kid Ronald Bailey is jailed when he blatantly defies the law. As Bailey waits for his influential father to bail him out, Andy teaches him the lesson of self-responsibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218020000 +0000" stop="20260218023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Your Place Or Mine?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ray's parents stop speaking, Marie moves in with Ray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218023000 +0000" stop="20260218030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>In-laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ray's in-laws come for a visit, he begs his parents to be nice to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218030000 +0000" stop="20260218033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happiness Is A Warm Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Klink finds Sergeant Schultz drunk he gets a tough new replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218033000 +0000" stop="20260218040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Russian Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to get a Russian pilot, who refuses to escape to London, back to Russia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218040000 +0000" stop="20260218043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Laughter Is the Best Medicine, Carol can't control her laughter while Harvey attempts to propose. Then, in Assembly Line, Carol tells her husband she wants a divorce while at work in the factory. Finally, in The Little Foxes, a film parody, Carol plays Bette Davis, a woman hoping her husband will die so she can inherit his fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218043000 +0000" stop="20260218053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Perjured Parrot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The courtroom action in this episode takes place at a coroner's inquest as a parrot holds the key to freeing suspect Ellen Sabin from blame in the murder of her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218053500 +0000" stop="20260218060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>To Serve Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kanamits, nine-foot-tall aliens, arrive on Earth with one lofty goal: To Serve Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218060500 +0000" stop="20260218070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Death Scene  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A mechanic with show business ambitions writes a play for the daughter of a once-famous director.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218070500 +0000" stop="20260218080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Return To Summer Grove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>At a request of a friend, Mannix returns to his hometown, Summer Grove. His friend is not only seriously ill, he also is a murder suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218080500 +0000" stop="20260218090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An expert hunter and gamekeeper dies, mauled to death by a lion that was supposedly tranquilized. His widow hires Cannon to figure out what happened and who is responsible.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218090500 +0000" stop="20260218100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Band Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby and J.R. help a cowgirl look for a missing broncobuster, unaware that he's already been murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218100000 +0000" stop="20260218103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218103000 +0000" stop="20260218110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218110000 +0000" stop="20260218113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 76 -- The Militants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed participate in the search for two black militants who ambush and critically wound two officers in their patrol car. When one of the suspects subsequently dies in custody, a bitter public relations battle begins with the militant group as the search for the other suspect continues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218113000 +0000" stop="20260218120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 164 -- The Poachers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young employee at the city garage steals a patrol car and engages in a high speed pursuit. Afterward, Malloy and Reed arrest a young woman trying to cash an old-age benefits check she found on the ground, report to an apartment complex garage that had its security camera stolen, investigate a break-in at a mortuary and arrest a couple of pill pushers at a warehouse in Officer Ed Well's territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218120000 +0000" stop="20260218130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Personality Crisis</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony, Bill and Quizzer take personality tests, which leads to a crisis of identity for the Quiz-man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218130000 +0000" stop="20260218133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To Ella</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After coming home late on a school night, Ward and June punish Beaver by not allowing him to go anywhere on school nights. Beaver feels the punishment is unfair, so Eddie suggests Beaver write to an advice column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218133000 +0000" stop="20260218140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Bachelor-at-large</sub-title>
    <desc>"The news that Eddie has moved out of his parent's house and into an apartment of his own has June worried that Wally may be contemplating something similar. However, Wally gets a picture of just how "happy" Eddie is being on his own and it makes him think twice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218140000 +0000" stop="20260218150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crippled Cougar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike Preston is a bitter man who despises Hugh Jamison because he mistakenly believes Jamison stole $100,000 from him and is responsible for him being crippled. Trying to entrap Jamison, Preston makes a mistake and is set up for murder by the real culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218150000 +0000" stop="20260218160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Seduction, The (aka The Quaterback)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock is hired to defend Brad Bingham, an aging football star with a reputation as a womanizer who was about to be cut from the team. Charlene is resistant to her father's choice, as she believes everything the tabloids have to say about Brad...not only that, but years earlier, he'd had a brief relationship with her friend Ellen Hawley, who had tried to kill herself after they broke up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218160000 +0000" stop="20260218170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Which Way Did They Go?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A career criminal fools McGarrett and the team into protecting the wrong bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218170000 +0000" stop="20260218180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Airmail Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Engine trouble on the air mail transport plane means the Waltons have a guest for a few days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218180000 +0000" stop="20260218190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Honor Before Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An Indian girl's father is sentenced to die for a murder he didn't commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218190000 +0000" stop="20260218200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Guilty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunman with vengeance on his mind tracks retired Sheriff Lem Partridge to Virginia City and is soon holding Lem's son, Jimmy, and good friend, Ben Cartwright, hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218200000 +0000" stop="20260218203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Flowers By The Door</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas unmasks a killer posing as a door-to-door seed salesman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218203000 +0000" stop="20260218210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Trek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance run into trouble transporting a captured killer back to face trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218210000 +0000" stop="20260218220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Marie Dupree Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful woman riding with the train likes flirting. When she gets mixed up with the wrong man, she strings along a boy on the train in order to make him jealous, playing one man's love against another's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218220000 +0000" stop="20260218230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>On Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A camera crew follows Squad 51 while a teenager is bitten by a snake, a would-be stuntman dangles from an I-beam, a boy falls off a cliff and a man is trapped under a burning fuel truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218230000 +0000" stop="20260218233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260218233000 +0000" stop="20260219000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219000000 +0000" stop="20260219003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219003000 +0000" stop="20260219010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219010000 +0000" stop="20260219013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manicurist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful manicurist from the city comes to Floyd's to set up shop. She makes all the wives in town extremely nervous as she manicures their husbands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219013000 +0000" stop="20260219020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After a series of mishaps, Henry Bennett gets a reputation in town as a jinx. The more Andy tries to dispel the rumor the deeper the hole gets, until Henry decides it would be best if he left town altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219020000 +0000" stop="20260219023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Win, Lose, Or Draw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray gets tired of being treated like a kid at his father's poker game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219023000 +0000" stop="20260219030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Turkey Or Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides it's her turn to prepare the holiday meal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219030000 +0000" stop="20260219033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>An Evening Of Generals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as waiters, Hogan and the gang scheme to get rid of a room full of German generals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219033000 +0000" stop="20260219040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Loves A Snowman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys must smuggle a U.S. bomber crew out of camp while under surveillance by Hochstetter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219040000 +0000" stop="20260219043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Hollow Hero, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice has a flashback to when she first started dating her husband. Then, in The Hollow Hero, a guard refuses to the King and Queen inside without first receiving a popsicle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219043000 +0000" stop="20260219053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shattered Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah Werner asks Mason to find her husband, Hugo Werner, who ran off with her inheritance. Hugo, now using the name Hans Breel, is working on a gem scam but his scheme backfires when he is murdered and Sarah is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219053500 +0000" stop="20260219060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man possessing the power of transformation tries to help a crippled little girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219060500 +0000" stop="20260219070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer And The Undertaker  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Arthur Mannix is a photographer and Hiram Price is an undertaker. Both hide behind their respective professors to conceal another profession: hired killer. Both men, it turns out, have the same boss, who gives each an order to eliminate the other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219070500 +0000" stop="20260219080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Haughty actor Mitch Cantrell is not exactly loved by his colleagues. When at a film shoot, a murder attempt is made on him, and it is soon up to Mannix to protect the obnoxious actor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219080500 +0000" stop="20260219090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Voice From The Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>"Reverend" Will can heal the sick by the power of faith. Or can he? Either way, his "powers" won't keep a witness to murder from coming forward, and that means... another murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219090500 +0000" stop="20260219100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Voice Of The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman who allegedly killed herself a year ago is now the unlikely suspect in a series of murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219100000 +0000" stop="20260219103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219103000 +0000" stop="20260219110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219110000 +0000" stop="20260219113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219113000 +0000" stop="20260219120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219120000 +0000" stop="20260219130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1990</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony revisit the year 1990."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219130000 +0000" stop="20260219133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Sheep Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>At school, Beaver gets into an argument with a girl who retaliates by making fun of Beaver's hair, calling him a sheepdog. Incredibly self-concious, Beaver goes out to the store and buys different hairsprays and gels to try to improve his hairdo. He doesn't get the reaction he was expecting when he tries his new hairdo out on his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219133000 +0000" stop="20260219140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Car Accident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for the weekend and Wally asks to borrow Ward's new car to go to a dance. Although hesitant, Ward finally gives in and lets him take it. However, after the dance, Lumpy runs into some car trouble which results in Wally smashing the headlight on the car. Wally is now faced with having it repaired and paying for it himself and trying to find a way to break it gently to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219140000 +0000" stop="20260219150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Absent Artist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cartoonist Pete Manders is elated when the owner of the comic strip "Zingy" offers to sell him the strip for a song. However, Pete then learns that his girlfriend is running away to Europe with the strip's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219150000 +0000" stop="20260219160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Don: Part 1  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents Nicholas Baron, a well-known mobster who has been accused of murdering a rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219160000 +0000" stop="20260219170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett gets more than he bargained for when a birthday present explodes and blinds him. As the Five-O team searches for the would-be assassin, McGarrett tries to recuperate with the help of the tough Nurse Edith Lavallo (played by Marion Ross of 'Happy Days').</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219170000 +0000" stop="20260219180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy's growing attachment to Miss Hunter is rocked when she becomes interested in someone else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219180000 +0000" stop="20260219190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt captures a young outlaw, who waits for his brother to free him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219190000 +0000" stop="20260219200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lawmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights may have to take the law into their own hands when Virginia City's temporary sheriff uses his new badge as a license to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219200000 +0000" stop="20260219203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Actress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A deathbed request from an old friend sends Lucas to a neighboring town in search of the man's long-lost sweetheart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219203000 +0000" stop="20260219210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas thinks he has seen a ghost when a young man, eerily similar to a man he killed in the Civil War, challenges him to a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219210000 +0000" stop="20260219220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Called Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Horse, a name he comes to be called, is searching for himself. Because he doesn't feel that he found happiness in Boston, where he grew up, he tries out west, under the watchful eye of a small tribe of Crow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219220000 +0000" stop="20260219230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communications</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A young worker gets his arm caught in a machine. A communication snafu occurs between Squad 51 and the hospital. Dr. Morton treats a young violinist. Two boys get a car trapped on the roof of a house. A woman tries to commit suicide by overdosing and won't let the paramedics treat her, making them wait until she passes out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219230000 +0000" stop="20260219233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260219233000 +0000" stop="20260220000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220000000 +0000" stop="20260220003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220003000 +0000" stop="20260220010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220010000 +0000" stop="20260220013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbreak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>State police come to town in search of payroll robbers. They want Andy and Barney to stay out of the way, but end up needing them more than they thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220013000 +0000" stop="20260220020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Medal For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his heart set on winning a medal in a foot race at the town picnic. When he loses, he exhibits poor sportmanship. Andy teaches him a lesson about being a good sport.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220020000 +0000" stop="20260220023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Nemo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is reminded by Debra that their kids are growing up fast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220023000 +0000" stop="20260220030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ball, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray begins to doubt if anyone actually tells the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220030000 +0000" stop="20260220033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plays a waiting game with a German general. The scheming general has planted a rocket-fuel depot right outside Stalag 13 in hopes of trapping the area's resident saboteur, whom he suspects is Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220033000 +0000" stop="20260220040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Carter Turns Traitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter pretends to be a traitor so he can learn the location of a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220040000 +0000" stop="20260220043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Openers / Jacques Touteaux / Fortune Cookies</sub-title>
    <desc>In Easy Openers, a hungry Carol tries to open her food locked in its container. Then, in Jacques Touteaux, Harvey describes the great feats Tim the diver will do, only he's too scared to do them. Finally, in Fortune Cookies, Carol suspects her best friend and husband are cheating together after a fortune cookie tells her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220043000 +0000" stop="20260220053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Brunette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Eva Martell is hired out of numerous candidates by Melvin Slater to impersonate a woman named Helen Reynolds. Eva is paid extremely well and given a nice apartment for assuming the identity of Helen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220053500 +0000" stop="20260220060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>To her parents' horror, a six-year-old girl vanishes into the fourth dimension after rolling under her bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220060500 +0000" stop="20260220070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Thou Still Unravished Bride  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A police officer fears that his fiancée has fallen prey to a murderer terrorizing the city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220070500 +0000" stop="20260220080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Question Of Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix examines a long-forgotten hospital scandal: After a rich businessman died in a hospital, the doctor attending to him was convicted of malpractice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220080500 +0000" stop="20260220090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady In Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young dancer who teaches at a lonely hearts club winds up dead. One of his clients hires Cannot to find out who killed him. It isn't long before Frank discovers the dancer was also a con man who had bilked several women out of their life savings. And that lengthens the list of suspects considerably.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220090500 +0000" stop="20260220100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must beat a bounty hunter to an escaped convict who can vindicate a prison trustee charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220100000 +0000" stop="20260220103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220103000 +0000" stop="20260220110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220110000 +0000" stop="20260220113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220113000 +0000" stop="20260220120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220120000 +0000" stop="20260220130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Jobs Of Yesteryear</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill looks for a second job."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220130000 +0000" stop="20260220133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During one of his football team's games, Beaver is sent in and scores the winning touchdown, which results in a picture in the paper. Soon, Beaver finds himself swamped with attention and quickly lets it goes to his head. He begins acting like he's better than everyone and begins to alienate Gilbert, Whitey and Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220133000 +0000" stop="20260220140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Party Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks June and Ward if he could have a party and with some prodding, Wally finally gets their permission. June quickly begins the plans and Beaver gets a look at the guest list and quickly finds that he's not invited. For revenge, Beaver decides to sabotage Wally's party with a variety of gags that he bought at a magic shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220140000 +0000" stop="20260220150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prodigal Parent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>When Philip Larkin, the owner of an import-export company, is murdered, his step-father, Joseph Harrison, is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220150000 +0000" stop="20260220160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Don: Part 2  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Even though they've lost a key witness, Matlock keeps defending mobster Nicholas Baron against the charge that he murdered a rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220160000 +0000" stop="20260220170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Run, Johnny, Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett refuses to accept that AWOL sailor John Mala shot a Navy MP without cause. Christopher Walken guest stars as the friend of the shooting victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220170000 +0000" stop="20260220180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Awakening</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma is turning 68 and concerned about getting old</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220180000 +0000" stop="20260220190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Which Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Buffalo hunters kidnap Doc and Festus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220190000 +0000" stop="20260220200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Look To The Stars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A young genius, Albert Michaelson vies for a scholarship. Adam assists Albert in the boy's experiments. Albert only needs the school teacher's approval to be granted a scholarship, which will be very difficult to get considering Albert was expelled from school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220200000 +0000" stop="20260220203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas agrees to take a job as a federal undercover agent and goes to Wyoming to investigate rumors of sales of arms to renegade indians. His life is endangered by the town drunk, who stumbles onto his true identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220203000 +0000" stop="20260220210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark stays with Miss Milly, while Lucas is in Wyoming on the trail of a gang illegally selling weapons to the Indians. Mark suffers from loneliness and doubt while his father is away for two months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220210000 +0000" stop="20260220220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sarah Drummond Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>During a storm, Flint takes shelter at a farmhouse. He soon discovers the husband is refusing his wife the care of a midwife and must determine why before it's too late.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220220000 +0000" stop="20260220230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>To Buy Or Not To Buy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy thinks about buying a house, but delays too long. Responding to a fire, the firemen find two children trapped on the second floor. Two driving students are involved in a minor collision. Another traffic accident results in two injuries and a missing dog. A teenage epileptic is stranded on a concrete beam under a bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220230000 +0000" stop="20260220233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260220233000 +0000" stop="20260221000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221000000 +0000" stop="20260221003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221003000 +0000" stop="20260221010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221010000 +0000" stop="20260221013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221013000 +0000" stop="20260221020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a sort of publicity stunt, the town decides to pull over the first car that drives through Mayberry and make its occupant the town's guest of honor. That lucky driver? A recently released convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221020000 +0000" stop="20260221023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Debra's Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray tries to juggle the responsibilities of home and work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221023000 +0000" stop="20260221030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Handsome?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is reluctant to go on a date because he's insecure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221030000 +0000" stop="20260221033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Two Nazis For The Price Of One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A Gestapo agent knows about Hogan's operation and tries to leverage this knowledge to find out information about the Manhattan Project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221033000 +0000" stop="20260221040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Doctor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink's illness causes problems for one of Hogan's plots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221040000 +0000" stop="20260221043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Cher</sub-title>
    <desc>In Dual Pianos, a great pianist tries to calm his protege before they play together. Then in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV products, including Wish Detergent, Long Distance Phone Call, L'eggs Pantyhose, Buff-Up Toothpaste, and Second Cup of Coffee. Finally, in The Not So Eternal Triangle, a beautiful woman finds she can't compete with her frumpy husband's mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221043000 +0000" stop="20260221053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Glittering Goldfish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An inventor of a cure for sick fish is charged with the murder of the purchaser of a pet fish store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221053500 +0000" stop="20260221060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Person Or Persons Unknown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man wakes up one morning to discover that no one knows who he is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221060500 +0000" stop="20260221070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Completely Foolproof  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Counterplots flourish in this story of a woman's plot to divorce her rich, two-timing husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221070500 +0000" stop="20260221080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For The Peep-show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The uncle of a young woman has disappeared after giving her $300,000 dollars in cash for safekeeping. Mannix must find out where the money comes from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221080500 +0000" stop="20260221090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Kathy Ackers hires Cannon to find out why her father, a banker, committed suicide at a Caribbean resort. She thinks he was murdered, and wants Cannon to prove it. But the man was embezzling from his own bank, so maybe he did have a motive to kill himself...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221090500 +0000" stop="20260221100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Renegade's Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby's search for a 6-year-old boy leads him to the boy's father - a vagrant who deals in illegal arms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221100000 +0000" stop="20260221103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Young Matchmakers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Widow Kate's three daughters organize a lonely hearts club to find eligible bachelors for their mother.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
