<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705013000 +0000" stop="20250705020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705020000 +0000" stop="20250705023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Axis Annie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use a propaganda radio announcer to get information to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705023000 +0000" stop="20250705030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>What Time Does The Balloon Go Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A basket-weaving and a kite-flying contest are part of Hogan's plan to transport an agent to England in a balloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705030000 +0000" stop="20250705033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Stop At Willoughby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Riding home from work on a train, a stressed-out man falls asleep and dreams it is 1880 and he is entering a small town called Willoughby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705033000 +0000" stop="20250705043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unsuitable Uncle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An unscrupulous uncle, who is in reality the father of his niece, returns home from the sea seeking money from the sale of oil leases on his land. When the man is found murdered, his shipmate is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705043500 +0000" stop="20250705050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Police Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate a scam involving a phony LAPD newsletter, which comes with a card for subscribers entitling the bearer to preferential treatment from the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705050500 +0000" stop="20250705053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Three Dreams Of Findlater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband dreams constantly of a beautiful woman who prompts him to kill his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705053500 +0000" stop="20250705060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night The World Ended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of newspapermen plays a joke on a man who in return decides to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705060500 +0000" stop="20250705070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Cage A Sea Gull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The site of a helicopter accident uncovers the body of a member of the Nazi party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705070500 +0000" stop="20250705080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Beats The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon faces a mob kingpin threatening the life of a gambler's wife. Toby Hauser has accumulated 200,000 dollars in game debts. When he hides away his wife asks Cannon for help. Toby wants to put everything on a map. This game should be his last. Either he wins, or he dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705080500 +0000" stop="20250705090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The two amateur singers that Barnaby put in jail escape and head for Nashville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705090000 +0000" stop="20250705093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Umquaw Strip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad executive Homer Bedloe believes he has found a loophole in getting the Cannonball shut down: a Native American tribe may have a land claim to an area in which the tracks cross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705093000 +0000" stop="20250705100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>As Hooterville Goes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A new automatic voting machine in Crabtree Corners may end Hooterville's record as the first community in the state to file election returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705100000 +0000" stop="20250705103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale gets Jed to back the Beverly Hills Ballet Company, and Jed figures that ballet is the perfect way to keep Granny, who is tired of getting “butler sassed,” among other things, in Beverly Hills. Jed gets her interested in the dance just as Mrs. Drysdale gets the money she needs to save the ballet company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705103000 +0000" stop="20250705110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Sam Drucker's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts return from giving up J.C. Enterprises, and Granny gets a telegram saying that Sam Drucker, who won a trip to Hollywood, is going to visit, thinking he is coming to propose. When he arrives, she tries to get him to believe she is the goddess of the handsome Hollywood actors, as does Jethro, who doesn’t want Granny to move to Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705110000 +0000" stop="20250705113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Popeye For President, Weight For Me, Matinee Idol Popeye, Barbecue For Two</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Bluto run for President against each other., Popeye and Brutus return from six months at sea to find a very different Olive., Brutus is an egotistical French director making a film about Antony and Cleopatra, starring Popeye and Olive Oyl., Popeye's BBQ for two with  is interrupted by everyone else."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705113000 +0000" stop="20250705120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Brothers Carry-mouse-off, Goldilocks And The Three Bears, Jerry-go-round</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry uses radar to avoid any traps Tom has set up for him using food. Eventually Tom tries to dress up like a female mouse to trap Jerry but he is foiled when other cats chase him., Papa bear is a bit accident prone and somewhat cowardly in this version of the classic tale., Jerry helps out an injured elephant at the circus and the two work together to stop Tom from bothering them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705120000 +0000" stop="20250705130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Wrestling Wrecks, Ski-napper, Witty Kitty, Private Eye Pooch, Case Of The Cold Storage Yegg, Three Lazy Mice, Hot Noon Or 12 O'clock For Sure</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody heckles at a wrestling match and ends up in the ring with the champ., Chilly tries to borrow coal from a ski resort where Smedley is working. When Smedley refuses, Chilly uses skis for tinder instead., Doc tries to claim a turkey he won in a raffle, only to discover the raffle was a con, and the prize is guarded by a watchdog named Cecil., After escaping a taxidermists' office, Woody is pursued by Strongnose the Bloodhound, who is supposed to bring him back to be stuffed., Inspector Willoughby follows bank robber Yeggs Benedict around the world in an attempt to capture him., Three lazy mice try to get out of working by claiming to be blind., Woody is a piano player in the Old West. When Buzz Buzzard comes into town to kill the sheriff, the sheriffs ask Woody to take over and catch him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705130000 +0000" stop="20250705140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare We Go, Old Glory, Buckaroo Bugs, By Word Of Mouse, The Cat's Bah, Yankee Doodle Bugs</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs accompanies Christopher Columbus to search for America. , Porky learns about the importance of the Pledge of Allegiance from the spirit of Uncle Sam and gets a complete history lesson., The masked marauder strikes again! A local dopey-hero is hired to catch the villain. Bugs gives the hero a hard time until he realizes that the masked marauder is Bugs! , A foreigner mouse comes to America and is amazed by its economic system. He goes to a mouse professor who explains how it works while they are being chased by Sylvester. , Pepe is in search of a female, American tourist skunk to take back to the Casbah. The, unfortunate, object of his desire is a female cat who accidentally had paint make a stripe on her back., Bugs gives his nephew pointers on early American history, writing himself into about half of the events. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705140000 +0000" stop="20250705150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Undead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys become involved with a voodoo ceremony and the walking dead as they try to track down a missing scientist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705150000 +0000" stop="20250705160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Felizia Kingdom Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Tough as nails Felizia Kingdom controls an enormous amount of land by force, and no one is good enough to inherit the responsibility. When Flint handles her henchmen with ease, she decides he's the man for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705160000 +0000" stop="20250705170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Safe Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Three comically inept brothers try hard to crack a railroad safe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705170000 +0000" stop="20250705173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>No Chip</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hutch Dolan and his brothers cause trouble by putting their cattle on Jeff Mossman’s land. They cause more trouble but pouring flour onto Pete, Jeff’s son. When Jeff confronts the Dolan’s with a gun, Hutch shoots him. With Jeff in town at Doc's the Dolan's ride back to Mossman's ranch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705173000 +0000" stop="20250705180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Wave</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gus Mather comes into Dodge and throws a big wake for a man named Orson Boggs Doc and Chester are suspicious of this whole wake situation, but Chester and Doc attend the wake nonetheless and partake of the free drinks. When Matt comes back to Dodge from his business trip, Chester informs Matt on what has been going on . Matt also thinks something strange is going on as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705180000 +0000" stop="20250705190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss gets a taste of racism when he helps a black family get their farm in working order.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705190000 +0000" stop="20250705193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705193000 +0000" stop="20250705200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rancher dies after the bank forecloses the mortgage on his property, his son blames the banker for his father's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705200000 +0000" stop="20250705210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Deadhorse: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Town boss Jud Hammerklein remains confident that he will never be executed, despite the feverish activity of the hangman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705210000 +0000" stop="20250705213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Helen Of Abajinian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>An Armenian winemaker hires Paladin to find his runaway daughter and break up her ill-considered romance with a cowhand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705213000 +0000" stop="20250705220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Breakout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh in a federal prison plotting the great escape? The government employs Randall to portray an escaped prisoner in order to trick his cellmate into leading authorities to the $50,000 he stole and stashed away in a secret location.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705220000 +0000" stop="20250706000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Missing Links, Rockin Through The Rockies, G.i. Wanna Go Home, Merry Mavericks, Corny Casanovas, Uncivil War Birds</sub-title>
    <desc>"Larry, Moe and Curly go on a location to Africa when Curly is cast as a gorilla, and there they come face to face with danger when they encounter a real gorilla on the set.  , The Stooges are frontier guides leading a minstrel show west.  When hostile Indians run the horses run off they are stranded.  They must contend with a snowstorm and a marauding bear as well the Indians.  After almost killing each other ice fishing they solve their problems by rigging up a sail on the wagon and sailing west. , The Stooges are civil war soldiers who are constantly changing uniforms to avoid the opposing armies.  Eventually they decide to be loyal to the south, but remain disguised as Union soldiers.  Curly is detected as a spy, but Moe and Larry prevent his execution.  The boys escape with a secret map and marry their three southern belles. , The Stooges are discharged from the army and go to see their fiancées, but find they have been dispossessed and the wedding is off until they find a home.  The boys have trouble finding a vacant apartment so they set up housekeeping in a vacant lot.  Their housing problems seem to be solved until a farmer destroys their new home with a tractor.  The Stooges then build a house of their own, but the girls aren't impressed with the one room mansion and walk out on them. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are mistaken for lawmen and manage to capture a gang of crooks.  The boys then get the job of guarding some money in an old house reputed to be haunted by the ghost of an Indian Chief.  The crooks escape and go after the money disguised as ghosts, but Shemp, disguised as the Indian Chief, manages to knock them out. , Love is in the air for these laughable Lotharios. The Stooges all romance the same gold-digging gal with hilarious results.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706000000 +0000" stop="20250706023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Vampire</sub-title>
    <desc>"When an errant bomb unearths the coffin of a vampire during the London Blitz, a gravedigger unknowingly reanimates the monster by removing the stake from his heart."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706023000 +0000" stop="20250706030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>When The Rat's Away, The Mice Will Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler blackmails Commissioner Gordon: unless he's paid $1 million dollars, he'll destroy The Queen of Freedom Monument along with King Boris.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706030000 +0000" stop="20250706040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Where No Man Has Gone Before</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While exploring the edge of the galaxy, the Enterprise encounters an energy barrier that gives two crewmen godlike powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706040000 +0000" stop="20250706043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Through The Time Barrier</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Twiddle invents a time machine which takes Jimmy, Lois, Clark and a thug back 50,000 years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706043000 +0000" stop="20250706050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Talking Clue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Inspector's son is collecting sounds with a tape machine and records a safe being opened. When two crooks use the tape to their advantage, the son becomes an unwitting accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706050000 +0000" stop="20250706060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>There Were Giants In The Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Robinson discovers that the planet they are on will travel further from the sun. In an attempt to survive the Robinsons pack up and head south. Dr Smith stays at the Jupiter 2 while the Robinson family encounters a terrifying cyclops and an ancient deserted city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706060000 +0000" stop="20250706070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Phantom Strikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Havoc is wrought aboard the Seaview, as it is nearly destroyed by a phantom sub and its ghostly captain who seeks to reincarnate himself through Commander Crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706070000 +0000" stop="20250706080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings inadvertently cause a cave-in that traps two giant children, and Steve and Dan volunteer their services to Kobick to help rescue the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706080000 +0000" stop="20250706090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Massacre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers try to save themselves from the massacre of Custer's Seventh Cavalry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706090000 +0000" stop="20250706100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Watchers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A hotel owner is taken over by invaders awaiting a guest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706100000 +0000" stop="20250706110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Cub (pilot)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Little Eliza and her parents are headed out west. During a stop, she wanders off and they (unknowingly) leave without her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706110000 +0000" stop="20250706113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Flight</sub-title>
    <desc>"An analysis of the ‘miracle of flight’ from the soaring condors of the Andes to the backward-flying fairy terns of Midway."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706113000 +0000" stop="20250706120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Danger: Wild Animals</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim demonstrate how to handle dangerous animals of the zoo and the wild."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706120000 +0000" stop="20250706123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Prairie Village</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the base of Devils Tower near Horse Heaven Pass in Wyoming, is a wilderness city populated by the ….prairie dog."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706123000 +0000" stop="20250706130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Shines</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim rate the I.Q.’s of the gorilla, chimpanzee, baboon, orangutan, gibbon and ring-tailed monkey."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706130000 +0000" stop="20250706133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Island Outposts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go island-hopping around the world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706133000 +0000" stop="20250706140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Giants Of Dadanawa</sub-title>
    <desc>"Because of its inaccessibility to man and its climate, the South American jungles encourage the growth of its animal life.  Marlin and Stan Brock go on an expedition to capture the largest of their kind and to see just why these jungle giants grow to such proportions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706140000 +0000" stop="20250706143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Hair-brained Scheme</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby, wanting to get rich quick, begins selling bottles of hair tonic. One of his customers is his brother, Greg, who finds his hair turned orange, just days before his high school graduation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706143000 +0000" stop="20250706150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Libby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A troublesome letter about a blended family in an advice column draws Marcia's attention, and she assumes it was written by either Mike or Carol. She and the other kids devise a plot to keep their newly formed family together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706150000 +0000" stop="20250706153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Fonzie Gets Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Fonzie is accidentally shot during a weekend trip to Potsie's uncle's cabin, Fonzie, Chachi and Roger each describe their versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706153000 +0000" stop="20250706160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Monastery Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne is allowed to stay at a convent for a couple of weeks, but she soon gets on the Mother Superior's bad side when she has trouble keeping a vow of silence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706160000 +0000" stop="20250706163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706163000 +0000" stop="20250706170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Does The Tango</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Chicken-raising and practicing a tango for Little Ricky's school PTA meeting combine to get the Ricardos and the Mertzes in a verbal battle. It's up to Ricky, Jr., and his neighborhood pal, Bruce Ramsey, to straighten things out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706170000 +0000" stop="20250706173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat Builders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally, Chester and Tooey are building their own boat and plan to sail on it, despite Ward and June's forbidding Wally. Once at the lake, Beaver is the only one small enough to get in it and once on the water, the boat tips over leaving a soaked Beaver behind. However, it's trying to keep their afternoon of boating a secret from Ward and June, that's really going to wipe Wally and Beaver out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706173000 +0000" stop="20250706180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Garage Painters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lazy weekend leads Ward to direct Wally and Beaver to read a book, Tom Sawyer. The book influences them so much that they take on the job of painting the garage doors. However, they soon find the job to be awfully boring and messy. Chaos erupts when neighbor Bengie Bellamy stops by wanting to help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706180000 +0000" stop="20250706183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Guru</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro decides to become a guru, which he believes will help him get girls, seeking the help of Mrs. Drysdale's guru, who is really a fake after money. Granny tries to bust him, but after the two have some moonshine, she ends up becoming the Great Mother, the Queen of Gurus, herself. She decides to go to India with the guru. Drysdale hears of this and calls the police to arrest the phony guru, but when the police do show they end up arresting Granny in her guru getup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706183000 +0000" stop="20250706190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Jogging Clampetts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny sees Mrs. Drysdale chasing her husband, unaware that they are jogging, saying that she is really going to beat him. She starts believing that Mrs. Drysdale is beating her husband and the violence will spread. When Elly says that she beat Jethro, Granny worries the violence has spread, but Elly and Jethro clear everything up, telling her they’ve been jogging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706190000 +0000" stop="20250706193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan's Mother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A native family from another island comes seeking a husband for their lovely but large daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706193000 +0000" stop="20250706200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Beauty Is As Beauty Does</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan suggests a beauty contest to decide which of the three women will become "Ms. Castaway."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706200000 +0000" stop="20250706203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Bell  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint and Naomi hide a stray dog in the garage and convince Mama she is going senile when she complains of hearing a dog barking.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706203000 +0000" stop="20250706210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Very Dirty Dancing  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama enters a dance competition, nothing is going to stop her "Latin Sizzle" from winning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706210000 +0000" stop="20250706220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Chef</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubing's friend tries to cheer a former lover; the chef quits; an investigator (Bernie Kopell) probes a jewel theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706220000 +0000" stop="20250706223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rehabilitation Of Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to use psychology to reform Otis of his drinking habit but this eventually leads Otis to "take his business" elsewhere—the jail in Mt. Pilot!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706223000 +0000" stop="20250706230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Bruce Pascal- Hot Wheels</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bruce Pascal's got a need for speed.  As a child, he loved Hot Wheels.  Now, as an adult, he has a jaw-dropping, museum-like car collection that includes not just the cars. But also, some extremely rare items that were used to make the cars.  Today, Bruce takes Lisa on a tour of his collection, from a hand-drawn sketch of the Olds 442, to a wood model Ferrari, to the Holy Grail of Hot Wheels, Bruce has them all and loves sharing his passion with others.  Our expert, Joel Magee, will appraise Bruce's collection today, and who better than a self-proclaimed toy scout and a race car driver!  Joel will also attempt to pull off a heart racing car trade with Bruce.  One, one-of-a-kind prototype, for another.  Who will end up in the driver's seat, our expert or collector?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706230000 +0000" stop="20250706233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706233000 +0000" stop="20250707000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707000000 +0000" stop="20250707003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie In The Cellar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Irene installs the new lock on the cellar door just as Mike and Gloria go away for the weekend and Edith leaves for a baby shower leaving Archie home alone. Not having paid attention to Irene's instructions, Archie locks himself in the basement. After finding a bottle of Polish vodka, Archie spends a long night contemplating his life through the haze of a drunken stupor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707003000 +0000" stop="20250707010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Black Is The Color Of My True Love's Wig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to try something new, Gloria buys a brunette wig and it immediately arouses Mike, who desperately tries to get Gloria to wear it while they make love. However, Gloria is insulted which leads to a big fight that lands Mike to sleeping on the couch. Meanwhile, Archie is out of town on a Veteran's retreat, but when he arrives home he finds himself in the middle of the argument centering on the wig.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707010000 +0000" stop="20250707013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Second Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>For her 25th wedding anniversary, Edith is planning a romantic second honeymoon getaway to Atlantic City, the same place they went on their first honeymoon. However, trying to keep it a secret and trying to get Archie to come along may be a challenge, since he is all excited about an upcoming basketball game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707013000 +0000" stop="20250707020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Taxi Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's moonlighting, driving cabs for Bert Munson, puts him in harms way when a young man pulls a gun on him and demands his wallet. Down at the police station, Archie is eager to identify the suspect, that is until an influential politician attempts to dissuade Archie by bribing him from pressing charges against the perpetrator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707020000 +0000" stop="20250707023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Steve Lawrence  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 09/28/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707023000 +0000" stop="20250707030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 04/28/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707030000 +0000" stop="20250707033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>See Rob Write, Write Rob, Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura is inspired to write a children's book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707033000 +0000" stop="20250707040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>You're Under Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Angry after a fit, Rob has an even worse night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707040000 +0000" stop="20250707043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Alice And The Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and Nortons visit the Wedemeyers and the wives believe their husbands are neglecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707043000 +0000" stop="20250707053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Death Ship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A three-man spacecraft lands on a planet and discovers the wreckage of a spacecraft identical to their own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707053000 +0000" stop="20250707060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hands Of Mr. Otterhole</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial killer uses the heavy London fog to confuse the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707060000 +0000" stop="20250707070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Flip Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF must break up a drug-smuggling ring. Bracken gets his drugs from Mexico compliments of Diego Maximillian, who gets his drugs legally from C.W. Cameron. The IMF must connect Cameron to Bracken.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707070000 +0000" stop="20250707080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Nicest Fella You'd Ever Want To Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While traveling though a small town in Arizona, Kimble is arrested by the brutal and sadistic Sheriff Jo Bob Sims who has political ambitions. Sheriff Sims (unaware of Kimble's true identity) subjects him to slave labor with a group of other vagrants he a</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707080000 +0000" stop="20250707090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of A Murder</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell fights to prove the innocence of a mentally retarded teenager accused of homicide."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707090000 +0000" stop="20250707093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese widow is senselessly murdered, leaving her small daughter an orphan. Friday has a hard time controlling his emotions while seeking the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707093000 +0000" stop="20250707100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707100000 +0000" stop="20250707103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Adoption</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate the ransacking of a college football locker room and uncover a controversial performance enhancing drug program. They also investigate suspicious parents who backtrack after their maid reports their baby as missing, apprehend a reported prowler who is then suspiciously let into the home by the female accuser and engage in a bullet-riddled high speed chase through a residential area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707103000 +0000" stop="20250707110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Mary Hong Loves Tommy Chen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An undercover cop is left in a coma after being shot while investigating a potential attack by a youth gang on an elders' association in chinatown, but his girlfriend refuses to disclose time critical information to malloy and reed on orders from her powe</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707110000 +0000" stop="20250707120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Treehouse Adventure</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony build the treehouse of their dreams."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707120000 +0000" stop="20250707123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Pug Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When the new girl, Gloria, tells Wally that he has a pug nose, he becomes incredibly self-conscious and purchases a contraption that is suppose to give him a strong Roman nose. When Ward discovers the device, he gives him a pep talk which just makes matters worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707123000 +0000" stop="20250707130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Pigeons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Larry and Whitey begin a pigeon club and they each purchase pigeons of their own. Beaver names his two Miss Canfield and Miss Landers, after his two teachers. However, when Beaver comes down with chicken pox, Wally is forced into caring for them, but soon finds Beaver isn't the only one ill, Miss Canfield and Miss Landers are also ailing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707130000 +0000" stop="20250707140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baffling Bug</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The suspected theft of industrial secrets leads to an investigation by Drake, spying and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707140000 +0000" stop="20250707150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Reunion  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of Matlock's old law school pals is murdered, he faces the unpleasant task of proving that a former classmate is guilty of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707150000 +0000" stop="20250707160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Dish Best Served Cold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A swindlers homecoming upsets his wife and the families of his victims - especially Etta.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707160000 +0000" stop="20250707170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Comeback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason's scholarship at the music academy is canceled</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707170000 +0000" stop="20250707173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Fool</sub-title>
    <desc>"A scheming woman (Else Hedgepath), who is after the money and wealth of Hannibal Bass, makes a play for Hannibal, but runs into some serious, SERIOUS trouble though when she tangles with *MRS* Bass!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707173000 +0000" stop="20250707180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Love</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gus Blake is killed when Jonas’s store is robbed by one of the Cumber’s brothers. Matt has to figure out which brother it was Nate or Frank."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707180000 +0000" stop="20250707190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sgt. Samuel Bellis, accused of desertion, murder, and selling guns to the Indians. Bellis insists that he's innocent, and Candy believes him-but before he can clear Bellis' name, he must elude the Army patrol that is hot on the fugitive sergeant's heels. In a further plot complication, Bellis is married to an Indian woman named Nanata (Evelyn Davalos), whose own loyalties are greatly in doubt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707190000 +0000" stop="20250707193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind Reader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E40</episode-num>
    <desc>When a wealthy rancher is killed, Mark suggests that they seek the aid of a mind reader to identify the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707193000 +0000" stop="20250707200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707200000 +0000" stop="20250707210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jess Macabbee Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint, scouting ahead of the wagon train, is in search of fresh meat. With prospects none too good he comes upon a hidden paradise, green and lush and offering far more than he expected.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707210000 +0000" stop="20250707220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is thrown from a motorcycle into a cactus patch. A surprise birthday party is planned for Dixie, who breaks her ankle while shopping, and the ER falls apart without her. Gage and DeSoto rescue two workers trapped on the side of a building next to a 1,000-pound sign. A man is trapped in his new sauna. When an old woman refuses to leave her apartment during a gas leak, the building explodes with John inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707220000 +0000" stop="20250707223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. race against the clock to save a soldier from paralysis. B.J.'s harvesting an aorta from a dead soldier doesn't sit well with the soldier's friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707223000 +0000" stop="20250707230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707230000 +0000" stop="20250707233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250707233000 +0000" stop="20250708000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Stars And Stripes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friction arises between B.J. and Winchester when they are asked to write an article for a prestigious medical journal on how they saved a soldier's life with a daring operation. Meanwhile, Hot Lips receives an eventful visit from Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney receives a chain letter, but Andy goads him into throwing it away. Suddenly things begin going wrong for Barney and he's convinced he'll soon be out of a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708003000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Drysdale stops the clan from going back home to deliver a baby, the Clampetts try to help the Brewsters with their baby, while Jethro unsuccessfully tries to open his own version of the Kitty Kat Club. Of course, the Brewsters don't need the help because they are adopting, though after hearing the explanation given, the Clampetts believe they really need help and advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708013000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Bensonhurst Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph gets into an argument at the pool hall and has to fight a big guy at the gym. He arranges it so that he can pretend to knock out a bigger man and make the other one scared. Instead he knocks out a stranger, regaining his confidence to go ahead with the fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lebeau And The Little Old Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau tells the others he is taking messages to a little old lady, when really she is a beautiful lady he has fallen for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708023000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Escape From Prison Camp Without Really Trying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hides 30 prisoners in order to keep the SS busy while the Allies build reinforcements.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man, desperate to win the affection of a beautiful woman, slips her a love potion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708033000 +0000" stop="20250708043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Stand-in Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Two brothers, one a businessman, one a mobster, at separate times have claimed the same young girl as their daughter. Trouble follows when it is revealed that $100,000 due to the girl via a trust fund has been mishandled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708043500 +0000" stop="20250708050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An officer accused of taking a bribe has chosen Sgt. Friday to represent him at his trial board hearing. Witnesses saw the officer accept the money, but he insists it was for the payback of a loan made years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708050500 +0000" stop="20250708053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Greatly Beloved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A newcomer refuses to allow his garden to be used for a church activity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708053500 +0000" stop="20250708060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Martha Mason, Movie Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>After years of being teased by her husband, a woman discovers that she looks very similar to movie star and decided to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708060500 +0000" stop="20250708070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Bang, Bang, You're Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The story of a murder plot from a young girl seems to be the truth when she becomes the victim of a hit-and-run attempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708070500 +0000" stop="20250708080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708080500 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Inside Man, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An aspiring robber is declared a hero for facing his double-crossing partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708093000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sub-station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>On temporary assignment at LAX, Reed and Malloy have to save a stewardess who is taken hostage inside a lounge by a man desperately trying to get the attention of a television producer. Afterward, they go undercover as rental car employees to intercept a large narcotics delivery from Toledo, and then try to identify and apprehend a rape suspect before he's able to escape on a flight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up One L-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While transporting a burglar to the station with Malloy's assistance, Sgt. MacDonald strikes and kills a jaywalker with his cruiser, but unfortunately all of the witnesses on the sidewalk inexplicably claim she was in the crosswalk. With the burglar unmotivated to testify on MacDonald's behalf, Malloy has to take it upon himself to clear his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>To Be A Kid Again</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill spends the day like a kid!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver learns he has to go to the dentist and that's when his friends tell him some horror stories about the drill the dentist is going to use. This prompts Beaver to become downright scared of going to the dentist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708123000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets Adopted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally wins a trophy at school and Beaver accidentally breaks it. This leads Ward to accuse Beaver of being jealous of Wally and that he broke it on purpose. Upset, Beaver decides to get new parents and heads to an adoption agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A club owner is found dead, his partner charged. The men's animosity towards each other makes the case appear to be an open-and-shut ordeal, but Mason is not so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Divorce  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Duncan and Clara Farmington want to have the perfect divorce. What starts out as a simple division of property turns nasty as Leanne represents the wife and Matlock the husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A son (Edward Albert) is opposed to his father's plan to give land to slave descendants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Baptism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous evangelist visits Walton's Mountain to preach and baptize converts</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Sheriff</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ed Gance shoots his partner thinking he’s trying to back shoot him. James Hark and Bill Turloe catch Gance and pretend to bring him in for the reward. Matt and Chester meet them on the prairie and tell them they’ll all ride back to Dodge together."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Unloaded Gun</sub-title>
    <desc>"When 2 outlaws shoot and kill a storekeeper and his young employee, Matt sets out on to the prairie to find the killers. When one of the killers (Red Lime) dies from a gunshot wound from Marshall Dillon's gun, the other outlaw (Joe Lime) vows revenge on Matt Dillon for killing his brother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Emily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe is caught in a love triangle when he meets up with an old girlfriend, Emily, a woman he had planned to marry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708193000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Danny Benedict Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>He says his name is Tom Smith, but a young man Major Adams meets on the trail refuses to join the wagon train and won't say why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Daisy's Pick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny competes for a date with a new nurse. The paramedics rescue an engineer frozen to refrigeration equipment, a man whose hands are glued to his model ship, a comatose child and an injured man trapped in a theater fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yessir, That's Our Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby born to a Korean woman and an American GI is abandoned at the 4077th. Knowing that Amer-Asian children are often mistreated in Korean society, the troop sets about the frustrating task of finding a new home for the infant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708223000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottle Fatigue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrified by the gigantic size of his monthly bar tab at the officer's club, Hawkeye vows to give up booze for a week. Meanwhile, Winchester desperately tries to halt his sister's impending marriage to a man he considers unworthy of the Winchester heritage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heal Thyself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter turns crotchety when he catches the mumps, and his condition is worsened when Winchester gets the same disease and has to be quarantined with him. A temporary replacement surgeon, Newsome, is quickly brought into the 4077th and seems to be a gem in terms of both personality and ability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Old Soldiers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is appointed temporary commander of the 4077th when Colonel Potter rushes off to Tokyo on a mysterious mission. While in command, Hawkeye's main problem is housing a large group of Korean refugees comprised mainly of rambunctious children who need medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250709003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Runs For Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers taking an out-of-town job, and with the election nearing, no one has yet filed to run for Sheriff. Barney throws his hat in the ring, and then Andy's job prospect takes a turn.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709003000 +0000" stop="20250709010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>If I Had A Quarter-million</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney finds $250,000 stolen in a bank heist, he goes undercover to find the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709010000 +0000" stop="20250709013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Jethro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed and Granny decide Jethro needs a job. They send him down to the bank to try to get work. While he is there, he runs into a magician, Marvo the Magnificent. After Marvo learns of his uncle’s many, many millions, he agrees to go home with Jethro. Marvo puts on a show for the Clampetts, and afterwards Jethro decides to become a magician.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709013000 +0000" stop="20250709020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Dial J For Janitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph takes on a job as janitor of his building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709020000 +0000" stop="20250709023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Collector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a fortune in paintings from winding up in the collection of a general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709023000 +0000" stop="20250709030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Ultimate Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send German defenses to the wrong target by "giving" Schultz ESP so that the Allies can bomb an important target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709030000 +0000" stop="20250709033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Passage For Trumpet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Convinced he'll never amount to anything, a trumpet player attempts suicide and then finds himself in a world where no one can hear or see him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709033000 +0000" stop="20250709043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Weary Watchdog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Della asks Mason for $25,000 to help her friend, Janet Brent, who is being blackmailed by an employee of her husband, who has staged compromising photos of her in a motel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709043500 +0000" stop="20250709050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A statue of the child Jesus was stolen from a church. Joe and Bill have to get it back by Christmas. They have less than 48 hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709050500 +0000" stop="20250709053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>West Warlock Time Capsule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A taxidermist uses his art to dispose of his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709053500 +0000" stop="20250709060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Father And Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam needs the money his father will not give him so his girlfriend can marry him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709060500 +0000" stop="20250709070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Deja Vu</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A prediction from a fortune teller hits too close to home as it reveals how Mannix will die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709070500 +0000" stop="20250709080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709080500 +0000" stop="20250709090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Run Away To Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway thinks she committed a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709090000 +0000" stop="20250709093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709093000 +0000" stop="20250709100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709100000 +0000" stop="20250709103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Who Won?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed try to curb a chronic street racing problem by befriending the club leaders and working with a racing promoter to open a legitimate drag strip. Their efforts, along with a highly anticipated race between reed and officer wells, are put in</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709103000 +0000" stop="20250709110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a six-year-old boy who was apparently abducted while walking home from school, and later fear that an elderly witness's wildly inaccurate account may actually pertain to a different crime. They also respond to a barking dog complaint and become suspicious of the dog's owner, mediate a domestic dispute caused by a husband's obsession with watching football, respond to a very creative college prank and pursue armed robbery suspects through a crowded train depot with the aid of a police helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709110000 +0000" stop="20250709120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>1954 Was Red Hot!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill dials the clock back to '54, when rock was rollin' and Atomic Fireballs were the hot new thing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709120000 +0000" stop="20250709123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry become convinced that the Cooper house is haunted by a witch and Beaver and Larry are scared to death. So when June gets Beaver a job walking Mrs. Cooper's dog, Beaver's fear gets the best of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709123000 +0000" stop="20250709130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus Ride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward allow Wally to escort Beaver on a bus headed to a friend's house in Crystal Falls. However, on one of the stops, Beaver inadvertently gets on the wrong bus, a bus that takes him back to Mayfield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709130000 +0000" stop="20250709140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bogus Buccaneers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aspiring actor Tony Polk lands a job on a popular TV program. Part of his job consists of dressing up in a buccaneer costume and delivering gifts to viewers at their homes. Another actor and Tony trade lists and before too long he's up the creek.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709140000 +0000" stop="20250709150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Umpire  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a baseball umpire is murdered, Matlock has a whole team of suspects. It seems that everyone had a beef with the ump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709150000 +0000" stop="20250709160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Even Nice People: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Corrupt developers set their sights on Lana's farm. When she refuses to sell they enlist the services of an arsonist to force her out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709160000 +0000" stop="20250709170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Firestorm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy publishes excerpts from Hitler's writing in his newspaper and the town is upset.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709170000 +0000" stop="20250709173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tall Trapper</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marv Rowley and his wife Tassie stop for the night and camp with a trapper named Ben. Marv comes into Dodge for a doctor saying his wife is sick but when Doc gets there he discovers she was beaten to death. Rowley accuses Ben. When Matt gets to the wagon her body is gone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709173000 +0000" stop="20250709180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Love Thy Neighbor</sub-title>
    <desc>"12 yr old Pete Scooper dies after tearing his leg on barbed wire and getting blood poisoning. Leroy Galloway and his son chased Pete thinking he stole a sack of potatoes. Ben Scooper and his other son Harley come gunning for the Galloways. A bloody feud ensues with no winners."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709180000 +0000" stop="20250709190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Running Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When Candy receives an urgent letter from an old flame requesting his help in the town of Butlerville, he and Joe ride out and find that an old friend is part of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709190000 +0000" stop="20250709193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709193000 +0000" stop="20250709200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709200000 +0000" stop="20250709210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Vittorio Bottecelli Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A king orders his womanizing nephew to San Francisco. He joins the wagon train but causes the Major problems as the husbands are complaining about the man's salacious ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709210000 +0000" stop="20250709220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Quicker Than The Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A pregnant woman accidentally shoots herself. Tired of Chet's antics, the station gets their revenge by playing a practical joke of their own. A construction worker caught under a boat refuses an IV, and a man in an accident communicates through the use of his thumb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709220000 +0000" stop="20250709223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Morale Victory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of their constant complaints about the quality of recreational activities at the 4077th, Colonel Potter appoints Hawkeye and B.J. as the new morale officers. Winchester's morale has already reached a new peak: He's ecstatic about his operation on a wounded soldier, Sheridan, which saved the boy's leg, leaving only "negligible" side effects—less use of his right hand. However, the soldier was a concert pianist before the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709223000 +0000" stop="20250709230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lend A Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Irritated that the 4077th is planning a "surprise" party for him, Hawkeye volunteers to go to the aid of a wounded surgeon at the front. An additional irritant to Hawkeye is the arrival of Dr. Borelli, a wisecracking medical advisor with whom he habitually disagrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709230000 +0000" stop="20250709233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Cruel World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger redecorates his quarters, but the resultant ridicule he receives drives him to new heights in his efforts to get out of the Army. Meanwhile, the doctors are perplexed by the reaction of an Asian-American war hero who tries to kill himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250709233000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th can't escape the Korean War, even in its dreams. Exhausted after two days without sleep, members of the 4077th steal away for catnaps and experience dreams that reveal their fears, yearnings and frustrations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710000000 +0000" stop="20250710003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves pretend to be Hollywood producers in order to rob the Mayberry Bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710003000 +0000" stop="20250710010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy's pretty young cousin, Gloria, comes for a visit after breaking up with her boyfriend. Aunt Bee asks Andy to be nice to her and his attention makes Helen jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710010000 +0000" stop="20250710013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Folks Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>It is spring cleaning time, and Granny is trying to clean the mansion from top to bottom. Jed wants to stop her from doing this and thinks the way to do so is to get Granny out of Beverly Hills. He tells the family to make Granny think she is too tired and too old to work so hard, and Jethro and Elly lay it on a bit too heavy. But it works, and Granny does stop the cleaning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710013000 +0000" stop="20250710020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Here Comes The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's advice to a lodge brother on how to be head of the household has his wife (Alice's sister) in tears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710020000 +0000" stop="20250710023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets a stray chimpanzee to deliver radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710023000 +0000" stop="20250710030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Drums Along The Dusseldorf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan mines a bridge, he learns that a truck of Allied prisoners would be the first to cross it and a new plan is born which includes a flaming arrow from Sioux Indian Carter, aka Little Deer Who Goes Swift And Sure Through Forest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710030000 +0000" stop="20250710033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Bevis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric loser gets a new life from his guardian angel, but there is a price to keeping it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710033000 +0000" stop="20250710043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lurid Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A young widowed high school English teacher in a small town is accused via letter of making passes and more towards some of her male students. But a small town is a small town and it seems that all the key figures are involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710043500 +0000" stop="20250710050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710050500 +0000" stop="20250710053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Indestructible Mr. Weems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An apparently dying man is offered the first plot at a brand-new cemetery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710053500 +0000" stop="20250710060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Little Sleep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Two brothers, one of them a murderer, share a cabin with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710060500 +0000" stop="20250710070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellen Gray hires Mannix because she believes she has been stalked by a Vietnamese man ever since the death of her husband in Hong Kong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710070500 +0000" stop="20250710080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stone Seahorse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A smuggler is attacked by mobsters interested in learning where he has hidden his booty. He escapes in Raymond Durstin's gallery. He turns to Cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710080500 +0000" stop="20250710090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Beat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a TV reporter who fakes stories just to get big ratings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710090000 +0000" stop="20250710093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710093000 +0000" stop="20250710100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710100000 +0000" stop="20250710103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Wednesday Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed becomes preoccupied with the well being of a friend, an electrical engineer by profession, who has just qualified as a reserve police officer and has the bad luck of drawing Officer Wells as his partner. On patrol, Reed and Malloy help out a group of distrusting young adults who are planning to illegally camp in a public park after a rock concert, pull over a young couple in a stolen car and aid wells and the reservist in the foot chase of a heavily armed man who has been coercing innocent strangers into committing bank robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710103000 +0000" stop="20250710110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Dirt Duel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of purse snatching leads Malloy and Reed to investigate a motorcycle gang. Determined to convince the gang he has not prejudged them, Malloy challenges their leader to a motocross duel at Indian Dunes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710110000 +0000" stop="20250710120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Wild About Weather</sub-title>
    <desc>"What's the forecast? Bill will explain with the help of an actual meterologist. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710120000 +0000" stop="20250710123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Gilbert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors in the Gates family and Beaver befriends their son, Gilbert Gates (changed to "Bates" in later episodes). However, Ward, June and Wally quickly realize the obvious when Beaver comes home with all kinds of wild stories that Gilbert has told and that Beaver is convinced are true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710123000 +0000" stop="20250710130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Fame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying after school cleaning the chalkboards, Larry convinces Beaver that Mrs. Rayburn keeps a spanking machine in her office closet. Later, a curious Beaver sneaks a peek but soon finds himself locked in the principal's office. Beaver's fame doesn't go over well with his family, but Beaver has another problem on his hands: he's just gotten his head stuck in an iron fence in the park.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710130000 +0000" stop="20250710140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Midnight Howler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is accused of killing her ex-husband, shot to death during a live radio broadcast while giving an interview. His ex-wife admits to being present during the murder, but swears she did not pull the trigger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710140000 +0000" stop="20250710150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigation: Part 1  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Sam Gerard is a well-known mobster who is about to be exposed. His estranged son, Craig, is arrested for murder but refuses to go to Sam for help. He instead goes to Matlock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710150000 +0000" stop="20250710160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lake Winahatchee: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill discovers the motivation behind a crime syndicates attempt to muscle in on Sparta and the reason they are determined to get Lana's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710160000 +0000" stop="20250710170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen is engaged to Dr David Spencer and they plan the wedding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710170000 +0000" stop="20250710173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Seed</sub-title>
    <desc>"Trudy Trainer sneaks into Matt’s camp and tries to steal some meat. Trudy ran away from home and Matt tells her he’s bringing her back in the morning. Matt decides to bring Trudy to Dodge then the trouble begins."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710173000 +0000" stop="20250710180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kitty Shot</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kitty is shot by a man named Bayloe. Matt goes after Bayloe and catches him but while trying to bring him back to Dodge, they keep getting shot at."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710180000 +0000" stop="20250710190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Unwanted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lorrie Mansfield runs away with ranch hand Rick Miller, much to the ire of her marshal father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710190000 +0000" stop="20250710193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710193000 +0000" stop="20250710200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Town character Brett Conway blackmails Lucas with the knowledge that a young couple Lucas rescued are suffering from yellow fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710200000 +0000" stop="20250710210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The St. Nicholas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas Eve approaches, the wagon train encounters a happy time, the perils that go with hostile indians and a little lost boy who may have already been captured by those same hostiles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710210000 +0000" stop="20250710220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy consider trading cars. A frat pledge chokes during initiation. Dixie takes on hospital management after budget cuts affect her nursing staff. A young patient cures Dr. Early’s hiccups. A basketball player gets stuck in his car. A vehicle teeters on the edge of a drawbridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710220000 +0000" stop="20250710223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Co-respondent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. finds himself attracted to a famous war correspondent, Aggie O'Shea, who has fallen in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710223000 +0000" stop="20250710230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Back Pay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Angered by the way civilian doctors in the States are profiting from the war, Hawkeye presents the Army with a bill for his medical services. Meanwhile, Charles reluctantly demonstrates American medical practices to three Korean medics, and is on the receiving end of their medical expertise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710230000 +0000" stop="20250710233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>April Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A no-nonsense Colonel, who is notorious as a hard-nosed disciplinarian, visits the 4077th during an outbreak of April Fools' Day pranksterism. Colonel Potter tries in vain to halt the mayhem before Colonel Tucker arrives in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250710233000 +0000" stop="20250711000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Of Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to some R&amp;R in Tokyo, a North Korean soldier forces Hawkeye to perform an emergency roadside operation on his buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711000000 +0000" stop="20250711003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Punch In The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>In going through some courthouse paperwork, Barney discovers an open case involving Floyd and Charlie Foley. He tries to close the books on the case, but ends up reopening the arguments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711003000 +0000" stop="20250711010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie and his friends decide to start a newspaper. The early issues don't sell well, so the boys begin eavesdropping and printing local gossip in the paper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711010000 +0000" stop="20250711013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Becomes A Secretary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts learn that some of the bank employees are sick, so the clan decides to go down to the bank and offer Drysdale some help. Drysdale is getting ready for the Bankers’ Convention, and decides to let the Clampetts take over his bank while he is away. Jed acts as the president, and Elly is the secretary. Granny goes over to Jane’s apartment to help her get well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711013000 +0000" stop="20250711020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton buy a T.V. set together and constantly fight over what to watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711020000 +0000" stop="20250711023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Clearance Sale At The Black Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing something he shouldn't have, Schultz is ordered to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711023000 +0000" stop="20250711030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink Vs. The Gonculator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan leads Klink to believe a rabbit trap is a secret electronic device in order for Klink to bring an electronics expert, who wants to defect, to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711030000 +0000" stop="20250711033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The After Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is shocked to learn that the floor of a department store on which she bought a gold thimble doesn't exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711033000 +0000" stop="20250711043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fickle Filly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After her father's death, a young woman finds herself penniless and alone. Then a present from her father—for which he paid $50,000—drops on her lap. However, it turns out to be worthless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711043500 +0000" stop="20250711050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711050500 +0000" stop="20250711053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Dangerous People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Two travelers carefully watch each other, thinking that the other is a psycho escaped from jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711053500 +0000" stop="20250711060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Glass Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A shocking surprise awaits a woman who is about to meet her favorite star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711060500 +0000" stop="20250711070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Round Trip To Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix uncovers a mysterious world that surrounded the late husband of his client, Amanda Hewitt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711070500 +0000" stop="20250711080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer believes there's no other way out than putting the blame of a crime he committed on his sister, a retarded girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711080500 +0000" stop="20250711090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Mercenaries, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. is asked to find a man who hasn't been heard from since he became a mercenary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250711090000 +0000" stop="20250711093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
