<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101130000 +0000" stop="20251101140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bonanza Bunny, Chariots Of Fur, Cat's Paw, Apes Of Wrath, Awful Orphan, The Bashful Buzzard, From Hare To Heir (1960)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs joins an 1896 gold town and duels a French-Canadian version of Yosemite Sam. , Wile E. Coyote and Road Runner do battle yet again. , Sylvester tries to help Junior get a cat's paw badge for hunting birds. , The stork makes a mistake when he delivers Bugs to an expecting gorilla family., Charlie Dog tries to take up home in Porky Pig's house and Porky goes through great lengths to get rid of him. , A bashful buzzard has a hard time keeping up with the rest of his siblings on bringing back food. , Yosemite Sam can keep a million dollar prize if he minds his temper – something Bugs is making very hard. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101140000 +0000" stop="20251101150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Pelican</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>West and Pike receive a note to meet a woman at a Chinese restaurant in San Francisco with a promise of information about the militant Din Chang who has recently stolen a supply of fulminate of mercury from a military arsenal. Unfortunately, the woman is killed before they can talk to her and the only word she utters is "Pelican." To further complicate matters, the only person they manage to capture is supposedly still serving time at Alcatraz. Since it seems that Alcatraz and the woman are the two pieces they have of the puzzle, the two split up to track down Chang before he can use the volatile mercury.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101150000 +0000" stop="20251101160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Beckett Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"A Frenchman arouses strong---and polarized---emotions among the wagon train members: men distrust him, women adore him. He owes a substantial gambling debt and plans to pay it off by convincing a woman to pay it until he is killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101160000 +0000" stop="20251101170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Stallion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A ranch hand who has gotten too old for regular saddle work is determined to catch a wild stallion to prove he is as capable as ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101170000 +0000" stop="20251101180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tobe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tobe Hostader befriends a saloon girl whose ex-boyfriend is near.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101180000 +0000" stop="20251101190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Bucket Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamie falls in love with an unwanted Irish Setter, but he may not be able to save the animal's life because its rightful owner believes that the runt of the litter should always be destroyed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101190000 +0000" stop="20251101193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas hires an ex-con as a ranch hand, the man is the first one under suspicion when a robbery and murder occur in the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101193000 +0000" stop="20251101200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Meeting At Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas helps his former Army captain, now an undercover federal agent, infiltrate a gang of bank robbers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101200000 +0000" stop="20251101210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Long Shakedown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An overbearing Favor leads to many drovers quitting. Five replacements stir trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101210000 +0000" stop="20251101213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Five Books Of Owen Deaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin comes to the aid of a young sheriff from Philadelphia whose attempts to keep law and order in are particularly unsuitable for a cowboy town in Wyoming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101213000 +0000" stop="20251101220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Most Beautiful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John Garth comes to town looking for his darling, Lil, because he feels something terrible has happened. There was a fire in the saloon and he thinks she may have died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101220000 +0000" stop="20251102000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Dumb Clucks, No Census, How High Is Up, Crash Goes The Hash, Knutzy Knights, Pals And Gals, No Feeling</sub-title>
    <desc>"Their father's plan to marry prompts the Stooges to break out of jail to save him from himself and, it turns out, from this intended dangerous posse. , The Stooges get jobs as census takers and wind up in a fancy mansion looking for people to survey.  Moe and Larry are recruited to join a bridge game, while Curly adds Alum to the lemonade.  The resulting concoction is consumed by everyone, resulting in puckered lips and shrunken clothes.  The boys next try to take the census at a football stadium.  They disguise themselves as players and wind up in the middle of the game.  Curly runs off with the ball and all the other players in pursuit. , The Stooges are the 'Minute Menders', three tinkers who live under their car.  The boys decide to drum up some business by punching holes in the unattended lunch boxes of some workmen.  When they're caught in the act, they escape and accidentally get hired as riveters on a new building, working on the 97th floor.  Their ineptitude and lousy workmanship screw up construction of the building and they must parachute off the building to escape the wrath of the boss. , The Stooges are hired as reporters and their first assignment is to get a picture of a visiting prince who is planning to marry a local socialite.  The boys disguise as servants and infiltrate a party being in thrown in the honor of the prince.  The Stooges ruin the party, but save the day as they expose the prince as crook who is planning to rob the house.  Their boss is so grateful for the expose that he gives the boys a bonus and the rich lady decides to marry Curly! , Set in Elizabethan times, the Stooges help their friend Cedric the Blacksmith win the hand of the fair princess Elaine.  The only problem is that Elaine is promised to the Black Prince who is plotting to take over the kingdom.  The Stooges manage to foil the plot and the grateful King allows Cedric to marry Elaine. , The Stooges go out west for Shemp's health.  The boys soon run afoul of a local villain who is forcing pretty Nell to marry him.  The bad guy has Nell's sisters locked up, and its up to the Stooges to rescue them and save the day. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102000000 +0000" stop="20251102023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Abbott And Costello Meet Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Wolfman tries to help foil Dracula's attempts to transfer Lou's brain into the ailing Frankenstein monster."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102023000 +0000" stop="20251102030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Trumps An Ace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker returns to commit what appear to be senseless crimes, until he captures the Maharajah of Nimpah. Later, Batman and Robin are trapped inside a chimney with deadly gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102030000 +0000" stop="20251102040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Balance Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk pits the Enterprise against an invisible spaceship testing the Federation's defenses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102040000 +0000" stop="20251102043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A racketeer gets Kryptonite from a fallen meteor but mistakes Clark's friend Gary Allen for Superman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102043000 +0000" stop="20251102050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Phantom Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Gangsters use a machine to become invisible and execute mysterious robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102050000 +0000" stop="20251102060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien boy is sent to Priplanis to validate his prince status. Will is drawn into a battle to the death unbeknownst to his father. When his real intentions are learned, John substitutes himself in the challenge and the alien ruler substitutes himself for his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102060000 +0000" stop="20251102080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson and Commander Crane are subjects of an experiment in which they are ordered to kill each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102080000 +0000" stop="20251102090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After an air balloon accident, the castaways drift to the other side of the planet where they find a society run by a dictator, oblivious to their existence. Now, Steve must prove life on the other side of the planet or the castaways will die by his hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102090000 +0000" stop="20251102110000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Idol Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1519, Tony and Doug vow to slow down Cortez's conquest of Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102110000 +0000" stop="20251102120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Orphans</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams and Mad Jack take in 2 orphan children, Michele and Eugene. While the kids are grateful at first, soon they become bored by following rules. Secretly, they later wander off to find some fun but it may endanger them both."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102120000 +0000" stop="20251102123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of Eagles</sub-title>
    <desc>"A valley in the mountain country of the western United States is the territory of the Golden Eagle, America’s largest and most powerful bird of prey.  Marlin and Jim locate an eyrie (nest) of this magnificent bird, and build a blind high on a rocky cliff so they can photograph its nesting habits. Humor and drama are interwoven as the young eagle, in his search for food, follows a skunk into his den…and later finds out that a fast dive at a sitting duck results in his first unwanted bath.  His territory is invaded by a forest fire, and the hunting is made easier as the other animals of the valley flee the flames.  He is trapped by man in a scientific experiment, but later released to continue his life in the “Valley of Eagles.”"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102123000 +0000" stop="20251102130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Motion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Oddities of animal motion include mammals that fly, birds that climb with their shoulders, lizards that dive and snakes that travel sideways."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102130000 +0000" stop="20251102133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Sahara South</sub-title>
    <desc>"A horseback safari into the wilds of Rhodesia where Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore the vast grasslands, rivers and forests and observe an amazing variety of rare animals.  In this episode, the forming waters swirl around tons of struggling hippo in a dangerous project to tranquilize and capture one of the largest members of the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102133000 +0000" stop="20251102140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Against The Clock</sub-title>
    <desc>"Man loves speed and this episode answers some of the most pertinent inquiries as to what animals hold the records."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102140000 +0000" stop="20251102143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Monarchs Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the wild kingdom each animal owns a territory…and one animal rules every habitat.  A visit to each domain reveals why each is called a Monarch of the Wild."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102143000 +0000" stop="20251102150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tusker Territory</sub-title>
    <desc>"Of all the behemoths that once roamed the earth, only the elephant is left for us to marvel about.  And marvel we should for here’s an animal that weights 10 tons, yet leaves an imprint only a half-inch deep when walking on soft sand…can eat 200 pounds of hay a day, drink 50 gallons of water at one go, grow to be 13 feet tall at the shoulder, yet can use its trunk so delicately it can pick a flower off the ground without crushing it.  But many questions about this animal remain unanswered.  By literally living with a family of elephants in Bechuanaland, Africa, we observe their fascinating life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102150000 +0000" stop="20251102153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>A Fistful Of Reasons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Cindy comes home in tears after a bully, Buddy Hinton, begins picking on her because of her lisp. One afternoon, Peter encounters Buddy teasing Cindy and defends her, but gets a black eye in the process. Mike and Carol try to reason with Buddy's parents but get nowhere, and Peter goes into training so he can defend himself against Buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102153000 +0000" stop="20251102160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Not-so-ugly Duckling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan has been smitten with Clark Tyson and they've been studying together. However, when Marcia casually, steps in the family room, Clark is instantly smitten. Jan becomes insecure about her looks and seeks out ways to get rid of her freckles. However, later, not wanting people to feel sorry for her, Jan makes up an imaginary boyfriend, George Glass.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102160000 +0000" stop="20251102163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Fonzie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie is invited to a socialite dinner party, not knowing that the people who have invited him hope he will make a fool of himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102163000 +0000" stop="20251102170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Day Blind Dates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley unwittingly double-date with two criminals intent on robbing the bank next to the Pizza Bowl, the girls find themselves being held as hostages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102170000 +0000" stop="20251102173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Forecloses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Grumpy businessman Ben Weaver insists that Andy foreclose on a down-on-his-luck neighbor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102173000 +0000" stop="20251102180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ricky's Life Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Ricky is featured in Life Magazine, Lucy is more desperate than ever for a showbiz career. To prevent it, Ricky and Fred concoct an impossible dance routine for her. She gets back at them by upstaging Ricky during his own big number.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102180000 +0000" stop="20251102183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Poncho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver makes a trade with Larry Mondello, a glass doorknob for a chihuahua. Larry had found the dog in his garbage can, so when Beaver brings it home, Ward immediately breaks the news that he's going to place an ad in the lost-and-found and that Beaver probably won't be able to keep the dog. Despite this, Beaver quickly begins to grow close to the little dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102183000 +0000" stop="20251102190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The State Vs. Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward helps Beaver and Wally build a miniature race car powered by the lawn mower motor, and Ward makes the boys promise not to use it without his supervision. Later, Larry talks Beaver into taking it for a spin, resulting in the boys being pulled over by a traffic officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102190000 +0000" stop="20251102193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Buys The Freeway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A confidence man tries to sell Jed the Hollywood Bowl, Griffith Park and the Hollywood Freeway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102193000 +0000" stop="20251102200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Becomes A Banker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is made a bank vice president so he can compete in an interbank skeet shoot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102200000 +0000" stop="20251102203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>"v" For Vitamins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Professor determines that the lack of vitamin C on the island threatens the health of the castaways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102203000 +0000" stop="20251102210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs.???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A radio bulletin states that the minister who married the Howell's was a fraud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102210000 +0000" stop="20251102213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>National Mama  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama's dreams predict winning horses at the races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102213000 +0000" stop="20251102220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Soup To Nuts  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint judges a chili cook-off between Mama, Naomi and Iola.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102220000 +0000" stop="20251102230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>His Girls Friday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man offers the crew $10,000 to find him a wife; a girl must confront her former love; a man tries to dump his assistant for a blonde.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102230000 +0000" stop="20251102233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Sam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is suspicious of Mayberry's mysterious new farmer (William Schallert).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251102233000 +0000" stop="20251103000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Robots- James Zespy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Collector Zespy oddball collection of the quirkiest robots ever assembled range in size from the tiny, Telecoma action figures from Japan that transform into licensed food products, to the life-sized, a fully functional animatronic canine rock band. Lisa's brought along pop-culture appraiser and auctioneer Mike Boerschinger to put a value on Zespy's collection, after which Mike will try to tempt him into a trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103000000 +0000" stop="20251103003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rainbow Bridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>As Hawkeye and Trapper are planning to leave for Tokyo, an unusual offer to swap POW patients between the Chinese and the 4077th comes in. Henry, after much debate, agrees to send Hawkeye, Trapper, Frank, Radar and Klinger into enemy territory. Frank almost botches the swap when he brings a squirt gun to the exchange. Fortunately, the Chinese Dr. Lin Tam has a sense of humor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103003000 +0000" stop="20251103010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officer Of The Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Henry is away in Seoul, Burns and Houlihan are in charge, and Hawkeye is the officer of the day. His refusal to release a wounded Korean soldier, wanted by US Intelligence, leads to a confrontation with Colonel Flagg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103010000 +0000" stop="20251103013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Unemployment Story (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's self-esteem takes a beating when he loses his job on the loading dock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103013000 +0000" stop="20251103020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Unemployment Story (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A college grad threatens to commit suicide after he loses a jaintor's job to Archie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103020000 +0000" stop="20251103023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Operation (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's trip to the hospital is an ethnic nightmare. He's admitted by a Puerto Rican receptionist, treated by a Jewish physician, and is forced to accept a blood transfusion from a black doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103023000 +0000" stop="20251103030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Operation (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie recuperates in record time after he's called back to work-with a raise and a promotion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103030000 +0000" stop="20251103033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Civil War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray joins a Civil War re-enactment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103033000 +0000" stop="20251103040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Mia Famiglia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray's thrilled to finally meet a relative whom the whole family likes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103040000 +0000" stop="20251103043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Forty-four Tickets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob has two days to find 44 tickets to "The Alan Brady Show" promised to the PTA.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103043000 +0000" stop="20251103050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Empress Carlotta's Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob surprises Laura with a necklace that she secretly hates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103050000 +0000" stop="20251103053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Oh My Aching Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph hurts his back at a bowling tournament the night before his physical exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103053000 +0000" stop="20251103060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Queen Of The Nile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Columnist Jordan Herrick is startled to learn that a famous movie actress hasn't aged in years. Intrigued, he investigates—and soon learns a terrifying secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103060000 +0000" stop="20251103063000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Matched Pearl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A successful jewelry shop owner sells a rare black pearl to a wealthy client.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103063000 +0000" stop="20251103070000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Most Likely To Succeed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old college friends meet again after a long separation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103070000 +0000" stop="20251103080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Mindbend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Alex Pierson, a rising Syndicate member, has recruited Dr. Burke, a psychopathic behavioral psychologist who has developed a way to program men into killers. Pierson lures in underworld criminals with an offer of plastic surgery and turns them over to Burke.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103080000 +0000" stop="20251103090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Conspiracy Of Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a steward at a remote desert resort, Kimble is unaware that the area is a top-secret government test site for chemical weapons. Kimble tries to leave, but gets mistaken for a spy by Major Beck, the head of the project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103090000 +0000" stop="20251103100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Death Certificate</sub-title>
    <desc>"When private investigator Harry Orwell is hired to investigate medical malpractice, he finds himself involved in organized crime and murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103100000 +0000" stop="20251103103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103103000 +0000" stop="20251103110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103110000 +0000" stop="20251103113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess And The Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed report to a disturbance at a night club caused by a young folk singer whose career has been derailed by drug addiction and contends that she is being threatened with death by the manager who is a member of a large drug ring. Reed agrees to</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103113000 +0000" stop="20251103120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Tip</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bandits using tear gas and a unique escape route rob an armored truck at a savings and loan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103120000 +0000" stop="20251103130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Game Show Time!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill &amp; Toony explore the history of game shows with a special guest!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103130000 +0000" stop="20251103133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Broken Window</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing baseball in the street with Wally, Chester and Tooey, Eddie hits a baseball through the Cleaver's window resulting in Ward forbidding the boys to play baseball so close to the house. However, later, Beaver talks Wally into pitching one, and this results in a broken car window.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103133000 +0000" stop="20251103140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Train Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After a week-long visit with their Aunt Martha, Wally and Beaver prepare to head home to Mayfield on a train. After talking Martha into letting them buy their own tickets, they discover they're short the money after spending it on junk food and find themselves wondering how they are going to get home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103140000 +0000" stop="20251103150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dubious Bridegroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason returns to his office late one night and finds an attractive woman climbing into his balcony window. She claims to be Virginia Colfax, the secretary of Ed Garvin, who has an office next door to Mason's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103150000 +0000" stop="20251103160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Foursome  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to defend millionaire Ellis Blake when he's accused of murdering his daughter's fiancé, Jeffrey Holden, a blackmailing golf caddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103160000 +0000" stop="20251103170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer has personal reasons for trying to gain early release for a man who was sent to prison after an accident he caused while drinking and driving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103170000 +0000" stop="20251103180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Unthinkable</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier in Jason's company is Jewish. He tells the Waltons what is happening to Jews by the Nazis</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103180000 +0000" stop="20251103190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Come</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Elmo Sippy may seem polite on the outside, but he's a murderer on the inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103190000 +0000" stop="20251103200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>First Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamie falls in love with the abused wife of an unpopular Virginia City schoolmaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103200000 +0000" stop="20251103203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Nora</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas finds himself involved in murder when he gallantly steps to the aid of a beautiful woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103203000 +0000" stop="20251103210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hangman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict is blamed for a brutal crime despite his claims of rehabilitation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103210000 +0000" stop="20251103220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Nancy Lee Davis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>"Flint stops in a saloon with Bill and Charlie where he learns the whereabouts of a man he's been hunting for years---to kill. Bill has to restrain Flint who lapses into recalling his fiancé Nancy Lee Davis and his search for her killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103220000 +0000" stop="20251103230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Crash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy bring in a football player who was tackled too hard. A burglar has a heart attack. John wants Roy to apologize for calling him "some kind of nut." Dr. Early treats a hypochondriac. A babysitter brings in a child who has swallowed some pills. Roy and John rescue the occupants of a light plane that crashed in a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103230000 +0000" stop="20251103233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Iron Guts Kelly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>General 'Iron Guts' Kelly arrives for an inspection, and ends up dying in Margaret's tent. Hawkeye and Trapper help the General's aide smuggle him out of camp. The next day he is reported killed at the front, as that is where he would have wanted to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251103233000 +0000" stop="20251104000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>O.r.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The O.R. is filled with more wounded than the unit can handle. Hawkeye does heart massage on a soldier, which saves his life, but he dies four hours later. Sidney Freedman drops in during the deluge, and is dragged into the fray by Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104000000 +0000" stop="20251104003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Springtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When spring arrives, Klinger gets word from home that his sweetheart back in Toledo wants to marry him. Henry arranges for Father Mulcahy to do this over short wave radio. Radar falls in love with a nurse, while a grateful patient won't leave Hawkeye alone, and even threatens Major Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104003000 +0000" stop="20251104010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Check-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper gets an ulcer and a ticket home. Unfortunately, his going-away party is spoiled by a new Army regulation, which forces him to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104010000 +0000" stop="20251104013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Gets His Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict vows revenge on the man who sent him back to prison: none other than Deputy Barney Fife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104013000 +0000" stop="20251104020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry guitarist Jim Lindsey (James Best), a success as a solo artist, returns to a hero's welcome. However, Andy suspects trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104020000 +0000" stop="20251104023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Marie's Meatballs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gets upset when Raymond chooses his mother's cooking over hers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104023000 +0000" stop="20251104030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Checkbook, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond takes over the checkbook to prove to Debra how "easy it can be" to balance it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104030000 +0000" stop="20251104033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Collector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a fortune in paintings from winding up in the collection of a general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104033000 +0000" stop="20251104040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Ultimate Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send German defenses to the wrong target by "giving" Schultz ESP so that the Allies can bomb an important target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104040000 +0000" stop="20251104043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Dick Martin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Steve Lawrence and Dick Martin. Originally aired on 12/29/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104043000 +0000" stop="20251104053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cheating Chancellor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason returns to his college alma mater to receive an award, but there's no rest for the weary when he's called upon to defend Van Fowler for the murder of a professor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104053500 +0000" stop="20251104060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What's In The Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A cheating husband sees his secret revealed and its horrible consequences on his just-repaired TV set.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104060500 +0000" stop="20251104063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Four</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband searches desperately for his wife in a neighborhood where numerous murders have been committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104063500 +0000" stop="20251104070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Golden Opportunity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to leave his wife takes a turn he didn't foresee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104070500 +0000" stop="20251104080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Ragged Edge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix goes undercover as a heroin addict to discover who's trying to kill an old friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104080500 +0000" stop="20251104090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A private detective investigates the murder of his ex-girlfriend's husband and gets entangled in small-town corruption."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104090500 +0000" stop="20251104100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Leap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A man attempting suicide is really a diversion for a jewelry heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104100000 +0000" stop="20251104103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104103000 +0000" stop="20251104110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104110000 +0000" stop="20251104113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Parole Violator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy is told that the best player on the recreational league basketball team he coaches has begun using narcotics again, which he flatly denies despite evidence to the contrary. He and Reed also search for a hit-and-run driver who struck a child, and pull over a driver with a seemingly disrespectful and wanted passenger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104113000 +0000" stop="20251104120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Adoption</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate the ransacking of a college football locker room and uncover a controversial performance enhancing drug program. They also investigate suspicious parents who backtrack after their maid reports their baby as missing, apprehend a reported prowler who is then suspiciously let into the home by the female accuser and engage in a bullet-riddled high speed chase through a residential area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104120000 +0000" stop="20251104130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Roaring Twenties</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony revisit the roaring 20s with a special performance by the Windy City Ramblers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104130000 +0000" stop="20251104133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An 8th grade dance has Wally being pressured into attending with a girl, instead of going stag with Eddie. However, Mary Ellen Rogers becomes determined to have Wally take her and goes through Beaver to get to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104133000 +0000" stop="20251104140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Next Door Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to be liked by Wally's friends, Beaver makes up a wild story about the vacant lot next to his house being an Indian battle ground. After making a bet with Eddie, Beaver has Wally help him plant artifacts in the lot. However, that is forgotten when the kids make a discovery that they believe will make them rich.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104140000 +0000" stop="20251104150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lame Canary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ruth Prescott wants to divorce Walter Prescott so she can be with her true love, Jimmy MacLaine. After a brush with death, Ruth becomes convinced that Walter is trying to kill her, but then Walter turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104150000 +0000" stop="20251104160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104160000 +0000" stop="20251104170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Problem Too Personal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet and Eugene are devastated after Gene's father is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104170000 +0000" stop="20251104180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>There is a new teacher at school who is fun and modern.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104180000 +0000" stop="20251104190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>My Sister's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A grief-stricken widower gets a job as a hired hand for two sisters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104190000 +0000" stop="20251104200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Candy is framed for robbery and manslaughter, his fate rests in the hands of a confident yet inexperienced attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104200000 +0000" stop="20251104203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Trail Of Hate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is out for vengeance when Mark is used as a pawn in a bank robbery scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104203000 +0000" stop="20251104210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Woman From Hog Ridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas shoots a horse thief who turns out to be a member of the Boyle clan, and now Ma Boyle is after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104210000 +0000" stop="20251104220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Frank Carter Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke's resemblance to gambler Jason Carter makes him the target for a murderer's bullet when he visits Jason Carter's hometown looking for supplies. Jason has been missing for five years and only one man knows the truth about him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104220000 +0000" stop="20251104230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Decision (a.k.a. Problem)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John rescue a man whose engine has fallen on him during his car repair work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104230000 +0000" stop="20251104233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life With Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail from home worries Henry that Lorraine may be seeing other men. Father Mulcahy presides over a Jewish circumcision ceremony for the Korean-born son of a US GI.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251104233000 +0000" stop="20251105000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Alcoholics Unanimous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry's departure to Tokyo leaves Major Burns in charge of the 4077th. He declares total prohibition of alcohol, which leads to a near riot in the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105000000 +0000" stop="20251105003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>There Is Nothing Like A Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses are evacuated when the threat of an enemy parachute drop arises. Hawkeye and Trapper try to enliven everyone's spirits while they are gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105003000 +0000" stop="20251105010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Ribs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sick and tired of having liver and fish for an 11-day stretch, Hawkeye, driven near to insanity, starts a riot in the mess tent. He and Trapper then orders spare ribs and sauce from his favorite barbecue joint—in Chicago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105010000 +0000" stop="20251105013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bringing Up Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, believing that the jailhouse environment is adversely affecting Opie, forbids the lad to spend time at work with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105013000 +0000" stop="20251105020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Bully</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolboy bully makes life miserable for seven-year-old Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105020000 +0000" stop="20251105023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ride-along, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond gains a new respect for his brother, Robert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105023000 +0000" stop="20251105030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Family Bed, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ally, claiming that there are monsters in her room, insists on sleeping in her parent's bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105030000 +0000" stop="20251105033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets a stray chimpanzee to deliver radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105033000 +0000" stop="20251105040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Drums Along The Dusseldorf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan mines a bridge, he learns that a truck of Allied prisoners would be the first to cross it and a new plan is born which includes a flaming arrow from Sioux Indian Carter, aka Little Deer Who Goes Swift And Sure Through Forest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105040000 +0000" stop="20251105043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Eydie Gorme (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Eydie Gorme. Originally aired on 03/01/72."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105043000 +0000" stop="20251105053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impetuous Imp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason helps a young woman who believes her aunt was murdered by her husband, but he soon turns up dead, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105053500 +0000" stop="20251105060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Am The Night - Color Me Black</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>The sun won't rise on a small town where an execution is scheduled to occur.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105060500 +0000" stop="20251105063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Twelve Hour Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A meek clerk plots with his companions to rob the investment firm for which he works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105063500 +0000" stop="20251105070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Children Of Alda Nuova</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A man disappears while visiting little-known tourist attractions in Italy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105070500 +0000" stop="20251105080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait In Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix looks into why someone may be trying to kill one half of a successful singing duo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105080500 +0000" stop="20251105090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A private detective investigates the murder of his ex-girlfriend's husband and gets entangled in small-town corruption."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105090500 +0000" stop="20251105100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Echoes Of A Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The owner of a mountain lodge asks Barnaby to prove he didn't kill his wife, even though his guests swear they saw him do it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105100000 +0000" stop="20251105103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Dognappers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon set out to muzzle thieves who steal dogs and then collect hefty rewards from the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105103000 +0000" stop="20251105110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Persons - The Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Working with the slimmest of leads, police attempt to identify a woman's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105110000 +0000" stop="20251105113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Mary Hong Loves Tommy Chen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An undercover cop is left in a coma after being shot while investigating a potential attack by a youth gang on an elders' association in chinatown, but his girlfriend refuses to disclose time critical information to malloy and reed on orders from her powe</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105113000 +0000" stop="20251105120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sub-station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>On temporary assignment at LAX, Reed and Malloy have to save a stewardess who is taken hostage inside a lounge by a man desperately trying to get the attention of a television producer. Afterward, they go undercover as rental car employees to intercept a large narcotics delivery from Toledo, and then try to identify and apprehend a rape suspect before he's able to escape on a flight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105120000 +0000" stop="20251105130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Cautious Claymation</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony make their own claymation film and examine the history of stop-motion animation."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105130000 +0000" stop="20251105133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tenting Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a weekend spent at the movies goes awry for Ward, he decides the boys should spend their weekends outside and plans a camping trip. However, when Ward's called into work, Wally and Beaver decide to camp out in the backyard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105133000 +0000" stop="20251105140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Music Lesson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally makes the baseball team and Ward openly shows how proud he is of him, leaving Beaver feeling inferior. Trying to impress his parents, Beaver tries out for the band and begins practicing the clarinet. However, Beaver soon finds himself with more problems when he's let go from the band.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105140000 +0000" stop="20251105150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spurious Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Chapman returns home early from a business trip to find that his wife, Marie, wants a divorce. Chapman is shocked at this turn of events because he thought his wife had recently been strangled to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105150000 +0000" stop="20251105160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105160000 +0000" stop="20251105170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Final Arrangement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Sweet is heartbroken when an elderly woman who befriended him is murdered in her bookstore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105170000 +0000" stop="20251105180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Prodigals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeffrey and Josh steal from Ike's store and Josh gets caught.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105180000 +0000" stop="20251105190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Quint's Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Quint guides a family on a hazardous trail to Oregon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105190000 +0000" stop="20251105200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Marriage Of Theodora Duffy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Griff poses as Theodora Duffy, the "wife" of a government agent in order to nab a group of war criminals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105200000 +0000" stop="20251105203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Seven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Seven condemned murderers escape and take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105203000 +0000" stop="20251105210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pitchman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark finds gold on their property, a fast-talking salesman who tried to sell Lucas a new lightning rod offers instead to buy the ranch's mineral rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105210000 +0000" stop="20251105220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Turnbull Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bill and Charlie looking for horses help out an old friend John Turnbull (an Ute lawyer) defend his reservation against local land sharks who look to initiate a range war so the army will push the local residents off their land."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105220000 +0000" stop="20251105230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The station adopts a stray dog, which they name Boot. The firemen rescue a boy from a hole; he turns out to be an abused child. Roy and John rescue another boy whose head is stuck in a basement window. Dr. Early extracts a child's arm from a steering wheel. At a brush fire, Boot helps locate an injured hiker, and then leaves with a hook and ladder truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105230000 +0000" stop="20251105233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Full Rich Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye records a letter to his dad, detailing the exploits of a mad Turkish soldier who calls Hawkeye a "damn good Joe," the unfortunate loss of the corpse of a Luxembourg soldier (who turns out not to be dead), Lt. Henri-Batiste LeClerc and a gun-happy officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251105233000 +0000" stop="20251106000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Dogs And Servicemen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A local dog bites Radar, and the camp conducts a search to find the pooch so that Radar doesn't have to undergo a series of painful rabies vaccinations. Hawkeye defies Frank, to take care of a GI who's suffering from a case of hysterical paralysis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106000000 +0000" stop="20251106003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Charles Lamb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A Greek Colonel thanks the 4077th by giving them food and drink for an Easter celebration. But the feast is foiled when softhearted Radar saves the main course from the spit—a lamb, which Radar tricks Henry into giving a medical discharge and sends home to Ottumwa, Iowa. Thus, Hawkeye and Trapper invent the famed Spam Lamb!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106003000 +0000" stop="20251106010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp is under fire and is swamped with wounded. They are being attacked by their own artillery in a frightening "friendly fire" incident. After Trapper and Margaret get trapped in the supply tent together, Frank's jealousy of Trapper drives him to propose to Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106010000 +0000" stop="20251106013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Replacement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy is grooming a new man to replace him as deputy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106013000 +0000" stop="20251106020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106020000 +0000" stop="20251106023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Good Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra discovers that Marie, likes Robert's girlfriend, Amy, better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106023000 +0000" stop="20251106030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>T-ball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra brings an "unapproved snack" to Ally's T-ball game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106030000 +0000" stop="20251106033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Clearance Sale At The Black Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing something he shouldn't have, Schultz is ordered to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106033000 +0000" stop="20251106040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink Vs. The Gonculator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan leads Klink to believe a rabbit trap is a secret electronic device in order for Klink to bring an electronics expert, who wants to defect, to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106040000 +0000" stop="20251106043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Eydie Gorme (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Eydie Gorme. Originally aired on 03/01/72."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106043000 +0000" stop="20251106053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Carefree Coronary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Safeline Insurance Company notices an increase in heart attacks among their policy holders. The company suspects fraud and hires Mason and Paul to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106053500 +0000" stop="20251106060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Caesar And Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist's dummy goads him into committing burglaries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106060500 +0000" stop="20251106063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>First Class Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man makes a deal with a friend to keep from having to pay his wife alimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106063500 +0000" stop="20251106070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A man decides to demonstrate to his new girlfriend how he gets his kicks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106070500 +0000" stop="20251106080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Game Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When the daughter of one of Mannix's friends is kidnapped, the captors demand that the man lose a large sum of money in a card game as her ransom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106080500 +0000" stop="20251106090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Salinas Jackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon is called in to investigate a robbery and murder of six people at a rodeo. The police had come up with nothing after six weeks except for the knowledge that there was a film taken of the rodeo at the day of the crime. Cannon believes that there is a possibility that the rodeo clowns may have played a part in the crime and must now learn where the clown suit came from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106090500 +0000" stop="20251106100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Viper, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby suspects that a desert rancher's death was no accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106100000 +0000" stop="20251106103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - The Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Other people's credit cards are found in the possession of a forest ranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106103000 +0000" stop="20251106110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday arrests a member of his class for possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106110000 +0000" stop="20251106113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up One L-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While transporting a burglar to the station with Malloy's assistance, Sgt. MacDonald strikes and kills a jaywalker with his cruiser, but unfortunately all of the witnesses on the sidewalk inexplicably claim she was in the crosswalk. With the burglar unmotivated to testify on MacDonald's behalf, Malloy has to take it upon himself to clear his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106113000 +0000" stop="20251106120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Who Won?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed try to curb a chronic street racing problem by befriending the club leaders and working with a racing promoter to open a legitimate drag strip. Their efforts, along with a highly anticipated race between reed and officer wells, are put in</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106120000 +0000" stop="20251106130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Elmer Fudd, Wabbit Hunter</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106130000 +0000" stop="20251106133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>June has Wally stay home from school when he comes down with a sore throat and suddenly Wally is immersed in attention from his parents, friends and doctor. Jealous and feeling left out, Beaver fakes illness, seeking that same attention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106133000 +0000" stop="20251106140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Old Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver are helping Ward clean out the garage when they run across Beaver's old teddy bear, Billy. Beaver reluctantly throws him away after Ward and Wally tell him he's too old for dolls. However, Beaver changes his mind but he's too late: the garbage truck came, which leads Beaver to take drastic measures to get him back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106140000 +0000" stop="20251106150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Watery Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lorna Thomas is a has-been actress who once gave up her baby for adoption and lived to regret it. George Clark discovers that his wife might be Lorna's long-lost daughter and begins to see dollar signs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106150000 +0000" stop="20251106160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Outcast: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock retires from law after bungling up a case. He heads out of town to do some fishing, but after a hitchhiker he encounters dies mysteriously, Matlock decides to stick around and investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106160000 +0000" stop="20251106170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Family Matters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's dream of a better relationship with his Aunt Ruda and her son is shattered when his cousin takes part in a string of burglaries that result in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106170000 +0000" stop="20251106180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Remembrance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Zadok Walton visits the mountain. He seems eccentric, but turns out he is held in esteem by Boatwright University for his work</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106180000 +0000" stop="20251106190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Carter Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After a man gets beaten up for trying to steal a horse, he plots his revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106190000 +0000" stop="20251106200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A game of cat and mouse ensues when outlaw Bill Tanner steals the goods Joe is transporting on his wagon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106200000 +0000" stop="20251106203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Micah is badly injured by an escaping prisoner, Lucas tracks the prisoner back to his home town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106203000 +0000" stop="20251106210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Baranca</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an outlaw leader lures Marshal Torrance out of town, Lucas is the only one who can stop him from lynching a local man who killed one of the members of his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106210000 +0000" stop="20251106220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hiram Winthrop Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke quits the wagon train to take up a steady position as Deputy Indian Agent at San Marcos on an Apache reservation under Hiram Winthrope. Hiram is an Easterner with ideas of teaching the nomadic Apache to become farmers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106220000 +0000" stop="20251106230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A photo shoot at the station gets John excited. A country doctor helps Roy and John when they can't reach Rampart on a call. The paramedics rescue a man drowning in a swimming pool and two stuntmen trapped on a waterfall at a movie studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106230000 +0000" stop="20251106233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bulletin Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Camp activities include Henry's nervous delivery of a sex lecture, with Hawkeye and Trapper heckling, a Shirley Temple movie and a cookout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251106233000 +0000" stop="20251107000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Consultant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Borelli visits the 4077th to demonstrate his artery transplant technique. Unfortunately, being so close to the front at the 4077th causes Borelli's drinking problem to interfere at the worst time—when a patient needs the transplant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107000000 +0000" stop="20251107003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>House Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye hits Major Burns and Houlihan is a witness. Despite Hawkeye and Trapper's claims that it wasn't intentional, Frank makes allegations against Hawkeye, and he is put in house arrest facing court martial. A female colonel is sent to inspect the nurses. When she cries "Rape!" when Burns visits her tent, Houlihan recants her story, and Burns, not Hawkeye, ends up under house arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107003000 +0000" stop="20251107010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Aid Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye, Houlihan and Klinger go to an aid station at the front. Working closely together under heavy fire and unsanitary medical conditions, the three return to camp with new found respect for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107010000 +0000" stop="20251107013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Bankrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Myers is about to get evicted by the city council when he discovers an old bond that the city of Mayberry issued 100 years ago. Mayberry now owes him $350,000 and can't pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107013000 +0000" stop="20251107020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney On The Rebound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After a tiff with Thelma Lou, Barney is victimized by a scheming young couple.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107020000 +0000" stop="20251107023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Traffic School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's students complain that his class causes severe insomnia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107023000 +0000" stop="20251107030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Six Feet Under</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra tries to teach Raymond how to have a "normal" mid-life crisis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107030000 +0000" stop="20251107033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happiness Is A Warm Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Klink finds Sergeant Schultz drunk he gets a tough new replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107033000 +0000" stop="20251107040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Trucking Service... We Deliver The Factory To You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Crittendon shows up again and messes up Hogan's plans to destroy a ball bearing plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107040000 +0000" stop="20251107043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 03/29/72."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107043000 +0000" stop="20251107053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hasty Honeymooner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas Tolliver arrives in California from Oklahoma to meet the woman he was matched up with by a computer dating service. The woman, Miliicent Barton, is supposedly a rich widow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107053500 +0000" stop="20251107060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jeopardy Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A former KGB officer trying to defect finds himself trapped in a room with a bomb—and three hours before it detonates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107060500 +0000" stop="20251107063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Where Beauty Lies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman strives to keep her brother from running her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107063500 +0000" stop="20251107070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Got To Have Luck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man holds a woman hostage in her farmhouse while he plans his escape from the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107070500 +0000" stop="20251107080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Fine Day For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>One might think that after waking from a year-long coma, the worst would be in the past. But that is not true for Mannix's client, injured in a hit-and-run accident and now the target of killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107080500 +0000" stop="20251107090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Chain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The death of a bank manager's mistress leads Cannon into a case of murder and betrayal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107090500 +0000" stop="20251107100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Trial Run For Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A race-car driver murders his brother-in-law, then stages a smashup to cover it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107100000 +0000" stop="20251107103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>I.a.d. - The Receipt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a complaint that two veteran officers stole funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107103000 +0000" stop="20251107110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - The Harassing Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107110000 +0000" stop="20251107113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a six-year-old boy who was apparently abducted while walking home from school, and later fear that an elderly witness's wildly inaccurate account may actually pertain to a different crime. They also respond to a barking dog complaint and become suspicious of the dog's owner, mediate a domestic dispute caused by a husband's obsession with watching football, respond to a very creative college prank and pursue armed robbery suspects through a crowded train depot with the aid of a police helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107113000 +0000" stop="20251107120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Wednesday Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed becomes preoccupied with the well being of a friend, an electrical engineer by profession, who has just qualified as a reserve police officer and has the bad luck of drawing Officer Wells as his partner. On patrol, Reed and Malloy help out a group of distrusting young adults who are planning to illegally camp in a public park after a rock concert, pull over a young couple in a stolen car and aid wells and the reservist in the foot chase of a heavily armed man who has been coercing innocent strangers into committing bank robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107120000 +0000" stop="20251107130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Sooner State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony journey through the state of Oklahoma."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107130000 +0000" stop="20251107133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally jumps at the chance to paint a couple of garbage cans for Ward, who offers 50 cents a piece. However, when Eddie tells Wally that his father was charged $3.00 to have his painted, he becomes disinterested in the job and Beaver takes it over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107133000 +0000" stop="20251107140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bad Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An incident at the park leads to Beaver ripping the pants on his gray flannel suit. When he's questioned by Ward and June he makes up a wild story that his parents quickly see through. Lectured in telling the truth, Beaver does just that when the pants of his other suit are ripped but Ward and June don't believe him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107140000 +0000" stop="20251107150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Garrulous Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry Benton is a hard-luck guy. He gets in an argument in a poker game and knocks Mike Granger out cold. Then he is informed him that Granger is dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107150000 +0000" stop="20251107160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Outcast: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock retires from law after bungling up a case. He heads out of town to do some fishing, but after a hitchhiker he encounters dies mysteriously, Matlock decides to stick around and investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107160000 +0000" stop="20251107170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie receives word that a former Spartan is wanted for the murder of a socialite in Houston. But a ruthless bounty hunter, sent by the victim's jealous husband is already in Sparta and sees the man's sister as a means to locate his quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107170000 +0000" stop="20251107180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspiration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mamie Balwin has a cataract, but does not want an operation</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107180000 +0000" stop="20251107190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Ex-con</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict comes to Dodge with the intention of shooting Matt dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107190000 +0000" stop="20251107200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Rose For Lotta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights have to protect their land from ruthless mine owners who want the Ponderosa for its timber. They enlist the aid of actress Lotta Crabtree to carry out their plans, but she soon learns that she's getting into more than she bargained for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107200000 +0000" stop="20251107203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Martinet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A former army captain comes to North Fork to kill the man who shot down his son in a gunfight—Lucas McCain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107203000 +0000" stop="20251107210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Milly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A new store owner upsets the town by demanding that all credit accounts be paid off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107210000 +0000" stop="20251107220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Heather Mahoney Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>"Chris Hale has dinner with a society matron whose carriage team he had stopped after being spooked. A rival for the woman's attention is Chris' first problem while the crew's attempt to sabotage their relationship is the second one."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107220000 +0000" stop="20251107230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Virus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A sick lady with a monkey provides the key to a mysterious, highly contagious and deadly virus that strikes both Dr. Brackett and John. Meanwhile, the firemen rescue a boy from a treehouse and a man from a scaffold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107230000 +0000" stop="20251107233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love And Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper prevent a GI from marrying a call girl who has TB, while trying to help a Korean soldier join his pregnant wife. Radar, of course, provides his usual invaluable help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251107233000 +0000" stop="20251108000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108000000 +0000" stop="20251108003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108003000 +0000" stop="20251108010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108010000 +0000" stop="20251108013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108013000 +0000" stop="20251108020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Crime-free Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are honored for achieving the lowest crime-rate in the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108020000 +0000" stop="20251108023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond and Debra take a walk back in time -- to the very beginning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108023000 +0000" stop="20251108030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray fears that Debra is more interested in the wedding than in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108030000 +0000" stop="20251108033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>To The Gestapo With Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets three beautiful girls to pry secrets out of the guys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108033000 +0000" stop="20251108040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man's Best Friend Is Not His Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog buries a bone containing film from Carter's camera that has images of a new German tank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108040000 +0000" stop="20251108043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 03/29/72."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108043000 +0000" stop="20251108053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The 12th Wildcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Burt Payne coaches and owns 10% of a professional football team. His rich wife, Ellen, owns the remainder. Knowing that he's washed up and needing some quick cash, Burt tries to sell his share of the team to a group of investors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108053500 +0000" stop="20251108060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover In A Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Having had a little too much to drink the night before, a young couple wakes up in a strange house in a strange town called Centerville, a place where no one lives, the trees are props and the food is plastic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108060500 +0000" stop="20251108063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Glass Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A shocking surprise awaits a woman who is about to meet her favorite star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108063500 +0000" stop="20251108070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Right Kind Of A House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman schemes to avenge her son's death with a unique plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108070500 +0000" stop="20251108080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Walk On The Blind Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate thugs have kidnapped an informer—or so they believe. Their victim is actually Peggy Fair, Mannix's secretary, which puts the detective on their trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108080500 +0000" stop="20251108090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Call Unicorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon goes undercover as a truck driver to investigate a series of hijackings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108090500 +0000" stop="20251108100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Catch Me If You Can</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is on the hunt for a psychopathic murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251108100000 +0000" stop="20251108103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Baffling Raffle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe has purchased the winning raffle ticket for a new TV. The only problem? Kate has the ticket, and she's on jury duty.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
