<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615050000 +0000" stop="20250615060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Stowaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the year 1997 the Robinson family takes off to colonize Alpha Centauri. A spy from a foreign country, Dr. Smith, becomes trapped aboard while trying to sabotage the project. The ship is whisked off course and into a meteor storm due to Dr Smith's extra weight, upsetting navigational computers. Smith desperately tries to save himself by reviving the crew, resulting in the Robinson family becoming lost in space.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615060000 +0000" stop="20250615070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Terror On Dinosaur Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Aloft in the flying sub to photograph the emergence of a volcanic island, Admiral Nelson and Chief Sharkey are forced to parachute onto an island inhabited by prehistoric beasts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615070000 +0000" stop="20250615080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Target: Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Two giant scientists convince Mark to help them develop a spaceship so they can return the Spindrift crew to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615080000 +0000" stop="20250615090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are charged with espionage when they land in Louisiana just before the battle of New Orleans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615090000 +0000" stop="20250615100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Condemned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>David is framed for murder when a missing file could expose the aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615100000 +0000" stop="20250615110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Prediction</sub-title>
    <desc>"When another student begins having violent visions, Matt has to stop them from coming true."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615110000 +0000" stop="20250615113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Rent-a-pop   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zach hires an actor to play his dad when he learns he's failing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615113000 +0000" stop="20250615120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bayside   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack bets Slater that the winner of the Miss Bayside Beauty Pageant will be Screech.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615120000 +0000" stop="20250615123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Zack's War   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After being forced to join the Army Cadet Corps, Zack persuade the gang to join, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615123000 +0000" stop="20250615130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Model Students   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang takes over the student store but business is slow, prompting Zack and Screech to secretly take photos of the girl's swim team!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615130000 +0000" stop="20250615133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Running Zack   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack needs help with his failing grades, his teacher enlists the help of a tutor, who, like Zack, is Native American. Zack learns about his heritage but doesn't want to go to a rally when tragedy strikes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615133000 +0000" stop="20250615140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>House Party   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Screech's parents leave for Graceland. While they are gone the gang accidentally breaks his mother's Elvis statue. With only a little money, they decide to hold a party to get a new statue before his mother finds out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615140000 +0000" stop="20250615143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of This World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After meeting an astronaut, Bobby and Peter begin wondering about life on other planets. Their wonder turns to excitement when they claim to have spotted a UFO and camp out in the backyard to get it on film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615143000 +0000" stop="20250615150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome Aboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol breaks the news to Mike that she's expecting and an eavesdropping Bobby and Cindy assume that she's pregnant and pass it along to the rest of the family. She's expecting alright - the arrival of her nephew and the kids' cousin Oliver, that is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615150000 +0000" stop="20250615153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The Cunningham Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An ill Richie is home alone while the rest of the family go to see Cinerama. Hearing noises downstairs, he investigates and finds a burglar!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615153000 +0000" stop="20250615160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Window On Main Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The girls agree to live in Bardwell's main show window for a weekend in order to demonstrate the "house of the future."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615160000 +0000" stop="20250615163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Date For Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked by Andy and Barney to take Thelma Lou's cousin, Mary Grace Gossage, to the Chamber of Commerce dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615163000 +0000" stop="20250615170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Handcuffs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucy snaps a pair of antique handcuffs on herself and Ricky, they realize there's no key. A locksmith is found, but not before the Ricardos go to bed handcuffed together, and Ricky has to do a TV show with his "attached" wife trying to upstage him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615170000 +0000" stop="20250615173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Paper Route</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to get brand-new bikes so they ask Ward for some money; however, he suggests that they earn the money. This leads Wally and Beaver to get a job delivering papers. Later, while trying to help the boys out, Ward and June inadvertently almost get Wally and Beaver fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615173000 +0000" stop="20250615180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Child Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After Ward's bragging about Wally and Beaver being responsible, Herb and Janet Wilson assume that it would be alright to leave their four-year-old daughter in Wally and Beaver's care while they go out to a party with Ward and June. However, the trouble begins when the youngster locks herself in the bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615180000 +0000" stop="20250615183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot-rod Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro wants a new car, embarrassed by the truck. He buys two new cars for two different images he is trying. But Jed tells him to just get a few new parts for the truck. Granny, who is celebrating her birthday, believes that they are planning to replace her. But she learns the truth, and wants the truck to stay the way it was. Jethro ends up getting a whole new front for the truck, and when Jed tells him to fix it, he gets a whole new back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615183000 +0000" stop="20250615190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Week Before Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a letter from Sam Drucker in Hooterville, but Elly's bear eats it. So after Granny finds very little success knowing if she is engaged or not, Jed, Granny and Elly all decide to spend Christmas in Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615190000 +0000" stop="20250615193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Diogenes, Won't You Please Go Home?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways discover Gilligan's secret diary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615193000 +0000" stop="20250615200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Physical Fatness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan and the Skipper plan to join the Navy when they are rescued.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615200000 +0000" stop="20250615203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Many Unhappy Returns  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama puts Bubba in a bind with his boss when she returns a gift that wasn't meant for her and spends the money on presents for the family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615203000 +0000" stop="20250615210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Found Money  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After an ATM error, Mama is given $800 from another person's account. Everyone in the family convinces her to keep it, but then she meets the man who lost the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615210000 +0000" stop="20250615220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Expedition / Julie's Wedding / Mongala / Julie's Replacement / Three Rs / Professor's Wife (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Julie prepares to marry her fiancé Tony Selkirk during a stopover in Sydney, Australia. Meanwhile, New Zealand rancher Ralph Sutton has a secret that he won't share with English teacher and fellow passenger Barbara Carroll, while young beauty Connie Wilker has eyes for him. Gopher and Doc both compete for the affections of new cruise director Yvonne Petty."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615220000 +0000" stop="20250615223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Barney's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After being kicked out of Mrs. Mendlebright's boardinghouse, Barney becomes suspicious of the man who takes his room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615223000 +0000" stop="20250615230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Janay Smith- Sports &amp; Celebrities</sub-title>
    <desc>"Janay Smith is giving us a small glimpse at the world largest, private, game worn sports collection, a collection she inherited after her sports crazed, lawyer father left her, when he passed. Some of this spectacular collection is at the Smithsonian, but today, she'll show us Hank Aaron's jersey, and the game ticket from the day he broke Babe Ruth's home-run record. We'll see Muhammad Ali's trunks and training robe, Kobe Bryant's #8 autographed jersey, and Jim Brown's MVP trophy. Historian and African American material culture expert, Philip Merrill, will evaluate this collection with a number never heard before on "Collector's Call," and then attempt a trade Janay with a big-time big league offer. But will she play ball?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615230000 +0000" stop="20250615233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawk's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hawkeye bemoans the young age of the wounded, he appears to develop problems. Sleepwalking and bad dreams, according to Sidney Freedman, are taking Hawkeye back to a simple time, but the horrors of war continue to intrude. After Sidney's assurances that he is as sane as can be, Hawkeye's life once again seems to settle down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250615233000 +0000" stop="20250616000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Unforgettable Characters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets accepted into the "Famous Las Vegas Writers School," and begins to write his impressions of the camp. It happens to be Frank's birthday, so Hawkeye and B.J. stage a fight with each other to make Frank happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616000000 +0000" stop="20250616003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Learns His Lesson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie swears Edith into secrecy when he begins attending night-school classes to qualify for a high school diploma in hopes of getting a promotion at work. However, Edith spills the beans and soon Mike and Archie must learn to share a study space, but that proves to be difficult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616003000 +0000" stop="20250616010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria, The Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria comes home from work in a most unusual mood. She later confides in Edith that on the way to work, she had been attacked by a construction worker near a construction site. When Mike and Archie find out about this, they try to encourage her to report it, but she is hesitant and totally uncomfortable with the idea of telling a detective all the details of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616010000 +0000" stop="20250616013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Being her time of the month, Gloria is in a complete foul mood and gets into a big argument with Edith, lambasting her for letting Archie boss her around. Soon, Gloria gets into a big fight with Mike and decides to sleep on the couch, however, no one can sleep when Mike and Gloria's bickering keeps Archie and Edith up. Meanwhile, all of this puts a damper on Gloria's birthday celebration.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616013000 +0000" stop="20250616020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>We're Having A Heat Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A heat wave hits New York, putting all of the Bunkers in bad moods and, to put salt on an already open wound, the air conditioner breaks down. When the house next door is put up for sale, Archie puts together a petition to prevent more minorities from moving into the neighborhood. Henry Jefferson hops on board when he discovers that a Hispanic family is looking at the home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616020000 +0000" stop="20250616023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 05/04/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616023000 +0000" stop="20250616030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball, Eddie Albert, And Nancy Wilson</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball, Eddie Albert, and Nancy Wilson. Originally aired on 11/04/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616030000 +0000" stop="20250616033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Draw Me A Pear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura talks Rob into going to her art class, and he becomes the teacher's pet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616033000 +0000" stop="20250616040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Petrie Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Petries hunt for treasure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616040000 +0000" stop="20250616043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is baby-sitting to pay for a phone but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616043000 +0000" stop="20250616053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of The Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter finds himself trapped in a small town where people can reverse time and do many other amazing things.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616053000 +0000" stop="20250616060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Creeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial killer known as “the strangler” terrorizes a New York neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616060000 +0000" stop="20250616070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Amateur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A wannabe spy in an eastern European country happens upon an operation of the IMF team. But, in a cleaver twist, as this amateur's dreams of becoming a super sleuth turn to greed the IMF team manipulates him and government security forces to accomplish their mission and their escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616070000 +0000" stop="20250616080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Ballad For A Ghost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble finds himself working with Hallie, a woman who bears a strong resemblance to his late wife. Hallie knows of the resemblance, and Kimble's danger is increased when Hallie's husband becomes jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616080000 +0000" stop="20250616090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Road</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hit-and-run murder injects Harry Orwell into the investigation of an alcoholic woman attorney who suspects that she herself may be the killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616090000 +0000" stop="20250616093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616093000 +0000" stop="20250616100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Bunco - $9,000</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The search is on for a swindler who conned an old vaudevillian out of $9,000 he found on a sidewalk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616100000 +0000" stop="20250616103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 175 -- Con Artists</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy respond to a car rollover where a good samaritan makes matters worse. Afterward, they respond to several victims of a well-known family of seasonal home improvement con artists before finally catching them in the act. In the meantime, they search for a disgruntled ex-employee who is trying to sabotage his former workplace, and take a drunk driver off the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616103000 +0000" stop="20250616110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 115 -- Gang War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed loses a robbery suspect while in foot pursuit. Afterward, he and Malloy try to help a priest prevent bloodshed between rival hispanic gangs, and then respond to a battered wife whose husband is very familiar to the officers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616110000 +0000" stop="20250616120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Art Of Art</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill explores his artistic side with the help of an actual master painter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616120000 +0000" stop="20250616123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Account</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward tries to teach Wally and Beaver the importance of saving by giving them a piggy bank. The boys quickly save up a handful of change and are all ready to spend it on some baseball equipment. However, unknown to their parents, they change their minds and decide to spend the money on a most unselfish gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616123000 +0000" stop="20250616130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lonesome Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally goes away on a trip with the Boy Scout troop that he belongs to, leaving a lonesome Beaver behind. Finding his friends to be busy, Beaver takes up other means to make the time go by.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616130000 +0000" stop="20250616140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Grinning Gorilla</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A scientist involved in a lawsuit with his former housekeeper is found stabbed to death, and the housekeeper—though cornered by a loose gorilla—is present when the corpse is discovered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616140000 +0000" stop="20250616150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Reporter (aka The Widow)  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A reporter asks for Matlock's help in clearing a newlywed (Caryn Richman) charged with the murder of her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616150000 +0000" stop="20250616160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brother's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Louann's ne'er-do-well brother returns home after being paroled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616160000 +0000" stop="20250616170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen is eager to begin nursing school, but is unhappy to learn that she lacks the education in algebra and chemistry needed to enter</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616170000 +0000" stop="20250616173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Groat's Grudge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lee, a Southerner, comes to Dodge to wait for Tom Haskins. Lee wants to kill him. Lee believes Haskins was responsible for burning Lee's house outside Atlanta and killing his wife during the Civil War."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616173000 +0000" stop="20250616180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Big Tom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ex-prize fighter Tom Burr decides to fight Hob Creel but Doc tells him he has a bad heart and it could kill him. Matt locks Tom up so he can't fight. Matt winds up fighting Creel instead."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616180000 +0000" stop="20250616190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Vote</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss and Joe's bickering leads them into taking opposite sides in the Virginia City mayoral race. Their zealous actions divide Virginia City's citizens into two factions, causing nothing but arguments, fights and havoc in town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616190000 +0000" stop="20250616193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616193000 +0000" stop="20250616200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616200000 +0000" stop="20250616210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clara Duncan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Clara Duncan joins the train in a search for her artist fiance. But finding him could lead to trouble, as one of his missing paintings depicting a heinous crime may implicate some of the locals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616210000 +0000" stop="20250616220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Understanding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>At an explosive fire, a girl's horse is trapped in a burning barn. Dr. Brackett and Nurse McCall lecture a man who keeps forgetting his insulin shots. A girl calls the hospital, threatening suicide; firemen stand by while hospital workers attempt to trace the call. A hostage in a bank robbery has heart problems; the paramedics must treat him at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616220000 +0000" stop="20250616223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616223000 +0000" stop="20250616230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616230000 +0000" stop="20250616233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250616233000 +0000" stop="20250617000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617000000 +0000" stop="20250617003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And His Merry Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie and his friends find a hungry man in the woods who tells them the story of Robin Hood, the boys begin to steal for the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617003000 +0000" stop="20250617010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Cave Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is the laughingstock of the town after he mistakes the owner of the Mayberry Bank as a robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617010000 +0000" stop="20250617013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Play The Rams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro gets a date with the Drydales’ new maid, Linda, but she is only interested in the fact that he has a color television set. Instead of paying attention to Jethro, she watches a football game the first night and an ice hockey game the next. Jethro attempts trying out the games, but isn’t very successful at football and doesn’t like the hockey gear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617013000 +0000" stop="20250617020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617020000 +0000" stop="20250617023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reverend Kommandant Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan sneaks a French pilot's girl into camp and gets Klink to marry them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617023000 +0000" stop="20250617030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Escape-proof Camp I've Ever Escaped From</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Klink's "no escape" record is jeopardized when Malcom Flood, a British escape artist, lands in Stalag 13 and intends to continue his impressive escape record, a plan likely to endanger Hogan's scheduled rendezvous with an OSS agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617030000 +0000" stop="20250617033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Hitch-hiker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Alone on a cross-country trip, a woman keeps seeing the same hitch-hiker everywhere she looks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617033000 +0000" stop="20250617043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Absent Artist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cartoonist Pete Manders is elated when the owner of the comic strip "Zingy" offers to sell him the strip for a song. However, Pete then learns that his girlfriend is running away to Europe with the strip's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617043500 +0000" stop="20250617050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617050500 +0000" stop="20250617053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Momentum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>A man ends up running to the Mexican border after trying to collect money his employer owes him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617053500 +0000" stop="20250617060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Wet Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A vulnerable man is pinned with a murder he did not commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617060500 +0000" stop="20250617070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Fly, Little One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is asked to clear a psychotherapist charged with murder and robbery, the main witness being an autistic girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617070500 +0000" stop="20250617080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a man who is charged with arson and murder by burning down his textile company which killed his wife who was trapped inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617080500 +0000" stop="20250617090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must beat a bounty hunter to an escaped convict who can vindicate a prison trustee charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617090000 +0000" stop="20250617093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617093000 +0000" stop="20250617100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617100000 +0000" stop="20250617103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 26 -- Lemras</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed drive up on a convenience store robbery in progress, which results in the suspects taking hostages. Later, they pull over a reckless driver who has just committed a heinous crime, learn about a new computer system designed to help them be more productive and finally thwart a group of serial burglars who use motorcycles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617103000 +0000" stop="20250617110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 155 -- I.a.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Tony Johnson finds out he has been accused of a shakedown just after saving Malloy's life during a shootout. Reed and Malloy set out to find a bar girl named Ginger who Johnson says will prove his innocence, but her story leaves Malloy with an uneasy feeling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617110000 +0000" stop="20250617120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day June 17th</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony highlight pivotal moments in history."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617120000 +0000" stop="20250617123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cleaning Up Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins to outgrow his "sloppy" phase and becomes much neater. This is noticed by Ward and June who try to encourage Beaver to undergo the same transformation. However, Beaver changing like that just seems too extraordinary of a task.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617123000 +0000" stop="20250617130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward becomes a bit jealous when Wally and Beaver begin spending time playing basketball at Willie Dennison's house after Willie's dad put up a backboard and a basket. This prompts Ward to do the same thing but it just seems like things are working against him in his quest to be the perfect father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617130000 +0000" stop="20250617140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wrongful Writ</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young lawyer is framed for the murder of a man claiming to be a government agent, Mason must cull through witnesses to identify the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617140000 +0000" stop="20250617150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an abhorred doctor meets his end, four of his former medical students are considered likely suspects. Matlock, however, is tasked with defending the prime suspect, the man seen fleeing the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617150000 +0000" stop="20250617160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Frenzied Affair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea places herself in harm’s way trying to help one of her students, a disturbed and violent young man; after he is implicated in a murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617160000 +0000" stop="20250617170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Intruders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is upset at how he is treated at the mill</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617170000 +0000" stop="20250617173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Til Death Do Us</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jezra Cobb is shot at but the man gets away. Kitty overhears a drifter named Puggy say that he was paid $300 to kill Jezra. Matt rides out to Jezra's ranch to talk to him but his wife insists they have a piece of pie first before going to see Jezra in the barn."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617173000 +0000" stop="20250617180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Tragedian</sub-title>
    <desc>"Edward, as washed up actor, gets caught cheating at cards. Matt gets him a job washing dishes but Edward steals money and gets drunk. Matt has Chester lock him up while he looks for the brother of a murder who's out to shoot him so his brother won't stand trial."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617180000 +0000" stop="20250617190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Catch As Catch Can</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When residents of Tin Bucket claim the Cartwrights and Candy are dealing in stolen cattle hides, Ben is determined to discover who is actually responsible for the hide thefts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617190000 +0000" stop="20250617193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617193000 +0000" stop="20250617200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Italian count arrives in North Fork, his strange attire attracts the attention of Groder, a town bully. Groder, trying to have fun with this stranger, destroys some of the count's currency, mocks him and tries to humiliate him. Eventually the count challenges Groder to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617200000 +0000" stop="20250617210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Duke Lemay Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke Le May, an escaped convict, joins the wagon train under an assumed name. When a deputy shows up to arrest him and is killed, Flint is asked to escort him to the nearest fort for trial but he does all he can to prolong the journey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617210000 +0000" stop="20250617220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Computer Error</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple is rescued from a car wreck; the boy has a spinal cord injury and Dr. Early suspects the girl is pregnant. Roy and John rescue a woman trapped at the bottom of a well and an amateur magician from a safe. A rescue at a junkyard fire turns hazardous when phosphorus materials explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617220000 +0000" stop="20250617223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617223000 +0000" stop="20250617230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617230000 +0000" stop="20250617233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250617233000 +0000" stop="20250618000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618000000 +0000" stop="20250618003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie's Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy pays attention to a fatherless new boy in town, which makes Opie jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618003000 +0000" stop="20250618010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Crusader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and most of the women in town rally against Andy when he tries to evict a much-beloved butter and egg man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618010000 +0000" stop="20250618013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny tries to conjure a man for Elly May, but accidentally attracts Miss Jane's man, who is actually a hired escort Mr. Drysdale got for Elly. When the Clampetts find out, they work to get rid of him so Miss Jane can have her man back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618013000 +0000" stop="20250618020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Ralph Kramden, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton invests in Ralph's stock when Ralph wants twenty dollars. When Ralph thinks he is named in a millionaire's will, arguments arise. It turns out Ralph was simply left a pet bird named Fortune, and much of the money was left to the butler and maid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618020000 +0000" stop="20250618023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan blackmails General Burkhalter to keep Klink from being transferred to the Russian front for failing to keep Hogan from blowing up a radio tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618023000 +0000" stop="20250618030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Colonel Klink's Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink suffers at the hands of a tough sergeant sent to discipline prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618030000 +0000" stop="20250618033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When his wife wins a trip for two to Las Vegas, a man falls under the spell of a slot machine that calls his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618033000 +0000" stop="20250618043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fan-dancer's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After witnessing an automobile accident, Mason comes to represent the driver of the vehicle, an exotic dancer charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618043500 +0000" stop="20250618050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618050500 +0000" stop="20250618053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Fog Closing In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hears strange noises in her house while her husband is away on business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618053500 +0000" stop="20250618060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>De Mortius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An old college professor decides to take action when he finds out that his wife cheated on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618060500 +0000" stop="20250618070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Search For Darrell Andrews</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix suspects foul play when colleague Wes Tully is discovered floating dead in his swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618070500 +0000" stop="20250618080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Cain's Mark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired when a young brother of a gun manufacturer and collector vanishes from sight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618080500 +0000" stop="20250618090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Renegade's Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby's search for a 6-year-old boy leads him to the boy's father - a vagrant who deals in illegal arms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618090000 +0000" stop="20250618093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618093000 +0000" stop="20250618100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618100000 +0000" stop="20250618103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 66 -- The Vandals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy have a gun pulled on them after stopping a car that turns out to be stolen, but the contents of the trunk link the two suspects to an even more sinister crime. Afterward, a recently widowed father and his teenage daughter report that their home has just been toilet papered, which ends up being a prelude for a much more serious incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618103000 +0000" stop="20250618110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Man Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed, who is an optimist and still has faith in the human race, is subjected to ridicule from Officer Wells after he is swindled twice. On patrol, he and Malloy come to the aid of a woman whose baby has been kidnapped by a heavily armed man seeking a large ransom. Afterward, wells once again questions Reed's judgment during the search for an intoxicated sniper at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618110000 +0000" stop="20250618120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Movies To Animation</sub-title>
    <desc>"From the big screen to the small screen, movies that became animated series."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618120000 +0000" stop="20250618123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Poncho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver makes a trade with Larry Mondello, a glass doorknob for a chihuahua. Larry had found the dog in his garbage can, so when Beaver brings it home, Ward immediately breaks the news that he's going to place an ad in the lost-and-found and that Beaver probably won't be able to keep the dog. Despite this, Beaver quickly begins to grow close to the little dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618123000 +0000" stop="20250618130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The State Vs. Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward helps Beaver and Wally build a miniature race car powered by the lawn mower motor, and Ward makes the boys promise not to use it without his supervision. Later, Larry talks Beaver into taking it for a spin, resulting in the boys being pulled over by a traffic officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618130000 +0000" stop="20250618140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mischievous Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady private investigator and his pawn die mysteriously, the woman who may have been his intended target is charged with their murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618140000 +0000" stop="20250618150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 1  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618150000 +0000" stop="20250618160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Discovery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea has trouble dealing with the violent death of a student. Young Megan Fowler quickly finds herself yet another dangerous boyfriend and they are soon wanted by the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618160000 +0000" stop="20250618170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia and Elizabeth take a car trip; Jim-Bob is forced to also go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618170000 +0000" stop="20250618173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hinka Do</sub-title>
    <desc>"The new rootin tootin owner of "The Lady Gay" (Mamie) comes to Dodge and opens a saloon. When she opens the saloon, she lets the Dodge cowpokes know that she is very handy with a gun and will use that gun on any trouble makers in her saloon."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618173000 +0000" stop="20250618180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Judge</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Matt is away on business, Doc gets threatened by an ex-convict (Brice Harp) who claims that Doc Adams sentenced him to a long term in Prison. Doc tries to explain to the man that he was never a judge and has always been a doctor, but the man does not believe Doc."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618180000 +0000" stop="20250618190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A young brat and distant relative of the Cartwrights annoys everyone when he comes for a visit to the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618190000 +0000" stop="20250618193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Floyd Doniger comes to North Fork, looking to start a new life. He's got a steady job as the guard at the new bank and he's entertaining ideas of settling down on a spread of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618193000 +0000" stop="20250618200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618200000 +0000" stop="20250618210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kate Parker Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The wagon train pushes ahead after one of the passengers has an accident. With only a wagon between two couples, someone decides to leave with money including some gold coins. They have an accident and the storm's only getting worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618210000 +0000" stop="20250618220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy are disappointed when they are the only squad not called to a major brushfire. Dixie gets her hand caught in a vending machine. A lawyer collapses in the courtroom with an apparent heart attack. Roy and John finally make it to the brushfire and become trapped while rescuing another firefighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618220000 +0000" stop="20250618223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618223000 +0000" stop="20250618230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618230000 +0000" stop="20250618233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250618233000 +0000" stop="20250619000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619000000 +0000" stop="20250619003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady prisoner woos Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619003000 +0000" stop="20250619010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619010000 +0000" stop="20250619013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Real Nice Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts get a new next-door neighbor, and when Aggie, the maid of Mrs. Phillip Brentwood Carrington III, drops by to the use the phone, the Clampetts mistake her for Carrington. This is the first rich neighbor who has proven to be kind and considerate. Drysdale is happy because this rich woman has moved next door and might be a wife for Jed. Granny also sees her as a match for Jed. The two try to set Jed and Aggie up in different ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619013000 +0000" stop="20250619020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Alice And The Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and Nortons visit the Wedemeyers and the wives believe their husbands are neglecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619020000 +0000" stop="20250619023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Top Secret Top Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a top-secret document from Klink's coat to save him from being arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619023000 +0000" stop="20250619030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619030000 +0000" stop="20250619033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A World War I flying ace flies through a mysterious cloud—and lands at a modern U.S. air base in the year 1959.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619033000 +0000" stop="20250619043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Astronaut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Astronaut Matthew Heller is suspected of killing his old service rival, General Addison Brand, after Brand is put in charge of the astronaut program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619043500 +0000" stop="20250619050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619050500 +0000" stop="20250619053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Kill With Kindness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitz Oldham plans to torch his home and fake his death to collect insurance money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619053500 +0000" stop="20250619060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>None Are So Blind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Seymour Johnson disguises himself before killing his wealthy aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619060500 +0000" stop="20250619070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix sets out to prove the innocence of a young woman accused of shooting a businessman. A track leads Mannix to journalist Hackett, who was interviewing the victim moments before the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619070500 +0000" stop="20250619080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Moonlight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A young convict is being harassed by a prisoner who is running a gambling operation inside of the lock up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619080500 +0000" stop="20250619090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fraternity Of Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of amateur thieves attempt to cover up the death of their cohort during a holdup - at the risk of the diamonds they've stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619090000 +0000" stop="20250619093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619093000 +0000" stop="20250619100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619100000 +0000" stop="20250619103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 165 -- Once A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The search for a stabbing suspect leads to a bitter ex-cop who has just moved into the area. Afterward, Malloy and Reed deal with a naive and frustrated starlet who shoots up a telephone booth and loses her suitcase containing a live rattle snake. The officers then become involved in shootout at a train station that leads to another unfortunate run-in with the ex-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619103000 +0000" stop="20250619110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 76 -- The Militants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed participate in the search for two black militants who ambush and critically wound two officers in their patrol car. When one of the suspects subsequently dies in custody, a bitter public relations battle begins with the militant group as the search for the other suspect continues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619110000 +0000" stop="20250619120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Summer Break</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony plan a summer vacation!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619120000 +0000" stop="20250619123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Broken Window</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing baseball in the street with Wally, Chester and Tooey, Eddie hits a baseball through the Cleaver's window resulting in Ward forbidding the boys to play baseball so close to the house. However, later, Beaver talks Wally into pitching one, and this results in a broken car window.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619123000 +0000" stop="20250619130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An 8th grade dance has Wally being pressured into attending with a girl, instead of going stag with Eddie. However, Mary Ellen Rogers becomes determined to have Wally take her and goes through Beaver to get to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619130000 +0000" stop="20250619140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Laughing Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman being held in prison pending her trial sees the woman whom she believes committed the crime with which she has been charged on a televised gala.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619140000 +0000" stop="20250619150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 2  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619150000 +0000" stop="20250619160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Random's Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lana Gillespie comes to Sparta to claim her inheritance, but is stalked by a mobster who dated her mother. Meanwhile Harriet encourages Bill to talk to his daughter, but Lana doesn't seem to be interested. Officer Randy Goode helps keep the bad guys at bay by playing them a little tune on the guitar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619160000 +0000" stop="20250619170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob wonders if he is adopted because he does not look like other family members</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619170000 +0000" stop="20250619173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Moo Moo Raid</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tush (a cattle boss) accuses Bert (cattle boss of another herd) of murdering Onie Tucker &amp; his cow. An all-out war is looming when Matt won't arrest Burt right away."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619173000 +0000" stop="20250619180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kitty's Killing</sub-title>
    <desc>"When an older gentlemen, Jacob Leech, comes into the Dodge jail house and tells Matt and Chester that he plans to kill a man named Ollie Radford, Matt puts Jacob Leech in the jail for the night to cool off."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619180000 +0000" stop="20250619190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Survivors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is reunited with his wife after she was abducted years earlier by the Paiutes Indians—discovering that she now has a half-Indian baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619190000 +0000" stop="20250619193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiffauges, a wealthy and sadistic Frenchman who is used to getting whatever he wants, decides he wishes to purchase the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges' lead man, Xavier, proclaims Lucas to be muy macho, and does not believe Lucas will give in so easily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619193000 +0000" stop="20250619200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Apprentice Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Willard is filling in as temporary marshal while Micah is away. Some Texas cowhands are in North Fork looking for some fun and relaxation, but Dan keeps coming down hard on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619200000 +0000" stop="20250619210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Steve Campden Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint must find a way to get the wagon train around a snow-covered pass. On a scouting trek, he meets a father and son who are willing to help him, but they want to hike up the mountain. The adventure ahead has surprises for them all.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619210000 +0000" stop="20250619220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Messin' Around</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Chet starts a series of practical jokes against John, who eventually retaliates. A child is trapped in a burning tree house. A retiree pretends to be ill so he can amuse the children in the emergency department. A woman feeds her sick husband dieffenbachia sap to keep him quiet. At a trash fire, a gas station worker shows signs of a perforated ulcer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619220000 +0000" stop="20250619223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619223000 +0000" stop="20250619230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619230000 +0000" stop="20250619233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250619233000 +0000" stop="20250620000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620000000 +0000" stop="20250620003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Song Festers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's singing voice surprises everyone, especially Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620003000 +0000" stop="20250620010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620010000 +0000" stop="20250620013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Poor Farmer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale organizes a financial syndicate, which includes a billionaire who he wants in his bank. Jed is one of the potential members of this group, but never makes the meeting because a new invention of Jethro’s, a chemical that turns water into gasoline, doesn’t work. When Jed finally arrives, it is too late, and Mr. Sebastian has left. Jane suggests that he visits him at his health club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620013000 +0000" stop="20250620020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Dog's Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph feeds his boss dog food, thinking that it is an appetizer that Alice made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620020000 +0000" stop="20250620023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Crittendon Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon disrupts Hogan's plan to blow up a tunnel and stop a convoy of rocket fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620023000 +0000" stop="20250620030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Some Of Their Planes Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Germans plan to send their men into England via captured planes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620030000 +0000" stop="20250620033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Purple Testament</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A lieutenant develops the disquieting ability to foresee which of his men will die prior to battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620033000 +0000" stop="20250620043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby mysteriously appears in Mason's office along with a rare St. Christopher medal, which could help identify the baby's parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620043500 +0000" stop="20250620050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620050500 +0000" stop="20250620053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Toby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Albert finds his childhood love, and she agrees to marry him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620053500 +0000" stop="20250620060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Alibi Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Georgie is a gang member looking for an alibi after the death of his alter ego.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620060500 +0000" stop="20250620070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is involved in a war of nerves when he deals with blackmailers threatening an entire town with nerve gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620070500 +0000" stop="20250620080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Cats And Sudden Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Public prosecutor Mike Arnold needs Cannon's help. He is suspected of the murder of his wife. His problem: Dubious friends want him to finish a corruption investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620080500 +0000" stop="20250620090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sister Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A nun is accused of taking her terminally ill sister off life support.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620090000 +0000" stop="20250620093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Dognappers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon set out to muzzle thieves who steal dogs and then collect hefty rewards from the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620093000 +0000" stop="20250620100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Persons - The Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Working with the slimmest of leads, police attempt to identify a woman's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620100000 +0000" stop="20250620103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 164 -- The Poachers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young employee at the city garage steals a patrol car and engages in a high speed pursuit. Afterward, Malloy and Reed arrest a young woman trying to cash an old-age benefits check she found on the ground, report to an apartment complex garage that had its security camera stolen, investigate a break-in at a mortuary and arrest a couple of pill pushers at a warehouse in Officer Ed Well's territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620103000 +0000" stop="20250620110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620110000 +0000" stop="20250620120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Let's Talk, Talk</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony get front frow seats to Mr. Quizzer's new talk show. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620120000 +0000" stop="20250620123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Next Door Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to be liked by Wally's friends, Beaver makes up a wild story about the vacant lot next to his house being an Indian battle ground. After making a bet with Eddie, Beaver has Wally help him plant artifacts in the lot. However, that is forgotten when the kids make a discovery that they believe will make them rich.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620123000 +0000" stop="20250620130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tenting Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a weekend spent at the movies goes awry for Ward, he decides the boys should spend their weekends outside and plans a camping trip. However, when Ward's called into work, Wally and Beaver decide to camp out in the backyard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620130000 +0000" stop="20250620140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune teller gives a series of accurate predictions regarding a woman's future. But something goes wrong when she's charged with murdering her new husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620140000 +0000" stop="20250620150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Justice  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle defends college chum Andrea Morrow after she is accused of murdering her abusive lover, Clay Graham. Matlock soon becomes convinced that the murderer was Clay's blind friend, Arthur Hampton, but has a devil of a time proving how a blind man managed to carry off a near-perfect murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620150000 +0000" stop="20250620160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>An Occupational Hazard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A secretary takes drastic measures to protect herself from sexual harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620160000 +0000" stop="20250620170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben starts to hunt animals for their skins to sell for profit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620170000 +0000" stop="20250620173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbait Janet</sub-title>
    <desc>"A man his son and daughter hold up a train. The man kills a train employee to get some money to avenge the loss of the man's wife and everything they owned. Earlier the sparks from another train had set fire to the prairie where they lived in Newton, Ks. and caused their loss."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620173000 +0000" stop="20250620180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Unwanted Deputy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Vince Wiley come to Dodge to try and make Marshall Dillon draw on him first so he can kill Matt "in self-defense". Wiley is not his real name and he wants the Marshall dead for killing his brother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620180000 +0000" stop="20250620190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Sound Of Drums</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Georgio Rossi is at a loss as to why he is not allowed to have Indians living on his land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620190000 +0000" stop="20250620193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark, returning from selling their herd, share the stagecoach trip with a Marshal and his prisoner, Johnny Cotton. Johnny's gang arrives to free their partner and steal the contents of the stage's strongbox, as well as Lucas' money and rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620193000 +0000" stop="20250620200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620200000 +0000" stop="20250620210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Chuck Wooster, Wagonmaster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When a big snow halts the train, several of the men disappear mysteriously. After Flint, Major Adams and Hawks go missing, it's up to Chuck Wooster to lead the train to safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620210000 +0000" stop="20250620220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is injured when his chimney explodes. A brash young intern at Rampart thinks he knows more than the paramedics and makes a near-fatal diagnosis of a heart patient; Dr. Brackett send him on a ride-along with Squad 51. A girl gets her hand stuck in a mailbox. Johnny and Roy must rescue a heart attack victim trapped on an oil refinery tower in the midst of an explosive fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620220000 +0000" stop="20250620223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620223000 +0000" stop="20250620230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620230000 +0000" stop="20250620233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250620233000 +0000" stop="20250621000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621000000 +0000" stop="20250621003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621003000 +0000" stop="20250621010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621010000 +0000" stop="20250621013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Strike Oil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed Clampett's swamp is loaded with oil. When a wildcatter discovers the huge pool, Jed sells his land to the O.K. Oil Company and, at the urging of cousin Pearl, moves his family to a 35-room mansion in Beverly Hills, California. But when they get to their new home, which they think is a prison and the gardeners are inmates, they are mistaken for vandals and get arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621013000 +0000" stop="20250621020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Bensonhurst Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph gets into an argument at the pool hall and has to fight a big guy at the gym. He arranges it so that he can pretend to knock out a bigger man and make the other one scared. Instead he knocks out a stranger, regaining his confidence to go ahead with the fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621020000 +0000" stop="20250621023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>D-day At Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan pulls a hoax to get a general to believe Klink is replacing him as chief of staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621023000 +0000" stop="20250621030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621030000 +0000" stop="20250621033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Elegy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts land on what looks like Earth 200 years before they left—only all of the people seem frozen in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621033000 +0000" stop="20250621043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Counterfeit Crank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man, his dead nephew and a military base are tangled up in a confusing case for Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621043500 +0000" stop="20250621050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621050500 +0000" stop="20250621053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Conversation Over A Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Two sisters poison the banker who holds their mortgage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621053500 +0000" stop="20250621060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Crack Of Doom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason Bridges plays poker with wealthy clients. He gambles everything he has and everything his company owns on one game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621060500 +0000" stop="20250621070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon A Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After a string of strange accidents, a carnival-troupe boss employs Mannix to investigate the mishaps.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621070500 +0000" stop="20250621080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Sky Above, Death Below</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A trade union boss dies in the mountains of Colorado. His daughter believes it was murder and hires Cannon to investigate. While the detective is inspecting of the scene someone pursues him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621080500 +0000" stop="20250621090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Charade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty falls for a playboy who's planning a murder to gain an inheritance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621090000 +0000" stop="20250621093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Genghis Keane Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>When news spreads that Kate's former grade school teacher, Miss Keane, has returned to Hooterville, Kate tells her children how horribly strict her childhood teacher was. However, the years seem to have changed Miss Keane.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
