<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516173000 +0000" stop="20250516180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Matt is forced to serve an eviction notice on farmer Brandon Teek, Matt tries every way he can to help the farmer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516180000 +0000" stop="20250516190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Detector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is sure there's gold in an old mine he wants to buy, and has the gold detector to prove it. However, things are not what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516190000 +0000" stop="20250516193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark meet Mark Twain and find out that he hides a sad secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516193000 +0000" stop="20250516200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun From Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to stop embittered John Holliver from venting his wrath on the people who expelled him from town years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516200000 +0000" stop="20250516210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jennifer Churchill Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jennifer Churchill, pampered all her life, runs away from a smothering lifestyle and pending marriage to join the wagon train. With bounty hunters on her heels, she finds Flint, a man who she wants but doesn't want her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516210000 +0000" stop="20250516220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Drivers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets bugged by other people's bad driving habits. A college quarterback experiences back pain. Roy and John's former paramedic instructor dies, while Roy and John themselves teach a CPR class. A boy gets stuck inside a tree. A fire at a hotel is complicated by a cardiac victim on the third floor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516220000 +0000" stop="20250516223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516223000 +0000" stop="20250516230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516230000 +0000" stop="20250516233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516233000 +0000" stop="20250517000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517000000 +0000" stop="20250517003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517003000 +0000" stop="20250517010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517010000 +0000" stop="20250517013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed's Temptation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the day after Jed spent the night dancing with Phyllis, and he is stiff from all the dancing. Granny is throwing her “I told you sos” at him. And when Phyllis invites him to the horse races, he accepts. When Drysdale and Jane learn of the type of woman she is, they warn Granny and drive her down to the racetrack to stop them. Meanwhile, at the racetrack, Jed and Phyllis are finding great success, because Jed can tell which horse will win.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517013000 +0000" stop="20250517020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>To Watch A Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter puts a down payment on a watch for Miss Bunny at the PX, but Gomer mistakenly thinks he has stolen it and returns the watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517020000 +0000" stop="20250517023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reservations Are Required</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan tries to arrange the unscheduled escape of 20 men, his mission is complicated when a captured sergeant jumps the gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517023000 +0000" stop="20250517030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Anchors Aweigh, Men Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men are tasked with getting an escaped prisoner and smuggled German gun sight to England. To accomplish this Hogan convinces Klink that he is fatigued and should have an officer's club in which to relax.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517030000 +0000" stop="20250517033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Juliet Prowse And Martha Raye</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Juliet Prowse and Martha Raye. Originally aired on 11/20/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517033000 +0000" stop="20250517043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Moth-eaten Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Restaurateur Morey Allen, a friend of Mason and Della's, contacts Mason after his waitress, Dixie Dayton, is struck by a car while fleeing the restaurant after spotting a man stalking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517043500 +0000" stop="20250517050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Mover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man discovers that his business partner has the ability to control objects with his mind, the pair head to Vegas to win big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517050500 +0000" stop="20250517053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Children Of Alda Nuova</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A man disappears while visiting little-known tourist attractions in Italy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517053500 +0000" stop="20250517060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>First Class Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man makes a deal with a friend to keep from having to pay his wife alimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517060500 +0000" stop="20250517070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Rabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix accuses a man of murder, but the accused maintains that the death was an accident and that the dead man owed him money. The status of the victim's family complicates Mannix's investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517070500 +0000" stop="20250517080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Salinas Jackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon is called in to investigate a robbery and murder of six people at a rodeo. The police had come up with nothing after six weeks except for the knowledge that there was a film taken of the rodeo at the day of the crime. Cannon believes that there is a possibility that the rodeo clowns may have played a part in the crime and must now learn where the clown suit came from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517080500 +0000" stop="20250517090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Relations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to replace a detective who was murdered while looking for a woman's biological mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517090000 +0000" stop="20250517093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Hooterville Flivverball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Jo plans to use Orville Miggs' Flivver to power his own railroad and bankrupt the Hooterville Cannonball.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517093000 +0000" stop="20250517100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Kate The Stockholder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe turns to harassing Floyd and Charley to rid Hooterville of the Cannonball.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517100000 +0000" stop="20250517103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Buggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a buggy for her horse Ladybelle and gets the same thing for Mrs. Drysdale so they can have buggy races. But the horse she buys for her neighbor is known around the stables as "Old Gluepot." She tries to cheat to win, but ends up with Lightening, the poor horse, after Jed tries to teach her a lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517103000 +0000" stop="20250517110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>While Elly is washing her dogs, Granny calls that the food is ready, and the dogs trample her. Granny tells Jed and Elly that if the dogs don’t go, she will. Drysdale is also having dog troubles, annoyed with the fact that his wife’s dog gets beauty parlor treatment. Jed finally convinces Granny to let the dogs stay, but after changing her mind, she gets trampled by Elly’s new dogs, causing her to want them all out again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517110000 +0000" stop="20250517113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Dizzy Divers, Popeye, The Ace Of Space, House Tricks?</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bluto attempts to get to sunken treasure before Popeye can., Aliens from Mars abduct Popeye and perform experiments on him., Popeye and Bluto fight each other to prove they can build Olive Oyl's house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517113000 +0000" stop="20250517120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Zoot Cat, Little Gravel Voice, Puttin' On The Dog</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom gets a new suit to impress a girl cat after she doesn't accept Jerry as a gift., The ear-splitting brays of a little burro prevent any other young animals from befriending him., Tom chases Jerry right into a dog pound, so he puts on a dog disguise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517120000 +0000" stop="20250517130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Square Shootin' Square, Sleepy Time Bear, Goodbye Mr. Moth, Horse Play, Freeloading Feline, Fish Fry, Fat In The Saddle</sub-title>
    <desc>"Outlaw Dapper Denver Dooley stashes his loot in Woody's tree, and Woody runs away with it. In the end, Woody turns Denver and the loot in to the sheriff., Chilly has to save a hibernating Maxie from a hunter trying to capture him for the zoo., Andy Panda tries to get a moth out of his tailor shop., Woody has a run-in with an indigineous man who doesn't like Woody's horse., Champ gets mistaken for a waiter at a fancy party and fulfills his duties by keeping Doc, a free-loader, out., A hungry alley cat tries to steal Andy Panda's new goldfish., Woody Woodpecker struggles in his new job as a Pony Express rider, including a tussle with an indigenous bandit."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517130000 +0000" stop="20250517140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Piker's Peak, The Slick Chick, 3 Ring Wing-ding, Big Top Bunny, Fiesta Fiasco, Just Plane Beep, Broom-stick Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and Sam are in a race to see who can climb to the top of Schmatterhorn first and win 50,000 cronkites. , Foghorn Leghorn babysits a bad boy. , A hunter chases Cool Cat through all the acts in a circus. , Bugs becomes the star act of the circus. A jealous circus bear starts an ever-escalating stunt competition between the two. , Daffy gets word that the Mexican mice are throwing a party. To try and dampen things up, he builds a weather machine. , Wile E. Coyote learns of an "ACME War Surplus Sale" and orders a vintage World War I bi-plane to get the Road Runner. , Bugs makes a visit to Witch Hazel who is infatuated with her own ugliness and needs a rabbit for her stew... "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517140000 +0000" stop="20250517150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Iron Fist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>At the request of the Bosnian government, Count Draja is to be turned over for extradition. Learning of a plot to free the Count, Jim and Artie make plans to see that Draja reaches his destination. While Jim escorts Draja through 100 miles of no-man's land, they'll all meet up in Buffalo Springs - but there is the little matter of the $500,000 the Count hid somewhere in the U.S.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517150000 +0000" stop="20250517160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tobias Jones Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Adams allows two stowaways, Tobias Jones and his young friend, Midge, to stay with the train. But Tobias is in trouble because of his drinking, and things get worse when he's accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517160000 +0000" stop="20250517170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Legend Of A General: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barkleys refuse to give General Ruiz up for extradition to Mexico, even in exchange for Heath’s life. Instead, they embark on a plan to save both Heath and the general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517170000 +0000" stop="20250517173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Thoroughbreds</sub-title>
    <desc>"ck Portis comes to Dodge City and Matt is suspicious of him. Kitty sees him in a gunfight and claims she saw him draw first against two cowboys."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517173000 +0000" stop="20250517180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Stage Holdup</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three men hold up the stage Marshall Dillon and Chester are riding on. One of the men kills a passenger. In Dodge the Marshall recognizes the voice of one of the robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517180000 +0000" stop="20250517190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Trackers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man recently released from prison for bank robbery is accused of robbing the same Virginia City bank and gunning down a teller. The Cartwrights try to protect the accused man from a posse that intends to lynch him before his trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517190000 +0000" stop="20250517193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The High Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes the target of a vengeful mountaineer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517193000 +0000" stop="20250517200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend In Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself the unwilling companion of gunman Carl Avery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517200000 +0000" stop="20250517210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Wanderer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Michob, a peddler, comes out of a rain storm, bone dry. Things begin to go wrong and he is labeled a jinx.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517210000 +0000" stop="20250517213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Never Help The Devil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Doggie Kramer wins a gunfight, as the whole town he had been bullying watches, but ends up wounded. He needs Paladin to help him get out of town before the townspeople take their revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517213000 +0000" stop="20250517220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Angels Of Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A violent religious cult cast lots and it falls upon a young woman to act as its angel of vengeance. Her mission is to murder Josh Randall in retaliation for his killing their cult leader's son in a shootout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517220000 +0000" stop="20250518000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Saved By The Belle, Dizzy Pilots, If A Body Meets A Body, Fright Night, Scotched In Scotland, Pardon My Scotch</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are arrested for treason. , The Stooges are the Wrong brothers, three inventors trying to finish building an airplane they can sell to the army and thereby avoid the draft.  When their plane, the "Buzzard", turns out to be a flop, the boys are drafted into the army where they have trouble with a tough drill sergeant. , The Stooges are running the local drugstore and mix up a potion that a desperate businessman decides to sell as scotch.  , When Moe reads that Curly's rich uncle has died, and has left his estate to Curly, the boys go there to collect. They find that the uncle was murdered and his body and will are missing., The Stooges are managers of "Chopper", a beefy boxer, and they bet their bankroll on his next fight.  When a gangster tells them to have Chopper lose or they'll lose their lives, the boys decide to play along.  They try to soften Chopper up by feeding him rich food and having him spend time with their friend Kitty.  The fight gets canceled when Kitty dumps Chopper for his opponent and the two boxers engage in some pre-match fisticuffs that result in a broken hand for the opponent.  The Stooges think they've put one over on the gangsters, only to have the bad guys corner them in a deserted warehouse.  Instead of being rubbed out, the boys capture the crooks and get a reward. , Would be detectives, the Stooges get a job guarding a Scotch castle while the owner is away.  The servants are crooks intent on robbing the castle of its valuables.  Though they do their best to frighten the boys off, the Stooges prevail and expose the crooked goings-on. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518000000 +0000" stop="20250518023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ygor resurrects Frankenstein's monster and brings him to the original doctor's son, Ludwig, for help. Ludwig, obsessed with the idea of restoring the monster to full power, is unaware that his various associates all have different ideas about whose brain is to be transplanted into the monster's skull."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518023000 +0000" stop="20250518043000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Blair Witch Project</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three film students get more than bargained for when they investigate a legendary evil."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518043000 +0000" stop="20250518050000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Smack In The Middle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>As Batman tries to solve the Ridder's plot, he unwitting leads one of the Riddler's henchwomen, disguised as Robin, into the Batcave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518050000 +0000" stop="20250518060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Space Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The galactic showman, Farnum B, returns as the producer of the Miss Galaxy Beauty Pageant. He wants Judy to be in the contest, but she is not willing. However, Dr. Smith submits her anyways by forging her name to the contest roster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518060000 +0000" stop="20250518070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Saboteurs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Crane takes the flying sub on a deadly mission to destroy a secret computer used by the enemy to intercept manned Venus space probe capsules.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518070000 +0000" stop="20250518080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>On A Clear Night, You Can See Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant scientist develops a pair of infra-red goggles which lets him easily track the Earthlings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518080000 +0000" stop="20250518090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Rendezvous With Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug find themselves back in 1912 aboard the ill-fated Titanic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518090000 +0000" stop="20250518100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Storm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a hurricane mysterious avoids a church building, David investigates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518100000 +0000" stop="20250518110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Jackal</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matthew Star, a super-powered prince from outer space, must blend into high school while avoiding assassins sent to kill him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518110000 +0000" stop="20250518113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a freak accident, Screech can predict the future, an ability Zack uses to his advantage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518113000 +0000" stop="20250518120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Lisa Card   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Lisa splurges with her dad's credit card, she asks the Bayside gang to help get the money back before her dad discovers the shopping spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518120000 +0000" stop="20250518123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Election   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack finds out the Class President wins a trip to Washington, D.C., and campaigns hard against Jessie. But when the trip is canceled, he must campaign even harder to lose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518123000 +0000" stop="20250518130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing To The Max   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a dance contest is held at The Max, the gang splits off into pairs—Kelly and Slater, Zack and Jessie, and even Lisa and Screech!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518130000 +0000" stop="20250518133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Substitute   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The Bayside girls fall for a new substitute teacher, making the guys, especially Zack, jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518133000 +0000" stop="20250518140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Cream For A Day   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A zit threatens Kelly's attempt at homecoming queen, but Screech's secret cream may help—or cause disastrous effects!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518140000 +0000" stop="20250518143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Bobby pushes Peter out of the way of a falling ladder, Peter volunteers to be Bobby's slave for life, a situation Bobby takes advantage of. Meanwhile, the girls try to decide on a wallpaper for their room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518143000 +0000" stop="20250518150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Quarterback Sneak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia becomes involved with Jerry Rogers, a quarterback for the Fairview team. Greg immediately tells Marcia the only reason he's dating her is to get his playbook, a notion Marcia scoffs at, until Jerry actually does the deed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518150000 +0000" stop="20250518153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Guys Are</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to help Fonzie move on after his breakup with Ashley, Potsie, Chachi and Roger take him on a retreat to a singles resort. However, to get him to go, they tell him they're going to a sporting camp. When they arrive at the lake, Fonzie discovers what the resort is all about and says he's going to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518153000 +0000" stop="20250518160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Laverne And Shirley Go To Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In hopes of becoming a medical assistant, Shirley enrolls in night school and drags Laverne with her. There, they get mixed up with a nutty professor and accidentally destroy a skeleton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518160000 +0000" stop="20250518163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The New Mayor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and the new mayor are not on the same page in terms of Andy's style of managing Mayberry's sheriff's department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518163000 +0000" stop="20250518170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Diner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ricardos and the Mertzes buy a diner, name it "A Little Bit of Cuba" and go to work. Well, the Mertzes go to work; the Ricardos "greet." Not surprisingly, relations are soon strained. Can a food fight be far behind?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518170000 +0000" stop="20250518173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Bachelor-at-large</sub-title>
    <desc>"The news that Eddie has moved out of his parent's house and into an apartment of his own has June worried that Wally may be contemplating something similar. However, Wally gets a picture of just how "happy" Eddie is being on his own and it makes him think twice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518173000 +0000" stop="20250518180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Joins Record Club</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver wants to join a record club and asks Ward for the money to join. Fed up with Beaver constantly asking for money, Ward decides to put him on an allowance. However, Beaver is so thrilled with his records he disreguards the bills for them and quickly finds himself swamped with records, a rising bill and not enough allowance to pay for everything."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518180000 +0000" stop="20250518183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Crystal Gazers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny believes she has the power to predict the future, and she is set on doing whatever she needs to make her predictions come true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518183000 +0000" stop="20250518190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Private Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro continues his fantasy of being a double naught spy by getting an office at the bank. When two bank robbers arrive, who are interested in that office because it is above the vault, they make Jethro believe they are from London headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518190000 +0000" stop="20250518193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Wrongway Feldman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways are revisited by "Wrongway" Feldman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518193000 +0000" stop="20250518200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Matchmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Howell decides to engineer a romance between Gilligan and Mary Ann.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518200000 +0000" stop="20250518203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Ladies Choice  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama and Iola vie for the presidency of the Church Ladies League in a bitterly contested race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518203000 +0000" stop="20250518210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Talk  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Vint and Naomi start to think about having a baby, Mama decides to show them what having a baby is really like by bringing over a neighbor's particularly loud child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518210000 +0000" stop="20250518220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Crew Confessions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Isaac shocks the crew when he writes about them in a tell-all novel; a celebrity lookalike tries to convince a newfound romance that he isn't who she thinks he is; a reunited husband and wife share a deep secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518220000 +0000" stop="20250518223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Bachelors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie are left alone while Aunt Bee goes out of town. Peggy, Andy's new girlfriend, takes great delight in helping the boys handle things. Floyd warns Andy that Peggy is using her feminine wiles to "snare" him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518223000 +0000" stop="20250518230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Justin Cary- Toys</sub-title>
    <desc>"Eighties kid Justin Cary stares with Lisa the collection of vintage toys from his childhood that grew from a hobby into a full-time toy-dealing business. His fellow toy vendor John Davis appraises his hottest items, including McGyver and NeverEnding Story figures never available in the U.S., and a complete Masters of The Universe store display that may be the only one of its kind still around."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518230000 +0000" stop="20250518233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Kim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye operates on a five-year-old Korean boy, and Radar can't find his family. Henry plans to send him to the orphanage, and the camp enjoys his company while they can. Trapper decides to adopt him after consulting his wife, and has to rescue him after he wanders into the minefield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250518233000 +0000" stop="20250519000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>L.i.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporal Walker is being sent home, and he wants to marry his Korean girl so she and their baby can return with him. CID sends Lt Willis to investigate, but when he refuses Hawkeye and Trapper frame him. Hawkeye is upset that a nurse he was pursuing does not approve of the marriage between "a gook" and "one of us."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519000000 +0000" stop="20250519003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Comes Into Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike comes into some money when his Uncle Alex dies and leaves him $275. Archie tries to persuade Mike into giving the money to him for room and board, but Mike would rather give it to George McGovern's presidential campaign. This sparks a big feud, leading to a dinner separation: Gloria and Mike buy and cook their own food while Edith and Archie do the same.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519003000 +0000" stop="20250519010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Appendix</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Archie and Gloria come home in bad moods after a hard day's work. This leads to yet another argument over women's liberation. Meanwhile, Mike has been having a pain in the side and the doctor tells him that he needs to have an appendectomy. This leads Archie and Gloria's argument to the proficiency of women doctors. Mike would rather have a more expensive male doctor rather than a cheaper woman doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519010000 +0000" stop="20250519013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Winning Ticket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith finds some old lottery tickets that she has totally forgotten about, Archie hits the roof claiming she was wasting money. However, Archie's attitude quickly changes when the family discovers that one of the tickets is a winner, but there is a catch: Edith claims the tickets don't belong to her, but belong to George Jefferson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519013000 +0000" stop="20250519020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Bowling Team</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home in a fantastic mood for a change and it's all because he has the chance to possibly join a prestigious bowling team, the Cannonballers. After waiting six years, it seems that there is finally a vacancy on the team and Archie is planning to try out, even though the team practices discrimination in admitting members.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519020000 +0000" stop="20250519023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Trini Lopez And Nanette Fabray</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Trini Lopez and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/09/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519023000 +0000" stop="20250519030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jonathan Winters And Eddie Albert</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Jonathan Winters and Eddie Albert. Originally aired on 09/25/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519030000 +0000" stop="20250519033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>There's No Sale Like Wholesale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob gets more than he bargained for when he buys a wholesale coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519033000 +0000" stop="20250519040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Coast To Coast Big Mouth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura accidently reveals that Alan Brady is bald on live TV!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519040000 +0000" stop="20250519043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Opportunity Knock But</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Ed play pool with Ralph's boss and Ed gets a job at the bus company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519043000 +0000" stop="20250519050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Hundred Yards Over The Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1847 an American pioneer sets out to find medicine for his dying son—and stumbles into modern-day New Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519050000 +0000" stop="20250519060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Death And The Joyful Woman  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The secretary of a wine baron is driven to murder when her dream of marrying the man is shattered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519060000 +0000" stop="20250519070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Presidente Rojas plans to give a speech to the U.S. Congress. Meanwhile, his Chief of Internal Security Ferrar is planning a takeover and sends an assassin known only as Plato to kill the Presidente before he gives his speech.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519070000 +0000" stop="20250519080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Uncle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After finding refuge in an orphanage, Kimble becomes entwined in the plight of a troubled teenage boy who passes him off as his uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519080000 +0000" stop="20250519090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Lester</sub-title>
    <desc>"The nude body of a murdered college girl sends Harry Orwell on the trail of a psychotic killer!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519090000 +0000" stop="20250519093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519093000 +0000" stop="20250519100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519100000 +0000" stop="20250519103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 92 -- Tell Him He Pushed Back A Little Too Hard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to repeated calls about an argument between two men and their wives over a boat they co-own. The feud escalates and ends with a fatal conclusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519103000 +0000" stop="20250519110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 22: So This Little Guy Goes Into This Bar, And...</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fur burglary, a family fight and a loud party."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519110000 +0000" stop="20250519120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill And Toony Buy A Castle</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519120000 +0000" stop="20250519123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Car Accident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for the weekend and Wally asks to borrow Ward's new car to go to a dance. Although hesitant, Ward finally gives in and lets him take it. However, after the dance, Lumpy runs into some car trouble which results in Wally smashing the headlight on the car. Wally is now faced with having it repaired and paying for it himself and trying to find a way to break it gently to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519123000 +0000" stop="20250519130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Sheep Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>At school, Beaver gets into an argument with a girl who retaliates by making fun of Beaver's hair, calling him a sheepdog. Incredibly self-concious, Beaver goes out to the store and buys different hairsprays and gels to try to improve his hairdo. He doesn't get the reaction he was expecting when he tries his new hairdo out on his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519130000 +0000" stop="20250519140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Guilty Clients</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lola and Jeff Bronson are going through a divorce and can't wait to be rid of each other—until Bill Ryder sabotages Jeff's business and makes a play for Lola. When Ryder is found dead, Jeff and Lola are the two prime suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519140000 +0000" stop="20250519150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Judge  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock accepts the pro bono case of Kevin Meredith, a young man accused of murdering his lover, who, as Matlock discovers, had a shocking secret. In order to capture the real killer, Matlock must end a long-time friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519150000 +0000" stop="20250519160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Ruda's Awakening</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's Aunt Ruda is the only witness to a struggle between Bubba and a young robbery suspect that ends in the young man’s death. But her prejudice against the police -- and Virgil clouds her memory of the incident. Bubba returns to Los Angeles to testify at a murder trial and is reunited with Pat Day as they try to protect Mike from killers sent to prevent him from testifying.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519160000 +0000" stop="20250519170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Beguiled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy encounters a sassy, spoiled, selfish gal whose selfish ways cause problems for John Boy and even for Jim Bob's friend</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519170000 +0000" stop="20250519173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Rifle</sub-title>
    <desc>"Andy Spangler finds the body of Will Gibbs and suspects Ben Tiple of the murder. But Tiple is a good friend of Matt's and Ben denies murdering Gibbs. Matt tries to help Ben out."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519173000 +0000" stop="20250519180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Land Deal</sub-title>
    <desc>"A man tries to swindle a group of immigrants with the promise of railroad land and then tries to run off with the wife of one the immigrants."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519180000 +0000" stop="20250519190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Girl Named George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Can a photograph lie? The Cartwrights and Candy have to determine this when lawyer Cato Troxell uses a photograph as an alibi to prove that he didn't kill a Virginia City judge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519190000 +0000" stop="20250519193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Skull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for escape after he's captured by outlaws while seeking help for an injured Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519193000 +0000" stop="20250519200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Queen-to-be of France hides out in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519200000 +0000" stop="20250519210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Liam Fitzmorgan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Liam Fitzmorgan has come from Ireland on a mission to kill an informer he believes is traveling with the train. However, his mission is complicated when he falls in love with his target's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519210000 +0000" stop="20250519220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>School Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A new trainee appears to be lacking in confidence; a bookcase falls on an elderly gentleman searching for a book; a baseball player is injured; an ambulance is hit by a car; a boy's chemistry set explodes in his face; students play a practical joke on a sleeping man; and a man is injured at a junkyard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519220000 +0000" stop="20250519223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Of Henry Blake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Majors Houlihan and Burns press charges against Colonel Blake to get him arrested and put Frank in charge. They also put Hawkeye and Trapper under arrest so that they can't help Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519223000 +0000" stop="20250519230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad... Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Once more Hawkeye writes home to his father: the doctors operate on a soldier with a grenade shot into his body; Hawkeye and Trapper color the skin of a racist patient, who demanded the right color blood, while he is asleep; Henry gets a movie of his daughter's birthday from home; the officers hold the monthly staff meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519230000 +0000" stop="20250519233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A lone sniper has the 4077th pinned down—including Radar and Henry in the shower. The poor boy thinks he's firing on McArthur's headquarters, and a chopper finally comes by and wounds him with gunfire from above, ending the siege. Hawkeye walks out to into the bush to tend to the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250519233000 +0000" stop="20250520000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Carry On Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp succumbs to the Asian flu, except for Hawkeye and Margaret, who have to do everything themselves. As the others start to recover, Hawkeye falls ill but he still manages to operate when wounded arrive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520000000 +0000" stop="20250520003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes upset when Opie contributes a measly three cents to the Underprivileged Children's drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520003000 +0000" stop="20250520010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Mcbeevee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While walking through the woods, Opie meets Mr. McBeevee, a man who, Opie claims, "lives in the trees" and "jingles when he walks." Andy eventually learns that Opie's new friend works for the telephone company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520010000 +0000" stop="20250520013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Double Naught Jethro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro decides to give up his dream of becoming a brain surgeon to try his luck at the spy business. Meanwhile, The Banker’s Convention is going on, including the beauty contest for Most Beautiful Bank Employee, and Drysdale could lose because of Mr. Cushing’s contestant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520013000 +0000" stop="20250520020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit From Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee comes for a visit and strongly objects to Sgt. Carter's attitude towards poor Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520020000 +0000" stop="20250520023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Adolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys plan to destroy a gun emplacement so the Allies can attack on Hitler's birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520023000 +0000" stop="20250520030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Rush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>French gold has been stolen by the Nazis. Hogan convinces Klink to have it brought to Stalag 13 so the prisoners can steal it back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520030000 +0000" stop="20250520033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball, Tim Conway, And Gloria Loring</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball, Tim Conway, and Gloria Loring. Originally aired on 10/02/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520033000 +0000" stop="20250520043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crimson Kiss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fay Allison is getting married in a few days to Dane Grover. Her roommate, Anita Bonsal, is having a clandestine affair with a married man, Carver Clement. When Aunt Louise arrives early one morning to see Fay, she finds Fay and Anita both unconscious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520043500 +0000" stop="20250520050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Hocus-pocus And Frisby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A loud-mouthed braggart's boasts attract the attention of aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520050500 +0000" stop="20250520053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Revenge fuels a husband looking for the man who raped his wife</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520053500 +0000" stop="20250520060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A man decides to demonstrate to his new girlfriend how he gets his kicks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520060500 +0000" stop="20250520070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Eagles Sometimes Can't Fly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An African-American and a Native American witness a gunfight. When the police accuse them of intentional murder, they panic and flee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520070500 +0000" stop="20250520080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Chain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The death of a bank manager's mistress leads Cannon into a case of murder and betrayal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520080500 +0000" stop="20250520090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Taste For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man's long-range plans clash with his girlfriend's personal ambition, leading them to commit murder out of greed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520090000 +0000" stop="20250520093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520093000 +0000" stop="20250520100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520100000 +0000" stop="20250520103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 15 -- Exactly One Hundred Yards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On their day off, Malloy and Reed agree to give a talk to a group of fifth grade students, and then offer to let the kids watch them train for the California Police Olympics. But when the tires of their patrol car are slashed and a stopwatch goes missing out of reed's car, the two officers start to suspect one of the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520103000 +0000" stop="20250520110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 153 -- Find Me A Needle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for the "Mulholland Mauler," who has raped six female hitchhikers and left them for dead. They quickly make an arrest of a likely suspect and take him to the location of an abandoned vehicle, after learning its owner never made it to her destination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520110000 +0000" stop="20250520120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Pop Life</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520120000 +0000" stop="20250520123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During one of his football team's games, Beaver is sent in and scores the winning touchdown, which results in a picture in the paper. Soon, Beaver finds himself swamped with attention and quickly lets it goes to his head. He begins acting like he's better than everyone and begins to alienate Gilbert, Whitey and Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520123000 +0000" stop="20250520130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Autobiography</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been given an assignment in which he must write a autobiography for class but isn't sure about his abilities at writing. So, he convinces a girl, who likes him, to write it for him. When she discovers that he is merely using her, she writes an outrageous life story and hands it in, causing embarrassment for Beaver when the teacher reads it in class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520130000 +0000" stop="20250520140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tragic Trophy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hollywood wheeler-dealer is in desperate need of cash and has gotten himself in some trouble with the ladies. But before things can get any worse, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520140000 +0000" stop="20250520150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Affair (aka The Maid)  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents a maid accused of killing her employer at the request of the man's widow. The request is a little odd, but it seems the widow wants everyone to know exactly what kind of man her husband was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520150000 +0000" stop="20250520160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Unfinished Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to L.A. to testify in an organized-crime trial and to safeguard the key witness---a young boy (Mike Chin) who saw a mobster commit a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520160000 +0000" stop="20250520170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Caretakers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandpa and Grandma feel left out and move to house-sit for for a neighbor</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520170000 +0000" stop="20250520173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Lynching Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bob Gringle and Ed Shelby lynch Hank Blenis and take his horse. Charlie Drain doesn't think Matt is doing a good enough job trying to find the lynchers and decides to do it himself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520173000 +0000" stop="20250520180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>How To Kill A Friend</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ben Corden and Harry Duggan try to bribe Matt so they can run a crooked game. When the Marshall refuses they hire an old friend of Matt's (Toque Morlan) to kill him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520180000 +0000" stop="20250520190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Thirteenth Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The area ranchers are losing many cattle to rustlers, so they hire Marcus Alley to help discover the thieves' identities. However, his methods raise eyebrows as accused rustlers begin winding up dead instead of in custody.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520190000 +0000" stop="20250520193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gunfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah has an infamous outlaw, Charlie Gordo, in his jail waiting for the U.S. marshal from Denver to take Gordo to the Yuma prison for hanging. With the arrival of the stage, Micah finds that the lawman has been killed, and he has to look to his friends to defend the jail from Gordo's gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520193000 +0000" stop="20250520200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Quiet Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas' old Army pal settles in North Fork with his deaf daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520200000 +0000" stop="20250520210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctor Willoughby Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Concerned by one of the passengers on the wagon train, a woman doctor tries to help even though she's hampered by the fact that everyone shuns her. Later, an indian chief needs doctoring, but he and his tribe don't believe in female medicine men either.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520210000 +0000" stop="20250520220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Professor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man shows signs of schizophrenia for no apparent reason and the Secret Service won't give any clues. Roy has an admirer, yet John accuses him of having no charisma. The paramedics respond to a false alarm on a fireboat, and end up saving the victim of a plane crash; they also deliver a premature baby and rescue a man threatening to jump off a tall building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520220000 +0000" stop="20250520223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520223000 +0000" stop="20250520230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520230000 +0000" stop="20250520233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250520233000 +0000" stop="20250521000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521000000 +0000" stop="20250521003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Those Gossipin' Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Andy teases the fairer sex about gossiping, Aunt Bee pulls a prank to prove that men are gossips, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521003000 +0000" stop="20250521010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Briscoe Declares For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Briscoe Darling becomes obsessed with Aunt Bee after hearing her recite a poem, going as far as to kidnap her and bring her back to his shack in the hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521010000 +0000" stop="20250521013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is still working on being a 007 spy, though it is annoying Granny. And Elly has been crowned Queen of the Bankers Ball. Mr. Cushing is not happy about this though, as he wanted his contestant to win. Because Jethro is having more fun at Cushing’s bank, he tries to get Jed to transfer his money to the Merchant’s Bank. And Cushing sees this opportunity and tries to get that gorgeous Clampett account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521013000 +0000" stop="20250521020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Joins The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing Gomer's stories about how nice Sgt. Carter is, Opie Taylor runs away from Mayberry to join Gomer in the Marines. Ron Howard guest stars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521020000 +0000" stop="20250521023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Zolle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to detain a German general at camp for 24 hours to allow the Allies to amass troops. Things get complicated when a Gestapo officer comes in search of the reason for Klink's perfect record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521023000 +0000" stop="20250521030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes A Thief... Sometimes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of underground operatives that Hogan and his team begin working with is actually a group lead by a Gestapo captain who's set on capturing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521030000 +0000" stop="20250521033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Diahann Carroll, Smothers Brothers, And Richard Kiely</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Diahann Carroll, Smothers Brothers, and Richard Kiely. Originally aired on 10/23/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521033000 +0000" stop="20250521043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Malicious Mariner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>During a terrible storm at sea, First Officer Jerry Griffin dumps a million dollars worth of goods overboard to lessen the chances of his cargo freighter sinking. Once on shore, Jerry is hauled before a maritime court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521043500 +0000" stop="20250521050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Rip Van Winkle Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves put themselves into suspended animation for 100 years after hiding a million dollars worth of gold bars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521050500 +0000" stop="20250521053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One Grave Too Many</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is ridden with guilt after he takes a wallet from a heart attack victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521053500 +0000" stop="20250521060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Crime For Mothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic woman threatens to take her daughter from the guardianship of her foster parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521060500 +0000" stop="20250521070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Color Her Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend and colleague of Joe Mannix has been murdered. The lawyer of the arrested suspect asks Mannix to find an important witness for the defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521070500 +0000" stop="20250521080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Call Unicorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon goes undercover as a truck driver to investigate a series of hijackings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521080500 +0000" stop="20250521090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Burial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hires Barnaby to find her missing husband and the detective's investigation uncovers bigamy, blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521090000 +0000" stop="20250521093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521093000 +0000" stop="20250521100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521100000 +0000" stop="20250521103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 52 -- Good Cop: Handle With Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see a man passed out in an alley and stop to lend assistance, deliver bad news to a young wife, apprehend a mentally ill man who then becomes uncontrollably violent in their patrol car, and respond to a robbery that needlessly becomes a tragedy. All along the way the officers have their every move second guessed by a pair of young, unethical freelance journalists who are determined to document police brutality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521103000 +0000" stop="20250521110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521110000 +0000" stop="20250521120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Toons It Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill attempts to indulge in some mindful relaxation techniques despite Toony's constant interruptions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521120000 +0000" stop="20250521123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Party Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks June and Ward if he could have a party and with some prodding, Wally finally gets their permission. June quickly begins the plans and Beaver gets a look at the guest list and quickly finds that he's not invited. For revenge, Beaver decides to sabotage Wally's party with a variety of gags that he bought at a magic shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521123000 +0000" stop="20250521130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Mustache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's on-again off-again girlfriend, Julie Foster, seems to have thrown him over for a new guy in school who just happens to have a mustache. Wally's ego is bruised when Eddie tells him that Julie thinks he's naive and immature. This is the last straw and Wally decides to grow a mustache, much to the dismay of his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521130000 +0000" stop="20250521140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Reckless Rockhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a businessman responsible for decimating a local mining business returns to town, it is not long before he is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521140000 +0000" stop="20250521150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Seduction, The (aka The Quaterback)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock is hired to defend Brad Bingham, an aging football star with a reputation as a womanizer who was about to be cut from the team. Charlene is resistant to her father's choice, as she believes everything the tabloids have to say about Brad...not only that, but years earlier, he'd had a brief relationship with her friend Ellen Hawley, who had tried to kill herself after they broke up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521150000 +0000" stop="20250521160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The More Things Change</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his business partner and frames the man's illegitimate daughter for the crime in an attempt to gain the man's business and his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521160000 +0000" stop="20250521170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A cousin who is named after Olivia visits</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521170000 +0000" stop="20250521173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Grass</sub-title>
    <desc>"Joe Carter and Earl Brant try scaring Harry Pope pretending to be Indians. Pope defends himself killing Carter so their boss Ned Curry wants revenge."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521173000 +0000" stop="20250521180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Cast</sub-title>
    <desc>"Shell Tucker is normally a friendly and peaceful sort of a man. When Shell Tucker's wife swallows a nail, Shell's son (Rufe Tucker) sends for Doc Adams; however, Doc is unable to save Mrs. Tucker from this illness. Since Matt knows that Shell Tucker dislikes Doctors, Matt thinks Shell might try and take the death of his wife out on Doc Adams."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521180000 +0000" stop="20250521190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Burning Sky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A sadistic rancher livid over his son's friendship with a Sioux woman goes to vicious extremes to keep the two apart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521190000 +0000" stop="20250521193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sporting Chance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An Englishman arrives with a custom-made rifle—and a plan to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521193000 +0000" stop="20250521200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Young Man's Fancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The pangs of first love are painful for Mark: the object of his affections has eyes for another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521200000 +0000" stop="20250521210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bije Wilcox Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After offering a $5,000 reward to anyone who can track down his brother, a man gets a response from someone who walks through an indian party that's pinning down the wagon train. What he finds is not what he expected.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521210000 +0000" stop="20250521220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>John tries to convince Roy he has tonsillitis. An old flame of Dixie's, who is now a famous actor, is admitted to Rampart. Two kids are trapped on top of a gas tank; a girl's college lacrosse game turns violent; Boot has surgery to remove a tick; Dr. Early deals with a hypochondriac. Chet is injured during a rescue and is roomed with Roy, who has had his tonsils removed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521220000 +0000" stop="20250521223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521223000 +0000" stop="20250521230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521230000 +0000" stop="20250521233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250521233000 +0000" stop="20250522000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522000000 +0000" stop="20250522003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522003000 +0000" stop="20250522010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gives Gomer a ticket for making an illegal U-turn, but then when Barney does it, Gomer has no choice but to make a citizen's arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522010000 +0000" stop="20250522013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale's Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny demands to see her money in cash, and Drysdale tries to talk her out of it. He fails and upsets the Clampetts by accidentally throwing magazines at them, which were really aimed at his wife and her dog. He tries to make things better by showing Granny what a million dollars looks like to turn her off from the idea, but ends up throwing more stuff at her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522013000 +0000" stop="20250522020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit From Cousin Goober</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Goober pays Gomer a surprise visit. Goober says he's through working at the filling station and wants to give the Marines a try for a week to see if he likes it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522020000 +0000" stop="20250522023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522023000 +0000" stop="20250522030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522030000 +0000" stop="20250522033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jack Palance And Liza Minnelli</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Jack Palance and Liza Minnelli. Originally aired on 02/05/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522033000 +0000" stop="20250522043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crying Comedian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Comic Charlie Hatch learns that the woman he loved and lost, Anne Gilrain, has escaped from a sanitarium to which she was forced to commit herself by her husband, Tom. When Tom Gilrain is murdered, Charlie is afraid that Anne did the deed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522043500 +0000" stop="20250522050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A talkative man takes a $500,000 offer to keep silent for a year.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522050500 +0000" stop="20250522053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Where Beauty Lies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman strives to keep her brother from running her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522053500 +0000" stop="20250522060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Sorcerer's Apprentice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfaithful woman plans to get rid of her husband with the help of a stranded young man. (This episode was deemed too horrifying by a sponsor and was not broadcast until the series was sold into syndication.)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522060500 +0000" stop="20250522070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Return To Summer Grove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>At a request of a friend, Mannix returns to his hometown, Summer Grove. His friend is not only seriously ill, he also is a murder suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522070500 +0000" stop="20250522080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Country Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired to investigate when a famous singer is killed in a plane crash. But for some reason, his family is not cooperating and wants the case closed quickly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522080500 +0000" stop="20250522090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An art collector's wife plots to steal one of his paintings, but her plan is complicated by her husband's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522090000 +0000" stop="20250522093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522093000 +0000" stop="20250522100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522100000 +0000" stop="20250522103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522103000 +0000" stop="20250522110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522110000 +0000" stop="20250522120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Page From The Digest</sub-title>
    <desc>"A look back at parenting trends of the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522120000 +0000" stop="20250522123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Buys A Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend has a car for sale and Wally is interested; however, Ward and June are, as usual, hesitant about the whole thing. Ward decides to give in to Wally and allow him to buy the used car, with the condition that he inspect it first. Ward quickly finds problems with the car and he helps Wally look elsewhere giving Wally tips on the process of used car shopping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522123000 +0000" stop="20250522130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>More Blessed To Give</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert go to a carnival and Beaver surprisingly wins a fourteen caret gold locket in one of the carnival games. Beaver thinks about giving it to June but, thanks to Gilbert, decides to give it to a girl whom he has a crush on. However, soon it becomes apparent that this was a mistake when the girl's parents discover Beaver's gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522130000 +0000" stop="20250522140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Latent Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A man left unhinged by his wife's affair has been acting out in very strange ways, even attempting to rob a bank in his despair. And when his wife ends up murdered, he is the natural suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522140000 +0000" stop="20250522150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Don: Part 1  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents Nicholas Baron, a well-known mobster who has been accused of murdering a rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522150000 +0000" stop="20250522160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet, Sweet Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The lyrics to a blues song recall a murder that happened 50 years earlier. The victim - Sweet's grandfather. And the only people left with the answers are the bluesman who wrote the song and a retired sheriff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522160000 +0000" stop="20250522170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Choice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>John wants to expand the mill and call it Walton and Sons, but Jason wants to study music</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522170000 +0000" stop="20250522173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Robber Bridegroom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jack Fitch, a down on his luck rancher, robs the stage and kidnaps Laura. They fall in love but Laura's fiance wants Jack killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522173000 +0000" stop="20250522180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snakebite</sub-title>
    <desc>"When two town troublemakers kill Poney Thompson's dog , Poney goes after the two men. When one of the men who shot and killed Poney's Dog is found dead, Matt and Chester suspect that Poney killed the man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522180000 +0000" stop="20250522190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Salt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young woman inherits her late father's salt mine, a greedy rancher wants to buy all the salt for himself. Ben, standing for the smaller ranchers who cannot afford to pay the heiress' prices, bids against the wealthy rancher to get a fair price for all.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522190000 +0000" stop="20250522193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Salinas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Banker Hamilton is closing up for the day when Rudy Gray persuades him to stay open for one more transaction—a withdrawal at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522193000 +0000" stop="20250522200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Two Ounces Of Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sammy Davis Jr. stars as Tip Corey, son of a man allegedly murdered in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522200000 +0000" stop="20250522210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Millie Davis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Millie Davis reluctantly takes in an orphaned baby girl. Eight years later the girl's grandmother arrives to retrieve her. But Millie doesn't want to give up the child, so she claims that she and Flint are the parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522210000 +0000" stop="20250522220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Honest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A gas explosion results from a white lie, prompting Johnny to go on an honesty kick. At the hospital, doctors work to save a boy who is inexplicably choking to death. In the field, the paramedics rescue a teenage boy injured in a dive off a roof, and a baby and his blind grandfather trapped in a burning house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522220000 +0000" stop="20250522223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As You Were</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While there are no casualties, Hawkeye and Trapper crate up Frank while he sleeps and receive gorilla suits through the mail. Henry gets a tan and gives another sex orientation lecture. When the wounded start pouring in again, their own side shells the camp, hitting the generator, and Radar tries to get through to tell someone to stop the shelling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522223000 +0000" stop="20250522230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The supply lines to the camp are cut. Radar, the housing officer, starts doubling people up to save fuel and Klinger is thrown out of the nurse's tent. People start burning everything to stay warm while Frank wears his heated socks. The toilet paper supply is worst hit, and then wounded start arriving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522230000 +0000" stop="20250522233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Burns tries to slap a dishonorable discharge on a decorated soldier who admits to being a homosexual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250522233000 +0000" stop="20250523000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a new batch of mail leaves Trapper depressed, and thinking of desertion, despite Hawkeye's efforts to dissuade him. Meanwhile, Hawkeye learns that he has successfully tricked Frank into buying stocks in a fictitious company, Pioneer Aviation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523000000 +0000" stop="20250523003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Deputy Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has been writing letters to his brother and sister-in-law for some time on courthouse stationary. Because of this, they have come to believe that he is a deputy, something they expect to see on their upcoming visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523003000 +0000" stop="20250523010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523010000 +0000" stop="20250523013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampett money keeps rolling in as more oil is discovered on their land. And Mr. Brewster is coming out to marry his fiancée, Edythe. Granny is planning to go back home to the hills, but Jed decides to put up the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523013000 +0000" stop="20250523020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Goes Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer goes home to Mayberry and becomes involved in the search for the robber who held up Goober's gas station.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523020000 +0000" stop="20250523023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The 43rd, A Moving Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Plans to destroy an anti-aircraft battery are upset by Klink's new executive officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523023000 +0000" stop="20250523030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523030000 +0000" stop="20250523033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Dick Chamberlain, Gloria Loring, And Kay Medford</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Dick Chamberlain, Gloria Loring, and Kay Medford. Originally aired on 11/13/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523033000 +0000" stop="20250523043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Meddling Medium</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>On the case of a phony psychic who met with a grisly death, Mason devises a fantastic demonstration to prove his client innocent and expose the real culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523043500 +0000" stop="20250523050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapped in a recurring nightmare, a man tries to persuade those who are sentencing him to death that the whole scenario is not real.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523050500 +0000" stop="20250523053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Premonition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A pianist returns to his home town, hoping to mend a broken relationship with his father, and instead finds mystery and foreboding in everything he encounters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523053500 +0000" stop="20250523060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Triggers In Leash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Maggie, a restaurant owner, tries to prevent a duel between two customers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523060500 +0000" stop="20250523070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Haughty actor Mitch Cantrell is not exactly loved by his colleagues. When at a film shoot, a murder attempt is made on him, and it is soon up to Mannix to protect the obnoxious actor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523070500 +0000" stop="20250523080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Scream Of Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Charles Lassiter has been kidnapped and the crime seems to be an inside job. But when Charles escapes, he must be silenced before he can reveal who the kidnapper was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523080500 +0000" stop="20250523090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Heat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A father willing to do anything for his son to be on the Olympic swimming team gets himself involved in a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250523090000 +0000" stop="20250523093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
