<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712053500 +0000" stop="20250712060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Crime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous criminologist discovers that he has sent an innocent man to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712060500 +0000" stop="20250712070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>What Happened To Sunday?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix can't recall the events of the past 24 hours—other than a haunting memory of a little girl falling from a balcony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712070500 +0000" stop="20250712080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer was murdered. His latest book would deal with the biography of an industrialist. Cannon must protect the co-author and investigate the activities of the industrialist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712080500 +0000" stop="20250712090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Wife Beater, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a vicious husband who beats his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712090000 +0000" stop="20250712093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>My Dog The Actor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The family has a potential star in their midst. Billy Jo's dog is named as one of five finalists in a contest to be on a television dog food commercial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712093000 +0000" stop="20250712100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Buffalo Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe schemes to scam British sportsmen by bringing a buffalo to the Shady Rest and telling them it's a hunting lodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712100000 +0000" stop="20250712103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Collard Greens An' Fatback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is cooking collard greens and fat back for the Spring Collard Festival, just as the Drysdales are planning to sell their house to move into the house on the other side of the Clampetts. As the possible buyer, Pat Boone, is touring the house, he smells an unusual odor, which Mrs. Drysdale covers as orchid fertilizer. But Boone, who comes from Tennessee, knows it is collard greens and fat back and heads to the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712103000 +0000" stop="20250712110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Back To The Hills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is afraid of a mountain lion she sees in her root cellar, and Elly May reveals it is hers. But after reading the paper and seeing that Elverna Bradshaw’s daughter is getting married, Granny tells Jed they need to go home and return to the Hills to get Elly married first. As Granny is planning the trip home, Jethro reveals he is going to college, as Jed is unsuccessfully trying to have breakfast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712110000 +0000" stop="20250712113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Wood-peckin’, I Likes Babies And Infinks, Too Weak To Work</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye tangles with a tough woodpecker., Popeye's pal Swee'pea causes consternation when Olive Oyl is unable to stop him from crying and she calls upon the sailor man to help., Bluto thinks he needs a complete rest; Popeye, however, soon teaches him that honest toil is best as he puts him through a workout in a rest hospital."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712113000 +0000" stop="20250712120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Just Ducky, Bear That Wasn't, Purr-chance To Dream</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a duckling becomes separated from his mama duck, Jerry rescues the duckling from a hungry Tom., A bear settling down for a long winter hibernation ends up sleeping for a very long time and awakens to find out that mankind has progressed into the industrial age., Tom isn't sleeping well and keeps having nightmares about getting beat up by a bulldog."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712120000 +0000" stop="20250712130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>All Hams On Deck, St. Moritz Blitz, The Un-handy Man, Coo Coo Nuts, The Flying Turtle, Bungling Builder, Chilly's Hideaway, Niagara Fools</sub-title>
    <desc>"Captain Blah kidnaps Woody so his treasure can remain hidden., Smedley has to stop Chilly from cutting ice fishing holes in a skating rink., Charlie tries to build an automatic garage door opener., Woody is stranded on an island with a hungry castaway that likes woodpeckers., A Foolish Fable Cartoon. Herman the Turtle tries everything to learn how to fly only to get killed in the processs and turned into an angel with wings., Junior and Charlie attempt to build Bessie a sewing room themselves, and it doesn't go well., Smedley tries to evict Chilly Willy from Colonel Pot's mountain home., A guide at Niagra falls tries to stop Woody from going over the falls in a barrel, only to take the trip accidentally himself five times."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712130000 +0000" stop="20250712140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Now Hare This, The Prize Pest, Strangled Eggs, Devil's Feud Cake, Chimp And Zee, Beep Prepared, Forward March Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"In this parody of Little Red Riding Hood and Goldilocks, Bugs faces off against a big bad wolf., Porky won a radio quiz show contest, and his prize is Daffy popping out of a cake. , Foghorn Leghorn is completely out of food. To survive the long winter, Foghorn decides to court Miss Prissy. , Yosemite Sam robs a bank and hijacks a plane. He then jumps out of the plane without a parachute and ends up in Hell. He makes a pact with the Devil to catch Bugs and the Devil sends him through time, but Sam can never seem to get him. , Chimp and Zee must avoid capture from a hunter looking for exotic animals. , Wile E. Coyote chases the Road runner in this classic., Bug gets accidentally drafted into the military. It soon becomes clear that a rabbit does not belong in a man's army considering how much of catastrophe-causer he is. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712140000 +0000" stop="20250712150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Amnesiac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A stagecoach carrying the western states' entire supply of smallpox vaccine is attacked and the drug stolen. Furman Crotty, a convicted criminal serving time in Leavenworth, is demanding his release from jail with a full pardon and a ransom for the safe return of the drug. While Jim, injured in the attack on the stage, struggles with amnesia, Artemus tries to find both his friend and the drug before a full-scale epidemic hits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712150000 +0000" stop="20250712160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lita Foladaire Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Never having met Lita Foladaire, Major Adams learns a lot about her past, the town she grew up in, the people who loved her and, most importantly, what happened to her surrounded by those same people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712160000 +0000" stop="20250712170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Iron Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick and Heath are arrested by a corrupt sheriff and sent to a road-gang prison. When the warden learns that the two prisoners are of the “California Barkleys,” he plans to tempt Nick into leading a breakout so he can legally shoot the brothers outside the wire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712170000 +0000" stop="20250712173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Potshot</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hutch Dawkins sets off firecrackers in front of the Long Branch. Chester gets shot by a man hiding in the alley. Matt thinks its bank robbers trying to get him. Matt gets the robbers but they didn’t shoot Chester. Kitty thinks Hutch might have shot Chester."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712173000 +0000" stop="20250712180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Faces</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tilda and Tom Cook come to Dodge. Ed Ivers and Varden start trouble with Tom at the Long Branch. Tom is going to face Ivers in a gunfight until Tilda tells Tom the truth about her past. Ivers eggs Tom into a fight anyway."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712180000 +0000" stop="20250712190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Fence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>While Ben and Hoss visit an old friend to negotiate the purchase of a mine, former Confederate soldiers arrive wanting to exact revenge on the Cartwrights' friend for starving POWs during the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712190000 +0000" stop="20250712193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas makes a life-or-death decision when Micah is held hostage and the kidnappers demand the release of a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712193000 +0000" stop="20250712200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to do a good deed for the old town drunk but it backfires when the drunk's son believes he inherited Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712200000 +0000" stop="20250712210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Gilded Goddess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy's old acquaintance, Louise Temple, is on the run for killing a sheriff. She ran the Temple Of Gold gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712210000 +0000" stop="20250712213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Ella West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The promoter of a wild west show asks Paladin for help taming down a very wild and famous female sharpshooter and show her how to act like a lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712213000 +0000" stop="20250712220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Estralita</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Randall rescues Jake Pringle from a lynch mob's rope, he learns he's not the only one with an interest in keeping the killer alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250712220000 +0000" stop="20250713000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Punch Drunks, Disorder In The Court, Grips, Grunts And Groans, Hot Ice, Flagpole Jitters, Pain In The Pullman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Moe is a boxing promoter looking for a good fighter.  , The Stooges are witnesses at a trial where their friend, a dancer at a nightclub where they are musicians, is accused of murder.   , All aboard for non-stop hilarity! The Stooges and their pet monkey join a traveling vaudville troupe, making for a very bumpy ride. , The Stooges become trainers of "Bustoff", a champion wrestler.  The big boss has a lot of money bet on Bustoff and orders the boys to take good care of him.  Instead they accidentally knock him out and Curly must disguises himself as Bustoff and wrestle in his place.  The match doesn't go very well until Curly smells "Wild Hyacinth" perfume on a lady fan at ringside.  This drives him crazy and he knocks out his opponent and half the people in the stadium. , The Stooges apply for job as 'Yard Men' at Scotland Yard, thinking they'll become detectives, but instead wind up as gardeners.  When they accidentally see a memo about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The bad guys want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla. , The Stooges are taking care of their invalid friend Mary who is confined to wheelchair.  At their jobs in a theater, where they hope to earn money for an operation for Mary, they witness a hypnotist, doing his act.  The Stooges become subjects for his show and are hypnotized into walking out on a flagpole high above the ground.  When they come out of their trance and realize their predicament they fall into a window and foil a robbery in progress thus earning reward money to pay for Mary's operation.  [ A remake of "Hocus Pocus".] "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713000000 +0000" stop="20250713023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Invaders From Mars</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young boy learns that space aliens are taking over the minds of earthlings."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713023000 +0000" stop="20250713030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker's Flying Saucer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker uses an alien distraction in order to build his own flying saucer. Before Batman and Robin can stop him, the Joker's bomb destroys the Batcave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713030000 +0000" stop="20250713040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Naked Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange alien substance causes the crew to act out their deepest inhibitions, while the ship plummets out of orbit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713040000 +0000" stop="20250713043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The anti-Superstition Society is being threatened, and Superman uses a cat to help find the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713043000 +0000" stop="20250713050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Superman Week</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>While plans are made to celebrate "Superman Week," Sy Horton's mob forces Jimmy to reveal the secret of Kryptonite.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713050000 +0000" stop="20250713060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Hungry Sea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Robinson discovers that the planet's orbit will bring immense heat on the spaceship. With that knowledge, the Robinsons take off in the Chariot and head south. Dr. Smith stays behind because he believed them to be lying, but soon realizes the orbit is odd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713060000 +0000" stop="20250713070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Sky's On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>While the Van Allen belt burns, a fanatical unofficial kills several aboard the Seaview in an attempt to sabotage Nelson's plan to explode the burning gases from the atmosphere.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713070000 +0000" stop="20250713080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Sabotage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new giant security chief finds himself at odds with a senator championing the Earthling'ss cause. So he decides to eliminate two birds with one stone by killing Obek and framing the Earthlings for his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713080000 +0000" stop="20250713090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The travelers materialize in 1895 on Devil's Island, where they try to help French captain Alfred Dreyfus escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713090000 +0000" stop="20250713100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of The Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The death of an alien causes the invaders to try and cover up the evidence, even if it means killing an entire town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713100000 +0000" stop="20250713110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams recalls the tale of how he met Nakoma when he was a new "Greenhorn" to the ways of the wilderness. How Nakoma helped him learn survival and also the tribal ceremony that bonded their friendship as Blood Brothers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713110000 +0000" stop="20250713113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Puma Pass</sub-title>
    <desc>"A story of the community of wildlife living in a mountain valley, reigned over by a puma who lives at the head of the pass."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713113000 +0000" stop="20250713120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Fact Or Fallacy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim set out to separate fact from fallacy among many popularly held ideas about the animal kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713120000 +0000" stop="20250713123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Queen Of The Everglades</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim take us into one of the wildest areas of the natural wild kingdom in the U.S., the vast Everglades."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713123000 +0000" stop="20250713130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Survival In The Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Even under searing temperatures of 120 degrees or more, life tenaciously takes hold in the Sonora Desert.  This American Southwestern region is an arena of daily competition…between animals, plants and insects, struggling to survive the extremes and severities of the desert’s environment.  It’s truly a “survival of the fittest,” and a ruggedly beautiful adventure.  Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler are there observing as predator hunts its prey, be it the grey fox, badger or sidewinder snake.  Then you’ll be part of the intense excitement as a peccary…the only true wild pig in the United States…becomes the target of Marlin’s capture gun, which shoots a harmless, sleep-inducing drug into the animal.  The peccary is then tagged, so that its habits may be more carefully studied, and that life, under the difficult circumstances of the Sonora, may be more clearly understood by man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713130000 +0000" stop="20250713133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Poles Apart</sub-title>
    <desc>"Many animals dwell in the wild kingdom that literally are ‘poles apart’ in structure, habits and adaptations.  In the laboratory and in the wild, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore and explain such extreme contrasts such as: the slow heartbeat of the elephant and the rapid beat of a mouse; the alligators’ jaws built to crush and a tropical bird’s beak built to pry; birds that migrate and birds that ‘stay put’; a bird that flies a mile a minute and a sloth that travels a food a day."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713133000 +0000" stop="20250713140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Amazon Jungle (the Great)</sub-title>
    <desc>"The great tropical rain forest, supports life at all levels.  Fowler captures the largest mammal of the Amazon Jungle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713140000 +0000" stop="20250713143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>A-camping We Will Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Carol prepare for a family camping trip. However, the boys are not thrilled that the girls will be coming along, and the girls aren't exactly thrilled about sleeping in the wilderness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713143000 +0000" stop="20250713150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Cincinnati Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike has to present some plans for an addition to King's Island, an amusement park in Cincinnati, so he invites the whole family along. However, a mixup occurs and Mike is left with a Yogi Bear poster while Jan is left with Mike's plans for the amusement park.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713150000 +0000" stop="20250713153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Ah, Wilderness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys and their girls go on a camping trip for their spring vacation. Under Richie's leadership, however, everything seems to go wrong and nobody has a good time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713153000 +0000" stop="20250713160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Not Quite South Of The Border</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley arrive in New Mexico for a vacation, finding that half of their hotel room is missing and that they have to share the space with another guest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713160000 +0000" stop="20250713163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Barney In The Big City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying in Raleigh, Barney believes he is witnessing a man casing the hotel clientelle. Barney is right in believing a crime about to be committed, but he is tailing the house detective and has hooked up with the real crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713163000 +0000" stop="20250713170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Deep Sea Fishing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Lucy and Ethel vs. Ricky and Fred in a fishing contest while they're on a Florida vacation. The wager: $150 (about what Lucy and Ethel had spent in hotel boutiques), so both sides do a little cheating to ensure a victory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713170000 +0000" stop="20250713173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Train Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After a week-long visit with their Aunt Martha, Wally and Beaver prepare to head home to Mayfield on a train. After talking Martha into letting them buy their own tickets, they discover they're short the money after spending it on junk food and find themselves wondering how they are going to get home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713173000 +0000" stop="20250713180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward takes June and the boys away on a trip to a cabin in hopes of experiencing the "great outdoors." However, as he quickly discovers, getting away from today's modern conveniences will be more difficult then he anticipated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713180000 +0000" stop="20250713183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Fishing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale and Jane try to get the Clampetts interested in deep-sea fishing, but face an obstacle: Granny. She has a fear of water and refuses to go on a boat. So, Jane comes up with the idea of letting them visit Marineland. They decide to go right away and are impressed by the giant fishing holes. And Granny sees the fish of fishes, a giant whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713183000 +0000" stop="20250713190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Silver Dollar City Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the first day of the Silver Dollar City Fair, and Granny is working on getting Elly May a husband before Elverna Bradshaw’s daughter gets married. The two women continue to fight and argue, challenging one another more and more. But with the excitement of the fair, Elly enters a few contests, and Granny arranges plots to brag about Elly May.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713190000 +0000" stop="20250713193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan Meets Jungle Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan discovers a jungle boy living on the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713193000 +0000" stop="20250713200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous Hollywood producer crash-lands on the island. When he insults Ginger, the castaways stage a "Hamlet" musical play to restore her confidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713200000 +0000" stop="20250713203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Goes Hawaiian: Part 1  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An old Hawaiian custom rings true for Iola, Bubba and even Mama when a visit to Lover's Grotto brings them romance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713203000 +0000" stop="20250713210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Goes Hawaiian: Part 2  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama schemes to rid herself of Billy, the man she saved from drowning, and then goes sightseeing with Iola, Bubba and their new "true" loves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713210000 +0000" stop="20250713220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>His Girls Friday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man offers the crew $10,000 to find him a wife; a girl must confront her former love; a man tries to dump his assistant for a blonde.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713220000 +0000" stop="20250713223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taylors quickly realize why they haven't invited Bee's sister and her husband, Ollie, for a visit in more than a decade. When Uncle Ollie borrows Andy's squad car to go fishing, it's the final straw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713223000 +0000" stop="20250713230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Alex Arnold- Indiana Jones</sub-title>
    <desc>"Alex Arnold is known as “Indie” in the Indiana Jones collectors’ world. He was five years old when his parents introduced him to Indiana Jones, and he was instantly hooked; Indiana Jones was more relatable than superheroes with superpowers. He didn’t start collecting, though, until 2016, when his mother gave him a resin box that held Indiana Jones DVDs, a Blockbuster exclusive. After that, the hunt was on, and he began to collect every Indiana Jones item he could find. Today, his job as an RN can be taxing, and his R and R is turning on one of the movies. And posting Indian Jones related content on social media. His public exposure has led to everything from promoting Indiana Jones products to being invited to movie premieres. Alex will show us the treasures he has collected, and our pop culture expert Joel Magee, a.k.a “America’s Toy Scout", will put a price on the entire haul."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713230000 +0000" stop="20250713233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A War For All Seasons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>On New Year's Eve, the staff looks back on the highlights of 1951: The doctors invent an artificial kidney machine; Mulcahy plants a garden; Margaret takes up knitting; and Klinger and Winchester bet on which baseball team will win the pennant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250713233000 +0000" stop="20250714000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Retention Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger is so depressed by news that his ex-wife plans to remarry, he reenlists for an additional six-year stretch. Meanwhile, a male nurse has a gripe against the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714000000 +0000" stop="20250714003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Is Cursed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie spouts off his ideas about women in sports and claims that men can play any sport better than women. Hearing this, Irene challenges Archie to a pool match, where he is eager to prove his point, that is until he discovers Irene has won pool tournaments. This is when he backs off and complains of a sore back to get out of the bet, claiming Frank has put an Italian curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714003000 +0000" stop="20250714010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Christmas season has everyone in the Christmas spirit. For a joke, Archie purchases some fake nose and mustache glasses that were on sale, but Mike also happened to go to that same store and hit that same sale. Meanwhile, Edith returns from a doctor checkup and confides in Gloria the fact that she has a lump in her breast and she fears it may be breast cancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714010000 +0000" stop="20250714013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria Mix It Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>One evening, Edith and Archie go out for the evening to a party that Edith's Cousin Amelia is having, leaving Mike and Gloria with the house to themselves. When Gloria makes sexual advances on Mike, the two become embroiled in a huge argument, in which Mike insists that the man is supposed to make the first move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714013000 +0000" stop="20250714020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Feels Left Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Archie's 50th birthday and Edith, Gloria and Mike are planning a surprise party for him. However, Archie finds out about the party and Edith insists that he act surprised when he walks through the door. Meanwhile, Archie isn't so happy about celebrating his birthday when Archie insists that he's 49, but Mike confirms that he indeed is 50 years old, according to his birth certificate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714020000 +0000" stop="20250714023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eydie Gorme And Joan Rivers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eydie Gorme and Joan Rivers. Originally aired on 10/05/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714023000 +0000" stop="20250714030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 10/20/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714030000 +0000" stop="20250714033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fifty Two, Forty Five Or Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recalls a hard summer when Laura was pregnant and the show was on hiatus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714033000 +0000" stop="20250714040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Who Stole My Watch?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob accuses his friends of stealing his new watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714040000 +0000" stop="20250714043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Golfer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to learn how to play golf to impress his boss, and, of course, the situation turns into a disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714043000 +0000" stop="20250714053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Jess-belle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman enlists the aid of a witch to cast a spell that will make a man fall in love with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714053000 +0000" stop="20250714060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Heart Of Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con searches for a place to stay after he is released from prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714060000 +0000" stop="20250714070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the Middle East, Willy and Barney infiltrate a chemical plant to gain access to Dehominant-B, a quick-acting lethal gas. Barney is exposed to Dehominant-B and crippled; Willy escapes but Barney is captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714070000 +0000" stop="20250714080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Fun And Games And Party Favors</sub-title>
    <desc>"A family drama tangles Dr. Kimble up with two young lovers and a blackmail scheme."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714080000 +0000" stop="20250714090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Acolyte</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell follows a murder trail that leads him to a religious sect and a plot to defraud a mentally disturbed woman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714090000 +0000" stop="20250714093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714093000 +0000" stop="20250714100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714100000 +0000" stop="20250714103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lost And Found</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed transport an unconscious 8-year-old boy to Rampart General Hospital and help him and his parents cope with the ordeal. Afterwards, they assist a child welfare hotline operator locate a 15-year-old girl who has intentionally overdosed on pills, and then race to find the boy they brought in earlier after he escapes from the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714103000 +0000" stop="20250714110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After completing a hazardous driving refresher course, Sgt. MacDonald assigns Malloy and Reed to a nighttime undercover bicycle patrol to test Officer Wells' idea on how to deal with a rash of residential car break-ins. The next day, they pull over a hippie with an obnoxious passenger, and then put their refreshed driving skills to the test when called to a burglary in progress at a new car showroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714110000 +0000" stop="20250714120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bingo Bill</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tooners, join Bill and Toony for a game of B-I-N-G-O!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714120000 +0000" stop="20250714123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Says Good-bye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward makes an offer on a house located in a neighboring town and Beaver believes moving is going to be a sure thing. This leads him to tell all his classmates that he's moving, but when the deal falls through Beaver must tell his class that he won't be moving after all—after they've just thrown him a goodbye party and shoved a handful of presents in his face!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714123000 +0000" stop="20250714130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>While cleaning in the garage, Beaver and Wally come across an old typewriter. Beaver decides to fix it up and begin his own newspaper with Larry. However, someone is standing in his way, Wally, who claims the typewriter is his property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714130000 +0000" stop="20250714140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golfer's Gambit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Washed up golfer Chick Farley has made many enemies throughout the years and it's not really a surprise when he turns up murdered. But when fellow golfer Jim Harrell is charged with the death, Mason gets a mysterious envelope containing $2,500 and a request from Harrell to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714140000 +0000" stop="20250714150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Hucksters  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock sets out to prove that one of three people murdered a scheming huckster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714150000 +0000" stop="20250714160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Child's Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Chief Gillespie is fired by the city council and Sparta's new police chief Hampton Forbes arrives in town. Bill's last case with Sparta P.D. is a murder investigation in which a young boy has been implicated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714160000 +0000" stop="20250714170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Cloudburst</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A mining company comes to town and wants to buy land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714170000 +0000" stop="20250714173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Big Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Pat Swarmer gives Kitty a hard time at the Long Branch. Matt comes in and hits Pat and makes him leave but Swarmer says he’ll be back and get Kitty. When Pat is beaten to death Jud, who was drunk at the time, thinks he saw the Marshal do it. Matt has to prove it wasn’t him that did it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714173000 +0000" stop="20250714180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt &amp; Chester come upon a burning house. A man is dead but his step daughter is alive and now orphaned."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714180000 +0000" stop="20250714190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Ride In The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Tobias, April Horn and a former Army scout pull off a daring robbery, injuring Ben in the process, Hoss and Joe join the search posse, bent on catching the thieves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714190000 +0000" stop="20250714193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance hall singer asks Lucas to care for her daughter in an effort to hide the baby from her self-righteous, bigoted father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714193000 +0000" stop="20250714200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Coward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes involved in a battle between an aspiring writer and a cocky, bragging trail boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714200000 +0000" stop="20250714210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel Harris Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint goes to Fort Young to see the Harris family and Bowman Lewis, who were friends from his youth. He finds out that Mrs. Harris is dead and that her husband swears to wipe out all Indians including Lewis, who leads the Comanche and his mother, Princess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714210000 +0000" stop="20250714220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Firehouse Four</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The station enters the fireman's barber shop quartet contest. A man keeps requiring rescue while trying various ways to exercise. A woman overdoses on sleeping pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714220000 +0000" stop="20250714223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester takes command during Potter's absence; and B.J. and Hawkeye try to convince the Marines to grant a hardship discharge to an immigrant soldier, Private Jost Van Liter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714223000 +0000" stop="20250714230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Taking The Fifth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye uses a bottle of vintage wine to lure unsuspecting nurses into his den; and Potter tries to secure a different sort of anesthetic when the army threatens to ban a painkiller.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714230000 +0000" stop="20250714233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger saves Winchester's life when an explosion rocks the operating room; and B.J. is reluctant to reveal the extent of his injuries after the blast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250714233000 +0000" stop="20250715000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Sweat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret develops a case of prickly heat, Charles does his tax returns and Klinger takes the P.A. apart—just some of the events that occur during another unendurably hot night at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715000000 +0000" stop="20250715003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Luck Of Newton Monroe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant peddler comes to town (Don Rickles) and sells Barney, Floyd and Goober defective goods. After he disregards Andy's warning, he finds himself in the Mayberry jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715003000 +0000" stop="20250715010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715010000 +0000" stop="20250715013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Beautiful Maid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts take in Ulla, a Swedish actress hoping to learn their way of life for a movie, and a girl they think is a poor sharecropper's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715013000 +0000" stop="20250715020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman's Work Is Never Done</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of Ralph's endless domestic complaints, Alice takes a job and leaves a maid to take care of the housework.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715020000 +0000" stop="20250715023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>To The Gestapo With Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets three beautiful girls to pry secrets out of the guys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715023000 +0000" stop="20250715030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man's Best Friend Is Not His Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog buries a bone containing film from Carter's camera that has images of a new German tank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715030000 +0000" stop="20250715033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A World Of His Own</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A playwright has the ability to make his characters literally come to life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715033000 +0000" stop="20250715043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shoplifter's Shoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason digs into a dead man's past in search of evidence to clear an accused murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715043500 +0000" stop="20250715050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715050500 +0000" stop="20250715053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A toddler is the only witness to the murder of his babysitter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715053500 +0000" stop="20250715060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Reward To Finder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A very poor janitor finds a wallet containing $5,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715060500 +0000" stop="20250715070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Judas Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A missing police officer leads Chief Carl Yaring in search of the cop, a former ex-con who was suspected of robbery and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715070500 +0000" stop="20250715080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Conspiracy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank Cannon and Barnaby Jones team up for an investigation of a murder at a big corporation in which a deliveryman was charged with the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715080500 +0000" stop="20250715090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Yesterdays Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman with a shady past plots the murder of her blackmailer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715090000 +0000" stop="20250715093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715093000 +0000" stop="20250715100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A purse-snatching dog? This is the case Friday and Gannon must solve. Making things more difficult, victims give different descriptions of the four-legged thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715100000 +0000" stop="20250715103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Badge Heavy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed puts his reputation on the line when he decides to file a formal complaint against a fellow officer after witnessing him use excessive force. On patrol, he and Malloy search for suspects in two separate robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715103000 +0000" stop="20250715110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harry Nobody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed's investigation of a fatal shooting in a hotel room hinges on the eyewitness account of a hopeless wino named Harry who is desperate to make a name for himself. Meanwhile, they investigate a report of a peeping tom at the home of an exotic dancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715110000 +0000" stop="20250715120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Bayou</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit Louisiana on the next stop of Toon in With Me's "Trekkin' All 50" tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715120000 +0000" stop="20250715123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver sees an Eskimo sweater in a store window and becomes determined to get one. He finally convinces Ward and June to get him one, but the first day he wears it he sees Judy Hensler wearing the same sweater.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715123000 +0000" stop="20250715130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver spends the weekend at Larry's but the first night there they get into a terrible argument and Beaver goes home angry. After Ward tells Beaver a story about Damon and Pythias, Beaver and Larry swear to die for each other. Larry then promptly demands that Beaver give him his homework to prove himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715130000 +0000" stop="20250715140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sausalito Sunrise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An art dealer and his girlfriend are arrested for two murders related to a series of hijacks. Paul goes undercover to ferret out the hijacking ring, and Mason finds himself staring down the barrel of a gun pointed by a killer even he never considered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715140000 +0000" stop="20250715150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lovelorn  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a man who has been accused of murdering the relationship columnist whose response ended his relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715150000 +0000" stop="20250715160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hatton's Turn: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hampton Forbes assumes the office of Chief of Police and Bill becomes the Sheriff of Newman county. Former Spartan Wade Hatton returns to Sparta hoping to make sense of his life and rekindle his relationship with Sarah Hallisey. Bubba and Covey take the new chief on a tour of Sparta and Bill takes Wade to visit some distant cousins. Meanwhile two young criminals involve a mentally handicapped young man in a terrible crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715160000 +0000" stop="20250715170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Motorcycle Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob fixes up Ike's old motorcycle and enters a motorcycle race</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715170000 +0000" stop="20250715180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Perce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An outlaw named Perce McCall helps Matt fend off three gunmen, much to everyone's surprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715180000 +0000" stop="20250715190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Another Windmill To Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric who calls himself Don Q. Hought arrives in Virginia City and has a series of misadventures.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715190000 +0000" stop="20250715193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Surveyors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark runs away from home after his father questions his story about overhearing a plot to rob the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715193000 +0000" stop="20250715200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous buffalo hunter tries to goad Lucas into a shooting match.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715200000 +0000" stop="20250715210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Maidie Brandt Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Maidie Brant is found by the wagon train. Needing fresh horses after a cougar attack, she is reluctant to say why she would rather pay top dollar for the Major's horses rather than ride back into town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715210000 +0000" stop="20250715220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a call, Roy and John witness a pedestrian being struck by a car. A woman is badly burnt in a fire. John thinks about settling down. A belly dancer overdoses on diet pills. A child bites a dog and the dog bites back. At a burning building, Roy and John must jump to safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715220000 +0000" stop="20250715223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Depressing News</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger's army newspaper reports on Hawkeye's monument to military stupidity; a giant tower made from a half million erroneously shipped tongue depressors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715223000 +0000" stop="20250715230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Laughing Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye wagers that he can go a full day without a wisecrack, and Winchester finally confronts the major who exiled him to the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715230000 +0000" stop="20250715233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, How We Danced</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester is sent to inspect sanitary conditions on the frontlines, while the rest of the camp plans a surprise anniversary party for B.J.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250715233000 +0000" stop="20250716000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottoms Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Margaret's nurses tries to hide her severe drinking problem, and Hawkeye is scorned after a practical joke he plays on Winchester backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716000000 +0000" stop="20250716003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie goes to the carnival and blows all his money on a game to win a birthday gift for Andy. The game, however, is rigged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716003000 +0000" stop="20250716010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banjo-playing Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When former carnival man Jerry Miller becomes deputy to Sheriff Taylor, he finds himself jeopardizing Mayberry, making him question his decision to become a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716010000 +0000" stop="20250716013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Pad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro hires himself out cleaning Mr. Drysdale’s garage, and he discovers the magazine Swinger, a magazine for international playboys. After reading the magazine, he does all he can to become an international playboy. He gets a portable playboy parlor at the city dump and heads to the Kitty Kat Club to get some girls. He has no luck, but Drysdale arranges for two Kitty Kats to show up to Jethro, one being Miss Jane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716013000 +0000" stop="20250716020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Life And Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ralph thinks he's dying and sells the story to a magazine, he discovers it was a dog who was sick instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716020000 +0000" stop="20250716023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Never Play Cards With Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plan to blow up a rocket fuel factory boomerangs back at him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716023000 +0000" stop="20250716030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Color The Luftwaffe Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer to paint the headquarters of the Luftwaffe in order to steal an important map.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716030000 +0000" stop="20250716033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>King Nine Will Not Return</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A WWII captain finds himself in the desert, next to his crashed plane. Where is his crew? And why are futuristic jet planes flying overhead?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716033000 +0000" stop="20250716043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bluffing Blast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl searching for the father she has never seen seeks Mason's help when she's charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716043500 +0000" stop="20250716050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716050500 +0000" stop="20250716053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Enough Rope For Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal released after 10 years in imprison plans to recover his stash.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716053500 +0000" stop="20250716060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Last Request</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A longtime criminal is sentenced to death for a crime he did not commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716060500 +0000" stop="20250716070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>With Intent To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When attempts are made on the life of Detective Ira Deegan, who is in hot pursuit of a robber, his wife hires Mannix to keep an eye on her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716070500 +0000" stop="20250716080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gordon Bell gets involved in a fight. When his opponent dies, Gordon is arrested and charged with murder. Cannon has to bring the truth to light . The corpulent detective soon discovers that Gordon is only a pawn in a devilish scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716080500 +0000" stop="20250716090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Damocles Gun, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The victim of a hit-and-run disappears as the sole witness calls an ambulance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716090000 +0000" stop="20250716093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Pyramid Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A female con-artist uses an evangelistic approach to lure buyers into her pyramid scheme. The Bunco division can't charge her with false advertising, so they prosecute her for operating a lottery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716093000 +0000" stop="20250716100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Police Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate a scam involving a phony LAPD newsletter, which comes with a card for subscribers entitling the bearer to preferential treatment from the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716100000 +0000" stop="20250716103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Malloy's birthday, but he's consumed with anger over the thought his colleagues might have a plan to throw him a surprise party. On a busy patrol, he and Reed make an ironic traffic stop while responding to a burglary call at an antique store, deal with an extremely embarrassed theft victim at a lingerie store, investigate suspicious activity at a service station, use a creative approach to apprehend a serial jewelry store burglar and engage in a shootout inside the police station's parking garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716103000 +0000" stop="20250716110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed suspect that a well-armed immigrant tailor who claims to be defending his establishment from burglars is actually plotting a murder. In the meantime, they deal with a drunken traveling businessman who passes out in a bar girl's car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716110000 +0000" stop="20250716120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>That's A Racket</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony break down racket sports!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716120000 +0000" stop="20250716123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Dance Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets an invitation to attend a cotillion with Mary Ellen Rogers. At first he wants to turn down the invitation, but then decides to go anyway, despite the fact that Mary Ellen has signed them up to do the cha-cha in a dance contest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716123000 +0000" stop="20250716130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Haircomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins combing his hair a new way, which was inspired by a fad started by Eddie that has swept his school. However, June and Ward are aghast by his hairdo and June becomes determined to get Wally to change his haircomb back to his normal style.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716130000 +0000" stop="20250716140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Injured Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a test driver deliberately crashes a race car equipped with an experimental engine, claims the collision paralyzed him and then ends up murdered, Mason defends the investor behind the engine's creation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716140000 +0000" stop="20250716150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Genius  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's nephew, Irwin, is charged with murder, his investigation leads to a high-tech computer firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716150000 +0000" stop="20250716160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hatton's Turn: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Wade and Sarah try to keep young Henry from being punished for a crime he did not commit and Forbes and his officers search for the two men who are really responsible.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716160000 +0000" stop="20250716170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pony Cart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Martha Corrine, Grandpa's sister in law, comes to the mountain to visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716170000 +0000" stop="20250716180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Yellow Boots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune-hunting cowboy engaged to a wealthy woman is suspected of murdering her brother, who objected to their union.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716180000 +0000" stop="20250716190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights protect a witness involved with a recent stagecoach robbery. However, they are unaware that she is a compulsive liar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716190000 +0000" stop="20250716193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Order Groom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger arrives to marry the town spinster, two brothers who want her land try to discourage him with threats and a beating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716193000 +0000" stop="20250716200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Case Of Identity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself in grave danger when two unscrupulous detectives searching for a man's long-lost son claim that it is Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716200000 +0000" stop="20250716210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Larry Hanify Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>On his deathbed, Joe asks Flint to look after his 17-year-old son, Larry Hanify, and get him to California. The catch is that the boy is in jail, awaiting trial for armed robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716210000 +0000" stop="20250716220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John finally restore their old fire engine to ride in the California Fire Fighters Parade. A man with heart problems causes an accident for which the other driver blames herself. Dr. Early treats a patient who has a seizure in the waiting room. A man on a date passes out and has difficulty breathing. A child's medical condition causes an argument between his divorced parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716220000 +0000" stop="20250716223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Red/white Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter nearly blows his stack when his well-intentioned colleagues mollycoddle him in order to lower his blood pressure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716223000 +0000" stop="20250716230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bless You, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye can't stop a sneezing fit that has no apparent cause, psychiatrist Sidney Freedman digs into the surgeon's past for a clue to this unusual malady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716230000 +0000" stop="20250716233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is overcome by the devotion of a terminally ill G.I., who has leukemia, for his critically wounded buddy, but he has trouble coming to terms with the fact that he can't cure the man. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is worried about the impending visit of a Cardinal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250716233000 +0000" stop="20250717000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Foresight Saga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is given a gift of fresh-grown vegetables by a grateful Korean; and Potter questions the veracity of an upbeat letter from Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717000000 +0000" stop="20250717003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Housekeeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose, the former housekeeper, gets married and Opie is unhappy at her departure. Aunt Bee comes to live with Andy and Opie, and Opie is not exactly thrilled with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717003000 +0000" stop="20250717010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The state police arrogantly ask Andy and Barney to step aside while they search for an escaped convict in Mayberry, believing that the Mayberry sheriff's department is not capable of doing "real" police work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Bird Watchers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Jane’s bird watcher leader, Professor Biddle, comes to town to visit. And Jed and Granny are trying to get a man for Elly. After Elly shows up with Professor Biddle, Jed decides that fixing Elly May up with Dash Riprock couldn’t hurt. Drysdale blackmails Dash with a bad TV role to get Dash to ask Elly out. He doesn’t get to the Clampett mansion in enough time, and Jed has no luck with stopping Elly, so she ends up going with Professor Biddle, Miss Jane and Jethro on their bird expedition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717013000 +0000" stop="20250717020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Sleepwalker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton is sleepwalking and Ralph gets stuck looking after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717020000 +0000" stop="20250717023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who Came To Dinner?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan learns his underground contact may be a double agent after he arranges for her to go to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717023000 +0000" stop="20250717030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>No Names Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after Hogan helps a journalist escape from the Germans, an American paper tells of Hogan's operations at his camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717030000 +0000" stop="20250717033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Man In The Bottle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A discontented curio shop owner thinks he's finally found happiness when a genie  grants him four wishes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717033000 +0000" stop="20250717043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prankish Professor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When a college professor is murdered after publishing a lurid novel featuring thinly veiled versions of his colleagues' private lives, the man's estranged wife is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717043500 +0000" stop="20250717050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717050500 +0000" stop="20250717053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Young One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenager’s desire to be free leads her to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717053500 +0000" stop="20250717060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Diplomatic Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple tries to smuggle a corpse out of Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717060500 +0000" stop="20250717070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Crime That Wasn't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Dennis Coverly fears he and his family are in danger when a missing corpse is linked to a crime hit set for Mannix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717070500 +0000" stop="20250717080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Seventh Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon investigates a kidnapping case. The lawyer David Rackham has been abducted. Because he is diabetic and needs a certain drug, Cannon questions the pharmacists of the surroundings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717080500 +0000" stop="20250717090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gang War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang kidnaps J.R. and demands that he find out who killed the leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717090000 +0000" stop="20250717093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An officer accused of taking a bribe has chosen Sgt. Friday to represent him at his trial board hearing. Witnesses saw the officer accept the money, but he insists it was for the payback of a loan made years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717093000 +0000" stop="20250717100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A statue of the child Jesus was stolen from a church. Joe and Bill have to get it back by Christmas. They have less than 48 hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717100000 +0000" stop="20250717103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate an interstate bounty hunter who has an invalid gun permit and questionable tactics. Meanwhile, they deal with an elderly man who strongly dislikes hippies, and a frustrated wife who desperately wants to receive a traffic ticket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717103000 +0000" stop="20250717110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Spell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On an unseasonably hot day, Malloy and Reed suspect that an elusive bicyclist who overreacts to having his air pump stolen in a park is actually a drug pusher. Meanwhile, their investigation of a two-month-long yard sale leads to an armed fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717110000 +0000" stop="20250717120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>It's 64!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony revisit the pop culture highlights of 1964."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717120000 +0000" stop="20250717123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Fund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry have been put in charge of the class cookie fund and are taking turns guarding the money. A new kid takes advantage of them and cons Beaver and Larry out of three dollars from the fund.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717123000 +0000" stop="20250717130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Forgotten Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Beaver's, David Manning, invites him to a birthday party and Beaver promises to attend, but as the week passes Beaver forgets all about it. When the day arrives, June, Ward and Wally scramble to find the Beaver, who is spending the day with Larry, wandering around town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717130000 +0000" stop="20250717140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Twice-told Twist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young car thief—who helped strip Mason's car down to the frame—is charged with murder, Mason decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717140000 +0000" stop="20250717150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Magician  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a night at the magic show with Julie, Matlock agrees to defend magician Daniel Fontaine when he's charged with the murder of his assistant and lover, Sandy Farrell, a woman who was as devious as she was beautiful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717150000 +0000" stop="20250717160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Depraved Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The daughter of an old friend asks Bubba to arrest the man who knowingly gave her AIDS.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717160000 +0000" stop="20250717170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia wants this Christmas to be the best ever</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717170000 +0000" stop="20250717180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Kitty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Kitty takes a young boy off the stagecoach one night, Matt attempts to figure out his identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717180000 +0000" stop="20250717190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Silence At Stillwater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In the town of Stillwater, Candy is a victim of mistaken identity and finds himself jailed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717190000 +0000" stop="20250717193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Visitor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucas is drawn to a young widow passing through town on her way to claim an inheritance, but others who covet it are trying to kill her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717193000 +0000" stop="20250717200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young stablehand kills a notorious gunslinger, he is baffled by the hostility of the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717200000 +0000" stop="20250717210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clayton Tucker Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Taking a dangerous route through the desert to join up with the wagon train, a small band of settlers takes a turn for the worse when they lose the scout leading them and then can't agree on how to proceed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717210000 +0000" stop="20250717220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Bash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is trapped on a film set with a bear. When Roy and John rescue him, they are invited to a "thing" that the man is giving later that week. John talks Roy into getting overdressed for the event. Dr. Brackett treats a man suffering from trichinosis. A bomb blast injures two men. The paramedics resuscitate a musician at the party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717220000 +0000" stop="20250717223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Life You Save</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles is nearly felled by a sniper's bullet, he develops a philosophical obsession with death. Meanwhile, the officers have all been assigned new responsibilities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717223000 +0000" stop="20250717230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717230000 +0000" stop="20250717233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250717233000 +0000" stop="20250718000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Identity Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy counsels a GI who is plagued by guilt because he has swapped tags with a dead colleague. Meanwhile, B.J. and Charles consider ways of keeping a soldier-salesman quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718000000 +0000" stop="20250718003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Lindsey is a young guitarist that lives in Mayberry. When the famous musician Bobby Fleet and his band arrive in Mayberry, Andy and Barney scheme to arrest Bobby and his band so that Jim can get an audition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718003000 +0000" stop="20250718010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie Walker, the local pharmacist's niece, comes to Mayberry to replace him on a temporary basis. Her "new" approach to dispensing medicine shakes things up in Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718010000 +0000" stop="20250718013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Jethro’s from school, Armstrong Dueser McHugh III, comes to the mansion to visit. Armstrong is treated very delicately at his house, and his chauffeur is very worried about how the boy will be fare. At the Clampett mansion, Armstrong ends up having a really good time: eating real food, climbing trees, swimming, learning to fight and fishing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718013000 +0000" stop="20250718020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Better Living Through Televison</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton go on T.V. to sell a kitchen utensil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718020000 +0000" stop="20250718023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Day In Berlin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. undercover agent helps Hogan and his men get a defecting Nazi officer out of Berlin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718023000 +0000" stop="20250718030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Blue Baron Strike Again?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to throw a party for WW I flying ace Blue Baron in order to find his headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718030000 +0000" stop="20250718033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nervous Man In A Four Dollar Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ordered to commit a murder, a smalltime hood nervously looks in the mirror and sees the man he could have been.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718033000 +0000" stop="20250718043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of Constant Doyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After the death of her husband and partner, Joe Doyle, Constant Doyle takes on a case involving a young man who knew her husband. She asks for Mason's help and he suggests she hire the Paul Drake Detective agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718043500 +0000" stop="20250718050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718050500 +0000" stop="20250718053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Housewives being blackmailed by a plumber exact their revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718053500 +0000" stop="20250718060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Paisley's Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely woman learns to love a stray cat that wandered into her apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718060500 +0000" stop="20250718070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Gathering Of Ghosts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange college reunion for Mannix's old football squad at a ghost town ends in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718070500 +0000" stop="20250718080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Catch Me If You Can</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl turns up dead at the yacht party thrown by two jet set brothers, Edgar and Norman Bruce. Her father, George Able, wants to exact revenge, but before he can even get close to the siblings he is beaten up by his henchmen. Cannon is hired by Abel's second daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718080500 +0000" stop="20250718090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Daughter Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby trails a jewel thief who's using call girls to distract his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718090000 +0000" stop="20250718093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718093000 +0000" stop="20250718100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718100000 +0000" stop="20250718103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gifts And Long Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by investigating a deluded and reclusive parolee whose troubled girlfriend in the apartment next door has just attempted suicide for the second time. In the meantime, they provide vital information to a detective's search for an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718103000 +0000" stop="20250718110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>O'brien's Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's headstrong and elderly apartment manager stages a protest at the station after she's victimized by a serial purse snatcher, and Malloy suggests a stakeout will be their only chance to apprehend the suspect. On patrol, he and Reed chase a suspicious vehicle into a lumber yard, and investigate the murder of a young man at his parents' home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718110000 +0000" stop="20250718120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Return To Camp Watchington</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill goes scouting, trying to earn more patches for his sash."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718120000 +0000" stop="20250718123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Athlete</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting a poor grade in gym class on his report card, Beaver becomes determined to prove to everyone that he is a good athlete, so he signs up to play baseball—where it's the boys versus the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718123000 +0000" stop="20250718130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Found Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry invites Beaver to the carnival and tells him that his mother will treat him. However, when Mrs. Mondello refuses to give Larry money, Larry decides to find some. So Larry throws some of his mother's money out the window and when Beaver comes over, Larry pretends as if he's found it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718130000 +0000" stop="20250718140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Left-handed Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Health club instructor Ward Nichols wants to marry the daughter of his employer, but his estranged wife is pressuring him for money and claiming to be pregnant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718140000 +0000" stop="20250718150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Fisherman  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a Vietnamese fisherman and his son when they are accused of murdering a racist fisherman. And It isn't just the fishermen that Matlock ends up defending, as he, too, becomes a target of the racist townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718150000 +0000" stop="20250718160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Brewer's Pond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A night of revelry at a local pond turns deadly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718160000 +0000" stop="20250718170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Mustang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wild mustang is captured on Walton land and Grandpa wants it to remain be and remain free</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718170000 +0000" stop="20250718180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Harper's Blood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to balance the bad blood between his sons upon learning that his wife's grandfather was a murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718180000 +0000" stop="20250718190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Lawman's Lot Is Not A Happy One</sub-title>
    <desc>"When he is called to testify in an out-of-town lumber shark case, Roy recruits Hoss to temporarily serve as sheriff. Hoss quickly finds his hands full dealing with a reluctant groom, who plans a robbery to make himself less appealing to his assertive fiancé; and a persistent salesman wanting to sell stock for a resort in the Virginia City area. Will Virginia City ever be the same?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718190000 +0000" stop="20250718193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a horse dealer transporting a prize stallion stops in North Fork, two saddle tramps try to use trickery to obtain it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718193000 +0000" stop="20250718200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple moves to North Fork under an assumed name to hide the fact that they are the parents of a vicious killer. The plan backfires when the son shows up at their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718200000 +0000" stop="20250718210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Benjamin Burns Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>One dry water hole is normal but when the wagon train has two to worry about, Flint and Ben Burns lead a party to find a legend only indians speak of, Shining Water. Troubles await them but the worst may be a too-green city boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718210000 +0000" stop="20250718220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Transition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school classmate of John’s is assigned as Squad 51's new paramedic trainee. The firemen rescue a man trapped in his kitchen after a hydrogen sulfide explosion. The paramedics help treat accident victims at the hospital and tend to child at an amusement park. When an intoxicated man turns out to be a snakebite victim, Roy is hit in the eyes with cobra venom. Back at the amusement park, a heart attack victim is trapped high in the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718220000 +0000" stop="20250718223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rumor At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The latest scuttlebutt affects everyone's behavior when a visiting Army rep is rumored to be recruiting for a new M*A*S*H unit. The gang fears that the 4077th will be split up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718223000 +0000" stop="20250718230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em Hell, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes a heartfelt letter to President Harry Truman to protest at the continued fighting in Korea. Meanwhile, Colonel Ditka has promised a much-needed water heater if the 4077th beautifies the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718230000 +0000" stop="20250718233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Wheelers And Dealers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>On the eve of a big poker game, B.J.'s pride is bruised when he finds out his wife is working as a waitress. And Potter takes driving lessons from Klinger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250718233000 +0000" stop="20250719000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester infuriates the camp when he hoards his stateside newspapers, and Hawkeye reunites two Korean brothers who have been fighting on opposite sides of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719000000 +0000" stop="20250719003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Irresistible Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy comes to believe that Ellie is a "deadly female hunter" out to marry him so he tries to put her onto other quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719003000 +0000" stop="20250719010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie becomes friends with an eight-year-old runaway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719010000 +0000" stop="20250719013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Tonics A Birdwatcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>It is Tonic Time, and Granny has made a small batch, which is enough for the family and a few friends. She also hopes that she can tonic a man for Elly May to marry. Though Elly may not have a husband in her future, Jane thinks she does. She thinks that Professor Biddle will propose to her, but he reveals all he wants her to do is hatch a condor egg. Granny heads to the bank to get Jane and Drysdale to give Dash Riprock some of her tonic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719013000 +0000" stop="20250719020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pal O'mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's feelings are bruised when Ed buys a friendship ring for one of his pals on the sewer crew. Though Ralph gets it stuck on his finger, they eventually make up after Ed survives a sewer explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719020000 +0000" stop="20250719023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Colonel Klink Please Stand Up Against The Wall?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When Carter, in disguise as the camp kommandant, is seen near one of Hogan's operations, Klink is threatened with a treason charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719023000 +0000" stop="20250719030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to capture LeBeau, but not before he lets him complete his mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719030000 +0000" stop="20250719033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Thing About Machines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer feels that the machines in his house are conspiring against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719033000 +0000" stop="20250719043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Libelous Locket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance student is charged with murder when her instructor is found dead after they had a physical altercation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719043500 +0000" stop="20250719050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719050500 +0000" stop="20250719053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A tramp confesses to a crime. Unfortunately, the D.A. has already prosecuted another man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719053500 +0000" stop="20250719060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Percentage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young gangster tries to repay an old Army buddy by starting a business for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719060500 +0000" stop="20250719070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Day Filled With Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When a basketball star disappears, his family hires Mannix to hunt him down—before the syndicate does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719070500 +0000" stop="20250719080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Press Pass To The Slammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719080500 +0000" stop="20250719090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Captives, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway housewife gets involved with a gang of thieves plotting an armored-car heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719090000 +0000" stop="20250719093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo's Pen Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo's Japanese pen pal, Nobuko, comes for a visit to the U.S. and stays at the Shady Rest.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
