<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129203000 +0000" stop="20251129210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend In Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself the unwilling companion of gunman Carl Avery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129210000 +0000" stop="20251129220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty-five Santa Clauses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A conman and his wife con the drovers into pooling their efforts to prepare a Christmas celebration for a sickly Mexican boy. The boy isn't really sick and Rowdy ignores Favor's orders to move the herd across a river, trapping the herd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129220000 +0000" stop="20251129223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Be Not Forgetful Of Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Duane Eddy as a cowboy who arrives in town during Christmas with his pregnant wife---and no lodgings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129223000 +0000" stop="20251129230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Cent Reward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>On Christmas Eve Randall receives his most daunting assignment yet: bring in Santa Claus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129230000 +0000" stop="20251130010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Smart Saps, Gents Without Cents, Idiots Deluxe, Crime On Their Hands, Scheming Schemers, Saved By The Belle</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are engaged to the three daughters of a prison warden.  When they learn that some crooks have taken over the prison and their prospective father-in-law has been locked up, they decide to go undercover to rescue him.  The Stooges sneak into the prison where they find a casino with a fancy party in progress.  After swiping some formal attire, they crash the party and get candid camera evidence to expose the crooked goings-on.  With the crooks behind bars once again, the Stooges are able to get married and all ends well. , The Stooges are three small time actors looking for a job.  They meet three girl dancers in the situation and get a small part in a big producers show at the shipyard.  When the rest of the cast doesn't show up, the Stooges and the girls must put on the whole show themselves.  The show is a hit and the Stooges marry the girls and head to Niagara Falls for their honeymoon. , The Stooges are arrested for treason. , Moe is on trial for assaulting Curly and Larry with an ax.  Moe relates how Curly and Larry took him on a hunting trip for his nerves.  Out in the woods they confronted a bear, which Curly and Larry stunned, and thinking it was dead, threw it in the back of their car, where it came awake, tossed Moe out and drove the car into a tree.  The judge finds Moe not guilty and Moe promptly goes after Larry and Curly again with the ax. , The Stooges are janitors working in a newspaper office.  When an anonymous caller phones in a tip about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to become reporters and go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The crooks want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla. , The Stooges are three incompetent plumbers who foul up the plumbing in a fancy mansion where a society party is going on.  They manage to catch a couple of thieves masquerading as guests before the whole party degenerates into a pie fight.  [A remake of "Vagabond Loafers", with footage from "A Plumbing we will go" and "Half-Wits Holiday".  Joe Palma (face hidden) stands in for Shemp. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130010000 +0000" stop="20251130033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Devil Doll</sub-title>
    <desc>"An evil hyponotist/ventriloquist plots to gain an heiress' millions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130033000 +0000" stop="20251130060000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Brady Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"The entire Brady family manages to overcome personal obstacles to spend a happy holiday together."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130060000 +0000" stop="20251130070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Return From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <desc>"Nobody believes Will Robinson when he sends himself back to Earth with an alien transporter, since the world believes they all had died once they realized their ship had gone off course. Lost in Space's only Christmas program."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130070000 +0000" stop="20251130080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live The King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral Nelson must get a 12-year-old prince back to his country to assume the throne before the reds take over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130080000 +0000" stop="20251130090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of Thrombeldinbar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitzhuge pretends to be a magical holiday elf to entertain two orphan children. But the ruse turns deadly when he discovers that the giants ritually throw Thrombeldinbar into a fire to celebrate the holiday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130090000 +0000" stop="20251130100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Merchant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug set out to checkmate the crafty Machiavelli, who is making a game of the Civil War battle at Gettysburg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130100000 +0000" stop="20251130110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Life Seekers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A police shooting causes Vincent to investigate a possible alien encounter with hidden secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130110000 +0000" stop="20251130120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Choice (aka 'letting Go')</sub-title>
    <desc>"Robbie Cartman's deer Ginger,rescued sometime ago,should be sent back into the wild. Robbie loves his "pet" but Adams assures him it's right. Checking on her later,Rob can't find her anywhere. Can he,Adams and friends solve this mystery?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130120000 +0000" stop="20251130123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Adelie Of Antarctica</sub-title>
    <desc>"The life story of the Adelie penguin, the principal inhabitant of this barren continent at the end of the earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130123000 +0000" stop="20251130130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tigers Of Sariska</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin goes unarmed deep into the jungles of India to film the adventures of a full-grown Bengal tigress and her two young cubs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130130000 +0000" stop="20251130133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Voyage To Raza</sub-title>
    <desc>"Travel with Marlin and his band of adventurers as they explore the Golf of California, the last great unexplored marine paradise in the Western hemisphere, lying between the Mexican main land and Baja, California."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130133000 +0000" stop="20251130140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chincoteaque Roundup</sub-title>
    <desc>"There’s a legend that during the 16th century, Spanish ponies from a sinking galleon swam ashore to the island of Assateague, Virginia.  Today, once a year, men from neighboring Chincoteague Island gather for one of the most unusual roundups."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130140000 +0000" stop="20251130143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lions Of Gir Forest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin travels to Gir Forest in India in search of the king of beasts…the lion."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130143000 +0000" stop="20251130150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Falcon</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit the mountain prairies of Wyoming where falcons, eagles and hawks rule the air."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130150000 +0000" stop="20251130153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Voice Of Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol is asked to sing at church on Christmas, but loses her voice just days before the event. A hopeful Cindy asks a department store Santa Claus to bring Carol's voice back in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130153000 +0000" stop="20251130160000 +0000">
    <title>Full House</title>
    <sub-title>Arrest Ye Merry Gentlemen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Michelle and Jesse are almost arrested on Christmas Eve when a Scrooge-like merchant (MICKEY ROONEY) refuses to exchange a gift that Michelle bought for her dad.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130160000 +0000" stop="20251130163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who's Coming To Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie tells Al the story of the time an unexpected visitor turned Howard Cunningham's plans for a traditional family Christmas upside down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130163000 +0000" stop="20251130170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Some Enchanted Earring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne accidentally loses one of her mother's diamond earrings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130170000 +0000" stop="20251130180000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>The Story Of Santa Claus</sub-title>
    <desc>"The special presents an origin story for Santa Claus, who is depicted as a man named Nicholas Claus who wishes to give every child in the world a gift for Christmas. The elves of the North Pole become obligated to grant his wish, facing great obstacles. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130180000 +0000" stop="20251130183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Haircut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing his lunch money three days in a row, Ward gives Beaver one last chance by letting him handle his haircut money. However, when he loses that too, Beaver decides to give himself a haircut just days before he's scheduled to be an angel in a play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130183000 +0000" stop="20251130190000 +0000">
    <title>The Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet</title>
    <sub-title>The Miracle</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ozzie recalls a story from his childhood of when he wished for a white Christmas."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130190000 +0000" stop="20251130193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Home For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts decide to head home for Christmas, and once Drysdale and Jane hear about this, they make all the arrangements, getting Granny and Elly mink coats and giving the Clampetts their first plane ride in style. After a slight mix-up, the Clampetts finally get home, surprising Pearl and Jethrine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130193000 +0000" stop="20251130200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>No Place Like Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts arrive back at their old cabin to spend the Christmas holiday with Pearl. But since the cabin will be too crowded with the Clampetts and Brewster, Pearl suggests Brewster stays with her, in an attempt to get engaged. She tries to woo Brewster by showing herself off at the theatre she works at during the premiere of 'Ben Hur.'</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130200000 +0000" stop="20251130203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Gotta Fly, Fish Gotta Talk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During Christmas, the castaways get homesick and recall the day they were shipwrecked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130203000 +0000" stop="20251130210000 +0000">
    <title>The Lucy Show</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy And The Winter Sports</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy again tries to impress her athletic boyfriend by bragging about her mastery of various winter sports. When he invites her on a ski trip, she takes a crash-course in skiing from Mr. Mooney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130210000 +0000" stop="20251130230000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>The Love Boat: The Christmas Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc>"A woman tries to lure a wealthy man into a "stacked" card game with her mother, but complications arise when he falls for her. Meanwhile, Julie has hired has-been comedian to play Santa Claus during the voyage. At the same time, a woman debates whether to take her ex-husband back when she discovers he may have a secret."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130230000 +0000" stop="20251130233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251130233000 +0000" stop="20251201000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>David Schafer- Toys</sub-title>
    <desc>"Vintage memorabilia collector David Schafer has spent decades assembling the toys, comic books, and other collectibles from his childhood, all in strikingly pristine condition. David shares some of his rarest and most valuable items, including a Batman and Justice League playset released at the height of the Caped Crusader’s 1966 popularity; a Mad Magazine straitjacket that was available by mail only; and the 1941 comic that features the first appearance of Wonder Woman. Joining Lisa is “Collector’s Call” favorite Joel Magee, a.k.a. America’s Toy Scout. Joel appraises the entirety of David’s dazzling  collection, then makes a trade offer for one of David’s Disney rarities. The show concludes with David unveiling to Lisa a 1982 Mad Magazine parody of "The Facts of Life.""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201000000 +0000" stop="20251201003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201003000 +0000" stop="20251201010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201010000 +0000" stop="20251201013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Day At The Bunker's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Christmas Day and Archie is the only one not in the Christmas spirit. Mike and Gloria question him, but he refuses to reveal what's bugging him. The Jeffersons come over to wish the Bunkers a "Merry Christmas", but this does anything but cheer Archie up especially since Henry is dressed as Santa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201013000 +0000" stop="20251201020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Christmas season has everyone in the Christmas spirit. For a joke, Archie purchases some fake nose and mustache glasses that were on sale, but Mike also happened to go to that same store and hit that same sale. Meanwhile, Edith returns from a doctor checkup and confides in Gloria the fact that she has a lump in her breast and she fears it may be breast cancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201020000 +0000" stop="20251201023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Draft Dodger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The clash of two worlds explodes in this episode. Mike's friend is a Draft Dodger and it is Christmas dinner and unbeknownst to Archie this guy is sitting at his Christmas dinner table. The guy is exactly everything Archie hates about Mike's generation. On top of this Archie's friend is also spending Christmas dinner with the Bunkers and he lost his son to the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201023000 +0000" stop="20251201030000 +0000">
    <title>Sanford and Son</title>
    <sub-title>Ebenezer Sanford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred is a Scrooge-like miser during the Christmas season and his friends try to get him to join into the Christmas spirit, but he rejects the attempts. After being accused of a being a Scrooge, Fred falls asleep and dreams up "A Christmas Carol." Now it i</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201030000 +0000" stop="20251201033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Toaster, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is overjoyed by the reaction he is getting from gifting a toaster to his family and friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201033000 +0000" stop="20251201040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Picture, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray believes he has found the ultimate Christmas gift for his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201040000 +0000" stop="20251201043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Alan Brady Show Presents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Alan Brady Show" performs their Christmas variety show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201043000 +0000" stop="20251201050000 +0000">
    <title>The Mary Tyler Moore Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas And The Hardluck Kid Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Single Mary agrees to work on Christmas so others can be with their family."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201050000 +0000" stop="20251201053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201053000 +0000" stop="20251201060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Third From The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>With all-out nuclear war about to ignite, a scientist and his pilot friend plot to escape on an experimental spaceship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201060000 +0000" stop="20251201070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>A Tangled Web  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A French maid runs away with and marries a professional burglar with hopes of making him honest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201070000 +0000" stop="20251201080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Underwater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Berlinger, a millionaire manufacturer and stolen gem dealer, will be transferring diamonds to a Syndicate boss for $75 million. Only one man knows where the diamonds are: Hoffman, Berlinger's former lieutenant, who stole them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201080000 +0000" stop="20251201090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Landscape With Running Figures (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"While being pursued by the police, Dr. Kimble finds himself on the same bus as Marie Gerald, Lieutenant Gerald's wife."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201090000 +0000" stop="20251201100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Mortal Sin</sub-title>
    <desc>"The seal of the confessional must be preserved as Harry O goes after a deranged killer who confessed his crimes to a priest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201100000 +0000" stop="20251201103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Pyramid Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A female con-artist uses an evangelistic approach to lure buyers into her pyramid scheme. The Bunco division can't charge her with false advertising, so they prosecute her for operating a lottery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201103000 +0000" stop="20251201110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Police Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate a scam involving a phony LAPD newsletter, which comes with a card for subscribers entitling the bearer to preferential treatment from the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201110000 +0000" stop="20251201113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Van Nuys Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy returns from vacation sporting a mustache, but finds it difficult getting his colleagues to accept his new look. On patrol, he and Reed respond to a small plane crash by a drunkard that critically injures his young son, investigate the theft of valuable stamps from a mansion, search for a jewelry store armed robber with the aid of a talented witness, deal with a very unlucky purse snatcher and interrogate an evasive department store shoplifter with a big surprise in her purse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201113000 +0000" stop="20251201120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While assisting in a tactics training course, Malloy and Reed meet Officer Wells' new partner, an overconfident probationary officer who seems destined to put himself and his colleagues in danger. On patrol, they deal with an unconventional bank robber, come to the aid of a motor officer who is injured during a traffic stop and investigate a credible bomb threat at a grocery store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201120000 +0000" stop="20251201130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Hand Me Downs</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201130000 +0000" stop="20251201133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Dance Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets an invitation to attend a cotillion with Mary Ellen Rogers. At first he wants to turn down the invitation, but then decides to go anyway, despite the fact that Mary Ellen has signed them up to do the cha-cha in a dance contest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201133000 +0000" stop="20251201140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Haircomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins combing his hair a new way, which was inspired by a fad started by Eddie that has swept his school. However, June and Ward are aghast by his hairdo and June becomes determined to get Wally to change his haircomb back to his normal style.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201140000 +0000" stop="20251201150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mischievous Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady private investigator and his pawn die mysteriously, the woman who may have been his intended target is charged with their murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201150000 +0000" stop="20251201160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Juror  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Called to jury duty, Matlock butts heads with the other jurors, who think the defendant is guilty of murder. Matlock implores them to reexamine the evidence before sentencing the man to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201160000 +0000" stop="20251201170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The More Things Change</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his business partner and frames the man's illegitimate daughter for the crime in an attempt to gain the man's business and his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201170000 +0000" stop="20251201180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben returns home. He plans on leaving the Waltons' mill and becoming an engineer</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201180000 +0000" stop="20251201190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bently</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Chester doubts a man's deathbed murder confession, so he sets out to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201190000 +0000" stop="20251201200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Fear Merchants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights are in Virginia City to celebrate the birthday of Jimmy Chang. The fun quickly vanishes when Jimmy is accused of murder and the Cartwrights have to battle a racist lawyer to prove their friend's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201200000 +0000" stop="20251201203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Skull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for escape after he's captured by outlaws while seeking help for an injured Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201203000 +0000" stop="20251201210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Queen-to-be of France hides out in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201210000 +0000" stop="20251201220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Naomi Kaylor Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hawks rides to the John Kaylor ranch to buy horses for the train but John just died. His widow Naomi refuses to sell the horses at the price John had promised. Naomi shows no sorrow over her husband's death, only wanting to sell the ranch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201220000 +0000" stop="20251201230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Rip-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John are accused of stealing money from a victim. A premature delivery and a blinded man result from a car crash. A perilous rescue involves a plane that might explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201230000 +0000" stop="20251201233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251201233000 +0000" stop="20251202000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202000000 +0000" stop="20251202003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202003000 +0000" stop="20251202010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202010000 +0000" stop="20251202013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Rival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is afraid that Andy's new girlfriend, Peggy, will take his place in his father's heart, and sets out to sabotage their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202013000 +0000" stop="20251202020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Convicts-at-large</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Floyd run out of gas while coming home from a fishing trip. While looking for a telephone they are captured by three female escaped convicts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202020000 +0000" stop="20251202023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Gerard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra points out how alike Ray and his annoying cousin are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202023000 +0000" stop="20251202030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Debra's Workout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is bewildered  when Debra starts initiating sex more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202030000 +0000" stop="20251202033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Parachute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets the Germans to look for an allied agent by planting an opened parachute in camp. This gives him the opportunity to get at the briefcase that was handcuffed to a courier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202033000 +0000" stop="20251202040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Antique</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to open an antiques business selling "rare" cuckoo clocks, a business venture that is actually a ruse enabling the POWs to smuggle information out in the timepieces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202040000 +0000" stop="20251202043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Eydie Gorme</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol and Vicki disturb Harvey while he attempts to finish his taxes. Then, in Salute to RKO Studio, the gang parodies classic films, including "The Pride of the Yankees", "Notorious", "The Outlaw", and "Quasimodo".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202043000 +0000" stop="20251202053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fanciful Frail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Things keep going from awful to good grief for poor Ethel Andrews. First she's left at the altar by her fiancee, Bruce Strickland, who also lets her take the blame for a $50,000 securities theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202053500 +0000" stop="20251202060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Shot An Arrow Into The Air</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts crash-land on what they believe to be an asteroid and have limited water supplies to sustain them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202060500 +0000" stop="20251202070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Butterfly  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Bill and Janet Nelson are besieged by the understanding that a troubled neighborhood boy is planning to slay them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202070500 +0000" stop="20251202080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Bird Of Prey: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's client hires him to find the man who saved his son's life. The search takes him to an island near South America, and then the next link in the chain turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202080500 +0000" stop="20251202090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Island Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con is threatened when his safe cracking skills are needed for a theft of 1 million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202090500 +0000" stop="20251202100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Woman In Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a plastic surgeon accidentally kills his patient, he remodels his nurse to look exactly like her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202100000 +0000" stop="20251202103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An officer accused of taking a bribe has chosen Sgt. Friday to represent him at his trial board hearing. Witnesses saw the officer accept the money, but he insists it was for the payback of a loan made years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202103000 +0000" stop="20251202110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202110000 +0000" stop="20251202113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Capture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The captain has ordered top priority be given to ending a rash of burglaries in the area, and all signs point to career criminal Reno West. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed use their creativity to neutralize a vicious guard dog at the home of an unresponsive diabetic man, investigate the theft of a jade figurine from a mansion and respond to a domestic dispute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202113000 +0000" stop="20251202120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a new dispatcher on today's day watch, and while Reed can't stand her voice, Malloy sees the situation much differently. On patrol, they search for a hit and run driver who left a small girl in serious condition, investigate a break-in at a synagogue, deal with a drunk woman who is searching for her daughter and become part of a SWAT team attempting to neutralize a sniper terrorizing the movie studio from which he was just fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202120000 +0000" stop="20251202130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Suburban Life</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill buys a house in the burbs, and has a shocking new neighbor, Simon Shock!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202130000 +0000" stop="20251202133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Fund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry have been put in charge of the class cookie fund and are taking turns guarding the money. A new kid takes advantage of them and cons Beaver and Larry out of three dollars from the fund.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202133000 +0000" stop="20251202140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Forgotten Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Beaver's, David Manning, invites him to a birthday party and Beaver promises to attend, but as the week passes Beaver forgets all about it. When the day arrives, June, Ward and Wally scramble to find the Beaver, who is spending the day with Larry, wandering around town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202140000 +0000" stop="20251202150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crying Cherub</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A valuable Matisse painting is stolen from a museum. When the thief is found murdered, museum employee June Sinclair and her boyfriend, David Lambert, are charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202150000 +0000" stop="20251202160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Umpire  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a baseball umpire is murdered, Matlock has a whole team of suspects. It seems that everyone had a beef with the ump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202160000 +0000" stop="20251202170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet, Sweet Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The lyrics to a blues song recall a murder that happened 50 years earlier. The victim - Sweet's grandfather. And the only people left with the answers are the bluesman who wrote the song and a retired sheriff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202170000 +0000" stop="20251202180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Whirlwind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jonesy arrives in town and meets Mary Ellen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202180000 +0000" stop="20251202190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kitty Cornered</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A rival saloon owner forces Kitty into a deadly competition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202190000 +0000" stop="20251202200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Spanish Grant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Cartwrights find out that some of the Ponderosa may be forfeited under the Spanish Land Grant, they decide to take legal action in order to stop it. Adam, however, takes another plan of action, which involves getting to know the beautiful heiress who is claiming the land under the grant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202200000 +0000" stop="20251202203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gunfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah has an infamous outlaw, Charlie Gordo, in his jail waiting for the U.S. marshal from Denver to take Gordo to the Yuma prison for hanging. With the arrival of the stage, Micah finds that the lawman has been killed, and he has to look to his friends to defend the jail from Gordo's gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202203000 +0000" stop="20251202210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Quiet Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas' old Army pal settles in North Fork with his deaf daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202210000 +0000" stop="20251202220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hollister John Garrison Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bitter alcoholic Stevenson Drake develops a dislike for the even tempered John Hollister, a fellow Southerner, when he learns he didn't fight for the Confederacy. He also is bothered by the friendliness between his wife and Hollister."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202220000 +0000" stop="20251202230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Audit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>John is audited by the IRS. A man hit on the head wants to be treated by a doctor, not the paramedics. A child is rescued from a locked car. A pregnant girl has difficulty breathing. A professional medical con man shows up at Rampart. A construction worker is trapped when part of the building his crew is working on collapses, and he wants Roy to remove his leg before the rest of the building falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202230000 +0000" stop="20251202233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251202233000 +0000" stop="20251203000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203000000 +0000" stop="20251203003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203003000 +0000" stop="20251203010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203010000 +0000" stop="20251203013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bed Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bea longs for a special present: a blue bed jacket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203013000 +0000" stop="20251203020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to convince everyone of a lack of security at Mayberry Bank, and is furious that no one listens to him. Taking matters into his own hands, he ends up stuck in the bank vault.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203020000 +0000" stop="20251203023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Left Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is shocked to discover that he was left back in school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203023000 +0000" stop="20251203030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>What's With Robert?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra raises the notion that Robert may be gay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203030000 +0000" stop="20251203033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203033000 +0000" stop="20251203040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Two German officers interfere with Hogan's operations when one tries to turn Stalag 13 into an officer's retirement home the other wants to use the facilities to interrogate the citizens of the local town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203040000 +0000" stop="20251203043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests David Hartman And Paula Kelly</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nora Desmond, Carol plays a washed-up, silent film actress who goes to dinner for the first time in years. Then, in George and Zelda, Carol questions a doctor's methods to treat her sick husband. Finally, in This Is Your Lifetime, a parody of "This Is Your Life", Carol is embarrassed  when she's caught on camera at the gym after gaining weight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203043000 +0000" stop="20251203053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unwelcome Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Powerful and avaricious businessman Jerome Klee has made a fortune in oil and intends to make a lot more. But after crossing a business associate and his wife, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203053500 +0000" stop="20251203060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When his wife wins a trip for two to Las Vegas, a man falls under the spell of a slot machine that calls his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203060500 +0000" stop="20251203070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Paragon  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>John Pemberton comes up with an everlasting answer for dealing with his cruel, intrusive wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203070500 +0000" stop="20251203080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Bird Of Prey: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Still searching for the man who saved his client's son's life, Mannix stumbles into the ugly side of politics: an assassination plot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203080500 +0000" stop="20251203090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Deadly Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The parents of a teen girl hire Cannon when they discover a charismatic young man is trying to lure their daughter into a cult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203090500 +0000" stop="20251203100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Image In A Cracked Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune hunter marries rich women and makes off with their valuables.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203100000 +0000" stop="20251203103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203103000 +0000" stop="20251203110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are convinced that "Brother" William Bentley's Temple of the Expanded Mind is just a sham—a front for Bentley to sell LSD to the students of a nearby elementary school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203110000 +0000" stop="20251203113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Northeast Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has full faith that an Explorer Scout volunteering at the station can repair his television set in time to watch 'King Kong,' but Malloy thinks he's crazy for letting a teenager work on expensive electronics. On today's patrol, they engage in a high-speed chase with a teenager on a modified dirt bike, investigate a report of a woman who may have buried her husband in their backyard, search for a female bank robber, deal with a group of women illegally protesting outside a supermarket and respond to a call of a robbery in progress at a coffee shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203113000 +0000" stop="20251203120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>If The Shoe Fits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While Reed is having his shoes fixed at the repair shop, the squeakiness of his replacement shoes is driving Malloy crazy. On patrol, they deal with a deranged homeowner destroying his own possessions, stop a cargo van whose driver misunderstands the meaning of double jeopardy, search for a young boy hiding in an industrial building about to be demolished and create a hostage situation after shooting a bank robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203120000 +0000" stop="20251203130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Advice For Life</sub-title>
    <desc>"Do you need advice? Bill,Toony, and a special guest comedian are here to help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203130000 +0000" stop="20251203133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Athlete</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting a poor grade in gym class on his report card, Beaver becomes determined to prove to everyone that he is a good athlete, so he signs up to play baseball—where it's the boys versus the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203133000 +0000" stop="20251203140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Found Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry invites Beaver to the carnival and tells him that his mother will treat him. However, when Mrs. Mondello refuses to give Larry money, Larry decides to find some. So Larry throws some of his mother's money out the window and when Beaver comes over, Larry pretends as if he's found it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203140000 +0000" stop="20251203150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nimble Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is sought out by land tycoon Adam Thompson, who suspects one of his nephews of rifling the house safe. The twist? The land tycoon's next in command is found dead, after it's found out that he was the one stealing the secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203150000 +0000" stop="20251203160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lovelorn  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a man who has been accused of murdering the relationship columnist whose response ended his relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203160000 +0000" stop="20251203170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sparta Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A deputy provides protection for a cotton grower who is running a pot growing operation. But the deputy makes a big mistake when he wounds Bubba's girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203170000 +0000" stop="20251203180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Tempest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen travels to Florida.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203180000 +0000" stop="20251203190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Promoter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-farmer decides to become a fight promoter to make his fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203190000 +0000" stop="20251203200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A sheepherder and his men try to drive their sheep across the Ponderosa. Ben and Adam disagree about how to stop them. Ben wants the Cartwrights to handle their own matters, but Adam wants to call in the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203200000 +0000" stop="20251203203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sporting Chance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An Englishman arrives with a custom-made rifle—and a plan to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203203000 +0000" stop="20251203210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Young Man's Fancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The pangs of first love are painful for Mark: the object of his affections has eyes for another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203210000 +0000" stop="20251203220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lily Legend Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"While riding through the desert plains, Duke and Charlie come across a sheriff as he is about to die of a heart attack and his female prisoner, Lily Legend, a childhood sweetheart of Duke who the sheriff is taking to be hanged for murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203220000 +0000" stop="20251203230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Frequency</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Johnny's policeman friend is injured in a car crash, the paramedics can't reach the hospital because another squad is using the biophone. A child with a mysterious malady turns out to be drunk. Roy and John assist at the hospital when the victims of a motorcycle gang war are brought in for treatment. An artist becomes trapped in his own sculpture. A father and son are trapped in a collapse at a construction site.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203230000 +0000" stop="20251203233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251203233000 +0000" stop="20251204000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204000000 +0000" stop="20251204003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204003000 +0000" stop="20251204010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204010000 +0000" stop="20251204013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204013000 +0000" stop="20251204020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204020000 +0000" stop="20251204023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Bully On The Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra learn that Ally has been bullying another child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204023000 +0000" stop="20251204030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Prodigal Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone gets on Ray's case because he's doesn't go to Mass.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204030000 +0000" stop="20251204033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Rise And Fall Of Sergeant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is stymied in the rescue of a captured member of the underground until a potential diversion appears in the form of an old WWI buddy of Sgt. Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204033000 +0000" stop="20251204040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204040000 +0000" stop="20251204043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests William Conrad And Isabel Sanford</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Harvey mistakenly steals another man's wallet. Then, in TV Blackouts, the gang salutes TV shows, including "Sonny and Cher, "Jack LaLanne", "Password", "The Golddiggers", and "Maude".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204043000 +0000" stop="20251204053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dead Ringer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While Mason is representing Barbara Kramer, who accuses Otis Swanson of stealing her father's intellectual property, Swanson hatches a nefarious scheme to discredit Mason and distract him from the case. Mason loses the case; however, Swanson soon turns up dead and Mason now defends Kramer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204053500 +0000" stop="20251204060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A World War I flying ace flies through a mysterious cloud—and lands at a modern U.S. air base in the year 1959.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204060500 +0000" stop="20251204070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Be The Judge, I'll Be The Jury  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A police officer uses his partner as a lure to catch a murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204070500 +0000" stop="20251204080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Design For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A politically ambitions publisher hires Mannix to find evidence that his wife is cheating. But when Mannix has no trouble finding this evidence, he begins to question the reasons he was hired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204080500 +0000" stop="20251204090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Flight Of Hawks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A suicide by a pilot leads to the discovery of a plan by a mercenary group to launch a coup of a small African country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204090500 +0000" stop="20251204100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Foul Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The owner of a basketball team accidentally kills a man who intended to blackmail the team's star player.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204100000 +0000" stop="20251204103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204103000 +0000" stop="20251204110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204110000 +0000" stop="20251204113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Southwest Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a baseless complaint against an elderly artist, Malloy decides to buy a random painting out of pity and makes Reed envious. Meanwhile, they question a man attempting to break into a gumball machine while his son looks on, get a big surprise after tracking down a suspected peeping tom, deal with a man who comes up with a creative way to avoid having his furniture repossessed and engage in a game of cat-and-mouse inside the Los Angeles Coliseum with a former football player turned suspected robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204113000 +0000" stop="20251204120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Sweet Smell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy elderly woman spills a large bottle of perfume in Malloy and Reed's patrol car, resulting in a most unpleasant work day. Meanwhile, a reported burglar in a church office results in a comical case of mistaken identity, a well-meaning man is accused of kidnapping his granddaughter and a young boy asks for help locating his stolen bicycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204120000 +0000" stop="20251204130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1960</sub-title>
    <desc>"From Andy Griffith to JFK, the first year of the Sixties is celebrated!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204130000 +0000" stop="20251204133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Most Interesting Character</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers assigns Beaver's class to write a short essay about the most interesting character they know. While Judy writes about her dad, Beaver debates over whom he should write about. Beaver finally decides to write about Ward, but Beaver isn't sure if Ward is interesting enough.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204133000 +0000" stop="20251204140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Date Committee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally becomes the chairman of the blind date committee for an upcoming dance. However, Wally quickly wants to resign from the position when he can't find anyone to go with the new girl, Jill Bartlett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204140000 +0000" stop="20251204150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Madcap Modiste</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of the biggest names in fashion is poisoned after embarrassing her husband on TV.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204150000 +0000" stop="20251204160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Leanne's ex-husband is charged with a murder, the possible motive makes Matlock despise his former son-in-law more than ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204160000 +0000" stop="20251204170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For An Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The father of a man Gerard prosecuted kidnaps the DA's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204170000 +0000" stop="20251204180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Carousel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When Cindy's father dies, she goes through his things and she finds adoption papers</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204180000 +0000" stop="20251204190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Trip West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A timid bank clerk goes through a surprising change in personality when he's told he only has a short time to live.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204190000 +0000" stop="20251204200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Emmett Dowd arrives at the Ponderosa to take back ranch hand Dave Walker to face trial in Los Angeles. Concerned by the way Dowd treats Walker and believing the man to be innocent, Adam and Hoss go along to make sure Walker reaches Los Angeles alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204200000 +0000" stop="20251204203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Salinas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Banker Hamilton is closing up for the day when Rudy Gray persuades him to stay open for one more transaction—a withdrawal at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204203000 +0000" stop="20251204210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Two Ounces Of Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sammy Davis Jr. stars as Tip Corey, son of a man allegedly murdered in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204210000 +0000" stop="20251204220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sara Proctor Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>"When children's dolls are found mutilated in her possession, passengers believe that Sara Proctor is either deranged or practicing witchcraft. Hale slowly arrives at the real story after Sara confides to him and Charlie's snooping."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204220000 +0000" stop="20251204230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Engine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John buy an old fire engine, and Station 51 gets a new engine. A woman overdoses on LSD and Roy tries to talk her down, leading the two paramedics on a chase to the top of a building. Brackett treats a resilient gunshot victim. A politician suffers a heart attack and the station responds to a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204230000 +0000" stop="20251204233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251204233000 +0000" stop="20251205000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205000000 +0000" stop="20251205003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205003000 +0000" stop="20251205010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205010000 +0000" stop="20251205013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205013000 +0000" stop="20251205020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>High Noon In Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets hysterical when Andy receives a letter from a man he arrested and sent to prison. The convict is to be released soon and says in the letter that he is coming to settle the score with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205020000 +0000" stop="20251205023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Rodeo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray feels tremendous guilt when he cancels plans with Robert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205023000 +0000" stop="20251205030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Tenth Anniversary, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra discovers that Ray taped over their wedding video.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205030000 +0000" stop="20251205033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Fat Hermann, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get a trainload of stolen paintings back to London, but things get complicated when Marya uses Schultz to impersonate Reich Marshall Goehring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205033000 +0000" stop="20251205040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Softer They Fall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kinchloe fights a German boxing champ, creating a diversion for a heist Hogan is planning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205040000 +0000" stop="20251205043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Barby And Ben / Rancid Harvest</sub-title>
    <desc>In Barby and Ben, a toy couple's marriage is threatened by the arrival of a G.I. doll. Then, in Rancid and Harvest, a parody of "Random Harvest", with Carol as Greer Garson, a woman who falls for a man with no memory of his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205043000 +0000" stop="20251205053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Misguided Model</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After he accidentally kills his friend's attacker—and she has him dispose of the body without alerting the authorities—a guilt-stricken ex-boxer decides to report the incident to Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205053500 +0000" stop="20251205060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Purple Testament</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A lieutenant develops the disquieting ability to foresee which of his men will die prior to battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205060500 +0000" stop="20251205070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Diagnosis: Danger  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Health department officials try to stop an anthrax outbreak spreading through Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205070500 +0000" stop="20251205080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search For A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires Mannix to locate a dead body. The twist is that the client is the murderer, a contract killer who wants to clean up after himself, and Mannix somehow fits into his scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205080500 +0000" stop="20251205090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a man who is charged with arson and murder by burning down his textile company which killed his wife who was trapped inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205090500 +0000" stop="20251205100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gathering Of Thieves, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A real-estate scam leads to four murders, including that of a professor who was not pleased with his new property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205100000 +0000" stop="20251205103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205103000 +0000" stop="20251205110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205110000 +0000" stop="20251205113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Trouble In The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a quiet patrol, Reed decides to spend part of his lunch break doing business at his bank while Malloy waits in the patrol car. Unfortunately, he walks into the clutches of a pair of ruthless robbers who take him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205113000 +0000" stop="20251205120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>North Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed volunteers to write a profile on Malloy for the LAPD's magazine to honor his 10th anniversary on the force, but soon discovers he may be in over his head. Out on patrol, an apparent gas station armed robbery gets turned on its head when they question the parties after a long chase, a man goes to extreme lengths to get his neighbor's poodle to stop barking, a woman's plan to get her husband arrested backfires and a liquor store robbery suspect barricades himself inside a house's garage after a high-speed chase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205120000 +0000" stop="20251205130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Twin Connection</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205130000 +0000" stop="20251205133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Bath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June allow Wally to babysit Beaver one evening while they attend a party. However, things go awry when Beaver gets ready to take a bath. He accidentally lets the bathtub overflow, causing the water to leak onto the bathroom floor and into the downstairs ceiling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205133000 +0000" stop="20251205140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A new school year has the bus service being extended to those students living in town. However, after not even a week, Beaver gets suspended from riding the bus after getting into a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205140000 +0000" stop="20251205150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Slandered Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Navy Commander Jerome Burke is assisting the police in the investigation of the murder of a cafe singer. The police believe that a sailor assigned to a Navy submarine committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205150000 +0000" stop="20251205160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Genius  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's nephew, Irwin, is charged with murder, his investigation leads to a high-tech computer firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205160000 +0000" stop="20251205170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Littlest Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lonnie makes a heartbreaking discovery about a woman he dated in high school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205170000 +0000" stop="20251205180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot Rod</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob and Jody open an auto repair place</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205180000 +0000" stop="20251205190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Scot Free</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob Scot leaves his family and prepares to start a new life with Nora Brand—after they dispose of her husband's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205190000 +0000" stop="20251205200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben's past catches up with him when an inspector from New Orleans arrives in Virginia City. It seems Ben is wanted for murder and must go back to face trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205200000 +0000" stop="20251205203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On the trail Len Richards and his brother, Ab, confront a Lucas McCain look-alike, Earl Bantry and his sidekick K.C. Peters, for slaughtering one of Richards' steers. Bantry kills Ab Richards, and Len wants Micah to arrest Lucas for the murder. More problems ensue because of this "evil twin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205203000 +0000" stop="20251205210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark stop on the way to the county fair to deliver a message to Micah, who is on the trail escorting a prisoner scheduled to be hanged. Mark and Lucas recognize the prisoner, Mr. Renolds, as someone who saved Mark's life from a snake bite a few years back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205210000 +0000" stop="20251205220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Emmett Lawton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke Shannon stops in the town High Times and almost right away gets into a fight with, and accidentally kills, one of the gunmen who are essentially holding the town hostage. Then he finds his horse missing and ignores advise to leave."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205220000 +0000" stop="20251205230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Alley Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stray cat decides to have her kittens on John's bed at the station. A family is trapped in a downed airplane. An old man gets his foot caught in a bear trap. A stage actress suffers an anxiety attack. A school develops a gas leak. Roy and John rescue the victim of a boating accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205230000 +0000" stop="20251205233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251205233000 +0000" stop="20251206000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206000000 +0000" stop="20251206003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206003000 +0000" stop="20251206010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206010000 +0000" stop="20251206013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206013000 +0000" stop="20251206020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206020000 +0000" stop="20251206023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Hackidu</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray screws up a "Hackidu" (a la Pokemon) trade for his daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206023000 +0000" stop="20251206030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Debra Makes Something Good</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra finally creates a dish that everyone likes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206030000 +0000" stop="20251206033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Gowns By Yvette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use the wedding of Burkhalter's niece to smuggle a defector out of Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206033000 +0000" stop="20251206040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One Army At A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter convinces the German he is one of them when he is captured in German uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206040000 +0000" stop="20251206043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In George and Zelda, a disguised Carol and Harvey complain to the audience before the show. Then, in The Spy, a WWII bomber pilot jumps without a parachute. Finally, in The Ham Actor, a TV debut for an acting duo goes horribly wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206043000 +0000" stop="20251206053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Positive Negative</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A respected retired general is blackmailed into declining an offer to clean up the city of San Carlos, which is being tarnished by the operations of mobster George Emory. When Emory turns up dead, the general is the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206053500 +0000" stop="20251206060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Elegy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts land on what looks like Earth 200 years before they left—only all of the people seem frozen in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206060500 +0000" stop="20251206070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely Hours  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A renter shows an odd interest in her landlord's kid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206070500 +0000" stop="20251206080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Hardball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A drug dealer and his gang take several hostages, hoping to force Mannix to locate and retrieve another gang member who betrayed them. Mannix fears someone's going to die no matter what he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206080500 +0000" stop="20251206090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Cain's Mark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired when a young brother of a gun manufacturer and collector vanishes from sight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206090500 +0000" stop="20251206100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A comptroller fakes his death to avoid getting arrested for embezzling from an investment firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206100000 +0000" stop="20251206103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo Goes To New York</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A week in New York City transforms Betty Jo from a country girl into a svelte sophisticate.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
