<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809140000 +0000" stop="20250809150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Doomsday Formula</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr.Crane, inventor of a new explosive, is missing along with his daughter. If his "doomsday formula" falls into the wrong hands, especially foreign ones, it could mean the end of the United States. West and Gordon must rescue the professor, his daughter, and the formula before it's too late.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809150000 +0000" stop="20250809160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Wagons Ho!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While preparing to return to St. Joseph, the men read the story "Wagon Ho" written and printed by Samuel T. Evans about his trip as a naive young Irishman headed west and his experiences and adventure on the trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809160000 +0000" stop="20250809170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Comet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Audra befriends a man she finds camping out on Barkley land; she is intrigued by his cynical, poetic manner, and learns he is being pursued by men from his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809170000 +0000" stop="20250809180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A widow arrives in Dodge to witness the shenanigans of town drunk Emil Peck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809180000 +0000" stop="20250809190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Two shady drifters target a friend of Joe's who has just struck gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809190000 +0000" stop="20250809193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Closer Than A Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for answers when recovering alcoholic Micah Torrence returns to the bottle—and turns in his badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809193000 +0000" stop="20250809200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Treasure Of Canyon Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In a ghost town, Lucas, Mark and Micah tangle with the Newman family and learn the secret of the town's 20-year-old mystery of a lost gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809200000 +0000" stop="20250809210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Enormous Fist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Fred Grant slugs Favor, he hits him back. Fred falls, fatally hitting his head against a fencepost. There is an inquest, and Favor has to deal with the widow and her three kids.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809210000 +0000" stop="20250809213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Bostonian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin protects a new landowner from Boston, who is having an escalating feud with an established cattle rancher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809213000 +0000" stop="20250809220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Tyrant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>On the trail of a Cavalry deserter and the horses he stole, Josh rides into a town ruled as the private fiefdom of its autocratic, psychopathic marshal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809220000 +0000" stop="20250810000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>They Stooge To Conga, Three Loan Wolves, Half Wits Holiday, Punchy Cowpunchers, Missed Fortune, Fifi Blows Her Top</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are repairmen who get a job fixing the doorbell in large house, which is the secret headquarters of some Nazi spies.  They manage to ruin most of the house while working on the wiring and then subdue the spies and sink an enemy submarine by remote control. , Told in flash back, the Stooges tell their son how he came to have three fathers.  The Stooges, owners of a pawnshop, owed money to the gashouse protection society, a bunch of loan sharks.  To complicate matters, a lady leaves a baby in the shop as part of a plan to sell a phony diamond and the Stooges wind up caring for the kid.  The Stooges manage to defeat the crooks and when they finish telling the story, the kid goes off to find his real mother. , The Stooges reminisce about their wartime romances in Europe.  After they finish their tales, they discover that Joe's girl Fifi, whom he left behind in Paris, has moved in next door.  The only problem is that she's now married, with a very jealous husband.  The husband turns out to be a real cad, and when Fifi overhears him tell about his plans to find a new wife, she clobbers him and goes back to Joe. , A professor bets one of his colleagues that he can turn the Stooges into gentlemen within 60 days.  With the aid of his pretty daughter, the professor tries to teach the boys proper etiquette.  After many frustrating attempts, he introduces the Stooges into society at a fancy party.  At first things go all right, but the party soon degenerates into a wild pie fight. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are three soldiers assigned to go undercover and spy on an outlaw gang that's terrorizing a nearby town.  The bad guys have the Arizona Kid locked up, so the boys set about rescuing him with the help of beautiful Nell, his girl.  They free the kid, and he rides to summon help.  The Stooges, with the help of Nell, manage to subdue the bad guys before the kid arrives with the cavalry. , Shemp wins $50,000 in a radio contest and the Stooges move into the Hotel Costa Plente where they live it up and wreck their fancy suite.  While they wait for the prize money to arrive, the boys are pursued by three gold-digging dames after their winnings.  When the check arrives however, it's only for $4.85 after tax deductions.  [Basically a remake of "Healthy, Wealthy and Dumb".] "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810000000 +0000" stop="20250810023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Werewolf Of London</sub-title>
    <desc>"The first Universal werewolf film tells the edgy, frightening tale of a British botanist who is cursed with the mark of the wolf after being bitten by a creature in the mountains of Tibet. A true horror classic. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810023000 +0000" stop="20250810030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Better Luck Next Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Robin is left balancing above a tiger pit while Catwoman searches for a hidden treasure using stolen cat statuettes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810030000 +0000" stop="20250810040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Miri</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk and a landing party are stranded on a planet afflicted by a disease that causes adults to die a painful death. What's more, they must deal with hostile children who have survived.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810040000 +0000" stop="20250810043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Flight To The North</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sylvester J. Superman, a backwoods character, reads an ad intended for Superman and mistakenly embarks on a mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810043000 +0000" stop="20250810050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Seven Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A curio dealer sells daggers supposedly bent by Superman himself. When they are used for violence, Superman investigates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810050000 +0000" stop="20250810060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Oasis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Smith eats some alien fruit, which turns him into a giant. Convinced that it was the Robinsons trying to kill him, he plots to take them out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810060000 +0000" stop="20250810070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Ship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After an entire technical crew is murdered by one of its own members aboard the Seaview, Nelson captures the killer and averts an enemy plot to blow up a seven-nation peace conference.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810070000 +0000" stop="20250810080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Six Hours To Live</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant has been framed for a murder he didn't commit and now awaits execution for the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810080000 +0000" stop="20250810090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Alamo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1836, the travelers find themselves trapped with the defenders of the Alamo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810090000 +0000" stop="20250810100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Outpost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent tries to decipher an alien's mysterious message.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810100000 +0000" stop="20250810110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Ark</sub-title>
    <desc>"A silent volcano becomes active and may erupt,so Adams and Nakoma try to save as many animals as possible. Also,a lawman named Pinkerton arrives to capture Adams and take him in for trial. Will the animals or Adams be lost in the end?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810110000 +0000" stop="20250810113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Mastermind Of The Sea</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim with experts from the Seaquarium in Miami set out to capture a porpoise and study its mysterious progress of learning – the hop-skip around the world to see porpoises in far away places as Port Elizabeth, in South Africa; Coolangatta in Australia; and Whaler’s Cove, in Hawaii."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810113000 +0000" stop="20250810120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Animals That Time Forgot</sub-title>
    <desc>"In remote corners of the wild kingdom remaining untouched by forces of change there also remain animals that span the bridge of time back into prehistoric eras…like the Komodo Dragons off the coast of Java; marsupials that are rare and birds that appear as if they just flew out of the still streaming marshlands of the Mesozoic era."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810120000 +0000" stop="20250810123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Strangest Of All</sub-title>
    <desc>"A few of the many bizarre and strange animal behaviors that abound in the wild kingdom, the strangest of all are revealed in this episode."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810123000 +0000" stop="20250810130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>South Through The Sonora</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim travel by jeep at the hottest time of the year to the rugged Sonora Desert in Arizona on a reptile collecting expedition."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810130000 +0000" stop="20250810133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bayou Backwaters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey by flat-bottomed boat into the uncharted, moss-covered silence of the Louisiana bayou country on an animal collecting trip."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810133000 +0000" stop="20250810140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tale Of The Fox</sub-title>
    <desc>"This is the tale of the fox cub as it explores the wild kingdom for the first time in the North Woods of Wisconsin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810140000 +0000" stop="20250810143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Power Of The Press</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter comes home with the great news that he's been given his own column in the school newspaper. He quickly becomes popular with his classmates when they find their names in his newspaper column. This newfound popularity goes to Peter's head, however, as he tries to improve a poor grade in biology by flattering his teacher in the column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810143000 +0000" stop="20250810150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Vote For Brady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg and Marcia rush home after school with the news that they're both running for student body president. The boys and girls each take sides and soon each one of them is accusing the other of sabotage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810150000 +0000" stop="20250810153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>American Musical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Chachi struggles with an essay on the causes, hardships and influences of immigration until Fonzie tells him several stories in a series of musical vignettes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810153000 +0000" stop="20250810160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Bachelor Mothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Date-night drama leads to Lenny and Squggy watching Fonzie's godson for Laverne and Shirley. After the guys give the baby to a man claiming to be its father, chaos ensues when the girls find out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810160000 +0000" stop="20250810163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pickle Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's canning time again, and Aunt Bee has put up another batch of pickles. After realizing the only thing they're good for is killing flies brave enough to land on them, Andy and Barney decide to substitute store-bought for her homemade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810163000 +0000" stop="20250810170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy's Mother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky's mother comes to visit, and poor Lucy can't speak Spanish, so she finds a Spanish-speaking mindreader and it works like a charm—as long as he's around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810170000 +0000" stop="20250810173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has joined an all-male club at school and learns that they are putting on a play. He's not too happy when he learns that the part he's supposed to play is that of a chorus girl. Later, Beaver and Gilbert make matters worse when they stumble upon Wally's costume, a dress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810173000 +0000" stop="20250810180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Day Of School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>The last day of school has each one of Miss Landers' students bringing her a gift. June orders some nice handkerchiefs for the gift and a slip for herself. Beaver mistakes the slip as the gift for Miss Landers and debates on whether or not to give her this very "personal" gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810180000 +0000" stop="20250810183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>What Happened To Shorty?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Shad Heller visits the Clampetts, Jed asks what happened to Shorty Kellems, but Shad doesn't know. Meanwhile, the Clampetts are having food stolen from the root cellar. They decide to investigate during the night and catch Shorty in the kitchen having a snack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810183000 +0000" stop="20250810190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep Shorty in line, Shad has built a cage. Shorty escapes but is soon captured and brought to his wedding rehearsal. The slippery Shorty, however, escapes again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810190000 +0000" stop="20250810193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Nyet, Nyet — Not Yet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Two Russian cosmonauts land on the island in a space capsule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810193000 +0000" stop="20250810200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Hi-fi Gilligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan's mouth becomes a radio after he is accidentally hit on the head. When the castaway's regular radio is broken, Gilligan becomes the sole source of information on an approaching typhoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810200000 +0000" stop="20250810203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>April Fools  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On April Fools' Day, Mama gets the last laugh on the rest of the family when she pulls off the best practical joke ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810203000 +0000" stop="20250810210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Reading The Riot Act  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama starts a campaign to impeach poorly performing Church Lady League President Lolly Purdue, but has a change of heart when she learns a secret about Lolly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810210000 +0000" stop="20250810220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Love, Honor And Obey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A widow plays matchmaker for her sister; Isaac's dental filling receives transmissions; a couple's vow stops at "obey."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810220000 +0000" stop="20250810223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets an offer to become the sheriff of Greendale, and Andy tries to discourage him. Unsure how to handle matters, Andy gets the idea to let Barney be sheriff of Mayberry for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810223000 +0000" stop="20250810230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Denise Davis- Star Trek Memorabilia</sub-title>
    <desc>"Denise Davis may be a Star Trek collector, but she's no typical Trekkie. Her passion for collecting all things Star Trek began after reading collector's books and deciding she too wanted to collect, but not the usual type items. Today Denise will show us her vast as the galaxy collection, including a hard-to-find Lt. Uhara doll, a Star Trek lamp with some serious sentimental connections and even some Star Trek clothespins. We've brought along our expert and fellow Star Trek fan, Mark Short, who'll appraise Denise's collection, and then attempt to make a trade. While Denise is leery of giving up anything in her collection, Mark's  brought an item he knows Denise wants, and hoping resistance is futile."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810230000 +0000" stop="20250810233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250810233000 +0000" stop="20250811000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811000000 +0000" stop="20250811003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Helping Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The rising tide of feminism confronts Archie on all sides when Edith joins a women's group and Irene lands a job alongside him on the loading dock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811003000 +0000" stop="20250811010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria's Shock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria is shocked when Mike announces that he doesn't plan on having children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811010000 +0000" stop="20250811013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Where's Archie (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith holds her first Tupperware party under a cloud of worry when Archie disappears on his way to a union convention in Buffalo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811013000 +0000" stop="20250811020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Is Missing (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>With no word from Archie after twenty-four hours, the family faces the possibility that he might've run off with another woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811020000 +0000" stop="20250811023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Ross Martin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Ross Martin. Originally aired on 11/16/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811023000 +0000" stop="20250811030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nancy Wilson And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nancy Wilson and Bernadette Peters. Originally aired on 09/29/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811030000 +0000" stop="20250811033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Buddy Sorrell, Man And Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Sally wonder if Buddy is having an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811033000 +0000" stop="20250811040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Reception In Albany</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Stuck in a hotel for a family wedding, Rob tries to find a TV for a work project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811040000 +0000" stop="20250811043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Head Of The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tells a newspaper that he's head of the house, but then has to prove it to a co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811043000 +0000" stop="20250811053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Dream Of Genie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man considers several possibilities when offered one wish by a genie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811053000 +0000" stop="20250811060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Tea Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman confronts the wife of a rich man and tries to convince her to give her husband a divorce.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811060000 +0000" stop="20250811070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Cat's Paw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry Collier, newspaper editor and Barney's brother, is killed while trying to establish a link between corrupt Police Chief Abbott and Corley, the head of a ghetto mob who masks his illegal activities with an insurance front company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811070000 +0000" stop="20250811080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Survivors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richard Kimble returns home when he learns his wife's family is in financial trouble. The complications are that his mother-in-law hates him, his sister-in-law loves him, and his father-in-law is being questioned by the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811080000 +0000" stop="20250811090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Group Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell masquerades as an alcoholic to join a therapy session and unmask a psychopathic killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811090000 +0000" stop="20250811093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811093000 +0000" stop="20250811100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811100000 +0000" stop="20250811103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program to help ground based officers better understand the abilities and limitations of helicopter assistance, malloy and reed are selected to be observers on several air support division missions. This morning's missions include a sea</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811103000 +0000" stop="20250811110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed take flight in separate helicopters to provide assistance in the search of a light plane stolen from the los angeles airport by a distraught man. Afterwards, they search for a group of robbery suspects who flee in separate cars, then reed</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811110000 +0000" stop="20250811120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Gut Instinct</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill helps Toony with his gut health!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811120000 +0000" stop="20250811123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Team</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While coaching Beaver's football team, Wally makes up a secret play and Beaver just happens to mention it to Penny who inadvertently passes it on to the opposing team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811123000 +0000" stop="20250811130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Won't Eat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is determined not to eat brussels sprouts and adamantly refuses to eat them when June serves them for dinner. In order to go to a football game, Ward makes Beaver promise that he will eat brussels sprouts the next time they are served. Beaver quickly finds himself confronted with the "deadly" vegetables when the Cleavers go out to eat at a posh restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811130000 +0000" stop="20250811140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crimson Kiss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fay Allison is getting married in a few days to Dane Grover. Her roommate, Anita Bonsal, is having a clandestine affair with a married man, Carver Clement. When Aunt Louise arrives early one morning to see Fay, she finds Fay and Anita both unconscious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811140000 +0000" stop="20250811150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thief: Part 1  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a rare coin dealer is charged with murdering a thieving employee, he hires Matlock to defend him. Tyler is less than thrilled when Matlock enlists the help of a female investigator, and has his own suspicions of her motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811150000 +0000" stop="20250811160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Poor Relations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Comedic episode in which Parker's ne'er-do-well stepfather returns to Sparta with a new wife, a stolen painting and two inept art thieves who are determined to steal the painting back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811160000 +0000" stop="20250811170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly Indian and his grandson visit the mountain to find their family burial ground</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811170000 +0000" stop="20250811180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Durham Bull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang's luck turns around when they come to Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811180000 +0000" stop="20250811190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Decision At Los Robles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After Ben is forced to kill a corrupt town boss, the man's son vows revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811190000 +0000" stop="20250811193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Day At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in an explosion, Lucas fights despair as he prepares for a meeting with a gun-toting enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811193000 +0000" stop="20250811200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Two ex-Confederate officers seek revenge on Lucas. McCain was a lieutenant in the 8th Indiana, which defeated the 12th Cavalry 15 years earlier at the Battle of Fort Donaldson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811200000 +0000" stop="20250811210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Horace Best Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Adams' "distant" cousin Horace arrives hoping to be a wagon master. His trading skills allow him to steal the crew and vendors from Adams, but when Adams confronts him with the decisions he must make on the trail, there are second thoughts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811210000 +0000" stop="20250811220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Simple Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Swamped with paperwork, the paramedics are continually distracted by emergencies: a girl trapped in an overturned car, a beautician who has taken too many diet pills, an elderly man and workers stuck on a blazing ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811220000 +0000" stop="20250811223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811223000 +0000" stop="20250811230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811230000 +0000" stop="20250811233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250811233000 +0000" stop="20250812000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812000000 +0000" stop="20250812003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Farmer Takes A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeff Pruitt, a farmer from the hills, comes to Mayberry in search of a wife. He enlists Barney and Andy's help and ends up picking Thelma Lou!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812003000 +0000" stop="20250812010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Keeper Of The Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie joins a secret club that meets in Jubal Foster's barn. When Jubal burns his own barn down, he attempts to blame the group of boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812010000 +0000" stop="20250812013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Flying Saucer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts see part of the Drysales' new advertising gimmick: Martians and a flying saucer. Drysdale plans to have them fly over the Rose Bowl, throwing out Drysdale Dollars. Jethro thinks they have come for him, since he sees himself as the giant brain of the world. The Clampetts take the Martians in for food, though Granny is not happy about their manners. She ends up blowing up their space ship, a giant balloon, in the Drysdales’ back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812013000 +0000" stop="20250812020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Alice And The Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and Nortons visit the Wedemeyers and the wives believe their husbands are neglecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812020000 +0000" stop="20250812023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Gowns By Yvette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use the wedding of Burkhalter's niece to smuggle a defector out of Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812023000 +0000" stop="20250812030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One Army At A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter convinces the German he is one of them when he is captured in German uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812030000 +0000" stop="20250812033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapped in a recurring nightmare, a man tries to persuade those who are sentencing him to death that the whole scenario is not real.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812033000 +0000" stop="20250812043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Decadent Dean</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends the dean of a prep school on charges of murdering a teacher who had been embezzling and blackmailing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812043500 +0000" stop="20250812050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812050500 +0000" stop="20250812053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>And The Desert Shall Blossom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old men face being evicted from their shack when they show no evidence of self-support.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812053500 +0000" stop="20250812060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Herman And Mrs. Fenimore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Two women scheme to get rid of a rich old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812060500 +0000" stop="20250812070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Times Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating a case, Mannix is attacked and nearly killed. He concludes that someone wants to scare him off of one of the three cases he is currently working on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812070500 +0000" stop="20250812080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Well Remembered Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mobsters kidnap Judge Hayes's daughter, on the orders of their boss who is on trial in Hayes's courtroom. Cannon must find and rescue her before the judge is forced to preside over a miscarriage of justice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812080500 +0000" stop="20250812090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dangerous Affair, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman murders a customer who was going to expose his corrupt business practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812090000 +0000" stop="20250812093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812093000 +0000" stop="20250812100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - Dr-33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Crosby plays a hippie whose wife has been persuaded—by other hippies—to pass bad checks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812100000 +0000" stop="20250812103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed returns from vacation with a full-body sunburn, making for a miserable work day. Out on patrol, he and Malloy respond to a fiery traffic accident, use an informant's tip to track down a drug dealer, search for an armed robbery suspect based on a vehicle description and attempt to rescue two boys after their rowboat capsizes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812103000 +0000" stop="20250812110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>L.a. International</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed barely get acquainted with their fill-in assignment at LAX when a security camera spots a car being stolen from a parking structure. While on foot-beat as Zebra-12 inside the airport, they find a surprise inside of a stolen suitcase, deal with a man who picks the pocket of a returning soldier, chase down a man buying airline tickets with stolen credit cards, escort a runaway boy back to his mother and track down a suspect who robbed a parking structure attendant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812110000 +0000" stop="20250812120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day...august 12th</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812120000 +0000" stop="20250812123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend Beaver made at summer camp, Chopper, stays with the Cleavers for the weekend. Beaver is quickly introduced to Chopper's unusual life; he is the son of parents who have been married and divorced many times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812123000 +0000" stop="20250812130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Becomes A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver and Wally are fishing an abandoned canoe floats up and they responsibly return it to the owner, whose name had been carved in the paddle. However, after telling his friends the story, they adjust it to make it sound as if Beaver had saved a girl from drowning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812130000 +0000" stop="20250812140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Vagabond Vixen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hollywood producer John Addison picks up an attractive young hitchhiker. Far from innocent, she turns out to be a blackmailer and a witness to a murder with which Addison is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812140000 +0000" stop="20250812150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Thief, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock and Tyler realise that part of Linda's deception is routed in the recent kidnapping of her son. While Tyler helps her locate the child, Matlock finds the rare coin he needs to put the finish on the case."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812150000 +0000" stop="20250812160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Dangerous Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill and Harriet's wedding plans are interrupted by a sniper who mistakes Bill for Sheriff McComb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812160000 +0000" stop="20250812170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Seashore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Waltons visit the seashore and stay at the Baldwin's beach home</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812170000 +0000" stop="20250812180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Dealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman resents her suitor more than ever when he kills her father in self-defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812180000 +0000" stop="20250812190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Caution: Easter Bunny Crossing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Dressed as an Easter Bunny and on his way to entertain children at an orphanage, Hoss must first grapple with a gang of inept outlaws.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812190000 +0000" stop="20250812193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Assault</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman can't talk his way out of an assault charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812193000 +0000" stop="20250812200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Short Rope For A Tall Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are in another town to sell a bull to Joe Lovering. While there, Mark buys two horses from Mr. Schneider. Neither Mark nor his father knows that the horses have been illegally bought and resold to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812200000 +0000" stop="20250812210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Albert Farnsworth Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Arrogant British Colonel Albert Farnsworth causes an indian attack that results in the capture of a young girl by the Cheyenne and the mortal wounding of his long time aide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812210000 +0000" stop="20250812220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Tee Vee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The paramedics rescue a man from a manhole fire. Chet and John blow up the station's TV. Dr. Morton treats a man with a bleeding peptic ulcer. An aquarium is delivered to Dr. Brackett, who suffers a toxic reaction to a catfish bite. A man accidentally glues his eyes shut. A gas explosion and mudslide trap a man in his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812220000 +0000" stop="20250812223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812223000 +0000" stop="20250812230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As You Were</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While there are no casualties, Hawkeye and Trapper crate up Frank while he sleeps and receive gorilla suits through the mail. Henry gets a tan and gives another sex orientation lecture. When the wounded start pouring in again, their own side shells the camp, hitting the generator, and Radar tries to get through to tell someone to stop the shelling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812230000 +0000" stop="20250812233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The supply lines to the camp are cut. Radar, the housing officer, starts doubling people up to save fuel and Klinger is thrown out of the nurse's tent. People start burning everything to stay warm while Frank wears his heated socks. The toilet paper supply is worst hit, and then wounded start arriving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250812233000 +0000" stop="20250813000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Burns tries to slap a dishonorable discharge on a decorated soldier who admits to being a homosexual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813000000 +0000" stop="20250813003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bailey's Bad Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich kid Ronald Bailey is jailed when he blatantly defies the law. As Bailey waits for his influential father to bail him out, Andy teaches him the lesson of self-responsibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813003000 +0000" stop="20250813010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manicurist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful manicurist from the city comes to Floyd's to set up shop. She makes all the wives in town extremely nervous as she manicures their husbands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813010000 +0000" stop="20250813013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Are Overdrawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing the pool man putting chlorine in the pool, thinking it is poison, and getting a letter they are overdrawn, the Clampetts think that they are broke and Drysdale is trying to get rid of them. However, this is all a misunderstanding, since the letter Jed got was meant for another J.D. Clampett, Jake, who is an out-of-work actor. When Jake gets Jed’s letter, he takes advantage of the notice that he has $36 million dollars, buying a new car and other things.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813013000 +0000" stop="20250813020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph captures two thugs that followed him home after he witnessed a hold-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813020000 +0000" stop="20250813023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Standing Room Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to save Klink from an officer who plans on turning him in for not having balanced books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813023000 +0000" stop="20250813030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813030000 +0000" stop="20250813033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind And The Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A book on the power of thought enables an irritable man to re-create the world exactly as he wants it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813033000 +0000" stop="20250813043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spurious Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Chapman returns home early from a business trip to find that his wife, Marie, wants a divorce. Chapman is shocked at this turn of events because he thought his wife had recently been strangled to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813043500 +0000" stop="20250813050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813050500 +0000" stop="20250813053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Six People, No Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich man comes back to life to ensure that his funeral is not overly ornate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813053500 +0000" stop="20250813060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Morning After</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother is shocked to learn that her daughter is having an affair with a married man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813060500 +0000" stop="20250813070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Catspaw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning more about a blackmailer than his employer wanted him to know, private detective Tip Ellis turns up dead. Mannix received a letter from his friend shortly before his death, prompting him to investigate the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813070500 +0000" stop="20250813080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Arena Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Socialite Doris Hawthorne's fiance disappears. Only then does she learn he was actually married to a Swiss woman, and also a blackmailing extortionist with a long list of enemies, many of whom want his files.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813080500 +0000" stop="20250813090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Sanctuary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rapist terrorizes a resort where Betty is vacationing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813090000 +0000" stop="20250813093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813093000 +0000" stop="20250813100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813100000 +0000" stop="20250813103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clinic On 18th St</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Abe Strayhorn and his assistants from the major fraud and consumer protection division of the Los Angeles District Attorney's Office launch an investigation into a local doctor following the death of one of his patients, who was found wearing a strange belt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813103000 +0000" stop="20250813110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Team Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program, Malloy and Reed team with Motor Officer Grant to better combat crime. Out on patrol, they make a safety check at a residence, investigate a suspicious witness at the scene of a traffic accident, deal with a young member of a neighborhood watch, respond to an annoying complaint about illegally parked cars and perform a daylight stakeout to catch a serial burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813110000 +0000" stop="20250813120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Tabloid Toony</sub-title>
    <desc>""Cleam Monthly" magazine honors the incredible life of Toony."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813120000 +0000" stop="20250813123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Lifeguard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally is all set to begin his job as a lifeguard but is let down when he learns that had been a mistake and he's not old enough to fill the position, so instead he is hired to sell candy and hot dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813123000 +0000" stop="20250813130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Freckles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clarence gets fed up with Beaver calling him Lumpy, he gives Beaver a new nickname, Freckles. This leads Beaver to become self-conscious about his freckles and takes steps to try to remove them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813130000 +0000" stop="20250813140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Runaway Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed Davenport fears that his wife is trying to poison him. Later, Davenport falls ill and blames her from his deathbed. After he dies, his body disappears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813140000 +0000" stop="20250813150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Model  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock has finally had a breakthrough in the case he was struggling with, but after being hit by a car, he needs to put the case together from scratch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813150000 +0000" stop="20250813160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil Tibbs returns to Sparta and joins the police force as chief of detectives. His arrival is met with resistance from police chief Bill Gillespie - who resents having an officer hired without his approval. Virgil has trouble adjusting to the small, antiquated police force. Tibbs' first case is a racially charged murder case that is soon complicated when the suspect is murdered in his cell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813160000 +0000" stop="20250813170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Volunteer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>GW Haines proposes to Erin</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813170000 +0000" stop="20250813180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Summons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>An outlaw kills his partner thinking he will get a huge reward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813180000 +0000" stop="20250813190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hoss and Joe attempt to make a quick buck selling horses, the enterprise doesn't go exactly as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813190000 +0000" stop="20250813193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Bibs Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor-turned-gunfighter's reputation hangs on one lucky shot—and a lot of gall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813193000 +0000" stop="20250813200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813200000 +0000" stop="20250813210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Allison Justis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When someone yells horse thief, Flint shoots a man only to find he is the husband of a childhood friend. Flint learns the man is mayor and highly respected. The question of whether he killed an innocent man bothers him and the man's son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813210000 +0000" stop="20250813220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>On Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A camera crew follows Squad 51 while a teenager is bitten by a snake, a would-be stuntman dangles from an I-beam, a boy falls off a cliff and a man is trapped under a burning fuel truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813220000 +0000" stop="20250813223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a new batch of mail leaves Trapper depressed, and thinking of desertion, despite Hawkeye's efforts to dissuade him. Meanwhile, Hawkeye learns that he has successfully tricked Frank into buying stocks in a fictitious company, Pioneer Aviation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813223000 +0000" stop="20250813230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Smattering Of Intelligence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A classic episode in which Colonel Flagg and another secret agent from another intelligence agency come to the 4077th to keep their eyes on the camp. Hawkeye and Trapper trick them both into thinking that Burns is a traitor—one thinks he's a fascist, the other thinks he's a communist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813230000 +0000" stop="20250813233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General Flipped At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The MASH 4077th is visted by General Steele. He wishes to move the camp five miles down the road. Hawkeye and Henry are charged with mutiny. And Hawkeye also is charged with impersonating a reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250813233000 +0000" stop="20250814000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rainbow Bridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>As Hawkeye and Trapper are planning to leave for Tokyo, an unusual offer to swap POW patients between the Chinese and the 4077th comes in. Henry, after much debate, agrees to send Hawkeye, Trapper, Frank, Radar and Klinger into enemy territory. Frank almost botches the swap when he brings a squirt gun to the exchange. Fortunately, the Chinese Dr. Lin Tam has a sense of humor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814000000 +0000" stop="20250814003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After a series of mishaps, Henry Bennett gets a reputation in town as a jinx. The more Andy tries to dispel the rumor the deeper the hole gets, until Henry decides it would be best if he left town altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814003000 +0000" stop="20250814010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbreak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>State police come to town in search of payroll robbers. They want Andy and Barney to stay out of the way, but end up needing them more than they thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814010000 +0000" stop="20250814013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Retires</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny announces to the family that she is planning to retire from her doctor’s practice and tells Elly and Jethro she expects one of them to take over. Jed tells this to Jane and Drysdale, also mentioning how she wants her money to take back to the hills. Drysdale plans to get Granny to stay, so he gets Dr. Clyburn to go to the mansion. After Granny reveals why she is really going back to the Hills, to cure what she calls "Granny’s complaint," Clyburn visits the mansion for medical advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814013000 +0000" stop="20250814020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Loudspeaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph writes a speech because he thinks he's going to be Raccoon of the Year—but it turns out Norton receives the honor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814020000 +0000" stop="20250814023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Sergeant's Analyst</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After Burkhalter finds him sleeping on the job, Schultz is ordered to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814023000 +0000" stop="20250814030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814030000 +0000" stop="20250814033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Martian Please Stand Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Troopers follow the tracks from a frozen pond into a diner. Inside they find a soda jerk, a bus driver and his seven passengers. The bus driver is certain only six people boarded his bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814033000 +0000" stop="20250814043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bigamous Spouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a woman discovers that her friend's husband is leading a double life, complete with another wife, she enlists Mason on account that she fears the double-timing husband may try to poison her. But when the husband is found dead, the woman who was fearing for her life is charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814043500 +0000" stop="20250814050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814050500 +0000" stop="20250814053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Personal Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Two engineers fight each other and a mountain to get a tunnel built on time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814053500 +0000" stop="20250814060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Out There - Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman refuses to lend a man $50 to help his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814060500 +0000" stop="20250814070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Save A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a man tells a nun that his false witness statement put an innocent person in prison, Mannix decides to reopen the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814070500 +0000" stop="20250814080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Photo Finish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank agrees to look into a murder, convinced the Indian suspect did not commit the crime. His investigation unearths dozens of missing Indians and a drug smuggling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814080500 +0000" stop="20250814090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Hitch-hike To Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman claiming to be Barnaby's daughter asks him to clear her of false drug charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814090000 +0000" stop="20250814093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814093000 +0000" stop="20250814100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814100000 +0000" stop="20250814103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy invites a troubled boy along on an upcoming week-long group camping trip in the mountains after apprehending him during a burglary, but soon discovers the kid might be too much for him to handle. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a high-speed chase with a taxi, investigate a motorcycle versus pedestrian accident in a parking lot and respond to an armed robbery call.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814103000 +0000" stop="20250814110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Officers Malloy and Woods take a group of children to a youth camp, but Malloy becomes preoccupied with the 14-year-old boy he reluctantly brought along, who continues to compensate for his small stature by getting into trouble. Meanwhile, Reed goes on patrol alone, and deals with a woman who uses a unique weapon to fend off an attacker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814110000 +0000" stop="20250814120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Manners Matter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony calls an etiquette coach to help Bill with his bad manners."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814120000 +0000" stop="20250814123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Big Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Constantly entering contests, Beaver's latest one has him selling raffle tickets in hopes of winning a prize. Surprisingly, he does indeed win third prize and the prize is a $3,500 sports car. However, his dreams are dashed when Eddie's premonition comes true, Ward breaks the news that Beaver can't keep the car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814123000 +0000" stop="20250814130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Lander's Fiancee</sub-title>
    <desc>"While doing some yard work for Miss Landers, Beaver and Whitey witness their favorite teacher in the midst of a gentleman caller, which makes Beaver a bit jealous. However, Beaver gets sick to his stomach when he discovers Miss Landers is engaged to be married and the man he saw was her fiance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814130000 +0000" stop="20250814140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crooked Candle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Martha Bradford is waiting for her appointment at a beauty parlor, she meets Rita Bradford, who apparently also is married to her husband and lives at the same address. Soon, Mr. Bradford turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814140000 +0000" stop="20250814150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cult  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A concerned father travels from Chicago to Atlanta to reclaim his son from a cult. When the cult leader is found dead, Matlock takes the case on behalf of the father's defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814150000 +0000" stop="20250814160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The investigation into the brutal murders of a young girl and the suspect in her death, leads Tibbs and Gillespie to the son of one of Sparta's wealthiest and most influential citizens. As they come closer to the truth things become dangerous for Virgil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814160000 +0000" stop="20250814170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandchild - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen gives birth to the Waltons' first grandchild</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814170000 +0000" stop="20250814180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Dreamers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A miner tries to use his new-found wealth to win over Kitty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814180000 +0000" stop="20250814190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>What Are Pardners For?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss tries to prevent two men he meets on the trail from committing a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814190000 +0000" stop="20250814193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814193000 +0000" stop="20250814200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814200000 +0000" stop="20250814210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jose Morales Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Hawkes is leading three wagons through indian territory. They run into trouble with Mexician bandits lead by Lee Marvin. When the two groups must band together to fight off an indian attack, certain biases and assumptions are thrown away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814210000 +0000" stop="20250814220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communications</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A young worker gets his arm caught in a machine. A communication snafu occurs between Squad 51 and the hospital. Dr. Morton treats a young violinist. Two boys get a car trapped on the roof of a house. A woman tries to commit suicide by overdosing and won't let the paramedics treat her, making them wait until she passes out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814220000 +0000" stop="20250814223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officer Of The Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Henry is away in Seoul, Burns and Houlihan are in charge, and Hawkeye is the officer of the day. His refusal to release a wounded Korean soldier, wanted by US Intelligence, leads to a confrontation with Colonel Flagg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814223000 +0000" stop="20250814230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Iron Guts Kelly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>General 'Iron Guts' Kelly arrives for an inspection, and ends up dying in Margaret's tent. Hawkeye and Trapper help the General's aide smuggle him out of camp. The next day he is reported killed at the front, as that is where he would have wanted to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814230000 +0000" stop="20250814233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>O.r.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The O.R. is filled with more wounded than the unit can handle. Hawkeye does heart massage on a soldier, which saves his life, but he dies four hours later. Sidney Freedman drops in during the deluge, and is dragged into the fray by Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250814233000 +0000" stop="20250815000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Springtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When spring arrives, Klinger gets word from home that his sweetheart back in Toledo wants to marry him. Henry arranges for Father Mulcahy to do this over short wave radio. Radar falls in love with a nurse, while a grateful patient won't leave Hawkeye alone, and even threatens Major Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815000000 +0000" stop="20250815003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Medal For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his heart set on winning a medal in a foot race at the town picnic. When he loses, he exhibits poor sportmanship. Andy teaches him a lesson about being a good sport.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815003000 +0000" stop="20250815010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815010000 +0000" stop="20250815013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampett Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is getting tired of the clan’s sixty-eight million dollars. When three struggling college girls visit the Clampetts asking for a donation to help them out, Jed hands over a check for their entire fortune. The Clampetts are flat broke, and they have never been happier, though Drysdale is now in a wreck. They pack up to head back to the hills, but end up running out of gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815013000 +0000" stop="20250815020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815020000 +0000" stop="20250815023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Crittendon's Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon is the only one to avoid capture when he and his commandos parachute into the area during a mission to capture Rommel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815023000 +0000" stop="20250815030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to think he is about to capture a POW escape ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815030000 +0000" stop="20250815033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsolete Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a future state where religion and books have been banned, a librarian is judged obsolete and sentenced to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815033000 +0000" stop="20250815043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Floating Stones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that her recently deceased father's office manager has made off with his small fortune in diamonds. She is eager to apprehend the crook, but before the thief can be brought to justice, he is found with a knife in his back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815043500 +0000" stop="20250815050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815050500 +0000" stop="20250815053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Total Loss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has problems keeping her husband's company solvent after his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815053500 +0000" stop="20250815060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Dark Step</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to get away from one woman so he can marry another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815060500 +0000" stop="20250815070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Nightshade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>TV star and comedian Danny Brite is blackmailed by a Vietnam veteran who has a photo showing Brite's son, Joey, murdering a sergeant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815070500 +0000" stop="20250815080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Duel In The Desert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Years earlier, Mel Danvers organized a successful hijacking and walked away with a cool million. But there is a witness: a stewardess. Danvers engineers a campaign of terror to keep her mum, until Cannon puts a stop to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815080500 +0000" stop="20250815090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nest Of Scorpions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. goes to a mountain resort to find real estate developer who's gone missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815090000 +0000" stop="20250815093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815093000 +0000" stop="20250815100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815100000 +0000" stop="20250815103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Roll Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An anonymous call of shots fired over the radio leads to an 'Emergency!' roll call and frantic search for Motor Officer Grant. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed respond to a citizen report of an armed robbery in progress at a bar, and Reed goes undercover as a pizza delivery driver to bust a dangerous scam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815103000 +0000" stop="20250815110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspect Number One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to find a way to help a 60-year-old career criminal he arrested 10 years ago, who was recently released and begs to be re-arrested so he can spend his retirement years in the federal penitentiary. Meanwhile, he and Reed become suspicious while investigating an apparent home burglary, and later respond to a bank robbery in progress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815110000 +0000" stop="20250815120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Yellow Belly Chickens</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill rejoins his pee-wee baseball league to settle some old scores."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815120000 +0000" stop="20250815123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Double Cross</sub-title>
    <desc>"Eddie crawls through the Cleaver house spreading the news that he's going steady with Caroline Schuster, something that worries June who doesn't want Wally to get any ideas about going steady. However, Wally has other worries when he overhears Caroline saying that she's only using Eddie while her boyfriend is grounded. Leaving Wally with the decision to tell Eddie or not."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815123000 +0000" stop="20250815130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's I.q.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning that he's going to be taking an I.Q. test, Beaver hits the books, scared after his friends tell him that if he doesn't pass he will be sent to "dumb school."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815130000 +0000" stop="20250815140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Negligent Nymph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Paul Drake are on a fishing trip when they spot a young woman being pursued by vicious guard dogs on an island estate. After the two men pull her from the ocean, it is discovered that in her possession is a note intended for her employer, accusing him of killing his rich uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815140000 +0000" stop="20250815150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Getaway  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An ex-convict is arrested for robbing the same bank he robbed years earlier. Matlock knows he didn't do it and has a star witness, who won't talk unless Matlock gets his father out of prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815150000 +0000" stop="20250815160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Road Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The affair between the husband of a wealthy woman and her distant cousin leads to her murder. Virgil immediately suspects the pair. But he has a difficult time persuading Gillespie, who is a longtime friend of the man and Bubba, who has been seeing the cousin. Bubba and Virgil clash again and Virgil is frustrated when the Chief rejects his theory about the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815160000 +0000" stop="20250815170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandchild - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen gives birth to the Waltons' first grandchild</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815170000 +0000" stop="20250815180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A young rider is wounded when he's suspected of being a horse thief's accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815180000 +0000" stop="20250815190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Circumstance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After the other Cartwrights leave on a cattle drive, Joe stays behind to tend to the Ponderosa and gets seriously injured by a berserk horse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815190000 +0000" stop="20250815193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815193000 +0000" stop="20250815200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815200000 +0000" stop="20250815210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess Of A Lost Tribe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ordered by Major Adams to guide three passengers to a campsite up a haunted mountain, Flint does so but with caution: rumors that an escaped group of Aztecs now live there, almost 400 years after Cortez wiped them all out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815210000 +0000" stop="20250815220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>To Buy Or Not To Buy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy thinks about buying a house, but delays too long. Responding to a fire, the firemen find two children trapped on the second floor. Two driving students are involved in a minor collision. Another traffic accident results in two injuries and a missing dog. A teenage epileptic is stranded on a concrete beam under a bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815220000 +0000" stop="20250815223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Check-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper gets an ulcer and a ticket home. Unfortunately, his going-away party is spoiled by a new Army regulation, which forces him to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815223000 +0000" stop="20250815230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life With Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail from home worries Henry that Lorraine may be seeing other men. Father Mulcahy presides over a Jewish circumcision ceremony for the Korean-born son of a US GI.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815230000 +0000" stop="20250815233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Alcoholics Unanimous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry's departure to Tokyo leaves Major Burns in charge of the 4077th. He declares total prohibition of alcohol, which leads to a near riot in the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250815233000 +0000" stop="20250816000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>There Is Nothing Like A Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses are evacuated when the threat of an enemy parachute drop arises. Hawkeye and Trapper try to enliven everyone's spirits while they are gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816000000 +0000" stop="20250816003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a sort of publicity stunt, the town decides to pull over the first car that drives through Mayberry and make its occupant the town's guest of honor. That lucky driver? A recently released convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816003000 +0000" stop="20250816010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling salesman Bert Miller is getting tired of traveling, so Andy and Barney plan to help him set up a small general goods shop on a vacant lot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816010000 +0000" stop="20250816013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Indians Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When she hears Native Americans are visiting Beverly Hills, Granny is worried about an Indian attack on their land. Drysdale, on the other hand, is worried about losing the Clampett land. However, the two Native Americans who visit, Chief Running Wolf and his son, Little Fox, come to talk and visit with Jed and Jethro.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816013000 +0000" stop="20250816020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Opportunity Knock But</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Ed play pool with Ralph's boss and Ed gets a job at the bus company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816020000 +0000" stop="20250816023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cuisine A La Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau decides to escape leaving the camp without a chef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816023000 +0000" stop="20250816030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Experts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan saves a German radio expert whom the Nazis want to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816030000 +0000" stop="20250816033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and a woman, on opposite sides of a future war, encounter each other in a deserted town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816033000 +0000" stop="20250816043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Festive Felon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy but dying Bebe Brent gives the bulk of her estate to her loyal nurse. Needless to say, this act angers the remainder of the Brent clan and leads to a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816043500 +0000" stop="20250816050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816050500 +0000" stop="20250816053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Morning Of The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman is apprehensive about meeting her future mother-in-law for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816053500 +0000" stop="20250816060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Diamond Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is told he has to retire from his job at the jewelry store where he has worked most of his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816060500 +0000" stop="20250816070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Babe In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After an engineer is shot, Mannix is hired to retrieve important construction plans, which may have been taken by the shooter. This leads Mannix to the discovery that the man led a double life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816070500 +0000" stop="20250816080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Where's Jennifer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxer Ron Johnson's manager convinces him that he killed a man in a barroom brawl, and uses that control to get the fighter to throw a bout so he can collect a fortune in unfair wages. Johnson's fiancee hires Cannon to dig him out from under.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816080500 +0000" stop="20250816090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A millionaire hires Barnaby to rescue his son from kidnappers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816090000 +0000" stop="20250816093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Billie Jo's First Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate is unhappy when Billie Jo lands a job as secretary to novelist Oliver Fenton, who has written books that are banned in Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
