<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111040000 +0000" stop="20260111050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Space Seed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise picks up a crew of genetic supermen from the 20th century, and their leader, Khan, plans to create a new empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111050000 +0000" stop="20260111053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Knight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The leader of "The Society for the Preservation of Knighthood and Dragons" steals a suit of armor and plans to do away with the other members to steal their money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111053000 +0000" stop="20260111060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric professor discovers a way to focus space-borne Kryptonite particles into a beam to disarm Superman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111060000 +0000" stop="20260111070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Adventure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After leaving their planet, Dr. Smith manages to plot a course back to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111070000 +0000" stop="20260111080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Fossil Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview battles hostile fossil men who wish to take over the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111080000 +0000" stop="20260111090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Marionettes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Earthlings help a sympathetic Giant puppeteer as his new puppets, the circus owner becomes suspicious and plans to collect the reward for their capture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111090000 +0000" stop="20260111100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Rendezvous With Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug find themselves back in 1912 aboard the ill-fated Titanic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111100000 +0000" stop="20260111110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Leeches</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The president of an electronics company fears aliens are kidnapping prominent minds -- and he's next!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111110000 +0000" stop="20260111120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>A Gentleman Tinker</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mad Jack overhears a short Irishman and Tinker (Inventor) discussing gold. Thinking he's found a leprechaun,that'll lead to a pot of gold, he tells Adams. Adams doubts him though,so Jack must prove he's wasn't seeing and hearing things."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111120000 +0000" stop="20260111123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Unwanted Cougar</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the cougar’s northernmost range, the Rocky Mountains of British Columbia, a mother cougar roams with her yearling cub, until the new litter comes along.  Then she must savagely chase the year old cub away."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111123000 +0000" stop="20260111130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Year Of The Otter</sub-title>
    <desc>"In a small Wisconsin lake, two otters are born.  We follow the appealing animals through the first year of their lives."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111130000 +0000" stop="20260111133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Hippo!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin Perkins, Jim Fowler and Stan Brock journey to Kruger National Park in South Africa to go after one of the most difficult to capture of all the world’s wild animals…the hippo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111133000 +0000" stop="20260111140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Condor</sub-title>
    <desc>"High over the mountains of Peru spirals a giant of the skies: the Andean condor. Jim Fowler and Marlin Perkins join an expedition to catch the giant birds and attach tracking gear on them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111140000 +0000" stop="20260111143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Experiment At Doddieburn</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin Perkins visits the Dobbieburn Ranch to find out if the techniques of cattle ranching can be used to domesticate the wild animals of Africa."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111143000 +0000" stop="20260111150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Danger: Wild Animals</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim demonstrate how to handle dangerous animals of the zoo and the wild."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111150000 +0000" stop="20260111153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Kelly's Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Brady's friends, the Kellys, adopt three boys, all of different ethnic backgrounds, and soon find themselves dealing with racist neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111153000 +0000" stop="20260111160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Grand Canyon Or Bust (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping the jail cell, Mike and Peter return with the prospector, who apologizes for locking them up and stealing their car. Later, the Bradys finally arrive in the Grand Canyon and set up camp. Later, the family is thrown into a panic when Bobby and Cindy get lost in the canyon while chasing an Indian boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111160000 +0000" stop="20260111163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Giant Jackrabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>At the mansion, the clan is in need of food because the hunting in Beverly Hills is horrible. They call a catering company, but get mean-mouthed. At the bank, Drysdale gets a call and learns that he got a kangaroo from a friend and it is at his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111163000 +0000" stop="20260111170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick arrives with his daughter, Essiebelle. He found love letters Jethro wrote to his daughter, a beauty contest winner. He plans to get Jethro and Essiebelle married so he can get his paws in the Clampett fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111170000 +0000" stop="20260111173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111173000 +0000" stop="20260111180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Has Her Eyes Examined</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy finally gets her chance to be in show business when she tricks Ricky into letting her do the jitterbug in one of his shows. She's terrific during rehearsals, but problems occur before the show when the eye doctor puts eyedrops in Lucy's eyes to relax them—making her vision blurry for the next 24 hours!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111180000 +0000" stop="20260111183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Poster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers is having Beaver's class do projects on the colonial period and Beaver is one of three students creating posters. Whoever makes the best one gets a prize and Beaver is sure that Ward will paint the poster for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111183000 +0000" stop="20260111190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's Helper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighborhood cleaning woman, Mrs. Manners, gets a request from June asking her to help out a couple times during the week. Mrs. Manners is too busy herself but instead sends over her daughter, a girl whom Wally instantly falls for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111190000 +0000" stop="20260111200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>The Mexican Connection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie assigns the girls to find the saboteurs of a charter plane carry a cache of heroin. They travel south of the border to Mexico, their mission known only to the lone-surviving pilot of the ill-fated flight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111200000 +0000" stop="20260111210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Passport To Murder</sub-title>
    <desc>"On a Mexican fishing trip, the Harts must save Max's old friend from being extorted by drug traffickers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111210000 +0000" stop="20260111220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Prince, The / Sheriff, The</sub-title>
    <desc>"John Burke's fantasy comes true when he discovers the man responsible for his partner's death was arrested. If it hadn't been for Julie, innocent people wound have been killed and they now have a life to share. A handsome rich man becomes the noblest of all when the "Prince" becomes a nobody on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111220000 +0000" stop="20260111230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Love Boat Musical (my Ex-mom / The Show Must Go On / The Pest / My Aunt, The Worrier) (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"The crew surprises Captain Stubing with the news that they are putting on a musical revue as entertainment for the passengers, with a script co-written by Gopher and Isaac. The Captain publicly declines to play the lead role in it, but privately fantasizes about being in it and even practices for it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111230000 +0000" stop="20260111233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260111233000 +0000" stop="20260112000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Meet Larry Strauss</sub-title>
    <desc>"After the beloved actress Charlotte Rae passed away in 2018, her son, Larry Strauss, inherited her personal collection of memorabilia – a collection that chronicles Charlotte’s illustrious career in showbiz. Now, Larry and our host, Lisa Whelchel, who was Charlotte’s longtime friend and colleague, want to share these incredible treasures with the world. The collection includes the master recording of Charlotte’s 1955 solo album, Songs I Taught My Mother, as well as many valuable television props, like a wardrobe hat from Sesame Street and two amazing set props from The Facts of Life. Joining Larry on this special episode of Collector’s Call is his daughter, Carly, and we’ve brought in archivist and pop culture historian Rob Klein to put an estimated value on the collection. Lisa also has something very special to share with Larry; plus legendary comedian (and fellow Facts of Life star) Geri Jewell stops by to chat, and to shock us with her own remarkable treasure."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112000000 +0000" stop="20260112003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112003000 +0000" stop="20260112010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112010000 +0000" stop="20260112013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Road Back (part 2 Of Bitter Pill)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A despondent Archie retreats to his bedroom, until Harry offers to bail him out with a partnership offer for the bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112013000 +0000" stop="20260112020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Eats And Runs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home for a nice dinner that Edith has prepared: beef and mushroom stew. Later, when Mike comes to the table for dinner, he finds Archie has completely finished his meal and then breaks the news that there has been a recall at the supermarkets of a certain brand of mushroom. Convinced that he has food poisoning, Archie rushes down to the hospital for treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112020000 +0000" stop="20260112023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Sings The Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria comes home from work one evening in a total apathetic mood. When Archie tries to find out what's wrong with her, she snaps at him and storms off. Later, Edith gets to the bottom of Gloria's mood when she confides in Edith that she thinks that she has temporarily fallen out of love with Mike (something that Edith confesses happened to her and her feelings for Archie). Meanwhile, Archie and Mike prepare for a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112023000 +0000" stop="20260112030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The family relives Mike and Gloria's blind date where they first insulted each other and ended up having sex in the kitchen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112030000 +0000" stop="20260112033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Pet The Bunny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie is upset that Ray didn't write a eulogy for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112033000 +0000" stop="20260112040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Who Am I?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray admits he no longer enjoys his juvenile pursuits with his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112040000 +0000" stop="20260112043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Happy Spangler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob returns a favor and hires an old friend and immediately regrets it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112043000 +0000" stop="20260112050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Never Name A Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob brings home two ducklings from the show, and Richie wants to keep them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112050000 +0000" stop="20260112053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Glove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is getting the apartment re-decorated for free but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112053000 +0000" stop="20260112060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flight 33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial aircraft mysteriously travels back through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112060000 +0000" stop="20260112070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Anyone For Murder?  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A psychologist offers a unique solution for miserable marriages: murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112070000 +0000" stop="20260112080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Connection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reese Dolan is the new Syndicate heroin distributor on the East Coast. Dolan uses an island base off the coast of northwest Africa and is going to use it as a distribution point for heroin into the U.S. The IMF must identify his overseas opium source and put an end to Dolan's operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112080000 +0000" stop="20260112090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>When The Wind Blows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>In rural Wyoming, Kimble seeks refuge from the local constable at a small hotel run by Lois Carter, a young widow who hires him as a handyman. Kimble soon befriends Lois' son Kenny, a particularly sensitive young boy who protects Kimble from the police wh</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112090000 +0000" stop="20260112100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Material Witness</sub-title>
    <desc>"Pressed into service by the police, Harry Orwell must protect an eyewitness against attempts to assassinate her before she can testify against a murderer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112100000 +0000" stop="20260112103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112103000 +0000" stop="20260112110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112110000 +0000" stop="20260112113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 112 -- You Blew It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The shift starts with the officers talking about another officer's judgment. Little do they realize they will be facing the same problem several times during the shift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112113000 +0000" stop="20260112120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 51 -- A Jumper - Code Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have one of those nights where they either have no calls or minor issues they can do nothing about. But at the end of the shift, Malloy must cook up a dangerous solution to a suicide jumper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112120000 +0000" stop="20260112130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Art Of The Con</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony look at some of the biggest cons and conartists of all time!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112130000 +0000" stop="20260112133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Dramatic Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After joining the dramatic club at school, Beaver is given the lead role in a play. However, after reading the script, he discovers he must kiss a girl and wants out of the production.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112133000 +0000" stop="20260112140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Dudley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A close friend of June's moves into the neighborhood and June arranges to have Wally show the new kid, Dudley, around school. However, everyone thinks Dudley is a creep and Eddie and Lumpy plan to make a fool of Dudley at a party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112140000 +0000" stop="20260112150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Torrid Tapestry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Having served a six-year prison sentence for a fire he didn't start, Claude Demay has devised a plan to expose the real criminal, Leonard Voss, who tried to burn down a warehouse containing a valuable art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112150000 +0000" stop="20260112160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Brennan  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock vies with a formidable district attorney while defending a client accused of killing a city councilwoman, discovering a secret hiding in the man's past that is affecting his judgment in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112160000 +0000" stop="20260112170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>By The Numbers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A winning lottery ticket drags an army private into the murky world of mob politics.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112170000 +0000" stop="20260112180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Dust Bowl Cousins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>John's cousin, her husband and children seek refuge in Walton's Mountain after losing their Kansas farm to the Dust Bowl</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112180000 +0000" stop="20260112190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Dry Road To Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt investigates why a gunman is stalking a temperance preacher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112190000 +0000" stop="20260112200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Duke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After a cruel prizefighter beats up a man in a bar fight, the Cartwrights challenge him to a bout with John Heenan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112200000 +0000" stop="20260112203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark manages to capture a hawk, but then falls into danger from a rattlesnake. When a stranger comes to his rescue, the grateful Mark invites the man home, unaware that he is on the run from the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112203000 +0000" stop="20260112210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Three-legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rambunctious teenager wrecks a schoolroom, Lucas McCain, as a member of the North Fork school board, asks the boy's reluctant uncle to pay for the damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112210000 +0000" stop="20260112220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Herman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>"Don Brooke is desperate for money for his pregnant wife Bonnie, who's condition is too delicate for the long trip without more medical care so he seeks a bank loan. When he sees an opportunity at the bank, it leads to tragedy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112220000 +0000" stop="20260112230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Daisy's Pick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny competes for a date with a new nurse. The paramedics rescue an engineer frozen to refrigeration equipment, a man whose hands are glued to his model ship, a comatose child and an injured man trapped in a theater fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112230000 +0000" stop="20260112233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260112233000 +0000" stop="20260113000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113000000 +0000" stop="20260113003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113003000 +0000" stop="20260113010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113010000 +0000" stop="20260113013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113013000 +0000" stop="20260113020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113020000 +0000" stop="20260113023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert Needs Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra decide to lend Robert $1,000.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113023000 +0000" stop="20260113030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sigh, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray decides to give Debra exclusive use of their bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113030000 +0000" stop="20260113033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113033000 +0000" stop="20260113040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113040000 +0000" stop="20260113043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Bus Stop, strangers at a bus stop rush to answer the phone, which may be a quiz show. Then, in Brief Encounter, a film parody, Carol and Roddy have a romantic encounter using only one-word responses. Finally, in The Family, Eunice's successful brother returns home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113043000 +0000" stop="20260113053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Robert Crane is charged with the murder of his sister's estranged husband, Mason needs the testimony of sister Helen Reed to clear him of the charge. Unfortunately for all concerned, Helen suffers from multiple personality disorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113053500 +0000" stop="20260113060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Dingle, The Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Martians give Luther Dingle the strength of 300 men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113060500 +0000" stop="20260113070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Beast In View  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A woman fears that her brother's ex-fiancée is going to kill her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113070500 +0000" stop="20260113080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Comes Up Roses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find an airport security officer's wife, but gets no cooperation. It seems that Rose Anderson does not wish to be found—or someone does not wish her to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113080500 +0000" stop="20260113090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A serial murder targets Cannon as his next victim. At first the homicide wanted to be finally released from his compulsion to kill. Cannon accepted to help him. But Cannon got too involved in the killer's demands."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113090500 +0000" stop="20260113100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Honeymoon With Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby searches for a woman who disappeared on her wedding day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113100000 +0000" stop="20260113103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Dognappers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon set out to muzzle thieves who steal dogs and then collect hefty rewards from the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113103000 +0000" stop="20260113110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Persons - The Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Working with the slimmest of leads, police attempt to identify a woman's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113110000 +0000" stop="20260113113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 73 -- I'm Still A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While Malloy is attending college, radicals learn he is a cop. They reject him and antagonize him on the job. After helping arrest demonstrators, his new car is vandalized. When a timer is found missing, he locates and disarms a bomb using it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113113000 +0000" stop="20260113120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 102 -- We Can't Just Walk Away From It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to a call about a drug overdose and track the drugs to a 17-year-old who has barricaded himself in his room with a gun and threatens kill himself. They contend with a distraught mother and an overbearing father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113120000 +0000" stop="20260113130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Close Encounter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Professional allligator wrangler, Frank Robb, teaches Bill how to wrangle a gator."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113130000 +0000" stop="20260113133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Spends The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally invites Eddie to spend the night. However, during a game of chess, Eddie accuses Wally of cheating and they get into a big argument ending with Wally ordering Eddie to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113133000 +0000" stop="20260113140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Report Card</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets out of school early to go to the dentist, which prompts Gilbert to drop off his report card. However, Eddie and Lumpy get a hold of it and Eddie decides to alter Beaver's arithmetic grade from a D- to a B+.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113140000 +0000" stop="20260113150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Violent Vest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Advertising executive Herman Albright is in the wrong place at the wrong time wearing the wrong clothes. These mistakes cost poor Herman his life in a case of mistaken identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113150000 +0000" stop="20260113160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The P.i.  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A private investigator's daughter shoots some photos that get the wrong man accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113160000 +0000" stop="20260113170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Yesterday Dies And Tomorrow Won't Be Born</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When McGarrett is shot and badly wounded on a beachside jog, Danno and the team work feverishly to find the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113170000 +0000" stop="20260113180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Baldwin sisters plan to hold a family reunion when their cousin Homer visits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113180000 +0000" stop="20260113190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty Miles From Dodge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of outlaws abducts Kitty and her fellow stagecoach passengers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113190000 +0000" stop="20260113200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Little Joe is on his way back home with a beautiful white stallion, a birthday gift to Ben, when an Indian uprising breaks out, cutting him off from the fort where he is to meet his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113200000 +0000" stop="20260113203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The McCains try to be tolerant of their embittered neighbor, Abel MacDonald, who tells Lucas to keep off his land and won't allow his son to become friends with Mark. However, McCain decides he's gone too far when he won't allow his injured boy to get medical treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113203000 +0000" stop="20260113210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfounded rumor causes North Fork's outspoken feminist schoolteacher to be attacked by a mob of angry townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113210000 +0000" stop="20260113220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bonnie Brooke Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>"Teacher Mary Lee McIntosh refuses to pay what she feels is an excessive fee to join the wagon train, so she decides instead to follow behind it in her wagon alone, and refuses help from Hale. But after her wagon overturns, things change."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113220000 +0000" stop="20260113230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Quicker Than The Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A pregnant woman accidentally shoots herself. Tired of Chet's antics, the station gets their revenge by playing a practical joke of their own. A construction worker caught under a boat refuses an IV, and a man in an accident communicates through the use of his thumb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113230000 +0000" stop="20260113233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260113233000 +0000" stop="20260114000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114000000 +0000" stop="20260114003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114003000 +0000" stop="20260114010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114010000 +0000" stop="20260114013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114013000 +0000" stop="20260114020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rehabilitation Of Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to use psychology to reform Otis of his drinking habit but this eventually leads Otis to "take his business" elsewhere—the jail in Mt. Pilot!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114020000 +0000" stop="20260114023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Annoying Kid, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra are excited to have finally met a couple who are just like them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114023000 +0000" stop="20260114030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>She's The One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray sees Robert's date do something really strange.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114030000 +0000" stop="20260114033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The 43rd, A Moving Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Plans to destroy an anti-aircraft battery are upset by Klink's new executive officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114033000 +0000" stop="20260114040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114040000 +0000" stop="20260114043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests John Byner And Francine Beers</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Diner, two robbers pose as cook and waitress when the police interrupt their hold-up at a restaurant. Then, in Carol and Sis, Carol and Harvey's anniversary is ruined by a house guest. Finally, in Humanoids, two female robots compete to see which is better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114043000 +0000" stop="20260114053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Empty Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Doris Hocksley is shown a personal ad in a Los Angeles newspaper for locating the daughter of Adam Hocksley and providing proof of same. A friend, John Lowell, suggests she pursue the idea to prove she is the rightful heir to the Adam Hocksley estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114053500 +0000" stop="20260114060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Mover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man discovers that his business partner has the ability to control objects with his mind, the pair head to Vegas to win big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114060500 +0000" stop="20260114070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Behind The Locked Door  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Gloria Swanson plays a woman determined to protect her daughter from a fortune hunter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114070500 +0000" stop="20260114080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Point</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded boy gives Mannix a clue suggesting corruption, and then disappears, kidnapped by a criminal gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114080500 +0000" stop="20260114090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady journalist is forced to reveal her sources in a murder news or she will go to jail on a contempt charge. She enlist Cannon's service to unravel the murder of a missing excursionist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114090500 +0000" stop="20260114100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Alpha-bravo War, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A test missile misfires, causing a death and raising Barnaby's suspicions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114100000 +0000" stop="20260114103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - The Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Other people's credit cards are found in the possession of a forest ranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114103000 +0000" stop="20260114110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday arrests a member of his class for possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114110000 +0000" stop="20260114113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 152 -- A Dead Cop Can't Help Anyone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to shield an impressionable Reed from Officer Ed Wells, a shoot-first-ask-questions-later style officer. Wells' reckless philosophy endangers his own safety when he responds to a sniper, forcing them to come to his rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114113000 +0000" stop="20260114120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 12: He – He Was Trying To Kill Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"Malloy and Reed investigate a case of child neglect."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114120000 +0000" stop="20260114130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toon In's Wellness Wednesday: The Healing Power Of Laughter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Quizzer learn the healing power of laughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114130000 +0000" stop="20260114133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mistaken Identity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer catches Richard throwing rocks at the windows of an old abandoned house. When asked for his name, he tells the officer it is Theodore Cleaver. Meanwhile, Ward has joined a committee to organize a youth center.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114133000 +0000" stop="20260114140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Dream Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally falls head over heels for a popular girl in school, Ginny Townsend. To get them together, June slyly invites Ginny on a picnic and the Cleaver's quickly discover that Ginny is not exactly a barrel of laughs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114140000 +0000" stop="20260114150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Misguided Missile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Jerry Reynolds, an old war buddy of Mason's, is accused of killing an officer at Vandenburg Air Force Base during the investigation into mysterious missile crashes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114150000 +0000" stop="20260114160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cult  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A concerned father travels from Chicago to Atlanta to reclaim his son from a cult. When the cult leader is found dead, Matlock takes the case on behalf of the father's defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114160000 +0000" stop="20260114170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Deathwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett must protect a mob underboss so he is able to testify against his superior, Joe Matsukino. However, Matsukino has many tricks up his sleeve to silence his former colleague permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114170000 +0000" stop="20260114180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Minstrel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young wandering musician visits the Mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114180000 +0000" stop="20260114190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Pariah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An immigrant's life improves after he kills an outlaw—at least for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114190000 +0000" stop="20260114200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Cutthroat Junction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Virginia City is about to become a ghost town when the lifeline to the outside world, the stage line, is threatened to be cut off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114200000 +0000" stop="20260114203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When his employer begins to suspect him of embezzlement, bookkeeper Asa Manning decides to hire a professional gunman to take care of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114203000 +0000" stop="20260114210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Although a drought has forced local cowhands to seek work on a railroad construction project, railroad executives are afraid that their workers will desert them if they believe an old man's claim that he has found a way to make rain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114210000 +0000" stop="20260114220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain Sam Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"Tough and headstrong female ferryboat captain Samantha Stewart is asked by her son Johnny and his bride to accompany them on the wagon train to California, where they will board a ship for a Pacific voyage. But actually, Johnny is not telling his proud mother that her doctor has told him that she must stay with a dry climate on land or she will die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114220000 +0000" stop="20260114230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy consider trading cars. A frat pledge chokes during initiation. Dixie takes on hospital management after budget cuts affect her nursing staff. A young patient cures Dr. Early’s hiccups. A basketball player gets stuck in his car. A vehicle teeters on the edge of a drawbridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114230000 +0000" stop="20260114233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260114233000 +0000" stop="20260115000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115000000 +0000" stop="20260115003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115003000 +0000" stop="20260115010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115010000 +0000" stop="20260115013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney receives a chain letter, but Andy goads him into throwing it away. Suddenly things begin going wrong for Barney and he's convinced he'll soon be out of a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115013000 +0000" stop="20260115020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115020000 +0000" stop="20260115023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Marie's Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra suggests Marie visit an eye doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115023000 +0000" stop="20260115030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Grandpa Steals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank must find a way to fix his image with Ally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115030000 +0000" stop="20260115033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Psychic Kommandant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink he has ESP in order to get the plans to a new airplane with a silent engine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115033000 +0000" stop="20260115040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Prince From The Phone Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>An African prince comes to Stalag 13 to negotiate with the Germans for the rights to build a submarine base in his country. Hogan replaces him with Kinchloe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115040000 +0000" stop="20260115043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Commercials / Friends / Lucky Lady / Old Folks, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody classic TV products, including Phyllis' Milk of Magnesia, and Hostel Cupcakes. Then, in Friends, Carol misinterprets a man's kindness as flirting. Next, in Lucky Lady, a poor Carol is pitted against a rich Vicki for the contest title. Finally, in The Old Folks, a grumpy couple waits in line for gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115043000 +0000" stop="20260115053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Half-wakened Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Lawton goes to visit old friend Scott Shelby and ends up being charged with his muder. Fortunately for Lawton, Mason is another old friend of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115053500 +0000" stop="20260115060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Hundred Yards Over The Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1847 an American pioneer sets out to find medicine for his dying son—and stumbles into modern-day New Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115060500 +0000" stop="20260115070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Murder  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A car thief struggles to evade a murder rap after he steals a Rolls-Royce containing a dead body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115070500 +0000" stop="20260115080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To The Swiftest, Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellen Kovak suspects her husband's death in a racing accident wasn't an accident at all, and she hires Mannix to prove it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115080500 +0000" stop="20260115090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich lady, Cecilia Lasher, hires Cannon to locate the son her husband abandoned years before. She turns to Cannon after being blackmailed and terrorized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115090500 +0000" stop="20260115100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Flight To Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tracks a pair of heroin dealers who are using unsuspecting flight attendants as couriers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115100000 +0000" stop="20260115103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>I.a.d. - The Receipt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a complaint that two veteran officers stole funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115103000 +0000" stop="20260115110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - The Harassing Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115110000 +0000" stop="20260115113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 172 -- Boy...the Things You Do For The Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malloy gives a gorgeous wealthy blonde a traffic ticket, she stalks him, affecting him and the police force. Although uninterested in her, Malloy is forced to "take one" for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115113000 +0000" stop="20260115120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 92 -- Tell Him He Pushed Back A Little Too Hard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to repeated calls about an argument between two men and their wives over a boat they co-own. The feud escalates and ends with a fatal conclusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115120000 +0000" stop="20260115130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Dance Fever</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill prepares for a very special audition!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115130000 +0000" stop="20260115133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The School Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver's class is having a group picture taken, Gilbert goads Beaver into making a face with him when they snap the picture. However, when the picture is actually taken, Gilbert backs out and Beaver is the only one making a face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115133000 +0000" stop="20260115140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Rat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver making trades with his classmates is beginning to get on Ward and June's nerves because he seems to be the one who always walks away shorthanded. June especially thinks Beaver got the short stick in his latest trade when he comes home with a pet rat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115140000 +0000" stop="20260115150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Duplicate Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A mixed-up mess involving blackmail, murder and a boyfriend confounds Mason as he struggles to put all the pieces together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115150000 +0000" stop="20260115160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Priest  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends when a mobster is accused of murdering a priest. It doesn't take long before Matlock suspects that the Church is covering something up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115160000 +0000" stop="20260115170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Pray Love Remember, Pray Love Remember</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young female student is found murdered on campus, suspicions fall on her boyfriend but McGarrett senses that something is not right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115170000 +0000" stop="20260115180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Actress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Alvira Drummond, a famous stage and screen actress, is invited to stay at the Walton home after her car breaks down in Walton's Mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115180000 +0000" stop="20260115190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gilt Guilt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc treats a woman and her son for scurvy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115190000 +0000" stop="20260115200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Rival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>While visiting a girl he is courting, Hoss helps save the life of a rival suitor when the man is wanted by a lynch mob for the wrongful deaths of a family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115200000 +0000" stop="20260115203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain gives blood to save a dying man and is surprised by Marshal Torrance's odd behavior toward the man. Then three men arrive from a nearby town and demand custody of the stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115203000 +0000" stop="20260115210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger At Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's finding the body of a murder victim starts Lucas, his friend, Artemus, and Marshal Torrance on a search for the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115210000 +0000" stop="20260115220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Betsy Blee Smith Story</sub-title>
    <desc>"Despite the advice of some Coop decides to visit former girlfriend Eloise Blee, but finds Eloise gone, and instead winds up being talked into posing as her twin sister Betsy's missing husband and father of her baby daughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115220000 +0000" stop="20260115230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Camera Bug</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>John thinks he can be a photographer and pesters Roy for candid shots. A teenager suffers smoke inhalation at an elementary school fire. A fireman thinks he's having a heart attack. A woman is bitten by a scorpion. Dixie has "one of those days" as she and Dr. Brackett deliver a baby in a restaurant on their lunch hour. The driver of a truck full of dynamite is pinned behind the wheel of his vehicle as it catches fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115230000 +0000" stop="20260115233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260115233000 +0000" stop="20260116000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116000000 +0000" stop="20260116003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Showtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kaplan is to be shipped home, but becomes paranoid that something will happen to him before he leaves. He takes the wheel of the jeep to drive to Kimpo himself, but crashes and ends up in plaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116003000 +0000" stop="20260116010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Divided We Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brought on by Frank and Margaret's negative reports, General Clayton assigns a psychiatrist, Captain Hildebrand, to examine the 4077th M*A*S*H unit to see if it should be disbanded. Henry tells them to be on their best behavior, or else they will be split up. But the 4077th soon begins to act in their traditional, insane way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116010000 +0000" stop="20260116013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Runs For Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers taking an out-of-town job, and with the election nearing, no one has yet filed to run for Sheriff. Barney throws his hat in the ring, and then Andy's job prospect takes a turn.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116013000 +0000" stop="20260116020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>If I Had A Quarter-million</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney finds $250,000 stolen in a bank heist, he goes undercover to find the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116020000 +0000" stop="20260116023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Somebody Hates Raymond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray appears as a guest on a local sports radio show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116023000 +0000" stop="20260116030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Just A Formality</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Ray meet Amy's ultra-conservative parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116030000 +0000" stop="20260116033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116033000 +0000" stop="20260116040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116040000 +0000" stop="20260116043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests John Byner And Kenneth Mars</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Kiss-Off, John tries to break up with Carol. Then, in The Soap Opera Watcher, a woman obsessed with a TV show doesn't notice the drama in her own life. Finally, in Dreams, Carol dreams she's every man's desire, while her husband dreams of getting rid of her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116043000 +0000" stop="20260116053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Desperate Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Stefan Riker has come from Germany seeking the woman posing as Lisa Bannister. Attempting to help her stepmother, Doris Bannister pretends to be romantically interested in Stefan Riker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116053500 +0000" stop="20260116060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Rip Van Winkle Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves put themselves into suspended animation for 100 years after hiding a million dollars worth of gold bars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116060500 +0000" stop="20260116070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentleman Caller  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A robber stashes his booty in an mature woman's high-rise apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116070500 +0000" stop="20260116080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>End Of The Rainbow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Shortly after his release an ex-convict turns up dead. And in his pocket is a paper bearing the name "Joe Mannix." Mannix investigates and discovers a case of grand theft and double-dealing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116080500 +0000" stop="20260116090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hounds Of Hell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank travels to a small ranching town to help out a writer friend charged with a double murder. Frank's only clue is a cryptic note left by the man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116090500 +0000" stop="20260116100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Double Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman plots her revenge on the two men who conned her deceased father out of his land rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116100000 +0000" stop="20260116103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Police search for a safecracker who left his calling card at the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116103000 +0000" stop="20260116110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's cases range from purse snatching to homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116110000 +0000" stop="20260116113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 22: So This Little Guy Goes Into This Bar, And...</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fur burglary, a family fight and a loud party."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116113000 +0000" stop="20260116120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 15 -- Exactly One Hundred Yards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On their day off, Malloy and Reed agree to give a talk to a group of fifth grade students, and then offer to let the kids watch them train for the California Police Olympics. But when the tires of their patrol car are slashed and a stopwatch goes missing out of reed's car, the two officers start to suspect one of the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116120000 +0000" stop="20260116130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Granite State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit a snowy New Hampshire."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116130000 +0000" stop="20260116133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>In The Soup</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is throwing a party and is successful in getting Beaver out of the house, who is planning to spend the night at Whitey's. However, on the way to Whitey's house, he and Beaver get into an argument over a billboard that is advertising soup, leading Beaver to fall into the giant soup bowl mounted at the top of the billboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116133000 +0000" stop="20260116140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Community Chest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver volunteers to go around the neighborhood and collect for the Community Chest in June's place after she decides to attend Wally's open house at his school. Beaver brings along Gilbert and thanks to Beaver's astronomical mistake of losing the collection can, chaos erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116140000 +0000" stop="20260116150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Grumbling Grandfather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young David Gideon has his head turned by a conniving woman. In his haste to protect her and her supposed good name, the source of her pain turns up dead—namely her estranged husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116150000 +0000" stop="20260116160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Boy  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Hating his mother's new boyfriend, Tony Morgen kills the man and frames his mother. Matlock takes the case to prove the woman's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116160000 +0000" stop="20260116170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>King Of The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Danno is taken hostage by a delusional Vietnam veteran who believes everyone is out to get him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116170000 +0000" stop="20260116180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl whose mother died years ago, runs away from her father and new stepmother, back to her deserted house in Walton's Mountain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116180000 +0000" stop="20260116190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Lady From Brookline</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman tries to raise her son in Dodge after her husband is killed in a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116190000 +0000" stop="20260116200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Thunderhead Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Cartwright's suspicions are aroused when scruffy prospectors Cunningham and Furnas arrive in town, claiming to have struck a valuable silver lode at Thunderhead Mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116200000 +0000" stop="20260116203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116203000 +0000" stop="20260116210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116210000 +0000" stop="20260116220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Katy Piper Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie Wooster and Barnaby West have the task of escorting Dr. Katy Piper and her daughters to join up with the Chris Hale wagon train. Barnaby shoots and kills a masked bandit who hijacks the Piper wagon. The bandit turns out to be a teenage boy, and though Barnaby is cleared of any wrongdoing, a sense of guilt weighs heavily on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116220000 +0000" stop="20260116230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Firehouse Four</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The station enters the fireman's barber shop quartet contest. A man keeps requiring rescue while trying various ways to exercise. A woman overdoses on sleeping pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116230000 +0000" stop="20260116233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260116233000 +0000" stop="20260117000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117000000 +0000" stop="20260117003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117003000 +0000" stop="20260117010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117010000 +0000" stop="20260117013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves pretend to be Hollywood producers in order to rob the Mayberry Bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117013000 +0000" stop="20260117020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy's pretty young cousin, Gloria, comes for a visit after breaking up with her boyfriend. Aunt Bee asks Andy to be nice to her and his attention makes Helen jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117020000 +0000" stop="20260117023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Disciplinarian, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra convinces Ray that it's his turn to discipline the kids.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117023000 +0000" stop="20260117030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray starts spending less time at home when he volunteers at a hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117030000 +0000" stop="20260117033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon interferes as Hogan tries to help a defecting scientist, whom they were ordered to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117033000 +0000" stop="20260117040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cupid Comes To Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps Klink fall in love with General Burkhalter's sister to get his mind off not being promoted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117040000 +0000" stop="20260117043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Bedtime Honesty</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Momma and her family have come home from church, determined to keep with the spirit of loving each other despite their annoyances. Then, in Bedtime Honesty, Carol is dissatisfied with her body, despite Harvey's positive encouragement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117043000 +0000" stop="20260117053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Daring Decoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel Conway is involved in a vicious proxy war with Warner Griffith for control of an oil company. Conway's secretary, Rose Calvert, is spying for Griffith. When Rose is found dead, Conway fears he's being framed for murder and approaches Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117053500 +0000" stop="20260117060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A talkative man takes a $500,000 offer to keep silent for a year.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117060500 +0000" stop="20260117070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal Of Mrs. Snow  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Good-for-nothing Bruce Richmond prepares a plot to keep his wife's rich aunt from exposing him as a forger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117070500 +0000" stop="20260117080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Copy Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The key to a murder suspect is in a manuscript. But part of it, the most vital part, has disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117080500 +0000" stop="20260117090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Target In The Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank struggles to prove his friend did not commit murder, but someone (the real killer) is working equally hard to thwart him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117090500 +0000" stop="20260117100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must vindicate a doctor accused of murder by a girl subject to hallucinations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260117100000 +0000" stop="20260117103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Jury At The Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gluttonous jurors, lodged at the Shady Rest, refuse to reach a verdict because they like Kate's cooking so much.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
