<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405070500 +0000" stop="20250405080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former convict gets Cannon to help him find the man who sent him to jail for no reason."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405080500 +0000" stop="20250405090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Conspiracy Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Pulitzer Prize-winning author ends up dead after he gains a prisoner's confession of innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405090000 +0000" stop="20250405093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>My Daughter The Doctor: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo's late father has left her a $500 insurance endowment, which he wanted her to use to become a doctor. However, she has her hopes set on Hollywood instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405093000 +0000" stop="20250405100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Hooterville Vs. Hollywood: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate wants to stop Billie Jo from heading to Hollywood, enlisting the help of Judge Drucker to determine whether she has the legal grounds to do so.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405100000 +0000" stop="20250405103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts In London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are on the plane to England, with Sir Jethro as their leader. But with this comes a detour. The Clampetts get off the plane in San Francisco, after Jethro believes it is England. They get back on the plane and do finally arrive in England and are told that Jed’s cousin, Marcus, is late, meaning deceased, but they think he means late because he is diseased. After they arrive, Granny runs into trouble at the customs inspector’s office and gets her medical supplies and her jug confiscated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405103000 +0000" stop="20250405110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at Clampett Castle, and meet Mr. Faversham, who they call Major Domo after a misunderstanding with his name, also mistaking his name for a greeting. Granny decides to check on Marcus, but doesn’t know that the dog of the house is sitting in his bed. She feels the dog through the curtain and thinks the staff and doctors have been neglecting him. Jethro is working on fulfilling his duty as a knight and decides to start hunting dragons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405110000 +0000" stop="20250405113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Many Tanks, Wotta Nitemare, Let’s Celebrake</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye is in the Navy and Bluto is in the Army, but Bluto is confined to camp limits., Popeye has a nightmare in which he is unable to save Olive Oyl from Bluto., Popeye, Bluto, Olive and her Grandma are in a dance contest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405113000 +0000" stop="20250405120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mouse Troubles, Chump Champ, The Egg And Jerry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom starts to read a book called "How to Catch a Mouse"., Droopy and Spike compete at a Sports Carnival to be crowned the King of Sports., A baby woodpecker mistakes Jerry for his mother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405120000 +0000" stop="20250405130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loose Nut, Crow Crazy, Space Mouse, Wacky-bye Baby, Dizzy Kitty, The Overture To William Tell, Coy Decoy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody's golfing in the city makes life difficult for two cement workers., Andy faces off against a stubborn crow in his cornfield., Doc tries to capture and sell Hickory and Dickory as lab mice to NASA., Woody disguises himself as a baby so that millionaire Wally Walrus will adopt him., Andy and his father try to groom an alley cat for a Cat Show., Obstacles arise as Wally conducts an orchestra., Woody uses a hunter's own decoy ducks to confuse and hurt his hunting dog."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405130000 +0000" stop="20250405140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Bully For Bugs, Hawaiian Aye Aye, Tease For Two, Hot Cross Bunny, Unexpected Pest, Cock-a-doodle Duel, Bushy Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs becomes a bull-fighter., Granny, Sylvester and Tweety take a trip to Hawaii, and Tweety gets left on an island guarded by a pet shark. , Daffy Duck rides out to the woods looking for gold, but finds the Goofy Gophers instead. , Bugs Bunny is a science research test subject for the switching of his brain with a chicken. , Sylvester overhears his owners talking about getting rid of him. To keep his home, he must prove he is worth having by catching a mouse. , Foghorn Leghorn's dominance over the chicken coop is threatened by a younger rooster. , After drifting far out to sea while holding on to a bunch of balloons, Bugs Bunny is rescued by a passing stork -- only to be delivered into a mother kangaroo's pouch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405140000 +0000" stop="20250405150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of Montezuma's Hordes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An ancient Aztec map leading to the lost treasure of Montezuma is discovered in Mexico and points to a location in Texas. In order to ensure that a diplomatic incident does not occur, West and Gordon team up with Colonel Sanchez of Mexico and a noted archeologist in a trip across the Texan desert in search of the treasure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405150000 +0000" stop="20250405160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Emily Rossiter Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When her husband gets killed on the way to California, Emily Rossiter quickly re-marries in order to provide stability for her daughter. Unbeknownst to Emily, her new husband is a ruthless outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405160000 +0000" stop="20250405170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The River Monarch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barkleys’ riverboat is recovered years after its sinking, but the government gold it had been carrying is missing. The local newspaper editor starts a smear campaign, accusing the late Tom Barkley of having stolen the shipment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405170000 +0000" stop="20250405173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Spring Term</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt talks to a wounded man who was shot with a bullet meant for him. The wounded man says Stone shot him, Matt tells Chester that he knew Stone a while back and is worried that he will be shot next, Chester tells Matt that the Danch left before dawn. Matt learns that Danch was hired to kill Matt for Stone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405173000 +0000" stop="20250405180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Poor Pearl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Willie Calhoun's in town for a bath and a haircut, in preparation to court Pearl Bender. Willie meets Pearl in the Long Branch. He asks her to marry him. She says Webb Thorne won't let me marry you. Willie gets a rifle and goes after Webb."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405180000 +0000" stop="20250405190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Bridegroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe searches for a groom when a rancher makes plans to marry off his plain-looking daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405190000 +0000" stop="20250405193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spiked Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is kidnapped as he and Lucas try to protect Banker Hamilton's gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405193000 +0000" stop="20250405200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas makes a life-or-death decision when Micah is held hostage and the kidnappers demand the release of a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405200000 +0000" stop="20250405210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Rusty Shotgun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three brothers think Wish is their sister's intended.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405210000 +0000" stop="20250405213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Hatchet Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin is hired by the San Francisco Police to protect Joe Tsin, their first Chinese police detective. Tsin has been targeted by a dangerous group of Chinese criminals and Paladin must try to protect him without causing him to lose face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405213000 +0000" stop="20250405220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Legend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man with unwavering faith in a legend about lost treasure hires Josh to lead his family on an expedition into the desert to locate the cache of Spanish gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250405220000 +0000" stop="20250406000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Sappy People, Termites Of 1938, Matri-phony, Love At First Bite, Husbands Beware, Dunked In The Deep</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are phone repairmen who are mistaken for the psychiatrists in whose office they are working.  A rich man hires them to treat his impetuous young wife who is always running of for submarine rides and the like.  The boys ruin a dinner party at their client's mansion but their antics so amuse his wife the she is cured and the Stooges are paid off handsomely. , The Stooges are pest exterminators, mistakenly hired by a rich lady looking for an escort to a fancy society party.  The Stooges wreck the fancy mansion where the party is taking place and befuddle the guest of honor, an English Lord. , The Stooges are tricked into becoming stowaways by their neighbor "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that their friend has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , The Stooges are potters in ancient Rome during the reign of Emperor Octopus Grabus.  When the emperor orders all beautiful redheaded women to be brought before him so he can select a wife, Diana, a pretty redhead, seeks refuge with the Stooges.  Some soldiers find Diana's hiding place and they are all brought to the palace where the Stooges escape and try to pass of Curly as Diana, having broken the emperor's glasses.  Their ruse fails and they're caught by the palace guards as they try to escape. , The Stooges reminisce about the girls they met overseas while in the military.  As they wait for the girls' ship to arrive, they get drunk and Shemp winds up asleep with his feet in a tub of cement.  After sobering up, they free Shemp with a dynamite blast that lands them at the dock where their sweethearts are waiting. , To inherit a fortune, voice teacher Shemp must marry before six o'clock, but no girl will accept his proposal.  Finally one of his repulsive students agrees to marry him, just in the nick of time.  When the rest of the prospective brides hear about the inheritance, they show up at the ceremony and a free for all ensues.  Shemp marries his student before the deadline, and then finds out that there is no inheritance.  Moe and Larry have tricked him into marriage as revenge for their marrying his shrewish sisters.  [ A remake of "Brideless Groom".] "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406000000 +0000" stop="20250406023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Attack Of The 50 Foot Woman</sub-title>
    <desc>"When an abused socialite grows to giant size because of an alien encounter and an aborted murder attempt, she goes after her cheating husband with revenge on her mind."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406023000 +0000" stop="20250406030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Catwoman's Dressed To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Catwoman terrorizes the fashion world, Batman and Robin rely on Batgirl's help to stop her, only to find she's been captured herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406030000 +0000" stop="20250406040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>That Which Survives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk, McCoy and Sulu are stranded on a barren planet where a mysterious woman attempts to kill them one at a time, while the Enterprise must travel halfway across the galaxy to rescue them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406040000 +0000" stop="20250406050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Chopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on revenge, a headless motorcycle rider murders those who wronged him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406050000 +0000" stop="20250406060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Anti-matter Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Robinson is caught in a matter transfer emission ray, and subsequently ends up in another dimension where reality is twisted. The evil version of himself from the other dimension returns to his dimension and his family, attempting to take over Professor Robinson's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406060000 +0000" stop="20250406070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Cyborg</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A plot to destroy a third of the world by having a cyborg Nelson fire Seaview's warheads is aborted by the real Nelson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406070000 +0000" stop="20250406080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Double Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>An amnesiac Fitzhugh helps two Giant thieves with a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406080000 +0000" stop="20250406090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Merchant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug set out to checkmate the crafty Machiavelli, who is making a game of the Civil War battle at Gettysburg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406090000 +0000" stop="20250406100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A reclusive town has David wondering what secrets are hidden there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406100000 +0000" stop="20250406110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>The Quadrian Caper</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt are trapped in a bank during a robbery."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406110000 +0000" stop="20250406113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Zack's Birthday Party   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang takes summer jobs at a beach resort, but they have trouble dealing with their boss. Meanwhile, Zack falls for the boss' daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406113000 +0000" stop="20250406120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Game   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack bets Carosi that if his team wins a volley ball game, Carosi will sell his car to him. But Zack's team becomes a bit short handed when the star player is injured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406120000 +0000" stop="20250406123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Boss Lady   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Stacey is left in charge when her father is away. Everyone is pitching in to help her, but disaster strikes when someone accidentally booked two parties at the same time and then the chefs decide to quit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406123000 +0000" stop="20250406130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>My Boyfriend's Back   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the annual ATV race. Zack and the gang enter it, but Zack feels inferior when Stacey's ex-boyfriend shows up at the beach resort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406130000 +0000" stop="20250406133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Weekend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the last day at the beach resort and Zack and Stacy are hoping to spend it together. Carosi, however, doesn't approve of their romance. Meanwhile, a secret admirer is sending Slater love letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406133000 +0000" stop="20250406140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Best Summer Of My Life   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack stays home on the first day of school, and looks back on the time he's spent at Malibu Sands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406140000 +0000" stop="20250406143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>How To Succeed In Business?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter is ecstatic when he gets a job at Martinelli's bike shop. However, his wanting to do a thorough job inhibits his speed and work begins piling up and customers begin to get angry. This leads Mr. Martinelli to give Peter the axe. Peter then has a hard time breaking the news to Mike and Carol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406143000 +0000" stop="20250406150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Earring Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter's new detective kit comes in handy when Cindy loses a pair of antique earrings that Marcia has borrowed from Carol. This leads Peter and Cindy on a search for the missing earrings, hoping to find them before an impending costume party, at which Carol plans to wear them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406150000 +0000" stop="20250406153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Wish Upon A Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie wins a date with movie star Cindy Shea to a school dance, and Gloria breaks up with him because of circumstances surrounding it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406153000 +0000" stop="20250406160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Hi, Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when Laverne and Shirley thought they'd have some peace and quiet, look who moves into the building—Lenny and Squiggy are their new second-floor neighbors!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406160000 +0000" stop="20250406163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406163000 +0000" stop="20250406170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Becomes A Sculptress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucy is tricked into buying a bunch of clay at an art store, she is dead set on becoming a sculptor. When her first attempts fail and with Ricky threatening to take away her clay if she can't impress his art critic friend, Lucy devises a scheme to ensure her success as an artist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406170000 +0000" stop="20250406173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward's Uncle Billy arrives in Mayfield for a visit and begins telling Wally and Beaver exaggerated stories. Not realizing this, Beaver expects Billy to come through after promising Beaver a fishing reel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406173000 +0000" stop="20250406180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's latest girlfriend is Julie Foster, who just happens to be the daughter of a Mr. Foster, who teaches English. Meanwhile, at school, a new semester lands Wally in Mr. Foster's class and he quickly finds himself feeling uncomfortable—especially after Eddie tells him that his relationship with Julie will determine his grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406180000 +0000" stop="20250406183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Strike Oil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed Clampett's swamp is loaded with oil. When a wildcatter discovers the huge pool, Jed sells his land to the O.K. Oil Company and, at the urging of cousin Pearl, moves his family to a 35-room mansion in Beverly Hills, California. But when they get to their new home, which they think is a prison and the gardeners are inmates, they are mistaken for vandals and get arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406183000 +0000" stop="20250406190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Settled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at their new home, but find there aren't any of the conveniences of their old home. Jethro makes a few new discoveries, things they have never seen before, like pink chickens (flamingoes) and a cement pond. When Miss Jane Hathaway arrives, the executive secretary for Mr. Drysdale, she mistakes the clan for a staff of bumbling, insubordinate backwoods servants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406190000 +0000" stop="20250406193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Gotta Fly, Fish Gotta Talk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During Christmas, the castaways get homesick and recall the day they were shipwrecked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406193000 +0000" stop="20250406200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Three Million Dollars More Or Less</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Howell loses $3 million to Gilligan in a golfing contest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406200000 +0000" stop="20250406203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Room With No View  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama forms a family council to vote on a bedroom switch, the results create havoc for the household.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406203000 +0000" stop="20250406210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Mother  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Bubba comes home drunk, triggering painful memories in Mama regarding an embarrassing "drunken" incident with Eunice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406210000 +0000" stop="20250406220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Sally's Paradise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Gopher meets a lady customs agent; a widow tries to cool her son's romance; the boutique manager deals with three fiances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406220000 +0000" stop="20250406223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie goes to the carnival and blows all his money on a game to win a birthday gift for Andy. The game, however, is rigged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406223000 +0000" stop="20250406230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Bruce Pascal- Hot Wheels</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bruce Pascal's got a need for speed.  As a child, he loved Hot Wheels.  Now, as an adult, he has a jaw-dropping, museum-like car collection that includes not just the cars. But also, some extremely rare items that were used to make the cars.  Today, Bruce takes Lisa on a tour of his collection, from a hand-drawn sketch of the Olds 442, to a wood model Ferrari, to the Holy Grail of Hot Wheels, Bruce has them all and loves sharing his passion with others.  Our expert, Joel Magee, will appraise Bruce's collection today, and who better than a self-proclaimed toy scout and a race car driver!  Joel will also attempt to pull off a heart racing car trade with Bruce.  One, one-of-a-kind prototype, for another.  Who will end up in the driver's seat, our expert or collector?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406230000 +0000" stop="20250406233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250406233000 +0000" stop="20250407000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407000000 +0000" stop="20250407003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Accident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>At the grocery store, Edith has an accident in the parking lot. She loses control of her shopping cart which smashes into a car and a can of Cling Peaches (in heavy syrup) flies out of the cart, onto the car, and makes a dent. She immediately leaves a note on the car with her name and number. This boggles Archie's mind and he does all he can to try to get out of paying for damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407003000 +0000" stop="20250407010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Blockbuster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers are having problems with their furnace which gets Archie entertaining the idea of possibly moving to California. When an unscrupulous black real-estate salesman, Mr. Byrd, offers Archie a hefty sum of money for his home, Archie is all for it despite Mike's warnings that Byrd is a blockbuster (someone who persuades white home-owners to sell by appealing to the fear that minority groups will move into the neighborhood causing property values to decline).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407010000 +0000" stop="20250407013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike is all stressed out with upcoming exams leaving him impotent and frustrated. Gloria encourages him to discuss it with her, but he refuses. Gloria confides in Edith what the problem is, and in turn she tells Archie. This leads Archie to enter the situation, trying to give Mike advice, but this just makes matters worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407013000 +0000" stop="20250407020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Insurance Is Canceled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home from work in a particularly awful mood because he has to make an important decision at work: whether to lay off a minority worker or a white man. His decision to lay off a Puerto Rican leads to an interesting visit to the Bunker household. To compound his stress, Archie learns that his insurance has been canceled when his neighborhood is redlined as a bad risk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407020000 +0000" stop="20250407023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Paul Sand</sub-title>
    <desc>In Honeymoon Sweet, newlyweds Carol and Paul have honeymoon jitters. Then, Carol and the gang perform classic TV Commercial parodies, including Diaper Dampers, E.F. Mutton, the Innersplotch Water Mattress, Matador, Scoop Mouthwash, and Cross-My-Body-Bra. Finally, in Astronauts Going to Mars, Paul finds out that he wasn't invited to a barbecue back on Earth and rubs it in Harvey's face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407023000 +0000" stop="20250407030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Business Lunch, The / Mrs. Wiggins / Oldest Man, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Business Lunch, a strictly-professional Harvey proposes a business merger to Carol aka marriage. Then, in Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball fights the coffee machine. Finally, in The Oldest Man, a hurried man goes to his butcher, the Oldest Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407030000 +0000" stop="20250407033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Redcoats Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Petries are recruited to shelter popular British rock duo The Redcoats from fans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407033000 +0000" stop="20250407040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Pillow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob takes salesman to court over pillows that smell like chickens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407040000 +0000" stop="20250407043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Dial J For Janitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph takes on a job as janitor of his building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407043000 +0000" stop="20250407050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When his wife wins a trip for two to Las Vegas, a man falls under the spell of a slot machine that calls his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407050000 +0000" stop="20250407060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Be The Judge, I'll Be The Jury  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A police officer uses his partner as a lure to catch a murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407060000 +0000" stop="20250407070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Choice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Emile Vautrain, a mystic and charlatan, has gained sway over the Grand Duchess of Trent and plans to take control of the country. Jim and Prais fake a magic act to convince Vautrain they are working with First Minister Picard (loyal to the Grand Duchess).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407070000 +0000" stop="20250407080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Nemesis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble escapes from his workplace at a hatchery just as Gerard and the local sheriff come to arrest him. As Kimble drives off in the sheriff's car, he discovers that Gerard's son is hiding in the backseat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407080000 +0000" stop="20250407090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Heir</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell investigates murder and finds his suspects being killed one by one at the desert mansion of an eccentric recluse."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407090000 +0000" stop="20250407093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407093000 +0000" stop="20250407100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Parolee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon retrace a 14-year-old investigation to determine whether charges can be brought against a man up for parole.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407100000 +0000" stop="20250407103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Southwest Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a baseless complaint against an elderly artist, Malloy decides to buy a random painting out of pity and makes Reed envious. Meanwhile, they question a man attempting to break into a gumball machine while his son looks on, get a big surprise after tracking down a suspected peeping tom, deal with a man who comes up with a creative way to avoid having his furniture repossessed and engage in a game of cat-and-mouse inside the Los Angeles Coliseum with a former football player turned suspected robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407103000 +0000" stop="20250407110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Sweet Smell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy elderly woman spills a large bottle of perfume in Malloy and Reed's patrol car, resulting in a most unpleasant work day. Meanwhile, a reported burglar in a church office results in a comical case of mistaken identity, a well-meaning man is accused of kidnapping his granddaughter and a young boy asks for help locating his stolen bicycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407110000 +0000" stop="20250407120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>1974 Galore</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill takes a dreamy look back through the year 1974."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407120000 +0000" stop="20250407123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting Ward to become a millionaire, Beaver buys him a book called "I Became a Millionaire in Twelve Months." Ward thanks him for it but Beaver quickly learns that Ward is just being polite as to spare his feelings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407123000 +0000" stop="20250407130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After revealing that he wants to be a writer when he grows up, Ward buys Beaver a diary to practice writing and Beaver begins keeping a record of his daily activities. However, June and Ward pick the lock and sneak a peek at his diary after Beaver neglects to come home on time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407130000 +0000" stop="20250407140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Floating Stones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that her recently deceased father's office manager has made off with his small fortune in diamonds. She is eager to apprehend the crook, but before the thief can be brought to justice, he is found with a knife in his back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407140000 +0000" stop="20250407150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Brennan  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock vies with a formidable district attorney while defending a client accused of killing a city councilwoman, discovering a secret hiding in the man's past that is affecting his judgment in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407150000 +0000" stop="20250407160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Indiscretions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea does not realize that an old friend from Philly is hiding a dark secret, nor does Sweet who has fallen in love with the woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407160000 +0000" stop="20250407170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Airmail Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Engine trouble on the air mail transport plane means the Waltons have a guest for a few days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407170000 +0000" stop="20250407173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cholera</sub-title>
    <desc>"Chester worries about bugs &amp; sees Billy messing with a wagon. Matt &amp; Chester meet the owners of the wagon, they feel the newcomers have more trouble a head. McCready accuses the new family of stealing from him. A man comes looking for Doc because Cholera may have come to Dodge."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407173000 +0000" stop="20250407180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Pucket's New Year</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ira Pucket was abandoned on the prairie in subfreezing weather by his skinner Jed Larner. It's been 20 below the last three nights. Doc checks Ira out, and operates on his foot. Matt tells Ira he'll try to find Jed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407180000 +0000" stop="20250407190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Tommy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The father of a deaf-mute boy comes looking for him and his mother, both of whom are being protected by the Cartwrights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407190000 +0000" stop="20250407193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to do a good deed for the old town drunk but it backfires when the drunk's son believes he inherited Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407193000 +0000" stop="20250407200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance hall singer asks Lucas to care for her daughter in an effort to hide the baby from her self-righteous, bigoted father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407200000 +0000" stop="20250407210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Darro Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple on the train try to keep the husband's past from their son, but a tramp threatens to expose the secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407210000 +0000" stop="20250407220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Greatest Rescues Of Emergency! (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Johnny and Roy are promoted to Captain, they reminisce about their years working together. Flash-back sequences include the rescue of airplane passengers after a crash-landing, a potential suicide threatening to leap from a crane tower, and a girl whose toe is stuck in a faucet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407220000 +0000" stop="20250407223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407223000 +0000" stop="20250407230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407230000 +0000" stop="20250407233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250407233000 +0000" stop="20250408000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408000000 +0000" stop="20250408003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banjo-playing Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When former carnival man Jerry Miller becomes deputy to Sheriff Taylor, he finds himself jeopardizing Mayberry, making him question his decision to become a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408003000 +0000" stop="20250408010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Lindsey is a young guitarist that lives in Mayberry. When the famous musician Bobby Fleet and his band arrive in Mayberry, Andy and Barney scheme to arrest Bobby and his band so that Jim can get an audition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408010000 +0000" stop="20250408013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Raising</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed gets invited to the opening of Drysdale’s new Commerce Bank building. Granny thinks that he will actually be building the bank. Jed attends the party and meets two of Drysdale friends, who think he is a market wizard. When Jed is told he is helping to build the bank, he heads home to get tools and pick up Elly and Granny to help out. When they get there, they cause a bit of a disturbance and misunderstand what is going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408013000 +0000" stop="20250408020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis The Artist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney decides that Otis needs a constructive rehabilitation activity, so he has him take up art. Otis works hard on a large mosaic of a cow and gives it to the Taylors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408020000 +0000" stop="20250408023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408023000 +0000" stop="20250408030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408030000 +0000" stop="20250408033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Soap To Nuts</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice plays monopoly with a bored Mama. Then, in Soap to Nuts, Carol's soap opera addiction threatens her marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408033000 +0000" stop="20250408043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Credulous Quarry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends Richard Hammond, charged with killing his former girlfriend by running over her with his car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408043500 +0000" stop="20250408050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A World War I flying ace flies through a mysterious cloud—and lands at a modern U.S. air base in the year 1959.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408050500 +0000" stop="20250408053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Man Who Found Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveler William Benson learns the hard way that integrity may not always be the best strategy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408053500 +0000" stop="20250408060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Changing Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Dane Ross falls in love with a gorgeous lady who has an eccentric reliance on her watchmaker grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408060500 +0000" stop="20250408070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Another Final Exit (aka The Box)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bernie Farmer is mistaken as being responsible for a missing million dollars used as bait in a drug ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408070500 +0000" stop="20250408080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Ends At Noon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a Cuban exile to investigate the death of the man's brother at the hands of law enforcement officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408080500 +0000" stop="20250408090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Odd Man Loses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An industrialist is accidentally killed in a holdup before he's able to close a shady deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408090000 +0000" stop="20250408093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408093000 +0000" stop="20250408100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Bunco - $9,000</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The search is on for a swindler who conned an old vaudevillian out of $9,000 he found on a sidewalk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408100000 +0000" stop="20250408103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Trouble In The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a quiet patrol, Reed decides to spend part of his lunch break doing business at his bank while Malloy waits in the patrol car. Unfortunately, he walks into the clutches of a pair of ruthless robbers who take him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408103000 +0000" stop="20250408110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>North Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed volunteers to write a profile on Malloy for the LAPD's magazine to honor his 10th anniversary on the force, but soon discovers he may be in over his head. Out on patrol, an apparent gas station armed robbery gets turned on its head when they question the parties after a long chase, a man goes to extreme lengths to get his neighbor's poodle to stop barking, a woman's plan to get her husband arrested backfires and a liquor store robbery suspect barricades himself inside a house's garage after a high-speed chase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408110000 +0000" stop="20250408120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill The Conqueror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill believes he's the King of England."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408120000 +0000" stop="20250408123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Track Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is all set to compete in a track meet but after the coach catches him "horsing around" in the locker room, he's ousted from the meet, even though Lumpy and Eddie were egging him on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408123000 +0000" stop="20250408130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Old Buddy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Beaver's spends the weekend at the Cleavers and Beaver is all ready to have a great time like they used to. However, Beaver quickly discovers that people change and in this case Beaver's old buddy has indeed changed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408130000 +0000" stop="20250408140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Festive Felon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy but dying Bebe Brent gives the bulk of her estate to her loyal nurse. Needless to say, this act angers the remainder of the Brent clan and leads to a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408140000 +0000" stop="20250408150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The P.i.  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A private investigator's daughter shoots some photos that get the wrong man accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408150000 +0000" stop="20250408160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Racial tensions run high when a white cabbie is murdered in the bottoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408160000 +0000" stop="20250408170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy's growing attachment to Miss Hunter is rocked when she becomes interested in someone else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408170000 +0000" stop="20250408173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Cover-up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kitty's been riding in her riding skirt. Hoffer says he's going to kill Zach Ritter. Matt tries to take Hoffer's gun, as Zach enters. Matt gets winged."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408173000 +0000" stop="20250408180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Dobie, the hotel owner, wants Matt to make Big Dan Daggit and Rose, an Indian,leave the Dodge house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408180000 +0000" stop="20250408190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young singer agrees to perform at Virginia City's annual orphan's Christmas benefit, his shifty manager demands a cut of the donations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408190000 +0000" stop="20250408193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Coward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes involved in a battle between an aspiring writer and a cocky, bragging trail boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408193000 +0000" stop="20250408200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Surveyors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark runs away from home after his father questions his story about overhearing a plot to rob the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408200000 +0000" stop="20250408210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charles Avery Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint suspects that an Army officer has an ulterior motive while accompanying him to deliver a peace treaty to a once hostile Native American chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408210000 +0000" stop="20250408220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>What's A Nice Girl Like You Doing... (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto travel to San Francisco, where they observe some topnotch women paramedics in action during major rescue missions. An injured worker is stranded on the Golden Gate bridge. Ambulance squads treat a heart attack victim at a dance bar and an epileptic at a coffee shop. A bad driver causes a traffic accident involving an ambulance carrying the heart patient, resulting in his death and five other injuries. Johnny dates a nurse interested in a long-term relationship. Careless workers and deadly chemicals combine to spark an explosive fire at a pier on the Embarcadero."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408220000 +0000" stop="20250408223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408223000 +0000" stop="20250408230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408230000 +0000" stop="20250408233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250408233000 +0000" stop="20250409000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409000000 +0000" stop="20250409003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie Walker, the local pharmacist's niece, comes to Mayberry to replace him on a temporary basis. Her "new" approach to dispensing medicine shakes things up in Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409003000 +0000" stop="20250409010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Irresistible Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy comes to believe that Ellie is a "deadly female hunter" out to marry him so he tries to put her onto other quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409010000 +0000" stop="20250409013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Crawdad Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>There is excitement going on at the hillbilly’s mansion when a package from home arrives. They get everything they can’t get in Beverly Hills, including crawdads. Meanwhile, at the bank, Lucas and Pendleton are trying to find out what crawdad is. They overhear Jane on the phone with Jed saying that he will share his stock of crawdad with Drysdale. The Clampetts are trying to figure out how many crawdads they have and learn of how the government put three men on the task of finding moon(shine).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409013000 +0000" stop="20250409020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Follow That Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A smuggler pilfers a radio from the camp, and when Gomer and Sgt. Carter try to retrieve it, they wind up captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409020000 +0000" stop="20250409023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must prevent the Germans from getting ahold of a secret device that was aboard a plane shot down near camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409023000 +0000" stop="20250409030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Defector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a defecting field marshal to England, whom Hochstetter has followed to Stalag 13.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409030000 +0000" stop="20250409033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Oldest Man, The / Morning After, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Oldest Man, Harvey gets a hot dog from the Oldest Man. Then, in The Morning After, Carol and Harvey can't remember what happened at last night's party, and they fear the worst.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409033000 +0000" stop="20250409043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ill-fated Faker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Ferris is having an affair with his uncle's bored young wife. They concoct a scheme to finagle $80,000 from the man by faking a kidnapping. It doesn't take long before things go horribly wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409043500 +0000" stop="20250409050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Purple Testament</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A lieutenant develops the disquieting ability to foresee which of his men will die prior to battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409050500 +0000" stop="20250409053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Summer Shade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple moves to a new town and discovers that their child seems to be the only one around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409053500 +0000" stop="20250409060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Crime For Mothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic woman threatens to take her daughter from the guardianship of her foster parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409060500 +0000" stop="20250409070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Eight To Five, Its A Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate an alleged miracle that has been occurring on the land of a crime boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409070500 +0000" stop="20250409080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Search And Destroy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon tries to find a girl who went missing after witnessing a murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409080500 +0000" stop="20250409090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Forfeit By Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When a bondsman's client fails to deliver stolen valuables in exchange for bail, the bondsman kills him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409090000 +0000" stop="20250409093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409093000 +0000" stop="20250409100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409100000 +0000" stop="20250409103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Taking It Easy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed gets stuck manning the front desk after spraining his wrist, where he must deal with a caller who claims to have planted a bomb at the station, a young man who wants to file a claim of police brutality and an elderly man who walks in with a shotgun. Meanwhile, Malloy is assigned a partner who is a first-day rookie, and they deal with three young children from Oklahoma who are abandoned by their mother, and engage in a high-speed pursuit that ends in a most unexpected way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409103000 +0000" stop="20250409110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Krash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's brand new car gets dinged up when he has to bail out to chase down a purse snatcher, but Sgt. MacDonald promises him his kid brother in Beverly Hills can fix it on the cheap. Out on patrol, he and Reed search for a drunk man accused of randomly shooting arrows, respond to a robbery at a deli that results in tragedy and search for a drug store robbery suspect who gets away after being shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409110000 +0000" stop="20250409120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill And Toony Make A Commercial</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony unleash their inner ad executives, crafting commercials that range from high-end luxury to catchy jingles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409120000 +0000" stop="20250409123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tonsils</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When Beaver becomes sick, the doctor thinks Beaver may need to have his tonsils taken out. Ward quickly puts Beaver's fears to rest by telling him everyone will bring him presents when they visit him in the hospital. This leads Beaver to tell everyone that he's going to have surgery, but then he finds out he may not need the operation after all.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409123000 +0000" stop="20250409130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Fish Count</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie makes it known to everyone that he's just gotten a job down at Parker's Pet Store, which happens to be holding a contest in which you guess the number of fish in a tank. After hours of counting and re-counting, Gilbert suggests to Beaver that they ought to just ask Eddie for the count, but Beaver is a bit hesitant about cheating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409130000 +0000" stop="20250409140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Devious Delinquent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a crook double-crosses his partner and ends up dead, Mason must maintain the man's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409140000 +0000" stop="20250409150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Clown  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend aging clown Homer Fleming after he's charged with the murder of his long-time partner. After asking Conrad to go undercover as a roustabout at the circus, Matlock learns that the deceased had many enemies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409150000 +0000" stop="20250409160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen Trundel: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet's sister is murdered on the orders of the wealthy white man who fathered her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409160000 +0000" stop="20250409170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Awakening</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma is turning 68 and concerned about getting old</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409170000 +0000" stop="20250409173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kick Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Bent and Fred Myers just robbed the bank in Wichita. Harry and Fred's wife, Jennifer, plan on running away together. Fred followed Harry after they split up and overheard their plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409173000 +0000" stop="20250409180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Executioner</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young gunfighter, Tom Clegg, forces farmer Abe Curry into a duel and kills him. Matt can't arrest Clegg since Abe drew first. However, Abe's brother Morgan plots revenge. Morgan, who is unarmed, follows Clegg constantly. Clegg soon grows tired of it and attempts to take care of his "problem.""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409180000 +0000" stop="20250409190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Ponderosa Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ponderosa is overrun with furry critters when two unscrupulous old men convince Hoss and Joe to raise rabbits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409190000 +0000" stop="20250409193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous buffalo hunter tries to goad Lucas into a shooting match.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409193000 +0000" stop="20250409200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Order Groom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger arrives to marry the town spinster, two brothers who want her land try to discourage him with threats and a beating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409200000 +0000" stop="20250409210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Halstead Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Halstead joins the wagon train to search for the son she deserted years before. Could a wounded young man picked up by the train be him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409210000 +0000" stop="20250409220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>What's A Nice Girl Like You Doing... (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto travel to San Francisco, where they observe some topnotch women paramedics in action during major rescue missions. An injured worker is stranded on the Golden Gate bridge. Ambulance squads treat a heart attack victim at a dance bar and an epileptic at a coffee shop. A bad driver causes a traffic accident involving an ambulance carrying the heart patient, resulting in his death and five other injuries. Johnny dates a nurse interested in a long-term relationship. Careless workers and deadly chemicals combine to spark an explosive fire at a pier on the Embarcadero."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409220000 +0000" stop="20250409223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409223000 +0000" stop="20250409230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409230000 +0000" stop="20250409233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250409233000 +0000" stop="20250410000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410000000 +0000" stop="20250410003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie becomes friends with an eight-year-old runaway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410003000 +0000" stop="20250410010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy The Matchmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, trying to lift Barney's spirits, stages a minor robbery and tries to match his deputy with a shy seamstress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410010000 +0000" stop="20250410013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Dress Shop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Drysdale buys the Clampetts a dress store using their money, and the clan decides to check it out. When they arrive at The House of Renee, they are mistaken for poor and Renee tries to help them. She thinks they need jobs. However, the Clampetts think Renee and her models are poor and starving. Renee gives the Clampetts money for food, and they think it is for them to buy food for Renee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410013000 +0000" stop="20250410020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes Two To Tangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer spots Bunny with another man at the diner. Feeling sorry for Sgt. Carter, he reveals what he saw, setting off a chain reaction of goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410020000 +0000" stop="20250410023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Parachute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets the Germans to look for an allied agent by planting an opened parachute in camp. This gives him the opportunity to get at the briefcase that was handcuffed to a courier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410023000 +0000" stop="20250410030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Antique</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to open an antiques business selling "rare" cuckoo clocks, a business venture that is actually a ruse enabling the POWs to smuggle information out in the timepieces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410030000 +0000" stop="20250410033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Torchy Song</sub-title>
    <desc>In Torchy Song, the gang parodies the classic film, with Carol playing a demanding Joan Crawford on a warpath.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410033000 +0000" stop="20250410043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Singular Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is accused of obstructing justice when he defends a woman who had faked her own suicide by running an empty car off a cliff. It seems as though the police found the body of another woman in the wreckage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410043500 +0000" stop="20250410050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Elegy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts land on what looks like Earth 200 years before they left—only all of the people seem frozen in time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410050500 +0000" stop="20250410053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A practical joke has a devastating effect on an adulterous spouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410053500 +0000" stop="20250410060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Greatest Monster Of Them All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A horror-film actor plans payback after an incompetent director ruins his comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410060500 +0000" stop="20250410070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Delayed Reaction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix discovers that a 20-year-old crime is attached to a mysterious hit-and-run accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410070500 +0000" stop="20250410080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410080500 +0000" stop="20250410090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blueprint For A Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Recently released from prison, the leader of a burglary ring murders his partner for taking his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410090000 +0000" stop="20250410093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410093000 +0000" stop="20250410100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410100000 +0000" stop="20250410103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Routine Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by responding to a call of a drunken woman threatening the patrons of a bar with a handgun. Afterwards, they search for a group of four carjackers who go on a robbery spree after targeting a man with a cache of guns in his trunk, and investigate the suspicious death of a mentally disabled man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410103000 +0000" stop="20250410110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed returns from vacation with a full-body sunburn, making for a miserable work day. Out on patrol, he and Malloy respond to a fiery traffic accident, use an informant's tip to track down a drug dealer, search for an armed robbery suspect based on a vehicle description and attempt to rescue two boys after their rowboat capsizes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410110000 +0000" stop="20250410120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1980</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony look back at the events and pop culture that defined the year 1980."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410120000 +0000" stop="20250410123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Poster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers is having Beaver's class do projects on the colonial period and Beaver is one of three students creating posters. Whoever makes the best one gets a prize and Beaver is sure that Ward will paint the poster for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410123000 +0000" stop="20250410130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's Helper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighborhood cleaning woman, Mrs. Manners, gets a request from June asking her to help out a couple times during the week. Mrs. Manners is too busy herself but instead sends over her daughter, a girl whom Wally instantly falls for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410130000 +0000" stop="20250410140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bouncing Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An insurance policy, an untimely death and a plot of land surround a murder and a suspect who may be innocent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410140000 +0000" stop="20250410150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Star  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an aging actress is found dead, stabbed with the prop knife that made her famous, suspicion lands on the horror film director who wanted her off his picture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410150000 +0000" stop="20250410160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen Trundel: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Willins reveals Trundel's motive; and Sweet finds---and Trundel's wife sees---the missing photo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410160000 +0000" stop="20250410170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Olvia and John finally get a chance to take their postponed honeymoon to Virginia Beach</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410170000 +0000" stop="20250410173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gone Straight</sub-title>
    <desc>"A man comes into Dodge City looking for Jim Glass, Matt believes Jim Glass changed his name and learns that Nate Timble was protecting someone Matt was looking for."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410173000 +0000" stop="20250410180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bloody Hands</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt Dillon begins having nightmares due to a gunfight in which Matt killed three men. Joe Stranger thinks Matt likes killing people. When Matt refuses to fight him, he calls Matt a coward. Matt turns in his badge because he's sick of killing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410180000 +0000" stop="20250410190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe forces the only suspect in the murder of his fiancée to come forward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410190000 +0000" stop="20250410193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Case Of Identity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself in grave danger when two unscrupulous detectives searching for a man's long-lost son claim that it is Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410193000 +0000" stop="20250410200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Visitor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucas is drawn to a young widow passing through town on her way to claim an inheritance, but others who covet it are trying to kill her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410200000 +0000" stop="20250410210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Zeke Thomas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Zeke Thomas and his second wife are headed West with the train when he's confronted with a huge problem. During a stopover, Zeke sees his first wife—who he thought had died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410210000 +0000" stop="20250410220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Convention, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto work their medical magic at a convention in this 2-part feature-length episode of Emergency!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410220000 +0000" stop="20250410223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410223000 +0000" stop="20250410230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410230000 +0000" stop="20250410233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250410233000 +0000" stop="20250411000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411000000 +0000" stop="20250411003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Feud Is A Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy strives to end a long-running feud between two neighboring families.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411003000 +0000" stop="20250411010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie For Council</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie's decision to run for town council sparks a battle of the sexes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411010000 +0000" stop="20250411013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The House Of Granny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is waking up the family so they can get to their new store: The House of Granny. Jethro wakes up sleepy, not wanting to be up, but as soon as Granny mentions breakfast, he is dressed in a split second. Jed is carving a Y in the kitchen, and when Jethro sees the shavings in the bowl, he thinks it is cereal. Jed tells him to have corn flakes instead. Granny goes to wake up Elly May, saying that her store opens at a decent hour—the crack of dawn!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411013000 +0000" stop="20250411020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Whither The Weather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer uses a strange but reliable method for predicting the weather. When the platoon is left in charge of a VIP's arrival at the camp, Sgt. Carter must decide whether he trusts Pyle's power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411020000 +0000" stop="20250411023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411023000 +0000" stop="20250411030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411030000 +0000" stop="20250411033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Ken Barry</sub-title>
    <desc>In Babes in Barns, the gang parodies the classic film "Babes in Arms", with Carol playing Judy Garland and Ken playing Mickey Rooney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411033000 +0000" stop="20250411043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lavender Lipstick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A heiress to a cosmetics company is charged with the murder of the company's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411043500 +0000" stop="20250411050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mirror Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman encounters her doppelgänger at a bus terminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411050500 +0000" stop="20250411053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>West Warlock Time Capsule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A taxidermist uses his art to dispose of his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411053500 +0000" stop="20250411060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Throwback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Immature Elliott Gray challenges a much older gentleman for the hand of Enid Patterson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411060500 +0000" stop="20250411070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Writer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix is hired to prevent a murder of a mystery writer, the intended victim wants no help in solving the crime himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411070500 +0000" stop="20250411080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Conspiracy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank Cannon and Barnaby Jones team up for an investigation of a murder at a big corporation in which a deliveryman was charged with the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411080500 +0000" stop="20250411090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Clycle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An insurance settlement hangs on the result of an investigation of a motorcycle manufacturer's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411090000 +0000" stop="20250411093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411093000 +0000" stop="20250411100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411100000 +0000" stop="20250411103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program to help ground based officers better understand the abilities and limitations of helicopter assistance, malloy and reed are selected to be observers on several air support division missions. This morning's missions include a sea</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411103000 +0000" stop="20250411110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed take flight in separate helicopters to provide assistance in the search of a light plane stolen from the los angeles airport by a distraught man. Afterwards, they search for a group of robbery suspects who flee in separate cars, then reed</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411110000 +0000" stop="20250411120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Minor Misunderstanding</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony step into the courtroom!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411120000 +0000" stop="20250411123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Dramatic Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After joining the dramatic club at school, Beaver is given the lead role in a play. However, after reading the script, he discovers he must kiss a girl and wants out of the production.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411123000 +0000" stop="20250411130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Dudley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A close friend of June's moves into the neighborhood and June arranges to have Wally show the new kid, Dudley, around school. However, everyone thinks Dudley is a creep and Eddie and Lumpy plan to make a fool of Dudley at a party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411130000 +0000" stop="20250411140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Badgered Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When two brothers inherit their father's chain of department stores, disagreement abounds and leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411140000 +0000" stop="20250411150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Con Man  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a victim of a group of con men is charged with murdering one of them, Matlock takes the case while Michelle attempts to get close to the remaining con artists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411150000 +0000" stop="20250411160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs travels to Philadelphia to uncover the truth behind the apparent suicide of a friend who had knowledge of a police cover-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411160000 +0000" stop="20250411170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An offer to buy their land makes the Waltons think about what it would be like to have more money than they need</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411170000 +0000" stop="20250411173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Skid Row</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hank Groat bothers Kitty. Chester comes to her rescue. Ann Cabot arrives from Connecticut to marry Jack Shomer. Matt, Chester and Doc go to see Jack. He's drunk in his shack as usual. They sober him up. Jack says he can't face Ann."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411173000 +0000" stop="20250411180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet And Sour</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rena Decker, a new dance hall girl, purposely gets her admirers into fighting over her. Despite Kitty's negative opinion of her, Matt befreinds Rena and gets her a job at the Long Branch. Soon afterward, 4 men are dead and Rena is the cause."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411180000 +0000" stop="20250411190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Bride For Buford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman shows interest in a young prospector, Hoss tries to prove that she is really only interested in the man's fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411190000 +0000" stop="20250411193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young stablehand kills a notorious gunslinger, he is baffled by the hostility of the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411193000 +0000" stop="20250411200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a horse dealer transporting a prize stallion stops in North Fork, two saddle tramps try to use trickery to obtain it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411200000 +0000" stop="20250411210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Riley Gratton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Adams sets out to recover passengers' money that was taken by con man Riley Gratton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411210000 +0000" stop="20250411220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Convention, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"San Francisco firefighters and paramedics rescue a man. A paramedic convention brings Gage and DeSoto back to San Francisco. While attending a picnic, SF firefighters and paramedics are called back to work for a mutual aid response in Marin County. Gage and DeSoto tag along on a rescue."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411220000 +0000" stop="20250411223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411223000 +0000" stop="20250411230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411230000 +0000" stop="20250411233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411233000 +0000" stop="20250412000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412000000 +0000" stop="20250412003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412003000 +0000" stop="20250412010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger comes to town, Barney and the people of Mayberry grow suspicious when he seems to know too much about them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412010000 +0000" stop="20250412013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Continental Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Having been given a stylish makeover by a famous French couturier, Elly May is mistaken for a visiting foreign princess by Mrs. Drysdale. Hoping to get in good with "royalty," Mrs. Drysdale throws a fancy party for Elly. This time around, the old dear is certain that her soiree won't be invaded by "those dreadful hillbillies."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412013000 +0000" stop="20250412020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Barney Fife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney returns home to Mayberry for a brief visit and discovers that his former girlfriend, Thelma Lou, has married. Fortunately, Nettie Albright, a secret admirer from days gone by, shows up at Barney's high school reunion dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412020000 +0000" stop="20250412023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412023000 +0000" stop="20250412030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412030000 +0000" stop="20250412033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Petula Clarke And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Moving Day, a young elevator operator has a crush on Carol, who plays it up to make Harvey jealous. Then, in As the Stomach Turns, Carol's soap opera alter ego inherits money from her late, great uncle, but problems arise when her family stops by for a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412033000 +0000" stop="20250412043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wandering Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man accused of a murder is freed from prison upon newly discovered eyewitness testimony, it starts a chain reaction of blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412043500 +0000" stop="20250412050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Monsters Are Due On Maple Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paranoia strikes the residents of Maple Street when they believe human-looking aliens have invaded the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412050500 +0000" stop="20250412053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kiss-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After spending six years in prison for a robbery he didn't commit, a man decides to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412053500 +0000" stop="20250412060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a man turns to prayer, he starts to win at the races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412060500 +0000" stop="20250412070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Frame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate a possible forgery of a Renoir when the collector sees the model who posed for the painting in person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412070500 +0000" stop="20250412080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Medicine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates a doctors claim that he is innocent of a death he was charged with concerning a patient he was treating that had slipped into a diabetic coma. Cannon becomes involved in a medical malpractice suit when a young resident physician is charged with making the wrong diagnosis on a woman in an apparent diabetic coma who dies after his treatment. Hired by the hospital facing a two million dollar suit, Cannon hears testimony of the accused Dr. Jeff Reston, played by guest star David Birney, that the woman he treated wore a diabetic's bracelet. She was, in fact, suffering from hypoglycemia. But the bracelet disappeared and none of the nurses attending with Reston can back up his story. Reston then gives Cannon a motive for a possible conspiracy against him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412080500 +0000" stop="20250412090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must find out what happened to a woman who disappeared after dating a country singer's ex.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412090000 +0000" stop="20250412093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bobbie Jo And The Beatnik</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beatnik poet, Alan Landman, makes his way through Hooterville and Bobby Jo is entranced by him. It's up to Kate to show Bobby Jo the young man's true colors.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
