<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250120220000 +0000" stop="20250120230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young OD victim is brought into the ER. A man fakes back pain to get a free ride to the hospital. John gets peeved at all the frivolous calls the squad goes on while real emergency victims need help. A man is shocked after kicking in his TV screen. The ambulance carrying the paramedics and a heart attack victim is involved in a traffic accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250120230000 +0000" stop="20250120233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250120233000 +0000" stop="20250121000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121000000 +0000" stop="20250121003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121003000 +0000" stop="20250121010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121010000 +0000" stop="20250121013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Saves A Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie encourages and helps a female farmhand to express her femininity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121013000 +0000" stop="20250121020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Forecloses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Grumpy businessman Ben Weaver insists that Andy foreclose on a down-on-his-luck neighbor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121020000 +0000" stop="20250121023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Settled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at their new home, but find there aren't any of the conveniences of their old home. Jethro makes a few new discoveries, things they have never seen before, like pink chickens (flamingoes) and a cement pond. When Miss Jane Hathaway arrives, the executive secretary for Mr. Drysdale, she mistakes the clan for a staff of bumbling, insubordinate backwoods servants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121023000 +0000" stop="20250121030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Dance, Marine, Dance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer and Sgt. Carter are scammed by a phony dance studio when they both sign lifetime contracts for lessons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121030000 +0000" stop="20250121033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reservations Are Required</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan tries to arrange the unscheduled escape of 20 men, his mission is complicated when a captured sergeant jumps the gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121033000 +0000" stop="20250121040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Anchors Aweigh, Men Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men are tasked with getting an escaped prisoner and smuggled German gun sight to England. To accomplish this Hogan convinces Klink that he is fatigued and should have an officer's club in which to relax.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121040000 +0000" stop="20250121043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Born Free, Carol debates returning her domesticated lion back to the jungle. Then, in My Buddy, ship wrecked survivors fight for the only woman on the island. Finally, in The Third Degree, Vicki is interrogated for murder and responds by telling "Little Red Riding Hood".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121043000 +0000" stop="20250121053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Pint-sized Client</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbers lift a bundle from the Hargrove Finance Company and Frank Anderson is murdered in the aftermath. Anthony "Pop" Renzi is identified as one of the robbers and charged with both the robbery and the murder. Mason sets out to clear him of both charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121053500 +0000" stop="20250121060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Piano In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man discovers that the piano he bought his wife for her birthday possesses magical properties—the music it plays makes people reveal their true essence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121060500 +0000" stop="20250121063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Paisley's Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely woman learns to love a stray cat that wandered into her apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121063500 +0000" stop="20250121070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A tramp confesses to a crime. Unfortunately, the D.A. has already prosecuted another man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121070500 +0000" stop="20250121080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>All The Dead Were Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates when a plane crash is followed by murder attempts on the survivors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121080500 +0000" stop="20250121090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer believes there's no other way out than putting the blame of a crime he committed on his sister, a retarded girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121090500 +0000" stop="20250121100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>School Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Drug dealers infiltrate a treatment center and murder J.R.'s counselor friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121100000 +0000" stop="20250121103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121103000 +0000" stop="20250121110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121110000 +0000" stop="20250121113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121113000 +0000" stop="20250121120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121120000 +0000" stop="20250121130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Day Of Days</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony embrace all of the holidays that make January 21st special."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121130000 +0000" stop="20250121133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors, the Donaldsons, and June sends Beaver over to welcome them with a vase of flowers. However, when Mrs. Donaldson thanks Beaver by kissing him on the cheek, Beaver becomes convinced that Mr. Donaldson will kill him because he let a married woman kiss him, and it's all thanks to Eddie Haskell, who planted that idea in Beaver's mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121133000 +0000" stop="20250121140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>June has had it with Wally and Beaver's fighting and demands they make a pact to be nice to one another and do things together. However, when each boy gets an invitation for individual social outings, they each attempt to break the pact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121140000 +0000" stop="20250121150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Brazen Bequest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Cromwell, the president-elect of Euclid College, worries that some less than stellar moments from his past will be exposed when Maisie Freitag arrives at the college.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121150000 +0000" stop="20250121160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Nightmare  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a bump on the head, Matlock dreams he's in the Old West—and Conrad is about to be lynched by an angry mob!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121160000 +0000" stop="20250121170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Ches And The Grand Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lonnie must protect his Aunt Cordelia when her cherished friendship with Ches Collins angers one of his cousins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121170000 +0000" stop="20250121180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Premonition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While happy the war is over, Cindy has a premonition that Ben is in trouble</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121180000 +0000" stop="20250121190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>A Game Of Death...an Act Of Love: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The lawyer defends the two renegade indians accused of murder, and the victim's husband's is determined to see they are lynched if they are acquitted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121190000 +0000" stop="20250121200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Of Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this Western retelling of 'The Taming of the Shrew,' Adam, against his will, is called upon to teach a beautiful but hot-tempered maiden how to become sweet, mild tempered and gentle so that she can become suitable for marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121200000 +0000" stop="20250121203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Knife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark try to persuade a persecuted young mute to return stolen money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121203000 +0000" stop="20250121210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bertie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A lively old lady arrives in town hot on the trail of a notorious bandit—and the reward money for capturing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121210000 +0000" stop="20250121220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Augustus Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>"John Augustus in a game of cards with a Chinese merchant wins a beautiful Chinese girl. But when he takes her on the wagon train, other passengers ask Hale to have him and the girl kicked off the train for their "indecent" relationship."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121220000 +0000" stop="20250121230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>905-wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny and Roy answer a pre-dawn call at a small grocery store for a man down, bleeding. Searching the back of the store, Johnny is confronted with a Bengal tiger. A big brush fire threatens a suburban canyon area with lots of domesticated animals and things get dicey all around for the fire department and the Animal Control guys. Rampart becomes a veterinary surgical center for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121230000 +0000" stop="20250121233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250121233000 +0000" stop="20250122000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122000000 +0000" stop="20250122003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122003000 +0000" stop="20250122010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122010000 +0000" stop="20250122013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Sam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is suspicious of Mayberry's mysterious new farmer (William Schallert).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122013000 +0000" stop="20250122020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Gets His Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict vows revenge on the man who sent him back to prison: none other than Deputy Barney Fife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122020000 +0000" stop="20250122023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Meanwhile, Back At The Cabin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts find that the comforts of the mansion do not always compare to the comforts of their former mountain shack. Elly gets gifts and tips from Miss Jane on how to be a Beverly Hills girl, and Jethro believes Jane likes him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122023000 +0000" stop="20250122030000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee, The Swinger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and a retired Congressman, who has just returned to Mayberry, hit it off and paint the town red.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122030000 +0000" stop="20250122033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Adolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys plan to destroy a gun emplacement so the Allies can attack on Hitler's birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122033000 +0000" stop="20250122040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Rush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>French gold has been stolen by the Nazis. Hogan convinces Klink to have it brought to Stalag 13 so the prisoners can steal it back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122040000 +0000" stop="20250122043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In As the Stomach Turns, Carol receives a visit from the Godfather. Then, in I'm Not a Doctor, a man finds himself in the middle between a sick man and a nurse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122043000 +0000" stop="20250122053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sardonic Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Frank Lessing, a payroll officer on an Army base, is found murdered and Sergeant Joseph Dexter is charged with the crime. The case hinges on a payroll robbery committed in the Philippines years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122053500 +0000" stop="20250122060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Rites Of Jeff Myrtlebank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man comes back to life at his own funeral and soon begins to act very strangely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122060500 +0000" stop="20250122063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Percentage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young gangster tries to repay an old Army buddy by starting a business for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122063500 +0000" stop="20250122070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Together</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is trapped in an office with the body of the woman he just murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122070500 +0000" stop="20250122080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Race Against Time: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix travels to a Latin American country and gets himself involved with a revolution against its dictatorship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122080500 +0000" stop="20250122090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer was murdered. His latest book would deal with the biography of an industrialist. Cannon must protect the co-author and investigate the activities of the industrialist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122090500 +0000" stop="20250122100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Cry For Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-policeman, whose son was killed as a warning not to interfere with the local protection racket, leads a vigilante group in a barrio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122100000 +0000" stop="20250122103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122103000 +0000" stop="20250122110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122110000 +0000" stop="20250122113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122113000 +0000" stop="20250122120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 63 -- Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's wife is in the hospital expecting their first child, and Reed soon regrets his decision to report for work as usual. Out on patrol, they encounter a drunken man directing traffic, chase down a robbery suspect, investigate the theft of money from washing machines and become involved in a minor traffic accident that results in a major delay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122120000 +0000" stop="20250122130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Shipwrecked</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122130000 +0000" stop="20250122133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Water, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally and his friends are trying to earn enough money to buy baseball uniforms so they put a plan into action by doing their chores at a slow pace in order to maximize their hourly pay. Meanwhile, Beaver, also wanting to be on the team, begins selling water to his family and neighbors."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122133000 +0000" stop="20250122140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Crush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has a crush on his teacher, Miss Canfield. When Judy, Whitey and Larry tease him for being a "teacher's pet," Beaver tries to prove them wrong and places a spring snake in her desk. However, Beaver has second thoughts and becomes determined to remove the snake before she finds it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122140000 +0000" stop="20250122150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Renegade Refugee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A journalist is murdered while tracking an ex-Nazi war criminal who may be posing as an executive at a company called Space Associates, Ltd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122150000 +0000" stop="20250122160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Marriage Counselor  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a marriage counselor is murdered, Matlock must sort through a list of suspects including the man's coworkers and patients, as he was known to seduce the female half of the couples he treated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122160000 +0000" stop="20250122170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Conspiracy Of One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil accepts a position at a prominent law firm. But as a former police officer he feels conflicting emotions when he realizes that one of their clients is guilty of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122170000 +0000" stop="20250122180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursuit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman accuses Jim-Bob of fathering her unborn child</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122180000 +0000" stop="20250122190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging Of Newly O'brien</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly attempts to save a hillbilly's life by using drastic measures. The family wants to hang Newly after the man dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122190000 +0000" stop="20250122200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballerina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A dancer and her father are taken in as guests in the Cartwright household after Hoss injures the latter, who plays the fiddle for his daughter while she dances. His injury now makes it impossible for either to perform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122200000 +0000" stop="20250122203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Six Years And A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor seeks revenge on the man he blames for ruining his practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122203000 +0000" stop="20250122210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Flowers By The Door</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas unmasks a killer posing as a door-to-door seed salesman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122210000 +0000" stop="20250122220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mavis Grant Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"In the midst of a dry spell and desperately in need of water, the wagons stop at Mavis Grant's station, the only source of water for miles. But Miss Grant is a bitter and cold hearted woman who demands an outrageous price for the water."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122220000 +0000" stop="20250122230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Stewardess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John falls for a stewardess and shows his stuff when a passenger has a heart attack; later, he tries to date her. The firefighters respond to a motorcycle accident and a chemical fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122230000 +0000" stop="20250122233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250122233000 +0000" stop="20250123000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123000000 +0000" stop="20250123003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123003000 +0000" stop="20250123010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123010000 +0000" stop="20250123013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry guitarist Jim Lindsey (James Best), a success as a solo artist, returns to a hero's welcome. However, Andy suspects trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123013000 +0000" stop="20250123020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bringing Up Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, believing that the jailhouse environment is adversely affecting Opie, forbids the lad to spend time at work with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123020000 +0000" stop="20250123023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Meet Mrs. Drysdale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mr. Drysdale describes Mrs. Drysdale as being a hypochondriac, the Clampetts assume she must be a drunk. With his wife coming home, Drysdale and Jane try to prevent her from meeting the family before they can shape the hillbillies up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123023000 +0000" stop="20250123030000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bazaar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Warren, enforcing a gambling ordinance to the letter of the law, arrests Aunt Bee and her women friends (meaning, most of Mayberry) for running a bingo game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123030000 +0000" stop="20250123033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Zolle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to detain a German general at camp for 24 hours to allow the Allies to amass troops. Things get complicated when a Gestapo officer comes in search of the reason for Klink's perfect record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123033000 +0000" stop="20250123040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes A Thief... Sometimes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of underground operatives that Hogan and his team begin working with is actually a group lead by a Gestapo captain who's set on capturing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123040000 +0000" stop="20250123043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Carl Reiner</sub-title>
    <desc>In Disaster '75, Carol and the gang parody "Airport '75", complete with rowdy passengers, romantic triangles, and a surprise landing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123043000 +0000" stop="20250123053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Curious Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhoda Reynolds is charged with murdering her blackmailing ex-husband, Arthur Kane. At the trial, Mason moves the proceedings to the room in which Kane was murdered in order to re-enact the fatal night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123053500 +0000" stop="20250123060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>To Serve Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kanamits, nine-foot-tall aliens, arrive on Earth with one lofty goal: To Serve Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123060500 +0000" stop="20250123063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Sylvia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Sylvia will do anything to get her ex-husband back into her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123063500 +0000" stop="20250123070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Motive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Tommy Greer is a crime buff who decides to commit a motiveless murder in order to confuse the police, selecting his victim from a phone book at random.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123070500 +0000" stop="20250123080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Race Against Time: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix travels to a Latin American country and gets himself involved with a revolution against its dictatorship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123080500 +0000" stop="20250123090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Scream Of Silence</sub-title>
    <desc>Young Charles Lassiter has been kidnapped and the crime seems to be an inside job. But when Charles escapes, he must be silenced before he can reveal who the kidnapper was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123090500 +0000" stop="20250123100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Run To Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's friend dies of an alleged heart attack during his constitutional.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123100000 +0000" stop="20250123103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123103000 +0000" stop="20250123110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123110000 +0000" stop="20250123113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 93 -- Once A Junkie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former convict and informant who Malloy helped give a second chance is accused of assaulting a priest, dealing drugs and stealing a gun after being fired from his dish-washing job at Duke's Longhorn Café. Malloy and Reed set out to determine if his story, which is full of suspicious coincidences, is actually true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123113000 +0000" stop="20250123120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 123 -- Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed feels a strong sense of accomplishment when he stumbles upon a large stash of narcotics as he secures a residence after executing a traffic warrant with Malloy and Officer Ed Wells. He's in for a rude awakening at the trial, however, when he's cross examined by the defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123120000 +0000" stop="20250123130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day... January 23</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony host another edition of "On this Day.""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123130000 +0000" stop="20250123133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubhouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and his friends build a clubhouse, and Beaver wants to join. Although the dues are $1 for 8th graders, Beaver has to come up with $3 in order to join their club. How can Beaver earn the money?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123133000 +0000" stop="20250123140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Girl Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver dread attending dance school, so when Wally suddenly takes a liking in it, June and Ward are dumbfounded. It seems Wally has developed a crush on a girl named Penny and Beaver soon feels neglected and left out when Wally begins spending all his time with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123140000 +0000" stop="20250123150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unwelcome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Walter Frazer has always blamed his daughter-in-law, Sue Ellen, for the failures of his son, Gregson. You can only imagine how he feels when Sue Ellen is accused of Gregson's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123150000 +0000" stop="20250123160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Dame  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While out at dinner, a chance encounter prompts Matlock to relate the story of a case from years earlier in which Matlock's father believed his friend was murdered by his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123160000 +0000" stop="20250123170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Rabbi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A Rabbi returns to Sparta after many years. Racists vandalize his synagogue and soon after their Torah is stolen. Forbes investigates but the Rabbi refuses to trust Bill because of his inaction while investigating a hate crime many years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123170000 +0000" stop="20250123180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Ten Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and another captured solider are led from camp on an unknown trip</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123180000 +0000" stop="20250123190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Susan Was Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman and Dillon's wounded prisoner fall in love, her selfish niece makes plans to turn him over to bounty hunters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123190000 +0000" stop="20250123200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Flannel-mouth Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After watching cattle disappear, the cattleman's association hires a detective in order to determine who is behind the recent thefts. Adam houses fears that small ranch owners will be wrongly accused.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123200000 +0000" stop="20250123203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Trek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance run into trouble transporting a captured killer back to face trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123203000 +0000" stop="20250123210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Actress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A deathbed request from an old friend sends Lucas to a neighboring town in search of the man's long-lost sweetheart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123210000 +0000" stop="20250123220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lisa Raincloud Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bill Hawks is caught with three Indian grave robbers being chased by the Indians. He is the only one captured and is to be killed until he and the Chief's daughter fall in love. However, the leading brave has other ideas for her and Bill."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123220000 +0000" stop="20250123230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Engine Cram</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fireman is injured in a practice drill. Roy and John think they have a buyer for the old fire engine. A man suffers a back injury while riding a motorcycle. A mother pressures Dr. Morton to give her son a prescription. A man having a heart attack walks into the station. DeSoto and Gage rescue a man who has fallen off a cliff on Catalina Island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123230000 +0000" stop="20250123233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250123233000 +0000" stop="20250124000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Are You Now, Margaret?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Congressional aide, Williamson, visits the 4077th on a supposedly routine fact-finding tour, but it's discovered that his motives are far deeper—too uncover Margaret as a communist sympathizer. His case is full of innuendo, so the gang set out to help Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124000000 +0000" stop="20250124003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124003000 +0000" stop="20250124010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124010000 +0000" stop="20250124013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Bully</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolboy bully makes life miserable for seven-year-old Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124013000 +0000" stop="20250124020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Replacement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy is grooming a new man to replace him as deputy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124020000 +0000" stop="20250124023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Plans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Matthew Templeton says he’d be proud to marry Elly, the Clampetts begin to plan and rehearse Elly's wedding. Meanwhile, Drysdale tries to stop this wedding from happening, or at least from losing his largest account. He goes to Silver Dollar City and decides to buy the Bank of Bugtussle so he can still handle his favorite account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124023000 +0000" stop="20250124030000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Warning From Warren</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Warren is convinced he has ESP and feels that Andy and Helen are in grave danger if they go to the lake. He tries to warn them but they do not take him seriously. He takes it upon himself (with Goober's help) to "protect" them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124030000 +0000" stop="20250124033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124033000 +0000" stop="20250124040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124040000 +0000" stop="20250124043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Alan Alda</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nobody Does It Like Me, a department store Santa and a toy department wrapper sing after the store has closed. Then, in The Family, Eunice's brother visits, but every time he tries to speak, they cut him off with their problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124043000 +0000" stop="20250124053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Buried Clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Slimy Jack Hardisty embezzles $100,000 from his father-in-law, Dr. Blane. The greedy Hardisty then tries to blackmail the doctor for more. Mason is hired by Dr. Blane to put an end to Hardisty's machinations but before he can swing into action Hardisty is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124053500 +0000" stop="20250124060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man possessing the power of transformation tries to help a crippled little girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124060500 +0000" stop="20250124063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bracegirdle Does Her Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly maid leaves the parsonage in search of her sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124063500 +0000" stop="20250124070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Equalizer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eldon Marsh sets out to confront the man who stole his wife from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124070500 +0000" stop="20250124080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix struggles to recall events that led to him being shot with his own gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124080500 +0000" stop="20250124090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gordon Bell gets involved in a fight. When his opponent dies, Gordon is arrested and charged with murder. Cannon has to bring the truth to light . The corpulent detective soon discovers that Gordon is only a pawn in a devilish scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124090500 +0000" stop="20250124100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Anger, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A black cab driver runs from a murder scene on the grounds that circumstantial evidence - and racism - would make him the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124100000 +0000" stop="20250124103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124103000 +0000" stop="20250124110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124110000 +0000" stop="20250124113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 143 -- Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin their shift responding to a disgruntled tenant who is holding his landlord at knife point. Later, they investigate a rash of property theft from multiple homes in a quiet neighborhood, stake out an apparent bag of laundry left on the side of the road and search for a runaway boy who gets himself into a life-threatening situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124113000 +0000" stop="20250124120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 142 -- As High As You Are</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy and Reed's patrol begins, an uneventful traffic stop becomes more interesting when something catches Malloy's eye. Later, they discover an unusual situation responding to a break-in at a hospital supply warehouse, which becomes even more odd when the warehouse owner and a group of revenge-seeking thugs show up at the scene. The shift ends in a fitting way when they are called to an apartment where a baby has been left unattended with a pet lion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124120000 +0000" stop="20250124130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Panic At The Museum</sub-title>
    <desc>"What begins as a relaxing day trip to a local history museum turns into a overnight fiasco."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124130000 +0000" stop="20250124133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Short Pants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When June goes on a trip to visit her sister, Peggy, June's Aunt Martha steps in and stays with Ward and the boys. They do their best not to hurt Martha's feelings, but Beaver has the hardest time, when she buys him a suit, knee socks, a cap and short pants and makes him wear the outfit to school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124133000 +0000" stop="20250124140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfume Salesmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to win a fancy film projector and in order to get it they have to sell 24 bottles of perfume. However, the appalling aroma of the perfume quickly leads to zero sales and has Ward trying to think up a sales gimmick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124140000 +0000" stop="20250124150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Roving River</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Working to settle a land dispute in the Manzana Valley, Mason soon finds himself defending his client against a murder charge when the key witness is blown up by a homemade bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124150000 +0000" stop="20250124160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Defense  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends teenager Danny Hayes, who is accused of murdering his father. Danny insists that his father was going to kill his mother, but the testimony of his father's best friend damages the young man's story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124160000 +0000" stop="20250124170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hard Choices</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eugene tries to protect a friend who was an unwilling accomplice to a robbery and in doing so endangers his probation -- and his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124170000 +0000" stop="20250124180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben returns home. He plans on leaving the Waltons' mill and becoming an engineer</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124180000 +0000" stop="20250124190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus does what he can to help a mentally challenged young man, but soon learns the responsibility is more than he can handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124190000 +0000" stop="20250124200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ponderosa Birdman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Klump and Amanda pull Hoss into their flying machine scheme. The "Hoss-mobile" doesn't seem to be destined for a great take-off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124200000 +0000" stop="20250124203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas thinks he has seen a ghost when a young man, eerily similar to a man he killed in the Civil War, challenges him to a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124203000 +0000" stop="20250124210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Closer Than A Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for answers when recovering alcoholic Micah Torrence returns to the bottle—and turns in his badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124210000 +0000" stop="20250124220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Shiloh Degnan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"An officer Chris knows is found near the wagon train near death. He tells Chris that a passage in the bible describes him and his commander - Shioh Degnan. Chris returns him to Fort Bannerman to the Army where the truth is revealed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124220000 +0000" stop="20250124230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Election</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John become candidates for a welfare committee. A man gets his arm stuck in an appliance drain while his brother aspirates on a can tab. A delirious child causes problems at the hospital. A sculptress’ model is stuck inside a plaster cast. A construction worker is trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124230000 +0000" stop="20250124233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250124233000 +0000" stop="20250125000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125000000 +0000" stop="20250125003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125003000 +0000" stop="20250125010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125010000 +0000" stop="20250125013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125013000 +0000" stop="20250125020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Bankrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Myers is about to get evicted by the city council when he discovers an old bond that the city of Mayberry issued 100 years ago. Mayberry now owes him $350,000 and can't pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125020000 +0000" stop="20250125023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Servants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are doing repairs for their home, just as Elly is adapting to the look of a city girl, but not enjoying being called a “city girl.” Drysdale and Jane have figure out a way to improve the Clampetts by lending them servants. However, the Clampetts don’t want any servants, so Drysdale tells them that some of his staff is just going to be staying with them for a few days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125023000 +0000" stop="20250125030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Carter Gets A "dear John" Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter is shocked when his girlfriend dumps him—for Gomer!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125030000 +0000" stop="20250125033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The 43rd, A Moving Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Plans to destroy an anti-aircraft battery are upset by Klink's new executive officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125033000 +0000" stop="20250125040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125040000 +0000" stop="20250125043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Joan Rivers And Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Alice Portnoy, Carol plays a Fireside girl scout who blackmails a best-selling author. Then, in The Ham Actor, the understudies rebel against the players in order to perform. Finally, in The Walnuts, Carol and the gang parody the hit TV show "The Waltons".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125043000 +0000" stop="20250125053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Married Moonlighter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A moonlighting school teacher is charged with the murder of an acquaintance he had taken home after the man had earlier raised a disturbance at his night job at a cafe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125053500 +0000" stop="20250125060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>To her parents' horror, a six-year-old girl vanishes into the fourth dimension after rolling under her bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125060500 +0000" stop="20250125063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>On The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has problems staying away from the race track and it threatens her marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125063500 +0000" stop="20250125070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Guest For Breakfast</sub-title>
    <desc>"A marriage about to be broken is saved by a killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125070500 +0000" stop="20250125080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Night Full Of Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's police department pal, Lieutenant Malcolm, is a victim of a setup. The private eye tries to get to the bottom of things in order to clear his friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125080500 +0000" stop="20250125090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Seventh Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon investigates a kidnapping case. The lawyer David Rackham has been abducted. Because he is diabetic and needs a certain drug, Cannon questions the pharmacists of the surroundings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125090500 +0000" stop="20250125100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Point, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks for a millionaire's mistress, unaware that she's stolen a priceless objet d'art.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125100000 +0000" stop="20250125103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Whiplash, Whiplash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Selma Plout tries to slap a lawsuit against Uncle Joe for a whiplash injury suffered in a fall from a hammock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125103000 +0000" stop="20250125110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Higgins Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A feud develops over the Bradley family dog's apparently divided loyalty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125110000 +0000" stop="20250125113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Beautiful Maid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts take in Ulla, a Swedish actress hoping to learn their way of life for a movie, and a girl they think is a poor sharecropper's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125113000 +0000" stop="20250125120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Pad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro hires himself out cleaning Mr. Drysdale’s garage, and he discovers the magazine Swinger, a magazine for international playboys. After reading the magazine, he does all he can to become an international playboy. He gets a portable playboy parlor at the city dump and heads to the Kitty Kat Club to get some girls. He has no luck, but Drysdale arranges for two Kitty Kats to show up to Jethro, one being Miss Jane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125120000 +0000" stop="20250125123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>King Of The Mardi Gras, Happy Birthdaze, Gym Jam</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Bluto strive for the title "King of the Mardi Gras," with the best man winning the title and Olive Oyl., In order to prevent fellow sailor Shorty's suicide attempts, Popeye invites him to a birthday party at Olive's home, but Shorty's clumsiness causes lots of mishaps., Bluto dresses as a woman to pursue Olive at woman's only day at the gym."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125123000 +0000" stop="20250125130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cat Above The Mouse Below, The Bookworm Turns, Springtime For Thomas</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom is a famous opera singer but his performance interrupts Jerry's sleeping and the mouse does his best to ruin the show for the cat., A crazed Dr. Jekyll switches out the brain of a crow for that of a bookworm., Jerry tries to break up Tom and his new girlfriend cat by getting an alley cat to fight for her affections."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125130000 +0000" stop="20250125140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>All Hams On Deck, Chilly's Ice Follies, Moochin Pooch, Woody's Kook-out, Sleepy Time Chimes, Chilly's Hideaway, The Dog That Cried Wolf, Canned Dog Feud</sub-title>
    <desc>"Captain Blah kidnaps Woody so his treasure can remain hidden., Chilly and Maxie accidentally free a baby wooley mammoth from a block of ice and have to take care of him., Charlie offers to babysit his boss' dog while he's out of town., Gabby lures movie star Woody to Florida with the promise of a feast. When Woody gets wise and tries to leave, Gabby convinces him that a hurricane is coming and he must stay put., Woody tries to stop a clock repairman from fixing the chimes in a tower he's sleeping in., Smedley tries to evict Chilly Willy from Colonel Pot's mountain home., Dizzy the sheep dog pranks his owner that a wolf is attacking the sheep. When a real wolf arrives, the rancher doesn't believe him., Woody is the object of desire for two feuding hillbillies' hound dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125140000 +0000" stop="20250125150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Haredevil Hare, Conrad The Sailor, Thugs With Dirty Mugs, Acrobatty Bunny, Porky The Giant Killer, Hare Ribbin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs gets blasted into space with a payload of carrots. He makes it all the way up to the moon and meets Marvin the Martian and stops him from blowing up the Earth. , Daffy gives Conrad Cat a hard time on board the deck of a navy ship. Conrad Cat gives chase to Daffy. , The police try to stop a gang who is robbing every bank in town in numerical order., While Bugs Bunny sleeps a circus comes to town and leaves a Lion's cage on top his home. The lion investigates Bug's hole. Bothered by the lion's invasive curiosity, Bugs opts to "fix" the wise guy., Porky confronts a hideous giant and contends with the giant's "baby" as well. , A Russian dialect dog wants a rabbit sandwich out of Bugs. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125150000 +0000" stop="20250125160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Cadre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When a mind-controlled warden releases a condemned prisoner, Jim impersonates another killer and is recruited by General Titus Trask in a scheme to kill President Grant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125160000 +0000" stop="20250125170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Levy-mcgowan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"When the Levy family joins the wagon train, the tranquility becomes less so as the fathers compete in checkers, young sons fight, and son and daughter fall in love. Lastly, a settler who tries to shake down the train to cross his property."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125170000 +0000" stop="20250125180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>By Fires Unseen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick brings his bride-to-be back from San Francisco; the family doubts, however, that she’s ready to marry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125180000 +0000" stop="20250125190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Child Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A wanted man goes into Dodge to get help for his sick baby and his indian wife. With Doc unavailable, Newly offers to help but will be torn between healing and his duty as a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125190000 +0000" stop="20250125200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam's search for troublesome look-a-like Tom Burns lands him in the Placerville jail for two murders committed by Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125200000 +0000" stop="20250125203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas agrees to take a job as a federal undercover agent and goes to Wyoming to investigate rumors of sales of arms to renegade indians. His life is endangered by the town drunk, who stumbles onto his true identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125203000 +0000" stop="20250125210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark stays with Miss Milly, while Lucas is in Wyoming on the trail of a gang illegally selling weapons to the Indians. Mark suffers from loneliness and doubt while his father is away for two months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125210000 +0000" stop="20250125220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Paradise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy rescues Nester Higgins from being used for target practice and gets involved in his fight to keep his farm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125220000 +0000" stop="20250125223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>One Came Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After serving 5 years in prison for crimes commited during the Civil War, Ben Harvey wants to go home to his brothers in Gila. He hires Paladin to protect him and his wagon of goods during the trip. They arrive in Gila to find that his brothers are wanted for murder and there's a posse out looking them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125223000 +0000" stop="20250125230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Drop To Drink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves are lying in wait to ambush mail carriers, and Josh is hired to help ensure that the mail will get through. The thieves have news about a $20,000 diamond ring that is in transit. The trail is through desert country with no water for miles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250125230000 +0000" stop="20250126010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Flatfoot Stooges, Rhythm And Weep, Malice In The Palace, He Cooked His Goose, Income Tax Sappy, Dopey Dicks</sub-title>
    <desc>"Moe, Larry and Curly take care of the horses.  , The Stooges pair with three dancers to put on a Broadway show, not realizing their sponsor is an escaped mental patient., It's mindless fun at its best when the Stooges meet a mad scientist in search of a human brain for his headless mechanical man.  , "Set in a desert land where the stooges run a restaurant, the boys set out to recover the stolen Rootin Tootin diamond after they learn from the thieves that the Emir of Shmo has absconded with the contraband jewel. They journey to the stronghold of Shmo where they disguise as Santa Clauses and scare the ruler into giving them the diamond. 
" , Larry is a pet dealer who's seeing Moe's wife while at the same time trying to steal Shemp's fiancee.  When Moe's become suspicious, Larry attempts to frame Shemp as the boyfriend.  He gets Shemp a job as a door-to-door pajama salesman and sends him to Moe's apartment, and then tells both Moe and Shemp's fiancee to go there and catch him in the act.  Larry's plan backfires when Shemp catches him and lets Moe deliver some punishment. , Tax cheats Moe, Larry and Shemp decide they're so good at cheating the government, that they start a business as crooked tax advisors.  They become rich, but an undercover agent from the IRS gets the goods on them, and it's off to jail for the Stooges. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126010000 +0000" stop="20250126033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Godzilla, King Of The Monsters!</sub-title>
    <desc>"A 400-foot (122-meter) dinosaur-like beast, awoken from undersea hibernation off the Japanese coast by atomic-bomb testing, attacks Tokyo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126033000 +0000" stop="20250126040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Ice Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E59</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Freeze plans to freeze Gotham using a scientist's instant ice formula. Bruce Wayne investigates an ice-skating star who he believes is helping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126040000 +0000" stop="20250126050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Tholian Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Enterprise investigates the disappearance of another starship, they lose Kirk in a dimensional interphase and must deal with a hostile alien race while trying to recover him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126050000 +0000" stop="20250126060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Devil's Platform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A politician on a meteoric rise murders his opposition through a pact with Satan which gives him the ability to turn into an invulnerable dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126060000 +0000" stop="20250126070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Space Primevals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>On a planet where a primitive people are ruled by a computer, Dr. Smith goes against character and saves Major West's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126070000 +0000" stop="20250126080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Exile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral Nelson is stranded on a life raft with the former premier of a hostile foreign power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126080000 +0000" stop="20250126090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Graveyard Of Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Twin brothers plot to take over the planet, and send the Earthlings to the Graveyard of Fools, a place fraught with hallucinatory visions, to recover an alien servo-actuator for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126090000 +0000" stop="20250126100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Invasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>June 1944. Near Cherbourg, France, Tony and Doug are captured by the Gestapo just before the Allied invasion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126100000 +0000" stop="20250126110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is given an alien crystal, which is soon believed to be a miracle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126110000 +0000" stop="20250126120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Winning</sub-title>
    <desc>"Against Walt's advice, Matt tries out for the football team, using his powers to excel."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126120000 +0000" stop="20250126123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Detention   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>If Zack can just get out of detention, he has a chance at winning a trip to Hawaii. Doing their best to get him off the hook, the gang ends up in detention, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126123000 +0000" stop="20250126130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Wrestling With The Future   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater and his father fight over where he should attend college and Zack tries to fix it. Meanwhile, Jessie becomes a cheerleader and worries about college acceptances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126130000 +0000" stop="20250126133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Class Rings   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack buys class rings for all the seniors at Bayside, he's embarrassed to find out he's been had when the rings turn out to be phonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126133000 +0000" stop="20250126140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Cut Day   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's senior cut day. Zack does his best not to get caught by Belding. Meanwhile, Jessie protests the use of plastic cups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126140000 +0000" stop="20250126143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>School Song   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang decides to write a new school song together for a Bayside competition. Zack schemes to get them to compete against one another, and when they find out it's time for revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126143000 +0000" stop="20250126150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Senior Prom   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's up to the gang to raise the funds needed for the senior prom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126150000 +0000" stop="20250126153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Pass The Tabu (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>During a surfing competition, Greg wears Bobby's taboo idol and wipes out. Soon after, Greg, Peter and Bobby learn of the ancient superstition from a construction worker, Mr. Hanalei. This leads the boys to search for an ancient burial ground to return the idol to break the curse. However, when they arrive there, they are unaware of a shadowy figure trailing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126153000 +0000" stop="20250126160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Tiki Caves (part 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An archeologist traps the boys in the caves at the burial ground, insisting they tell him where they found the idol. Meanwhile, Jan, Marcia and Cindy debate on whether to tell Mike and Carol about the boys' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126160000 +0000" stop="20250126163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>My Cousin, The Cheat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Chachi is caught by a truancy officer, Fonzie and Richie arrange for Joanie to tutor him. He then gets caught cheating on a test and, as a result, gets suspended from school and gets in hot water with Fonzie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126163000 +0000" stop="20250126170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Perfidy In Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling guilty for losing Laverne's favorite purse and then lying about it, Shirley dreams that her friend is trying to kill her to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126170000 +0000" stop="20250126173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney On The Rebound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After a tiff with Thelma Lou, Barney is victimized by a scheming young couple.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126173000 +0000" stop="20250126180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Diner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ricardos and the Mertzes buy a diner, name it "A Little Bit of Cuba" and go to work. Well, the Mertzes go to work; the Ricardos "greet." Not surprisingly, relations are soon strained. Can a food fight be far behind?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126180000 +0000" stop="20250126183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward make Wally and Beaver promise that they won't go see a scary movie. However, Wally and Beaver are talked into seeing it, thanks to Wally's so-called best friend, Eddie Haskell. The movie has quite an influence on Beaver, who makes a voodoo doll, names it Eddie Haskell and sticks it with pins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126183000 +0000" stop="20250126190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Part Time Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After taking an IQ test, Beaver scores the highest in his class and Mrs. Rayburn suggests that it would be best if Beaver went to a special school, where his abilities can be challenged. However, little does anyone know, everything is not as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126190000 +0000" stop="20250126193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Bird Watchers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Jane’s bird watcher leader, Professor Biddle, comes to town to visit. And Jed and Granny are trying to get a man for Elly. After Elly shows up with Professor Biddle, Jed decides that fixing Elly May up with Dash Riprock couldn’t hurt. Drysdale blackmails Dash with a bad TV role to get Dash to ask Elly out. He doesn’t get to the Clampett mansion in enough time, and Jed has no luck with stopping Elly, so she ends up going with Professor Biddle, Miss Jane and Jethro on their bird expedition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126193000 +0000" stop="20250126200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale's Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny demands to see her money in cash, and Drysdale tries to talk her out of it. He fails and upsets the Clampetts by accidentally throwing magazines at them, which were really aimed at his wife and her dog. He tries to make things better by showing Granny what a million dollars looks like to turn her off from the idea, but ends up throwing more stuff at her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126200000 +0000" stop="20250126203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret Of Gilligan's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When Gilligan finds a portion of a stone tablet that the Professor believes shows a way off the island, the castaways frantically search for the other parts of the tablet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126203000 +0000" stop="20250126210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Slave Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gilligan saves a beautiful native girl from drowning, she vows to be his slave forever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126210000 +0000" stop="20250126213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes Two To Watusi  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Naomi's divorced friend, Luann, falls for Bubba when he's a stand-in for a blind date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126213000 +0000" stop="20250126220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Fangs Alot, Mama  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint wants to join a secret society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126220000 +0000" stop="20250126230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Isaac's Teacher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Isaac hides from his high-school teacher; a man tries to please his seal; a wife who thinks she's dying wants to choose her successor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126230000 +0000" stop="20250126233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250126233000 +0000" stop="20250127000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Weird Al- Kenneth Guinup</sub-title>
    <desc>""Weird Al" Yankovic collector's Kenneth Guinup has everything from Al's very first EP to a screen-used guitar signed by the entire band. Lisa's brought along Jon "Bermuda" Schwartz, "Weird Al's" drummer and the band's archivist who has a shout-out from "Weird Al" himself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127000000 +0000" stop="20250127003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127003000 +0000" stop="20250127010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127010000 +0000" stop="20250127013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Final Respects</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is the sole mourner at her Aunt Rose's funeral.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127013000 +0000" stop="20250127020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Weekend In The Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie and Edith are invited to spend a fishing weekend with Barney and Blanche at their cottage. But after a game of Monopoly, an argument between Barney and Blanche begins. That night, Archie is uncomfortable to sleep with a man (Barney) in bed, while Edith and Blanche rate their husbands as a lovers. 
By the end, Blanche and Barney makeup and Archie tries to forget everything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127020000 +0000" stop="20250127023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarder Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Returning home unexpectedly, Archie and Edith surprise a scantily clad Teresa and her boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127023000 +0000" stop="20250127030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Vs. The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the TV broken, Edith decides to buy a new one for Archie for their 30th wedding anniversary. But when the clerk won't let Edith buy a TV without Archie's signature because she's a woman, she goes to the bank for a loan. There too, she can not borrow money because she is just a housewife with no job, making Edith furious. Helpless, Edith goes home and asks Archie for $500, but she won't tell him why (surprise). During their conversation, Edith discovers that Archie may be sexist also.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127030000 +0000" stop="20250127033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Kidnapping / Family, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Kidnapping, Carol gets her fifteen minutes of fame when her husband is kidnapped. Then, in The Family, Eunice is determined to win "The Gong Show" by singing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127033000 +0000" stop="20250127040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Beniha-Ha, a bus boy takes center stage as a chef. Then, in The Witness, Carol and Harvey can't agree to the facts surrounding a car accident they witnessed. Finally, in The Other Secretary, Carol finds out her boss has been "cheating" on her by using another secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127040000 +0000" stop="20250127043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Mother Can Beat Up My Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob tells a nurse how he wound up in the hospital, and it's Laura's fault.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127043000 +0000" stop="20250127050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of A Chantz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob, Laura, Buddy and Sally spend the night in a seemingly haunted cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127050000 +0000" stop="20250127053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph captures two thugs that followed him home after he witnessed a hold-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127053000 +0000" stop="20250127060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Person Or Persons Unknown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man wakes up one morning to discover that no one knows who he is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127060000 +0000" stop="20250127070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Ride The Nightmare  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An elderly acquaintance plunges Chris Martin into a nightmare stuffed with blackmail, kidnapping and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127070000 +0000" stop="20250127080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Falcon: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>General Sabattini has faked the death of Prince Stephan and plans to force Stephan's fiancee, Francesca, to marry him and let him ascend the throne over the simpleton Prince Nicolai. Once he has married Francesca, Sabattini plans to kill all three.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127080000 +0000" stop="20250127090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Taps For A Dead War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a roller rink supervisor, Kimble is recognized by the horribly scared Joe Hallop, a former Korean War veteran whom blames Kimble for his condition. Apparently back in the Korean War, Kimble was nearly killed in an enemy grenade explosion</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127090000 +0000" stop="20250127100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Mortal Sin</sub-title>
    <desc>"The seal of the confessional must be preserved as Harry O goes after a deranged killer who confessed his crimes to a priest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250127100000 +0000" stop="20250127103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
