<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115200000 +0000" stop="20251115203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Closer Than A Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for answers when recovering alcoholic Micah Torrence returns to the bottle—and turns in his badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115203000 +0000" stop="20251115210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Treasure Of Canyon Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In a ghost town, Lucas, Mark and Micah tangle with the Newman family and learn the secret of the town's 20-year-old mystery of a lost gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115210000 +0000" stop="20251115220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Josh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Seventy-year-old Josh Breeden's pride won't let him admit he's too old to be a drover. He blames Favor for all his problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115220000 +0000" stop="20251115223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Three Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Newlyweds with no place to stay end up in Paladin's suite. He learns that the groom's half-brothers are threatening to kill their father. Paladin goes to warn the father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115223000 +0000" stop="20251115230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Partners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh gets arrested for horse theft. He soon learns that Jason set him up so that he can go after Billy Joe Henry alone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251115230000 +0000" stop="20251116010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Healthy, Wealthy, You Natzy Spy, Even As I.o.u., Hokus Pokus, Dunked In The Deep, Three Sappy People, And Dumb</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Curly wins $50,000 the Stooges start living the high life? until they get the lowdown on exactly how much they get after taxes. , In this satire of the Nazis the Stooges are paperhangers in the country of Moronica.  When evil cabinet ministers overthrow the king, they decide to make Moe the new ruler as he'll be stupid enough to follow their orders.  Moe becomes Dictator, Curly is a Field Marshall and Larry becomes Minister of propaganda.  After successfully preventing a female spy from committing mayhem, the boys are run out of office by a mob and eaten by lions. , A destitute mother and child move into the stooge's vacant lot home and the boys decide to help them.  They steal the kids piggy bank and sneak into the race track.  They bet on a long shot that wins and then are gypped out of their winnings by two con men who sell them a washed up race horse.  Everything turns out happily when Curly swallows horse vitamins and gives birth to a colt! , When the boys witness a hypnotist, "The Great Svengarlic", doing his act on the street, they think he might be able to hypnotize a friend so she can walk., The Stooges are tricked into becoming stowaways by their neighbor "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that their friend has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , The Stooges are phone repairmen who are mistaken for the psychiatrists in whose office they are working.  A rich man hires them to treat his impetuous young wife who is always running of for submarine rides and the like.  The boys ruin a dinner party at their client's mansion but their antics so amuse his wife the she is cured and the Stooges are paid off handsomely. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116010000 +0000" stop="20251116033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Dracula Has Risen From The Grave</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dracula plots revenge against the priest who barred him from his castle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116033000 +0000" stop="20251116040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Death In Slow Motion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler and his cronies interrupt a silent film festival dressed as Charlie Chaplin and The Keystone Cops. Batman and Robin trace Riddler to Mother Gotham's Bakery, where he plans to film his robbery in the style of an old film comedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116040000 +0000" stop="20251116050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Galileo Seven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Galileo, under Spock's command, crash-lands on a hostile planet. As the Enterprise races against time to find the shuttlecraft, Spock's strictly logical leadership clashes with the fear and resentment of his crew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116050000 +0000" stop="20251116053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Tin Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A meek bookkeeper inadvertently captures a bank robber. He becomes a crime-busting reporter, which brings more trouble than he can handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116053000 +0000" stop="20251116060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Town That Wasn't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jimmy and Lois are victimized by a phony speed trap and held in a mysterious vanishing town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116060000 +0000" stop="20251116070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>His Majesty Smith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith is conscripted as the leader of a people from another world. Little does he know that the leaders of these people are routinely sacrificed and replaced with other expendable leaders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116070000 +0000" stop="20251116080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson is plagued by a slave trader ancestor who has come to take him away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116080000 +0000" stop="20251116090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Our Man O'reilly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A superstitious Irish Giant mistakes the Earthlings for leprechauns and captures them so they can help him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116090000 +0000" stop="20251116100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Pirates Of Deadman's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1805, the travelers try to escape from a pirate's Barbary Coast lair before it is shelled by U.S. warships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116100000 +0000" stop="20251116110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Vise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent discovers an up-and-coming official is actually an invader, but an ex-policeman stands in his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116110000 +0000" stop="20251116120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Gold Is Where You Find It</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two inept men with dreams of gold search for it on the mountain with a map they got for ten dollars. Their efforts upset the calm balance of nature around them leading Adams and others to try and stop them before real damage is done."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116120000 +0000" stop="20251116123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tale Of The Fox</sub-title>
    <desc>"This is the tale of the fox cub as it explores the wild kingdom for the first time in the North Woods of Wisconsin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116123000 +0000" stop="20251116130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bobcat Kingdom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim observe a family of bobcats in the Zion Canyon area in the Utah wilderness."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116130000 +0000" stop="20251116133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Mysteries Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"Many mysteries of the wild present a challenge to seek the answer. In this episode Jim Fowler brings to the viewer some of the most memorable scenes ever captured on film."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116133000 +0000" stop="20251116140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit South Africa to study and photograph the chacma baboons in their natural environment and to conduct some fascinating experiments."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116140000 +0000" stop="20251116143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"The chacma baboon has many homes.  Marlin and Jim explore all of ‘chacma country’ from the lush coastal areas to the semi-desert interiors of South Africa."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116143000 +0000" stop="20251116150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Whale</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim spend weeks traversing the Southern California Coast in search of a whale."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116150000 +0000" stop="20251116153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Confessions, Confessions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing ball in the house, Peter breaks Carol's favorite vase. The other kids cover for him, each confessing. Mike and Carol to deduce that Peter is the culprit and do their best to try to get him to confess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116153000 +0000" stop="20251116160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Impractical Joker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan's practical jokes begin to backfire, as Greg's science project (a mouse named Myron he's studying for class) gets loose, prompting Alice to call an exterminator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116160000 +0000" stop="20251116163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma Nussbaum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie and Chachi's grandmother becomes very upset at them for suggesting that she move into a retirement home after they observe signs of senility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116163000 +0000" stop="20251116170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Two Of Our Weirdos Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley discover that Lenny and Squiggy have run off to join the circus. However, it falls to the girls to inform their friends that the ringmaster doesn't want to hire them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116170000 +0000" stop="20251116173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbreak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>State police come to town in search of payroll robbers. They want Andy and Barney to stay out of the way, but end up needing them more than they thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116173000 +0000" stop="20251116180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Home Movies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky bores everyone by overplaying the home movies he's taken with his new camera. When the gang finds out he's making a TV pilot they try to get in on the act, but are stopped short. They decide to make their own movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116180000 +0000" stop="20251116183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Shave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Eddie and some of his other friends brag about shaving, Wally decides it's time he try. After nicking his face, Ward tries to discourage him but this just leads Wally to continue to shave. When Ward catches him again, he scolds him right in front of Eddie which leads to Wally being made fun of.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116183000 +0000" stop="20251116190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Pipe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward receives an antique pipe as a gift from Fred Rutherford and a curious Larry and Beaver decide to try it out. First they use coffee but then they try tobacco. When Ward discovers someone has used the pipe, he jumps to the conclusion that Wally is the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116190000 +0000" stop="20251116193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Jogging Clampetts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny sees Mrs. Drysdale chasing her husband, unaware that they are jogging, saying that she is really going to beat him. She starts believing that Mrs. Drysdale is beating her husband and the violence will spread. When Elly says that she beat Jethro, Granny worries the violence has spread, but Elly and Jethro clear everything up, telling her they’ve been jogging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116193000 +0000" stop="20251116200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Collard Greens An' Fatback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is cooking collard greens and fat back for the Spring Collard Festival, just as the Drysdales are planning to sell their house to move into the house on the other side of the Clampetts. As the possible buyer, Pat Boone, is touring the house, he smells an unusual odor, which Mrs. Drysdale covers as orchid fertilizer. But Boone, who comes from Tennessee, knows it is collard greens and fat back and heads to the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116200000 +0000" stop="20251116203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Pass The Vegetables, Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan finds a crate of radioactive vegetable seeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116203000 +0000" stop="20251116210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous Hollywood producer crash-lands on the island. When he insults Ginger, the castaways stage a "Hamlet" musical play to restore her confidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116210000 +0000" stop="20251116213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Steal One, Pearl Two  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>All fingers point to Bubba when Iola's pearl necklace is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116213000 +0000" stop="20251116220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's Smoke  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama is running for president of the Church Ladies League, but things go terribly wrong when Bubba harbors a buddy—who's escaped from reform school—in his room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116220000 +0000" stop="20251116230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Her Own Two Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Crew members make a valiant effort to keep six stowaways a secret from Capt. Stubing; meanwhile, a church member disapproves of her minister's new romance, and a nearly blind woman refuses to admit her problem until Doc intercedes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116230000 +0000" stop="20251116233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Medal For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his heart set on winning a medal in a foot race at the town picnic. When he loses, he exhibits poor sportmanship. Andy teaches him a lesson about being a good sport.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251116233000 +0000" stop="20251117000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Toys &amp; Lunchboxes- Steve Harris</sub-title>
    <desc>"Steve Harris collects many things, and insists his goal is not necessarily to have the most items, just the best of the best, and he's succeding! He'll impress Lisa with some of his perfectly curated collections which include vintage toys, comic book art, KISS memorabilia and lunchboxes. Our expert today, Joel McGee, America's pop culture scout, is on hand to appraise Steve's spectacular collections and then offer him a sweet deal. He's brought something he knows our collector wants, but in return, Joel is going to ask Steve to trade something that brings back old memories for him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117000000 +0000" stop="20251117003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Der Tag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter decides Frank would be less of a pain if the others were friendlier to him; they oblige, with some startling results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117003000 +0000" stop="20251117010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is injured in a jeep accident and, aware he has a concussion, babbles to a Korean family to keep himself awake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117010000 +0000" stop="20251117013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie enters Joey in a newspaper's beautiful baby contest, against the express wishes of Mike and Gloria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117013000 +0000" stop="20251117020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarder Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Returning home unexpectedly, Archie and Edith surprise a scantily clad Teresa and her boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117020000 +0000" stop="20251117023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Chair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike accidentally breaks Archie's Chair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117023000 +0000" stop="20251117030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Goes Skiing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike asserts his independence by leaving Gloria behind while he joins his friends on a weekend skiing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117030000 +0000" stop="20251117033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's entire demeanor changes when he starts clubbing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117033000 +0000" stop="20251117040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Frank's Tribute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A reluctant Ray and Robert are enlisted to prepare a tribute for Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117040000 +0000" stop="20251117043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Where Did I Come From?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie's simple question unfolds the hilarious tale of the day he was born.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117043000 +0000" stop="20251117050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Curious Thing About Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura is shocked when Rob uses their breakfast banter as basis for an "Alan Brady" sketch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117050000 +0000" stop="20251117053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Bensonhurst Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph gets into an argument at the pool hall and has to fight a big guy at the gym. He arranges it so that he can pretend to knock out a bigger man and make the other one scared. Instead he knocks out a stranger, regaining his confidence to go ahead with the fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117053000 +0000" stop="20251117060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A street salesman cleverly eludes Death. But if he lives, a little girl must die in his place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117060000 +0000" stop="20251117070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Final Vow  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Blaming herself for the robbery of a priceless figurine, an apprentice nun leaves her convent to track down the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117070000 +0000" stop="20251117080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Only two Syndicate men know where $8 million in heroin will be arriving: narcotics dealer Alvin Taylor and his executioner, Frank Kearney. When Jim approaches Kearney to make a deal and he refuses, Willie "shoots" Kearney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117080000 +0000" stop="20251117090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>All The Scared Rabbits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble responds to a newspaper ad for a driver and is hired to drive a certain Peggy Franklin and her 10-year-old daughter, Nancy, to California. But Kimble doesn't realize that Peggy has abducted Nancy from her ex-husband, a pathologist named Dean Frankl</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117090000 +0000" stop="20251117100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Admiral's Lady</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell races against time to thwart a deranged killer stalking the wife of a retired admiral."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117100000 +0000" stop="20251117103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117103000 +0000" stop="20251117110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117110000 +0000" stop="20251117113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Spell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On an unseasonably hot day, Malloy and Reed suspect that an elusive bicyclist who overreacts to having his air pump stolen in a park is actually a drug pusher. Meanwhile, their investigation of a two-month-long yard sale leads to an armed fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117113000 +0000" stop="20251117120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gifts And Long Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by investigating a deluded and reclusive parolee whose troubled girlfriend in the apartment next door has just attempted suicide for the second time. In the meantime, they provide vital information to a detective's search for an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117120000 +0000" stop="20251117130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Yuppie Kay Ay!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill goes full Yuppie and tries to revive the excess of the Eighties."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117130000 +0000" stop="20251117133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's New Suit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally needs a new suit for an upcoming dance and he convinces his parents that he's old enough to pick out his own clothes. So he and Beaver go down to the shop and pick out the loudest, cheapest plaid suit in the entire shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117133000 +0000" stop="20251117140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A school play has Beaver and his classmates assigned parts and Beaver is assigned the role of a canary. However, he doesn't seem to be graceful enough to fly around like a bird. To make matters worse, on the night of the play, Ward's words of encouragement lead to Beaver coming down with a case of stage fright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117140000 +0000" stop="20251117150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Artful Dodger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Allen Sheridan has more enemies than you can shake a stick at, even though he's due to inherit the healthy sum of $162,000. When Allen turns up dead his killer could be anyone, but his cousin, Sarette, becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117150000 +0000" stop="20251117160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassination: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock and his daughter, Leanne, become mired in a case involving local politics and murder when the town mayor is assassinated and soon after that a judge is implicated in another death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117160000 +0000" stop="20251117170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>First Deadly Sin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial rapist stalks Sparta.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117170000 +0000" stop="20251117180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Outrage - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Verdie's husband Harley is arrested for an old crime</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117180000 +0000" stop="20251117190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt heads to a nearby town to investigate a friend's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117190000 +0000" stop="20251117200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Henry Comstock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights meet a miner who has been swindled by Henry T.P. Comstock. They then tell the story of how they meet Comstock, how silver was discovered and how Virginia City got its name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117200000 +0000" stop="20251117203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Day At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in an explosion, Lucas fights despair as he prepares for a meeting with a gun-toting enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117203000 +0000" stop="20251117210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Two ex-Confederate officers seek revenge on Lucas. McCain was a lieutenant in the 8th Indiana, which defeated the 12th Cavalry 15 years earlier at the Battle of Fort Donaldson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117210000 +0000" stop="20251117220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Shiloh Degnan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"An officer Chris knows is found near the wagon train near death. He tells Chris that a passage in the bible describes him and his commander - Shioh Degnan. Chris returns him to Fort Bannerman to the Army where the truth is revealed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117220000 +0000" stop="20251117230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dinner Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman almost hits a kid on a bike, who starts choking; she later has an epileptic fit. A man is shot by his father-in-law when he learns his daughter is married and pregnant. Roy tries to set John up with his wife's cousin. Three drug addicts are treated in the hospital: a woman with a gangrenous hand, a poison victim and a man showing signs of tetanus. In the field: an alcoholic, an obese man with a pacemaker, and a child whose arm is caught in a swimming pool drain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117230000 +0000" stop="20251117233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Some 38th Parallels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank tries to distinguish himself by selling the camp garbage, but it's Hawkeye who finds a use for it: he dumps it on a troublesome Colonel Coner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251117233000 +0000" stop="20251118000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Novocaine Mutiny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has Hawkeye up on charges of mutiny for usurping his authority when Potter was away on leave and Frank was the commanding officer. B.J., Potter and Radar are in attendance of the preliminary hearing, at which they hear conflicting versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118000000 +0000" stop="20251118003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Smilin' Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th turns up a sick helicopter pilot, 'Smilin' Jack, who doesn't want to quit, and a twice-wounded GI who does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118003000 +0000" stop="20251118010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The More I See You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is reunited with a woman he thought was out of his life forever, but who never altogether leaves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118010000 +0000" stop="20251118013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118013000 +0000" stop="20251118020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a sort of publicity stunt, the town decides to pull over the first car that drives through Mayberry and make its occupant the town's guest of honor. That lucky driver? A recently released convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118020000 +0000" stop="20251118023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Cruising With Marie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray agrees to accompany Marie on a Caribbean cruise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118023000 +0000" stop="20251118030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ray Home Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is forced to confront the real reason he doesn't want to stay home alone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118030000 +0000" stop="20251118033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Hannibal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and the daughter of a German general try to photograph her father's plans designed to prolong the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118033000 +0000" stop="20251118040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>My Favorite Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A baroness is asked by Klink to get secrets out of Hogan, and he complies by giving her a British agent with phony invasion plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118040000 +0000" stop="20251118043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jack Gilford</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hat, a shy man becomes the center of attention when he puts on a hat. Then, in Carol and Sis, Carol fears her sister was kidnapped. Finally, in The Writer, the characters from Harvey's story come to life as he writes about survivors at sea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118043000 +0000" stop="20251118053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A club owner is found dead, his partner charged. The men's animosity towards each other makes the case appear to be an open-and-shut ordeal, but Mason is not so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118053500 +0000" stop="20251118060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Denton On Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A has-been, drunk gunslinger finds his fast-draw abilities magically restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118060500 +0000" stop="20251118070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Annabel  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A disturbed chemist refuses to accept his ex-girlfriend's marriage to a co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118070500 +0000" stop="20251118080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix travels to New Mexico to prove that a Native American's death was murder, he runs into resistance from the townsfolk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118080500 +0000" stop="20251118090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Lonely Place To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A syndicate boss may just be next in line to be murdered when Cannon investigates a case involving a triple homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118090500 +0000" stop="20251118100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a plane crash that resulted in a corporation president's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118100000 +0000" stop="20251118103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer is shot while making a routine check on a pair of paroled convicts parked near a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118103000 +0000" stop="20251118110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit And Run Driver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon use newspapers, radio and TV to publicize their clues to the identity of a hit-and-run driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118110000 +0000" stop="20251118113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>O'brien's Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's headstrong and elderly apartment manager stages a protest at the station after she's victimized by a serial purse snatcher, and Malloy suggests a stakeout will be their only chance to apprehend the suspect. On patrol, he and Reed chase a suspicious vehicle into a lumber yard, and investigate the murder of a young man at his parents' home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118113000 +0000" stop="20251118120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest - 484</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspected child stealer who has escaped custody with the baby after being arrested for shoplifting baby formula. Meanwhile, Reed has to think quickly when he is held at gunpoint while responding to a burglary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118120000 +0000" stop="20251118130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Wants A Trophy</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118130000 +0000" stop="20251118133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Visiting Aunts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally are all excited about going to the carnival; however, Aunt Martha throws a wrench into their plans when she makes an unexpected visit with a friend of hers, forcing Wally and Beaver to count the hours away, hoping she will leave soon enough so they can still go to the carnival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118133000 +0000" stop="20251118140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward takes June and the boys away on a trip to a cabin in hopes of experiencing the "great outdoors." However, as he quickly discovers, getting away from today's modern conveniences will be more difficult then he anticipated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118140000 +0000" stop="20251118150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lucky Legs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Marjorie Cluny wins a contest for best-looking legs sponsored by Frank Patton of Stellar Productions. Her prize is a trip to Hollywood and a role in Patton's next picture. Unfortunately, there was fine print in Marjorie's contract that she didn't read.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118150000 +0000" stop="20251118160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassination: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock and his daughter, Leanne, become mired in a case involving local politics and murder when the town mayor is assassinated and soon after that a judge is implicated in another death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118160000 +0000" stop="20251118170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Just A Country Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to Los Angeles to arrest an arsonist. When the man is murdered to keep him from talking Bubba teams up with a pretty insurance investigator to solve the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118170000 +0000" stop="20251118180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Outrage - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Verdie's husband Harley is arrested for an old crime</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118180000 +0000" stop="20251118190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Once A Haggen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Festus' is accused of murdering the man who bested them at poker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118190000 +0000" stop="20251118200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Magnificent Adah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Famous actress Adah Isaacs Menken pays a visit to Virginia City. She is an old friend of Ben's and the two begin to renew their friendship much to the chagrin of Adam, Hoss and Joe. Ben's sons believe that Adah has plans to become the next Mrs. Ben Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118200000 +0000" stop="20251118203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Assault</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman can't talk his way out of an assault charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118203000 +0000" stop="20251118210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Short Rope For A Tall Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are in another town to sell a bull to Joe Lovering. While there, Mark buys two horses from Mr. Schneider. Neither Mark nor his father knows that the horses have been illegally bought and resold to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118210000 +0000" stop="20251118220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Levy-mcgowan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"When the Levy family joins the wagon train, the tranquility becomes less so as the fathers compete in checkers, young sons fight, and son and daughter fall in love. Lastly, a settler who tries to shake down the train to cross his property."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118220000 +0000" stop="20251118230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Musical Mania</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Chet cracks a joke about John playing the squad horn, John takes up the bagpipes, trombone and guitar. Paramedics help a gardener suffering from tetanus. The father of a boy suffering from lead poisoning is reluctant to have it treated. The firemen rescue the driver of an ice cream truck. A schoolgirl dies from an overdose. A glider pilot crash lands. A man working under his house is trapped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118230000 +0000" stop="20251118233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deluge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A sudden deluge of wounded at the 4077th is followed by a fire and a rainstorm, which makes matters difficult for the staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251118233000 +0000" stop="20251119000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Interview</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Clete Roberts has arrived in Korea to interview the staff of the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital because of its high 97% efficiency rating. In Roberts' interviews with Hawkeye, B.J., Frank, Radar, Klinger, Mulcahy and Potter, they talk about how they cope with their situation, what they miss about home, how they feel about who they work with and whether they see any good in coming from war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119000000 +0000" stop="20251119003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A rumor that there's going to be a practice bug-out causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in to bug out, and the rumor suddenly comes to life! Meanwhile, Hawkeye begins surgery on a patient with a spinal injury. The bug-out proceeds without him, Hot Lips and Radar, and they quickly learn after the unit departs that they're in the midst of the front. When Potter, Mulcahy, BJ, Frank and the others arrive at the buildings which had been scouted by helicopter, they find the house full of "business girls," and Potter gives them Klinger's dresses to persuade them to leave the house. A helicopter comes to evacuate the spinal injury patient, and just as the three get ready to go to the new location, they find the 4077 is already returning, and eventually everyone reunites back at the camp, what with the Chinese being repulsed.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119003000 +0000" stop="20251119010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rumor that there's going to be a camp relocation causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in that the rumor is indeed fact!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119010000 +0000" stop="20251119013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling salesman Bert Miller is getting tired of traveling, so Andy and Barney plan to help him set up a small general goods shop on a vacant lot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119013000 +0000" stop="20251119020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Warden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Mayberry jail is filled to capacity with a group of moonshiners who blame Otis for their capture, Andy takes Otis home to serve his term.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119020000 +0000" stop="20251119023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Big Shots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray uses his "weight" as a sports writer to jump to the front of the line.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119023000 +0000" stop="20251119030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Move Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray confides to Debra that her need to cuddle is causing him many sleepless nights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119030000 +0000" stop="20251119033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Watch The Trains Go By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for Burkhalter's sister to keep Klink occupied, so he can leave camp and blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119033000 +0000" stop="20251119040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Old Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses the car of an SS man who's just married Klink's old girlfriend and is honeymooning in Paris, where Hogan needs to pass radios to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119040000 +0000" stop="20251119043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests John Davidson, Ruth Buzzi, And Burt Reynolds</sub-title>
    <desc>In Zelda and Gladys, Carol and Ruth disguise themselves in the audience and poke fun at the show. Then, in The Ham Actor, Carol fills in for a sick ballerina. Finally, in Salute to MGM studios, the gang parodies classic films, including "Lust for Life", "National Velvet", and "Camille".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119043000 +0000" stop="20251119053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bogus Buccaneers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aspiring actor Tony Polk lands a job on a popular TV program. Part of his job consists of dressing up in a buccaneer costume and delivering gifts to viewers at their homes. Another actor and Tony trade lists and before too long he's up the creek.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119053500 +0000" stop="20251119060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteen-millimeter Shrine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging former movie star lives and dreams in the past, constantly watching her old movies alone in isolation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119060500 +0000" stop="20251119070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>House Guest  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>John Mitchell gets more than he bargained for when he offers a young man a new start in life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119070500 +0000" stop="20251119080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Survivor Who Wasn't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man survives a plane crash—or does he? His wife has her doubts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119080500 +0000" stop="20251119090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>No Pockets In A Shroud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When an heir of a millionaire who prefers to live like a hermit is discovered to be missing, Cannon in hired to investigate and uncovers a mysterious case of murder and embezzlement. But the case is hampered by the hermit's attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119090500 +0000" stop="20251119100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Of The Dunes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A weekend motorcyclist witnesses a gangster burial, then pays for it with his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119100000 +0000" stop="20251119103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bookie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday goes undercover with the department's chaplain in order to bust a gambling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119103000 +0000" stop="20251119110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Subscription Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday learns about a scam artist with a novel twist: he uses an authentic Congressional Medal of Honor to solicit magazine subscriptions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119110000 +0000" stop="20251119113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed starts a flu epidemic that decimates the city's police force, forcing him and Malloy to work a double shift. During day watch, he and Malloy encounter a bookmaker being held at gunpoint, mediate a dispute over a cantaloupe, investigate a possible robbery in progress, engage in a foot chase with an athletic young man and pull over a motorist who turns out to be a VIP.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119113000 +0000" stop="20251119120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly appointed Police Commissioner Edna Dixon accompanies Malloy and Reed on night watch, where they deal with a naked elderly wino at a bar, try to diffuse a possible riot situation following a gang-related stabbing and pursue a deaf teenager in a stolen car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119120000 +0000" stop="20251119130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Parks And Record</sub-title>
    <desc>"All aboard the RV! Bill and Toony are hitting some of the lesser-known National Parks."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119130000 +0000" stop="20251119133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Present</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally decides that he is going to have a birthday party, and Beaver jumps to the conclusion that he won't be invited. While shopping for Wally's present, Larry talks Beaver into spending his money on a bow and arrow set for himself and buying a cheap gift for Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119133000 +0000" stop="20251119140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Grass Is Always Greener</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally make friends with the garbage man's kids, Chris and Pete. They quickly learn that they take for granted what they have. Simple things like just having a yard to play in leave Chris and Pete in awe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119140000 +0000" stop="20251119150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Violent Village</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On a fishing trip in a small Sierra Nevada town with his old friend, Sheriff Gene Norris, Mason gets sidetracked into a murder case when Phil Beecher returns from jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119150000 +0000" stop="20251119160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Annihilator  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>At Cassie's request, Matlock reluctantly agrees to represent a famous wrestler accused of killing a long-time rival. The key witness is a young girl whose story might not be completely accurate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119160000 +0000" stop="20251119170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>No Other Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet tries to keep Eugene from giving up when his father faces the death penalty. And the police search for three suspects in connection to a robbery/murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119170000 +0000" stop="20251119180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pledge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen wants to attend medical school</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119180000 +0000" stop="20251119190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>No Hands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc is threatened by the Ginnis clan when he fails to respond quickly to their demands for treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119190000 +0000" stop="20251119200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Truckee Strip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Luther Bishop and Ben Cartwright have had an ongoing land dispute for a number of years over a small tract called the Truckee Strip. One of Bishop's employee's has a grudge against the Cartwrights and wants to stir up the feud again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119200000 +0000" stop="20251119203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Bibs Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor-turned-gunfighter's reputation hangs on one lucky shot—and a lot of gall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119203000 +0000" stop="20251119210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119210000 +0000" stop="20251119220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Bernard Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Indians kidnap an elderly lady on the train. They will return her when the train takes the Chief's son to the doctor and cure him. However, some on the train don't want to help. The task becomes harder when they learn what the illness is."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119220000 +0000" stop="20251119230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Helpful</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy has an argument with his wife and Johnny tries to help. The firemen rescue a man from precarious auto wreck. A brilliant doctor's erratic behavior causes concern at the hospital. Doctors diagnose a woman's heart condition. Paramedics rescue a dog from a roof and two children lost in a rapidly flooding storm drain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119230000 +0000" stop="20251119233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret, calling from Tokyo, holds the camp in suspense until she returns with the news of her engagement to Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. Frank Burns takes the news hard and arrests a Korean family as spies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251119233000 +0000" stop="20251120000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Sight, Out Of Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While fixing a stove that explodes, Hawkeye's face is badly burned. His eyes are bandaged, and it is not known if he will ever see again. Meanwhile Frank bets on the outcome of a baseball game, which he has already heard on the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120000000 +0000" stop="20251120003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lt. Radar O'reilly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Following an offer of promotion made by Master Sergeant Woodruff at a poker game, Radar is promoted to the rank of lieutenant. Finding this position awkward, Radar opts to return to his position as an enlisted man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120003000 +0000" stop="20251120010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Nurses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hot Lips confines Nurse Baker to her quarters, little does she know that Baker's husband has arrived in the camp. Hawkeye and B.J. put them together in Hot Lips' tent, telling everyone that a quarantined patient has been placed there. When Hot Lips discovers what has happened, she breaks down and refuses to press charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120010000 +0000" stop="20251120013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The County Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Simpson, the county nurse, wants to get all of the farmers in the county to take their innoculations. Figuring everyone will follow suit if she can just get Rafe Hollister to do it, she enlists the help of Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120013000 +0000" stop="20251120020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Barney In The Big City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying in Raleigh, Barney believes he is witnessing a man casing the hotel clientelle. Barney is right in believing a crime about to be committed, but he is tailing the house detective and has hooked up with the real crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120020000 +0000" stop="20251120023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Getaway, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra and Ray feel tremendous pressure to show each other a good time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120023000 +0000" stop="20251120030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Working Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Debra gets a part-time job, Ray is left to fend for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120030000 +0000" stop="20251120033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Klink's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets himself sent to the hospital so he can get information from a wounded agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120033000 +0000" stop="20251120040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Purchasing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and crew are ordered to deliver airdropped ammo to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120040000 +0000" stop="20251120043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jerry Stiller And Anne Meara</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mary Worthless, Carol rains on the happiest married couple's parade. Then, in Mr. and Mrs. Chou En Lai, the Chinese leader and his wife discuss their recent visit to America. Next, in The Auto Accident, the juxtaposition between men and women is shown with two different car crashes. Finally, in Street Wedding, a poor couples decide to marry on the street, to the shock of their society parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120043000 +0000" stop="20251120053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Midnight Howler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is accused of killing her ex-husband, shot to death during a live radio broadcast while giving an interview. His ex-wife admits to being present during the murder, but swears she did not pull the trigger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120053500 +0000" stop="20251120060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120060500 +0000" stop="20251120070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Curtain  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A former amnesiac learns he is an accused killer wanted by the law and a hit man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120070500 +0000" stop="20251120080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Choice Of Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix looks into a businessman's murder, discovering that the man's wife may have been the real target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120080500 +0000" stop="20251120090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Stone Cold Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The reopening of the cold case of a salesgirl reveals that a bicycle she sold may be a clue to her death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120090500 +0000" stop="20251120100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Venus As In Fly Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A male-chauvinist author murder's her feminist lover's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120100000 +0000" stop="20251120103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese widow is senselessly murdered, leaving her small daughter an orphan. Friday has a hard time controlling his emotions while seeking the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120103000 +0000" stop="20251120110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120110000 +0000" stop="20251120113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a difficult night ahead of them when they get stuck with an old patrol car that it is riddled with problems. On patrol, they deal with a female car thief, chase down a prowler with a sympathetic story, pull over a motorist who points out an ironic detail, investigate suspicious activity at a warehouse and pursue an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120113000 +0000" stop="20251120120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Ground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>During a seemingly routine traffic stop, Malloy and Reed are ambushed and kidnapped by two men who are on the run after a foiled robbery attempt. Their only hope is a young woman who is led to believe that Malloy and Reed killed her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120120000 +0000" stop="20251120130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Constitution State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit the state of Connecticut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120130000 +0000" stop="20251120133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat Builders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally, Chester and Tooey are building their own boat and plan to sail on it, despite Ward and June's forbidding Wally. Once at the lake, Beaver is the only one small enough to get in it and once on the water, the boat tips over leaving a soaked Beaver behind. However, it's trying to keep their afternoon of boating a secret from Ward and June, that's really going to wipe Wally and Beaver out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120133000 +0000" stop="20251120140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Plays Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver find themselves tardy for the third time this week and decide to skip altogether. However, they quickly find themselves caught when they accidentally walk on the set of a live TV show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120140000 +0000" stop="20251120150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Frantic Flyer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A double cross, a double murder, a plane crash, missing money and an innocent widow charged with crimes she didn't commit are the elements of this case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120150000 +0000" stop="20251120160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Husband  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock agrees to defend Cassie's friend, Judy, he is shocked to learn that Judy's husband secretly had another wife. As the case continues, Matlock uncovers more shocking facts about Judy's husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120160000 +0000" stop="20251120170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Turning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea thinks Virgil needs a new line of work after seeing the aftermath of a deadly shooting at a roadhouse. Virgil finds himself in danger when they arrest the man who committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120170000 +0000" stop="20251120180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Triumph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason and his squad find out the war is over, but there is a German soldier still shooting at them</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120180000 +0000" stop="20251120190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>May Blossom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus' cousin, May Blossom, comes to town to marry him, honoring a pact between their fathers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120190000 +0000" stop="20251120200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging Posse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After a woman is murdered in an attempted rape, a posse is organized in town, led by an old tracker who incites the men for a hanging. He leads the posse out with no intention of bringing the suspects back alive, but Adam and Joe ride along to make sure they do.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120200000 +0000" stop="20251120203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120203000 +0000" stop="20251120210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120210000 +0000" stop="20251120220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kurt Davos Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>"Kurt Davos, a highly respected man, is badly injured while trying to save Florence Hastings trapped in a runaway wagon. Florence, scared of dogs had once tried to kill Kurt's dog, volunteers to live with and care for Kurt, now paralyzed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120220000 +0000" stop="20251120230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Drivers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets bugged by other people's bad driving habits. A college quarterback experiences back pain. Roy and John's former paramedic instructor dies, while Roy and John themselves teach a CPR class. A boy gets stuck inside a tree. A fire at a hotel is complicated by a cardiac victim on the third floor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120230000 +0000" stop="20251120233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Abduction Of Margaret Houlihan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing that North Korean prisoners have been released in the area, everyone is upset when Margaret disappears. Colonel Flagg is called in to investigate, and bungles things in his usual manner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251120233000 +0000" stop="20251121000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sigmund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman, feeling depressed, visits the 4077th to observe how they fare under the pressures of war. He begins a letter to Sigmund Freud as a form of self-therapy, and releases his tension in the form of a practical joke with B.J., aimed at Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121000000 +0000" stop="20251121003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mulcahy's War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Frank discovers that Danny Fitzsimmons has shot himself to get out of combat, Father Mulcahy is called in. Realizing his lack of understanding of the fighting, Mulcahy accompanies Radar to an aid station, where they encounter the real war at first hand. Mulcahy performs an emergency tracheotomy, guided by Hawkeye over the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121003000 +0000" stop="20251121010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Korean Surgeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Syn Paik, a North Korean surgeon, arrives with some wounded, he is passed off as a South Korean by Hawkeye and B.J., but to no avail. Hot Lips and Frank try to convince Potter that Paik is a spy. Paik, Hawkeye and B.J. agree that it would be in the interest of all for him to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121010000 +0000" stop="20251121013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Bells For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Clara convinces Aunt Bee that Andy won't be able to find a wife as long as she's around, Aunt Bee begins searching for a man whom she can marry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121013000 +0000" stop="20251121020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Every time Andy tries to be alone with Mary, Barney shows up. After Andy explains that he wants to be alone with her, Barney believes that Andy is planning to propose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121020000 +0000" stop="20251121023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Be Nice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra demands to know why Ray is more helpful to other mothers than her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121023000 +0000" stop="20251121030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Dancing With Debra</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray urges Debra to go swing dancing with Robert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121030000 +0000" stop="20251121033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan faces a startling development: His captors are sending him to America to demand surrender—with a super weapon supposedly supplied by the Russians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121033000 +0000" stop="20251121040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must destroy an anti-aircraft defense system designed by a beautiful English woman who may have defected to Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121040000 +0000" stop="20251121043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nora Desmond, Carol plays an washed-up, silent film actress doing a bug spray commercial. Then, in F. Lee Bunny, Carol asks a Rabbit to be her attorney. Finally, in The Oldest Man, the slaves on a ship get a new recruit -- the Oldest Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121043000 +0000" stop="20251121053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Vanishing Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Stacey Fielding's small airplane crashes and poison is found in his body, Miriam Fielding is arrested because the last thing Fielding drank was whiskey from a flask she had given him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121053500 +0000" stop="20251121060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Escape Clause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hypochondriac exchanges his soul for immortality and indestructibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121060500 +0000" stop="20251121070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Reckoning  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An easygoing guy has a curious difficulty: he can't convince anyone that he murdered his adulterous partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121070500 +0000" stop="20251121080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Word Called Courage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Haunted by the fact that he broke under torture during the Korean War, one of Mannix's former comrades kidnaps the detective, subjecting him to the same torture he underwent to prove that anybody would crack under such treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121080500 +0000" stop="20251121090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is A Double Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired to be a bodyguard for the daughter of a broker and his grandchildren, but is drawn in when the broker reveals that he believes his son in law is involved in a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121090500 +0000" stop="20251121100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is on the case when a rich woman's affairs seem to be ending in terrible accidents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121100000 +0000" stop="20251121103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121103000 +0000" stop="20251121110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121110000 +0000" stop="20251121113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Nightwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he can haggle another $12.50 off a used car, but malloy warns him that he's pushing his luck. On patrol, they test a suspected drunk driver who hit a light pole, investigate a home invasion that results in a man fatally shooting his ex-son-in-</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121113000 +0000" stop="20251121120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While off duty following shooting re-qualification, Reed fires his weapon at a would-be unarmed mugger whose armed accomplish drives off. When the would-be suspect later dies, the unfortunate circumstances leave Reed facing a possible suspension and murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121120000 +0000" stop="20251121130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On The Wagon</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill takes Toony on a covered wagon journey down the old Oregon Trail."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121130000 +0000" stop="20251121133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Garage Painters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lazy weekend leads Ward to direct Wally and Beaver to read a book, Tom Sawyer. The book influences them so much that they take on the job of painting the garage doors. However, they soon find the job to be awfully boring and messy. Chaos erupts when neighbor Bengie Bellamy stops by wanting to help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121133000 +0000" stop="20251121140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Pug Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When the new girl, Gloria, tells Wally that he has a pug nose, he becomes incredibly self-conscious and purchases a contraption that is suppose to give him a strong Roman nose. When Ward discovers the device, he gives him a pep talk which just makes matters worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121140000 +0000" stop="20251121150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wayward Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Sutton is listed as the author of a best-selling book describing his experiences in a Korean POW camp. When the real author is released from an Army hospital, Sutton is slain before he can tell the truth and his widow is arrested for the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121150000 +0000" stop="20251121160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It appears that a ghost has hired Matlock when the attorney learns the man who hired him to defend his wife is in fact the man she is accused of murdering!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121160000 +0000" stop="20251121170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman Much Admired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie's old flame returns to Sparta to settle some business matters and see Bill. When she is murdered he travels to Gulfport and meets his daughter Lana for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121170000 +0000" stop="20251121180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Premonition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While happy the war is over, Cindy has a premonition that Ben is in trouble</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121180000 +0000" stop="20251121190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Bassops</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A family finds Matt and a prisoner handcuffed to one another—with the prisoner claiming to be the marshal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121190000 +0000" stop="20251121200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While in the bank arranging for a letter of credit, Ben and Hoss encounter the bank robbing Morgan gang. Both Ben and one of Morgan's men get shot. When Billy Morgan dies, his brothers promise to avenge his death by going after Ben.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121200000 +0000" stop="20251121203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121203000 +0000" stop="20251121210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121210000 +0000" stop="20251121220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Eve Newhope Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>"Patrick O'Shaughnessy has come to visit his daughter Eve, believing her to be a respectable married woman. Knowing that Eve actually is the popular owner of a saloon, Hawks, Wooster, Duke, and Eve's favorite patrons decide to change Eve."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121220000 +0000" stop="20251121230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>School Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A new trainee appears to be lacking in confidence; a bookcase falls on an elderly gentleman searching for a book; a baseball player is injured; an ambulance is hit by a car; a boy's chemistry set explodes in his face; students play a practical joke on a sleeping man; and a man is injured at a junkyard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121230000 +0000" stop="20251121233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye Get Your Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After 24 hours of surgery, Hawkeye and Potter venture off to a Korean hospital to lend a hand. Hawkeye is appalled to learn that he must carry a gun. After helping the Koreans, they are shelled on the way back. They scramble from the jeep before it is shelled, and Potter urges Hawkeye to shoot in self-defense, against Hawkeye's will, and he does—into the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251121233000 +0000" stop="20251122000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Colonel Potter goes to Tokyo on R&amp;R, his horse develops colic. Klinger becomes chronically depressed, and Hot Lips gets appendicitis. The horse is flushed out with a hose, Hawkeye and B.J. perform an appendectomy on Hot Lips, and all are well when Potter returns, except Klinger. Potter offers Klinger a discharge for severe depression, and Klinger gets very excited, which loses him the discharge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122000000 +0000" stop="20251122003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Exorcism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Potter orders Radar to move a Korean spirit post believed to ward off evil spirits, things mysteriously begin to go wrong. When an old Korean man is brought into camp for medical attention, he refuses surgery unless the spirits in the camp are exorcised. A priestess is brought in, who exhibits her dance and her bells and chants. All is well, and Radar returns the spirit post to its original position.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122003000 +0000" stop="20251122010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawk's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hawkeye bemoans the young age of the wounded, he appears to develop problems. Sleepwalking and bad dreams, according to Sidney Freedman, are taking Hawkeye back to a simple time, but the horrors of war continue to intrude. After Sidney's assurances that he is as sane as can be, Hawkeye's life once again seems to settle down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122010000 +0000" stop="20251122013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bookie Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A bookie from Raleigh sets himself up in Floyd's barbershop as an extra barber, trying to avoid the heat. Andy gets suspicious when the new barber has the same three clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122013000 +0000" stop="20251122020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy On Trial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A news mogul swears revenge on Andy after he is arrested for what he deems a minor infraction. In retaliation, he sends a reporter to Mayberry to dig up whatever dirt she can on Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122020000 +0000" stop="20251122023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert Moves Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Amy are desperate to have some time to themselves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122023000 +0000" stop="20251122030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>How They Met</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a flashback episode as Ray and Debra reminisce about their first meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122030000 +0000" stop="20251122033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Major Bonacelli</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Italian officer who studied under Klink helps Hogan photograph an air base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122033000 +0000" stop="20251122040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Dear Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's men plan to surprise him for his birthday by blowing up an ammunition dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122040000 +0000" stop="20251122043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Lily Tomlin</sub-title>
    <desc>Lily Tomlin opens with a monologue as Laverna, a chatty woman in a restaurant. Then, in The Godfather, the gang parodies the classic film, with Steve playing Marlon Brando and Carol as his bride. Finally, in Caged Dames, Carol plots her escape from prison to get away from the gruff matron.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122043000 +0000" stop="20251122053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golfer's Gambit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Washed up golfer Chick Farley has made many enemies throughout the years and it's not really a surprise when he turns up murdered. But when fellow golfer Jim Harrell is charged with the death, Mason gets a mysterious envelope containing $2,500 and a request from Harrell to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122053500 +0000" stop="20251122060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122060500 +0000" stop="20251122070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Ride The Nightmare  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An elderly acquaintance plunges Chris Martin into a nightmare stuffed with blackmail, kidnapping and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122070500 +0000" stop="20251122080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of Mannix's detective friends is murdered, he discovers the man worked for a mafioso and sets out to learn why he died, despite pressure to stop digging.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122080500 +0000" stop="20251122090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An accountant wants to teach the world a lesson about the production of a deadly nerve gas when he steals a can of the substance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122090500 +0000" stop="20251122100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Platinum Connection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After a jeweler swindles his insurance company, he comes to suspect that his secretary is on to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122100000 +0000" stop="20251122103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Visit From A Big Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Shady Rest gets a visit from a Hollywood star, who wishes to lie low in Hooterville for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
