<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315180000 +0000" stop="20250315190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Big Shadow On The Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Immigrant winemakers decide to plant their grapes on Ponderosa land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315190000 +0000" stop="20250315193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315193000 +0000" stop="20250315200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315200000 +0000" stop="20250315210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Wild Deuces</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mushy wins $1,500 from saloon-owner Lorelie Mears, his troubles begin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315210000 +0000" stop="20250315213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ledge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin and four others debate what to do after a man falls off a ledge and it is uncertain whether he is alive or dead. Unresponsive and out of reach, the fallen man may be on the receiving end of a mercy killing if no one can find a way to get to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315213000 +0000" stop="20250315220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Ballot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Randall comes to assist a war buddy in his bid for the town's mayoralty, quickly running afoul of the established political machine and its corrupt mayor and sheriff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315220000 +0000" stop="20250316000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Ants In The Pantry, We Want Our Mummy, Boobs In Arms, Baby Sitters Jitters, Sweet And Hot, Yokes On Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are pest exterminators who drum up business by planting vermin in a ritzy mansion where a party is going on.  They are hired, but must pose as guests to work unobserved.   , The stooges go to Egypt in search of the mummy of king Rootin-Tootin for which a museum will pay a $5000 prize., Rejected by the armed services, the Stooges decide to "do their bit" by becoming farmers.  After paying $1000 and throwing in their car, the boys are owners of a run down farm, which lacks any livestock.  After capturing an escaped ostrich, they decide to carve jack-o- lanterns for profit and then must contend with some Japanese who have escaped from a relocation center.  The Stooges become heroes by capturing the escapees, with the help of explosive eggs laid by the ostrich who had swallowed some blasting powder. , The Stooges are greeting card salesmen who are mistakenly inducted into the army after escaping from the jealous husband of one of their customers.  In boot camp their sergeant turns out to be the same man, whom they constantly vex and bewilder.  When the boys are sent to the front lines and the sergeant is captured they must rescue him, which they do after doping themselves with laughing gas.  At the end they get shot off into the sunset on a cannon shell. , The Stooges are facing eviction and decide to raise some money by becoming baby-sitters.  Their first client is a women separated from her husband, who entrusts her son "Junior" to the boys' care.  When the husband steals the baby, the Stooges set out to find their missing charge and return him to his mother.  The boys confront the husband and find Junior, and in the process the estranged couple is re-united. , Nightclub performer Larry wants Joe and his sister Tiny to join the act.  The only problem is that Tiny is afraid to sing in front of people.  They take her to a psychiatrist (Moe) who cures her, and the act is a success. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316000000 +0000" stop="20250316023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost World</sub-title>
    <desc>"A professor leads an expedition into the Amazonian jungle to find dinosaurs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316023000 +0000" stop="20250316050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Puppet Master</sub-title>
    <desc>"An evil puppeteer targets psychics using his deadly marionettes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316050000 +0000" stop="20250316060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>A Day At The Zoo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A cave boy appears and attempts to lure Penny away, but she refuses and is instead caught in a net. She is transported to an intergalactic zoo, were she will be put on show. Meanwhile Dr. Smith tries to take over the zoo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316060000 +0000" stop="20250316070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Jonah And The Whale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to salvage information about a destroyed underwater laboratory, Admiral Nelson and Russian scientist Katya Markhova are swallowed by a whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316070000 +0000" stop="20250316080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict stumbles across the Spindrift and takes it with him, leaving half the group stranded and the other half trapped inside the ship, as the man falls into quicksand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316080000 +0000" stop="20250316090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Billy The Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers find themselves being hunted by Billy the Kid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316090000 +0000" stop="20250316100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Leeches</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The president of an electronics company fears aliens are kidnapping prominent minds -- and he's next!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316100000 +0000" stop="20250316110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>The Racer's Edge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt develops a new power and is tasked with protecting a diplomat's daughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316110000 +0000" stop="20250316113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Jessie's Song   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie is under pressure with midterms and her own singing group so she turns to caffeine pills, ignoring Slater's warning that the pills are hazardous to her health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316113000 +0000" stop="20250316120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Fabulous Belding Boys   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>If the gang fails a test in an obnoxious teacher's class, they won't be able to go on a class field trip. On the day of the test, however, the teacher doesn't show, so Belding's brother, Rod, takes over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316120000 +0000" stop="20250316123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Glee Club   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang joins the Glee Club, but soon the friends lose their pep. Jesse catches Lisa's cold, Screech makes a fool of himself in front of his girlfriend's parents and the gang's singing is totally off key.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316123000 +0000" stop="20250316130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Up Is Hard To Undo   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>First, it's splitsville for Zack and Kelly when Kelly goes on a date with her ex-boyfriend. Slater and Jessie are finally a couple, but things get messed up when they disagree on how to celebrate their coupledom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316130000 +0000" stop="20250316133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Video Yearbook   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and the gang decide to make a video yearbook for Bayside, but when Zack uses the opportunity to create the "Girls of Bayside Dating Service," his friends get him back big time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316133000 +0000" stop="20250316140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Aloha Slater   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater is torn when his Army father tells him they're moving away. Jealous the spotlight's not on him, Zack spreads a rumor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316140000 +0000" stop="20250316143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Her Sister's Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of being in Marcia's shadow, Jan is determined to do something that Marcia never did. She tries the pompom squad, and then an essay writing contest, where she wins first prize - or does she?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316143000 +0000" stop="20250316150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Personality Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter decides to try out a new funny, joke-telling personality, which he plans to unveil at an upcoming party. Meanwhile, Bobby and Cindy whip the house into shape after learning about fire safety at school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316150000 +0000" stop="20250316153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Married Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>It's their 23rd anniversary, and Howard and Marion are angry at each other over a rate-your-mate test they took in a magazine. They are to go on a second honeymoon, but Marion angers Howard even further when she wants everything to be exactly the same as it was on their first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316153000 +0000" stop="20250316160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Councilman Defazio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank is making his usual contribution to his local councilman. After the guy has taken Frank's money, he tells him that he plans to tear down Cowboy Bill's and build a high-rise on top of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316160000 +0000" stop="20250316163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Big House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When the state police leave two captured bank robbers in the custody of the Mayberry police department overnight, Barney is determined to show the prisoners that the Mayberry jail is as good as any other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316163000 +0000" stop="20250316170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Paris At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Equipped with an English-French dictionary, Lucy sets out to see Paris and "discover" an artist whose paintings will become very valuable, as she knows she has "the eye." Lucy's first encounter is indeed with an artist—a con artist who changes her American money for French. Lucy's adventures land Lucy, Ethel and Fred in jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316170000 +0000" stop="20250316173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Her Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes good friends with a classmate, Linda Dennison. However, their relationship is blown out of proportion by Beaver's classmates who begin to tease him and goad him into insulting Linda to prove that she isn't his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316173000 +0000" stop="20250316180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Library Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows Beaver to check out a book on his library card but when Beaver loses the book he becomes convinced that Ward will be put in jail, thanks to Eddie Haskell's wiseguy comments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316180000 +0000" stop="20250316183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Get Culture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are having no success getting acquainted with their neighbors. Not to mention, the clan is having trouble with Mrs. Drysdale and Mrs. Potts. They decide to go back home to the hills, and when they go see Drysdale, they feel they are not wanted. Drysdale tries to clear everything up, and even has his Italian suit maker create a full suit for Jed, though Jed thinks the suit maker is trying to tie him up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316183000 +0000" stop="20250316190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lib And Let Lib</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Troubles are following everyone after the women’s lib movement ended. Elly and Granny return home to the mansion, while Jethro still believes he is Japanese and the women should serve him because women should wait on man. And at the bank, the secretaries are working on better working conditions, but get bullied by Banzai, who is trying to get new girls from Japan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316190000 +0000" stop="20250316193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Old Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous painter who has renounced civilization visits the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316193000 +0000" stop="20250316200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Quacking</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways are faced with the dilemma of running out of food.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316200000 +0000" stop="20250316203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Positive Thinking  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After listening to tapes on positive thinking, Eunice becomes a changed woman, even securing a part in a play. But when the director cuts all of her lines, she starts to feel her old nature creeping back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316203000 +0000" stop="20250316210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Alien Marriage  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint schemes to make money by pretending to be married to a girl from Portugal in need of a green card—until Mama catches wind of the plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316210000 +0000" stop="20250316220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Return Of The Ninny / Touchdown Twins / Split Personality</sub-title>
    <desc>"Charo returns as April Lopez. Television sportscaster Ty Younger and his new fiancée can't leave his children and their "ninny" April behind them when they set sail. A college football player develops a crush on his friend's mother. A college friend of Gopher's tries to be one thing for the boss and another for the boss' daughter, all the while not realizing they are father and daughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316220000 +0000" stop="20250316223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316223000 +0000" stop="20250316230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Props/costumes- Jennifer Klein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jennifer Klein grew up in LA with a dad who worked in Hollywood, and her screen used Props &amp; Costumes collection from TV shows like "CHIPs" and films like "Back To The Future" is stunning.  Expert and longtime costume dealer Marcia Tysseling appraises Jen's collection and has brought some classic TV costumes to offer in trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316230000 +0000" stop="20250316233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Quo Vadis, Captain Chandler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Intelligence officer Colonel Flagg and psychiatrist Sidney Freedman grapple over the fate of a wounded officer, Captain Chandler, who claims to be Jesus Christ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316233000 +0000" stop="20250317000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317000000 +0000" stop="20250317003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Has Jury Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is all excited that she has been chosen for jury duty. When Archie realizes that she may be sequestered, he forbids her to be on the jury, wanting to keep her at home to cook and clean for him. When she is sequestered, Archie fends for himself. However, Edith's stay may be longer than anticipated when she turns out to be the hold out vote in a murder trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317003000 +0000" stop="20250317010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie, Mike and Gloria are stunned when Edith becomes a rollercoaster of moods, going from joy to anger to tears in a snap of a finger. Gloria sits her down and suggests that perhaps she's beginning menopause. This worries Edith, who becomes convinced that Archie doesn't love her or find her attractive anymore. Meanwhile, the family tries to cope with Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317010000 +0000" stop="20250317013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Lionel Moves Into The Neighborhood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Jim Bowman sells his house, Archie discovers that a new family is moving to the neighborhood. Fearing that Jim sold to a Jewish family, he goes over to investigate, only to discover that the new family is black. Archie quickly hopes to round the neighborhood up and try to force the family out of the area. However, Archie is in for a shock when he discovers it is Lionel's family that has come to the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317013000 +0000" stop="20250317020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Is Worried About His Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie stays up all night, expecting a phone call from a security guard who has inside information. It seems his company is laying off and he fears he may lose his job. With Archie not sleeping, no one else in the Bunker household can sleep either and it soon turns into a three ring circus as a cop, a drunk, a pizza delivery man and Edith's friend Clara all stop by at 4 a.m.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317020000 +0000" stop="20250317023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Ken Barry</sub-title>
    <desc>In Babes in Barns, the gang parodies the classic film "Babes in Arms", with Carol playing Judy Garland and Ken playing Mickey Rooney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317023000 +0000" stop="20250317030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Fan, The / Rebecky</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Movie Fan, Carol is an woman obsessed with movie culture, to the detriment of her husband. Then, in Rebecky, the gang parodies the classic film
"Rebecca", with Carol as Joan Fontaine and Harvey as Lawrence Olivier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317030000 +0000" stop="20250317033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>That's My Boy???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura think they brought the wrong baby home from the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317033000 +0000" stop="20250317040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Brother, Can You Spare $2,500</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An "Alan Brady" script, meant to air that night, is held for ransom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317040000 +0000" stop="20250317043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317043000 +0000" stop="20250317050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Cavender Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An angel trying to earn his wings comes to the aide of a down-on-her-luck woman who has just been fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317050000 +0000" stop="20250317060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>A Tangled Web  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A French maid runs away with and marries a professional burglar with hopes of making him honest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317060000 +0000" stop="20250317070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Lover's Knot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF must uncover "K," head of European espionage working against the U.S., using Lady Cora Weston, an enemy agent and the wife of an elderly British lord.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317070000 +0000" stop="20250317080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>World's End</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble answers a classified ad from Ellie Burnett, the daughter of his former defense attorney. They arrange to meet in Kansas City to discuss the information she received about a one-armed man from a private detective hired by her father. Gerard sees the</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317080000 +0000" stop="20250317090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Reasons To Kill (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell unearths a deadly power struggle when he investigates the murder of an old friend--and finds himself the prime suspect in a second killing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317090000 +0000" stop="20250317093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317093000 +0000" stop="20250317100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317100000 +0000" stop="20250317103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harry Nobody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed's investigation of a fatal shooting in a hotel room hinges on the eyewitness account of a hopeless wino named Harry who is desperate to make a name for himself. Meanwhile, they investigate a report of a peeping tom at the home of an exotic dancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317103000 +0000" stop="20250317110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Malloy's birthday, but he's consumed with anger over the thought his colleagues might have a plan to throw him a surprise party. On a busy patrol, he and Reed make an ironic traffic stop while responding to a burglary call at an antique store, deal with an extremely embarrassed theft victim at a lingerie store, investigate suspicious activity at a service station, use a creative approach to apprehend a serial jewelry store burglar and engage in a shootout inside the police station's parking garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317110000 +0000" stop="20250317120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Luck O' The Irish</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate St. Patrick's Day!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317120000 +0000" stop="20250317123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Election</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie nominates Wally for class president but Wally has no interest in the position; that is until Ward gives him some encouragement. Wally quickly gets wrapped up in the election and his friends see a change in him—a change that prompts them to vote against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317123000 +0000" stop="20250317130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An old acquaintance of Ward's stops by and offers to paint the trim on the house. However, June and Ward are both apprehensive about the prospect of an alcoholic coming in contact with Wally and Beaver, despite the fact that he says he's cleaned himself up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317130000 +0000" stop="20250317140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lawful Lazarus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man declared legally dead suddenly re-appears and tries to get a hold of his dying wife's money in order to protect their children's interests, her entire family rallies against him until one of them turns up murdered. "Lazarus" is naturally charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317140000 +0000" stop="20250317150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317150000 +0000" stop="20250317160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Most Ancient</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An unhappy wife asks her lover to place a bomb in her abusive husband's truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317160000 +0000" stop="20250317170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Bicycle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy's meddling in a long-distance romance backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317170000 +0000" stop="20250317173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Robin Hood</sub-title>
    <desc>"Victims won't testify against John Henry Jordan at his trial for robbing the stage. He's found innocent. Matt asks Vince a card sharp he reformed to clean out Jordan. Jordan rides off. Matt's going to follow, but Chester says Vince has been hurt bad."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317173000 +0000" stop="20250317180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Yorky</sub-title>
    <desc>"Yorky, a white boy who was brought up by Arapahoes, is victimized by horse thieves. Seeking revenge, he gets shot by Abe Brandt and his son who said that Yorky was trying to steal "their" horses."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317180000 +0000" stop="20250317190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Hoss And The Leprechauns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss goes leprechaun hunting, hoping to find gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317190000 +0000" stop="20250317193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward Haskins guns down Joe Flecker, who has evidence that could be used to blackmail him. Haskins thinks the information was given to Lucas because he brought Flecker to the doctor before he died. Stirred up by Haskins behavior, Lucas goes through Flecker's things, finding a wanted poster for Haskins in the sole of Flecker's boot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317193000 +0000" stop="20250317200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheridan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Blandon, a man with only one good arm, wanders onto the ranch. Lucas gives Blandon a job to "hire him and Mark a clear conscience." General Sheridan and his patrol wander by and Lucas offers to let them stay the night at the ranch. Blandon once pulled a gun on General Sheridan; as it turns out, Blandon was a Confederate soldier who once had General Sheridan in his gun sight during the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317200000 +0000" stop="20250317210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Wanda Snow Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"Wanda Snow has several times seen events before they have happened, causing several people on the wagon train to accuse her of being a witch. A medicine show peddler/magician gets the idea to use her in his act, but this creates friction between him and his devious partner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317210000 +0000" stop="20250317220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Bottom Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Paramedics out in the field begin to question the judgment of overcautious Dr. Morton who believes in acting strictly by the book. The firemen respond to a complaint of severe back pain. A man with phosphorous burns on his arm and a boy hit in the head with a baseball are treated at the hospital. While the firemen respond to a case of difficult breathing, the victim’s neighbor drowns in a hot tub. Vince is involved in a traffic accident and goes crazy due to a head injury, pulling his gun on Johnny.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317220000 +0000" stop="20250317223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317223000 +0000" stop="20250317230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317230000 +0000" stop="20250317233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Ma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes home to his mother, as Hawkeye conducts the camp foot inspection, and Colonel Potter gets some shrapnel in his backside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250317233000 +0000" stop="20250318000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Der Tag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter decides Frank would be less of a pain if the others were friendlier to him; they oblige, with some startling results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318000000 +0000" stop="20250318003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318003000 +0000" stop="20250318010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318010000 +0000" stop="20250318013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Garden Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale is having a garden party and tells the Clampetts not to attend. However, they misunderstand and think she wants them to come. Jane and Drysdale try to stop them, but when they say how they still want to go, Jane arranges for them to have society clothes. When they arrive at the party, Mrs. Drysdale sends them back next door to handle the overflow crowd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318013000 +0000" stop="20250318020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Joins The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing Gomer's stories about how nice Sgt. Carter is, Opie Taylor runs away from Mayberry to join Gomer in the Marines. Ron Howard guest stars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318020000 +0000" stop="20250318023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Scientist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau pretends to be a famous French scientist who is visiting camp while Hogan smuggles the real one out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318023000 +0000" stop="20250318030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Trucking Service... We Deliver The Factory To You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Crittendon shows up again and messes up Hogan's plans to destroy a ball bearing plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318030000 +0000" stop="20250318033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Working At Marriage / Natural Velvet</sub-title>
    <desc>In Working at Marriage, Carol and Tim have their weekly gripe promptly at 8am. Then, in Natural Velvet, Carol and the gang parody "National Velvet", with Carol playing the horse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318033000 +0000" stop="20250318043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wayward Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Sutton is listed as the author of a best-selling book describing his experiences in a Korean POW camp. When the real author is released from an Army hospital, Sutton is slain before he can tell the truth and his widow is arrested for the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318043500 +0000" stop="20250318050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Bewitchin' Pool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Two unhappy children find a happy escape in a swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318050500 +0000" stop="20250318053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Day Of The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a friend is killed, a man reminisces about an incident in their past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318053500 +0000" stop="20250318060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hitch Hike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman has second thoughts about having picked up a hitchhiker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318060500 +0000" stop="20250318070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Make Like It Never Happened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to get an innocent man, and father of a young girl, off death row. Meanwhile, he romances the mistress of a wealthy industrialist he is investigating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318070500 +0000" stop="20250318080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Killing In The Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former prostitute aids Cannon in an investigation involving mobsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318080500 +0000" stop="20250318090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Venus As In Fly Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A male-chauvinist author murder's her feminist lover's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318090000 +0000" stop="20250318093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318093000 +0000" stop="20250318100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318100000 +0000" stop="20250318103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed suspect that a well-armed immigrant tailor who claims to be defending his establishment from burglars is actually plotting a murder. In the meantime, they deal with a drunken traveling businessman who passes out in a bar girl's car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318103000 +0000" stop="20250318110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate an interstate bounty hunter who has an invalid gun permit and questionable tactics. Meanwhile, they deal with an elderly man who strongly dislikes hippies, and a frustrated wife who desperately wants to receive a traffic ticket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318110000 +0000" stop="20250318120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Oh My It's 75!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Music, movies, and mayhem collide in this 1975 throwback as Bill and Toony experience everything from explosive sweets to gravity-defying adventures!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318120000 +0000" stop="20250318123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Dance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Beaver and Larry are forced into attending dancing school by their parents and after one lesson, they find that they absolutely detest it, like they knew they would. This prompts them to skip class next time and they hide out behind a barn until it's time to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318123000 +0000" stop="20250318130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry's Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry is furious when Beaver leaves him out when he joins a club called the Bloody Five. To get revenge, Larry makes up a story that he is starting his own club and that people are waiting in line to join. This prompts Beaver to resign from the Bloody Five and he tries to join Larry's bogus club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318130000 +0000" stop="20250318140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Velvet Claws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A photographer snaps a picture of politico Harrison Burke and a married woman, Eva Belter, as they leave a local gambling establishment. Eva goes to Mason for help and tells him that a scandal sheet called "Spicy Bits" is blackmailing her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318140000 +0000" stop="20250318150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Other Woman  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend psychiatrist Lucas Forbes when he's arrested for killing the husband of one of his patients with whom he was reportedly having an affair. Matlock soon realizes that the patient in question has a host of deep-rooted psychiatric problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318150000 +0000" stop="20250318160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>First Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Sparta P.D. gets its first black policewoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318160000 +0000" stop="20250318170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Townie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy refuses to take friendship with a neighbor's sheltered daughter to the next level</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318170000 +0000" stop="20250318173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Reunion 78</sub-title>
    <desc>"Belle Archer recognizes Jerry Shand and hides her face. Jerry has a grudge against Andy Cully, a paunchy hardware drummer. At the Long Branch Jerry is beating Andy up. Matt's ready to lock Jerry up. Andy bails him out. On the street Andy apologizes and offers Jerry $600. Jerry knows Andy is a murderer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318173000 +0000" stop="20250318180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>20-20</sub-title>
    <desc>"Troy Carver, an aging ex-lawman gets off the stage. Matt calls to him. Troy turns and almost shoots Matt. Matt tells Troy if someone is after you I'll help. Troy says mind your own business. Moss tells Matt Lee Polen has been hanging for several days. Lee says he's going to kill Troy for killing his brother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318180000 +0000" stop="20250318190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Fighters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss befriends a washed-up prizefighter who's having a hard time adjusting to life outside the squared circle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318190000 +0000" stop="20250318193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318193000 +0000" stop="20250318200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318200000 +0000" stop="20250318210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Miss Mary Lee Mcintosh Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop and Charlie ride into a small village for supplies finding it deserted. There is an Indian who stays hidden and later three men and a woman ride into town. They have been looking for the woman's father in a cave filled with bats."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318210000 +0000" stop="20250318220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Firehouse Quintet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Station 51 basketball team qualifies for the semi-finals. The paramedics rescue victims at a gas explosion. While at basketball practice, the firemen treat an injured gymnast. The night before the big game the firemen get very little sleep: they respond to a number of emergencies, including a workman trapped at a studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318220000 +0000" stop="20250318223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is injured in a jeep accident and, aware he has a concussion, babbles to a Korean family to keep himself awake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318223000 +0000" stop="20250318230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Some 38th Parallels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank tries to distinguish himself by selling the camp garbage, but it's Hawkeye who finds a use for it: he dumps it on a troublesome Colonel Coner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318230000 +0000" stop="20250318233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Novocaine Mutiny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has Hawkeye up on charges of mutiny for usurping his authority when Potter was away on leave and Frank was the commanding officer. B.J., Potter and Radar are in attendance of the preliminary hearing, at which they hear conflicting versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250318233000 +0000" stop="20250319000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Smilin' Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th turns up a sick helicopter pilot, 'Smilin' Jack, who doesn't want to quit, and a twice-wounded GI who does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319000000 +0000" stop="20250319003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319003000 +0000" stop="20250319010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319010000 +0000" stop="20250319013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Needs A Maw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed visits the bank to tell Drysdale that he plans to go back home to look for a wife so Elly May can finally have a mother. Drysdale tries to think of a bride for Jed, and when Mrs. Fenwick visits, he decides that she would be a perfect match for Jed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319013000 +0000" stop="20250319020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Date With Miss Camp Henderson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter bets Gomer he can't get a date with Ms. Camp Henderson, which of course he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319020000 +0000" stop="20250319023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>To The Gestapo With Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets three beautiful girls to pry secrets out of the guys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319023000 +0000" stop="20250319030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man's Best Friend Is Not His Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog buries a bone containing film from Carter's camera that has images of a new German tank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319030000 +0000" stop="20250319033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary who can't use a door buzzer correctly. Then, in Medical Documentary, a starry-eyed doctor uses his patient to get famous. Finally, in The Lift, Carol reunites with an old flame in a series of one-word exchanges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319033000 +0000" stop="20250319043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prudent Proecutor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>DA Hamilton Burger asks Mason to defend an old friend who once saved his life in a boating accident 10 years before. The old friend of Burger's is now facing a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319043500 +0000" stop="20250319050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Where Is Everybody?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds himself in a town strangely devoid of people. What's more, he can't recall his own identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319050500 +0000" stop="20250319053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Across The Threshold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An overly possessive mother takes charge of her bachelor son's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319053500 +0000" stop="20250319060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Craig's Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's desire to marry into a rich family gets her into more trouble than she can handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319060500 +0000" stop="20250319070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Cost Of A Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating the location of a missing person, Joe uncovers the death of a colleague who appears to have committed suicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319070500 +0000" stop="20250319080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flashpoint</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is on the case when a psychiatric patient is accused of rape and murder after falling in with some unsavory companions. CANNON attempts to clear a young man accused of rape-murder while the real villain's mother accuses her son of the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319080500 +0000" stop="20250319090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is on the case when a rich woman's affairs seem to be ending in terrible accidents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319090000 +0000" stop="20250319093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319093000 +0000" stop="20250319100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319100000 +0000" stop="20250319103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Spell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On an unseasonably hot day, Malloy and Reed suspect that an elusive bicyclist who overreacts to having his air pump stolen in a park is actually a drug pusher. Meanwhile, their investigation of a two-month-long yard sale leads to an armed fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319103000 +0000" stop="20250319110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gifts And Long Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by investigating a deluded and reclusive parolee whose troubled girlfriend in the apartment next door has just attempted suicide for the second time. In the meantime, they provide vital information to a detective's search for an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319110000 +0000" stop="20250319120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill And Toony Make A Sitcom</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Toony wants a sitcom of his own, Bill tries to recreate the classics of the '50s and '70s."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319120000 +0000" stop="20250319123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally lends his school sweater to Frances and quickly finds getting it back is going to be difficult because the girl keeps making up excuses. Things reach a boiling point when Ward and June overhear Frances bragging to her friends how Wally is chasing after her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319123000 +0000" stop="20250319130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Hypnotist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing someone being hypnotized in a movie, Beaver sets out to do the same. He tries hypnotism on Eddie—who pretends Beaver has hypnotized him—and Beaver gets scared when Eddie won't snap out of the trance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319130000 +0000" stop="20250319140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lover's Leap</sub-title>
    <desc>"The victim of a swindle finds his troubles multiplying when he's accused of murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319140000 +0000" stop="20250319150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thief: Part 1  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a rare coin dealer is charged with murdering a thieving employee, he hires Matlock to defend him. Tyler is less than thrilled when Matlock enlists the help of a female investigator, and has his own suspicions of her motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319150000 +0000" stop="20250319160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Crackdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone is selling crack to teenagers and Sweet tries desperately to save a young addict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319160000 +0000" stop="20250319170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly neighbor reinforces John-Boy's feelings that despite hard times he is lucky to be surrounded by a loving family</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319170000 +0000" stop="20250319173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Helping Hand</sub-title>
    <desc>"A would-be tough guy picks on the wrong man in an attempt to make a name for himself when he tries to involve Marshal Matt Dillon by staging a street fight."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319173000 +0000" stop="20250319180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tap Day For Kitty</sub-title>
    <desc>"An old sodbuster comes to town and decides he wants to marry Kitty. When he won't leave her alone she declares she'll shoot him if he pesters her anymore. Out at night, he's shot in the back and Kitty is suspected, but then she is shot at too."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319180000 +0000" stop="20250319190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Home From The Sea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilly Maples arrives at the Ponderosa claiming to be a friend of Adam's but in reality his intentions are to rob a shipment of gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319190000 +0000" stop="20250319193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319193000 +0000" stop="20250319200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319200000 +0000" stop="20250319210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Isaiah Quickfox Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon train comes across old Jamison Hershey and Herman, his 3000 pound Belgian horse. The old man has made it safely through hostile Indian territory because the tribes are so in awe of his horse. Hershey and Herman are invited to ride with the train, though it becomes apparent that Herman is not able to travel very fast and may hold back the entire group."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319210000 +0000" stop="20250319220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie, the station mechanic, stores the boat he wants to sell at the station house, where the firemen decide that they want to chip in and buy it. The paramedics rescue two boaters from Catalina Island. A bookie has a heart attack. An explosion in a lab starts a fire at the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319220000 +0000" stop="20250319223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The More I See You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is reunited with a woman he thought was out of his life forever, but who never altogether leaves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319223000 +0000" stop="20250319230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deluge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A sudden deluge of wounded at the 4077th is followed by a fire and a rainstorm, which makes matters difficult for the staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319230000 +0000" stop="20250319233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Interview</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Clete Roberts has arrived in Korea to interview the staff of the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital because of its high 97% efficiency rating. In Roberts' interviews with Hawkeye, B.J., Frank, Radar, Klinger, Mulcahy and Potter, they talk about how they cope with their situation, what they miss about home, how they feel about who they work with and whether they see any good in coming from war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250319233000 +0000" stop="20250320000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret, calling from Tokyo, holds the camp in suspense until she returns with the news of her engagement to Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. Frank Burns takes the news hard and arrests a Korean family as spies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320000000 +0000" stop="20250320003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320003000 +0000" stop="20250320010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320010000 +0000" stop="20250320013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Topless Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Happy Gizzard isn’t doing well, and Jethro wants to improve his business. He thinks he has an idea to make his restaurant a huge success. After seeing signs outside other restaurants, he believes his restaurant should have topless waitresses. But he thinks this means the waitresses don’t wear hats. Jethro tells Drysdale just as he is working on landing a $20 million dollar account, scaring the millionaire Vanderponts away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320013000 +0000" stop="20250320020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Father Figure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer saves a man from jumping off a bridge, and soon befriends him. Before long it's discovered that the man makes a habit out of this, taking advantage of people's kindness along the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320020000 +0000" stop="20250320023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Never Play Cards With Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plan to blow up a rocket fuel factory boomerangs back at him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320023000 +0000" stop="20250320030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Color The Luftwaffe Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer to paint the headquarters of the Luftwaffe in order to steal an important map.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320030000 +0000" stop="20250320033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Whiplash / Family, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Whiplash, Harvey fakes an injury to scam an unsuspecting Carol. Then, in The Family, Eunice and Mama are mad after they attend the anniversary of her husband's co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320033000 +0000" stop="20250320043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gallant Grafter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporate intrigue is the backdrop of this episode when embezzling accountant Robert Doniger is murdered and Edward Nelson is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320043500 +0000" stop="20250320050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A street salesman cleverly eludes Death. But if he lives, a little girl must die in his place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320050500 +0000" stop="20250320053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Madame Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man creates a successful publicity campaign to advertise his new movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320053500 +0000" stop="20250320060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Little Man Who Was There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A little man comes into a mining town with surprising results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320060500 +0000" stop="20250320070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Days Beyond Recall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix receives a visit from Jane Haley after her alcoholic brother disappears without a trace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320070500 +0000" stop="20250320080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Couldn't Forget</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is in a full blown jam when he gets mistaken for the assassin of a bishop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320080500 +0000" stop="20250320090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Platinum Connection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After a jeweler swindles his insurance company, he comes to suspect that his secretary is on to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320090000 +0000" stop="20250320093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320093000 +0000" stop="20250320100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320100000 +0000" stop="20250320103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed starts a flu epidemic that decimates the city's police force, forcing him and Malloy to work a double shift. During day watch, he and Malloy encounter a bookmaker being held at gunpoint, mediate a dispute over a cantaloupe, investigate a possible robbery in progress, engage in a foot chase with an athletic young man and pull over a motorist who turns out to be a VIP.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320103000 +0000" stop="20250320110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly appointed Police Commissioner Edna Dixon accompanies Malloy and Reed on night watch, where they deal with a naked elderly wino at a bar, try to diffuse a possible riot situation following a gang-related stabbing and pursue a deaf teenager in a stolen car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320110000 +0000" stop="20250320120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Gem State</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320120000 +0000" stop="20250320123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Alma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After drawing Alma's name for a school picnic, Wally finds himself meeting her parents and her mother takes an immediate liking to Wally, setting him and Alma up on numerous dates, but then turns around and accuses Wally of monopolizing Alma's time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320123000 +0000" stop="20250320130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver asks his parents if he could ride his new bike to school instead of the bus, and after some hesitating they finally agree to it. However, on the first day, a naive Beaver gets his bike stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320130000 +0000" stop="20250320140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Elusive Element</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A promoter's plan to frame his wife and business partner for embezzlement fails, but they're arrested anyway for his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320140000 +0000" stop="20250320150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Thief, The (part 2)  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock and Tyler realise that part of Linda's deception is routed in the recent kidnapping of her son. While Tyler helps her locate the child, Matlock finds the rare coin he needs to put the finish on the case."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320150000 +0000" stop="20250320160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Time Of The Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a private investigator searching for a missing child is found dead, the evidence points to a local dance teacher - a neighbor that Parker has become very fond of.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320160000 +0000" stop="20250320170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy seeks some solitude to write his stories, but finds a life-altering situation</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320170000 +0000" stop="20250320173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Indian Scout</sub-title>
    <desc>"Twenty-three soldiers died at the hands of the Comanches at Cold Creek. Will Bailey lost his brother. Will says Amos Cartwright, the scout led them into an ambush. Matt tells Bailey let the cavalry handle it, and leave Amos alone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320173000 +0000" stop="20250320180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Pest Hold</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc is using the jail to quarantine people as they fall ill. The common thread between them seems to be that they all had a dinner meeting together, about the upcoming German festival, at Bendino's restaurant."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320180000 +0000" stop="20250320190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Mission</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and an Army colonel undertake a peace mission to the Paiute tribe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320190000 +0000" stop="20250320193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart arrives in North Fork in search of renegade indians suspected of the brutal killing of a Texas Ranger and his family. The townspeople are suspicious of him, however, when they discover that he, too, is an indian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320193000 +0000" stop="20250320200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarding House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Reformed card shark Julia Massini now runs a respectable boarding house in North Fork, but Sid Fallon is threatening to reveal her sordid past unless she lets him turn the establishment into a saloon and gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320200000 +0000" stop="20250320210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Herman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>"Don Brooke is desperate for money for his pregnant wife Bonnie, who's condition is too delicate for the long trip without more medical care so he seeks a bank loan. When he sees an opportunity at the bank, it leads to tragedy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320210000 +0000" stop="20250320220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Isolation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John are trapped at Station 86 when a rain storm washes out the bridge, and they become the only medical treatment in the area. They assist two victims of an auto accident and a child with bronchitis. Doctors at the hospital treat a policeman hit by lightning. Copter 15 transports the victims to the hospital, where a power failure complicates matters. Dr. Morton accompanies the paramedics back to Station 86, where they respond to an auto accident with multiple injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320220000 +0000" stop="20250320223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A rumor that there's going to be a practice bug-out causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in to bug out, and the rumor suddenly comes to life! Meanwhile, Hawkeye begins surgery on a patient with a spinal injury. The bug-out proceeds without him, Hot Lips and Radar, and they quickly learn after the unit departs that they're in the midst of the front. When Potter, Mulcahy, BJ, Frank and the others arrive at the buildings which had been scouted by helicopter, they find the house full of "business girls," and Potter gives them Klinger's dresses to persuade them to leave the house. A helicopter comes to evacuate the spinal injury patient, and just as the three get ready to go to the new location, they find the 4077 is already returning, and eventually everyone reunites back at the camp, what with the Chinese being repulsed.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320223000 +0000" stop="20250320230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rumor that there's going to be a camp relocation causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in that the rumor is indeed fact!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320230000 +0000" stop="20250320233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Sight, Out Of Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While fixing a stove that explodes, Hawkeye's face is badly burned. His eyes are bandaged, and it is not known if he will ever see again. Meanwhile Frank bets on the outcome of a baseball game, which he has already heard on the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250320233000 +0000" stop="20250321000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lt. Radar O'reilly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Following an offer of promotion made by Master Sergeant Woodruff at a poker game, Radar is promoted to the rank of lieutenant. Finding this position awkward, Radar opts to return to his position as an enlisted man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321000000 +0000" stop="20250321003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321003000 +0000" stop="20250321010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321010000 +0000" stop="20250321013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Man For Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is glued to the television set the Clampetts received for Christmas, especially because of one TV Western star, Quirt Manly. She really wants to meet him, and Drysdale arranges for it to happen. And Granny already has him set up for Elly May, because she knows he is probably the only who can tame the vine-swinging girl. However, when he arrives at the mansion, the Clampetts see he isn’t who they thought he was. Quirt Manly is actually a short actor with a high-pitched voice who doesn’t do any of his own stunts or riding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321013000 +0000" stop="20250321020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Desk Job For A Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter takes a new job as a training coordinator. But when he finds out the platoon is doing fine under Cpl. Boyle's command, he decides he wants his old job back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321020000 +0000" stop="20250321023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who Came To Dinner?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan learns his underground contact may be a double agent after he arranges for her to go to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321023000 +0000" stop="20250321030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>No Names Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after Hogan helps a journalist escape from the Germans, an American paper tells of Hogan's operations at his camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321030000 +0000" stop="20250321033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mildred Fierce</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mildred Fierce, Carol and the gang parody the classic "Mildred Pierce", with Carol playing Joan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321033000 +0000" stop="20250321043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wary Wildcatter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Houston cleverly gets away with killing his wife by making it look like she died in a car accident. Then a wildlife photographer shows up with the murder on film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321043500 +0000" stop="20250321050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Denton On Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A has-been, drunk gunslinger finds his fast-draw abilities magically restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321050500 +0000" stop="20250321053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mother, May I Go To Swim?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man tries desperately to free himself from the women who would control his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321053500 +0000" stop="20250321060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cuckoo Clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped mental patient terrorizes a woman left alone in a remote cottage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321060500 +0000" stop="20250321070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Beyond The Shadow Of A Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A mentally unstable woman is having trouble grasping the difference between nightmare and reality. Mannix is hired to figure which of her companions is creating her confusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321070500 +0000" stop="20250321080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Sounds Of Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon stirs up a hornet's nest worth of trouble after re-opening the case of an old shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321080500 +0000" stop="20250321090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Programmed For Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A genius and his partner use a computer to commit murder and larceny.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321090000 +0000" stop="20250321093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321093000 +0000" stop="20250321100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321100000 +0000" stop="20250321103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>O'brien's Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's headstrong and elderly apartment manager stages a protest at the station after she's victimized by a serial purse snatcher, and Malloy suggests a stakeout will be their only chance to apprehend the suspect. On patrol, he and Reed chase a suspicious vehicle into a lumber yard, and investigate the murder of a young man at his parents' home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321103000 +0000" stop="20250321110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest - 484</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspected child stealer who has escaped custody with the baby after being arrested for shoplifting baby formula. Meanwhile, Reed has to think quickly when he is held at gunpoint while responding to a burglary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321110000 +0000" stop="20250321120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day...march 21st</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony look back on historic events that took place on March 21st!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321120000 +0000" stop="20250321123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Orchid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks out a rich girl who drops hints that she would like an orchid for her corsage. Wally quickly discovers that getting one is going to be more difficult then he originally thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321123000 +0000" stop="20250321130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward's cherished autographed baseball becomes the object that Larry and Beaver just can't keep their hands off of. They decide to play catch with it and it ends up getting run over by a truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321130000 +0000" stop="20250321140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Greek Goddess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is hired by a sculptor charged with murdering the overbearing mother of his model.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321140000 +0000" stop="20250321150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Capital Offense  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock continues his five-year struggle to save a con artist from the electric chair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321150000 +0000" stop="20250321160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An outlaw family seeks revenge against Bubba after he is forced to shoot one of them during a holdup. The chief wants him to stay out of sight until they are arrested - a suggestion that does not set well with Bubba.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321160000 +0000" stop="20250321170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A misunderstanding and plain stubborn pride causes a rift between the Walton grandparents</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321170000 +0000" stop="20250321173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Big Broad</sub-title>
    <desc>"Big Lena Wave and her man, diminutive Emmett Fitzgood ride into Dodge to run a card game at the Long Branch. Chester accuses Emmett of cheating. Lena socks him. Lena uses a bottle on a guy. Matt's trying to figure out how to handle her. Lena kills Ed James, a buffalo hunter who made advances toward her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321173000 +0000" stop="20250321180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hack Prine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hack Prine, a friend of Matt's rides into Dodge. However he is there as a gunman, to kill Matt Dillon."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321180000 +0000" stop="20250321190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Dollar's Worth Of Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune teller predicts that two people will soon enter and change Hoss's life: a hot blonde chick and a dangerous gunman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321190000 +0000" stop="20250321193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas puts his life in jeopardy when he agrees to testify in a murder case involving a witness killed before he could testify and a killer still at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321193000 +0000" stop="20250321200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw Sam Morley falls in love with a young woman who has a serious illness. He asks Lucas to turn him in for the reward and then use the money to pay for her medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321200000 +0000" stop="20250321210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bonnie Brooke Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>"Teacher Mary Lee McIntosh refuses to pay what she feels is an excessive fee to join the wagon train, so she decides instead to follow behind it in her wagon alone, and refuses help from Hale. But after her wagon overturns, things change."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321210000 +0000" stop="20250321220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Upward And Onward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley worries that the chief will sabotage his attempt to pass the chief's exam. A soap opera doctor with mono causes havoc on set and in the hospital. John, Roy and a retired doctor with a self-diagnosed heart aneurysm get stuck in an elevator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321220000 +0000" stop="20250321223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Nurses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hot Lips confines Nurse Baker to her quarters, little does she know that Baker's husband has arrived in the camp. Hawkeye and B.J. put them together in Hot Lips' tent, telling everyone that a quarantined patient has been placed there. When Hot Lips discovers what has happened, she breaks down and refuses to press charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321223000 +0000" stop="20250321230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Abduction Of Margaret Houlihan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing that North Korean prisoners have been released in the area, everyone is upset when Margaret disappears. Colonel Flagg is called in to investigate, and bungles things in his usual manner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321230000 +0000" stop="20250321233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sigmund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman, feeling depressed, visits the 4077th to observe how they fare under the pressures of war. He begins a letter to Sigmund Freud as a form of self-therapy, and releases his tension in the form of a practical joke with B.J., aimed at Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250321233000 +0000" stop="20250322000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mulcahy's War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Frank discovers that Danny Fitzsimmons has shot himself to get out of combat, Father Mulcahy is called in. Realizing his lack of understanding of the fighting, Mulcahy accompanies Radar to an aid station, where they encounter the real war at first hand. Mulcahy performs an emergency tracheotomy, guided by Hawkeye over the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322000000 +0000" stop="20250322003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322003000 +0000" stop="20250322010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taylors quickly realize why they haven't invited Bee's sister and her husband, Ollie, for a visit in more than a decade. When Uncle Ollie borrows Andy's squad car to go fishing, it's the final straw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322010000 +0000" stop="20250322013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Giant Jackrabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>At the mansion, the clan is in need of food because the hunting in Beverly Hills is horrible. They call a catering company, but get mean-mouthed. At the bank, Drysdale gets a call and learns that he got a kangaroo from a friend and it is at his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322013000 +0000" stop="20250322020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, The Would-be Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sgt. Carter stops a robber in a diner, he makes Gomer the hero so he won't get caught with another woman by Bunny. It's not long before Carter wants the credit he is due, but by then no one will believe that he was the hero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322020000 +0000" stop="20250322023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Day In Berlin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. undercover agent helps Hogan and his men get a defecting Nazi officer out of Berlin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322023000 +0000" stop="20250322030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Blue Baron Strike Again?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to throw a party for WW I flying ace Blue Baron in order to find his headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322030000 +0000" stop="20250322033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mother Of The Bride / Stradivarius / Perfect Crime, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mother of the Bride, Carol gives daughter Vicki last minute marriage advice. Then, in Stradivarius, Harvey desperately seeks a repairman for his violin. Finally, in The Perfect Crime, Carol is married to a billionaire who is the most boring man alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322033000 +0000" stop="20250322043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mythical Monkeys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Author Mauvis Meade sends her secretary, Gladys Doyle, out to a mountain cabin to pick up a package. Gladys gets lost and her car gets stuck in the mud. She then walks to a cabin looking for help and encounters a mysterious man who appears to know her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322043500 +0000" stop="20250322050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteen-millimeter Shrine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging former movie star lives and dreams in the past, constantly watching her old movies alone in isolation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322050500 +0000" stop="20250322053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Detectives Later</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's search for his wife's murderer leads to a small hotel room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322053500 +0000" stop="20250322060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Two men meet aboard a ship at sea, and one of them is sure he knows the other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322060500 +0000" stop="20250322070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Huntdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is stuck in a farm town with an injured foot, and a group of citizens who seem to be keeping a deadly secret from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322070500 +0000" stop="20250322080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322080500 +0000" stop="20250322090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gold Record For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to preserve his reputation for genius, a rock star kills the ghost writer who always complained for never getting credit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250322090000 +0000" stop="20250322093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Honeymoon Hotel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe decides to turn the Shady Rest into a honeymoon haven, after being made a Justice of the Peace.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
