<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621093000 +0000" stop="20250621100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo's Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo has made a new friend, a dog which keeps following her around. Although she wants to keep him, Kate insists he must go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621100000 +0000" stop="20250621103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Teenage Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Rock 'n' roll idol Johnny Poke visits the Clampetts while in town to play the Hollywood Bowl. Granny's not too happy about it; she's worried Jethro will pick up his bad habits. Granny loses her temper and thinks she turned Jethro into a puppy when she says he needs to be taught a lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621103000 +0000" stop="20250621110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale And Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts and Miss Jane return from spending Christmas in Hooterville to learn that Drysdale has driven after them, along with Fairchild, Elly’s bear. Back in the hills, Drysdale gets arrested for vagrancy and bootlegging in a place called Ripley. When they learn, the people at the bank couldn’t be happier that their boss has been locked up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621110000 +0000" stop="20250621113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Klondike Casanova, Doing Impossikible Stunts, Little Swee’pea</sub-title>
    <desc>"Fur farmer Bluto kidnaps Olive Oyl., Popeye tries to get a job as a movie stunt man by showing studio executives movies of some of his most daring exploits., Popeye tackles lions, bears, snakes and countless other animals chasing after Swee'pea at the zoo only to find himself the victim of an assault by Olive for scaring Swee'pea with a toy on their arrival home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621113000 +0000" stop="20250621120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Little School Mouse, Dumb-hounded, Little Quacker</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry teaches Nibbles how to outwit a cat., A wolf convict escapes prison but wherever he runs the slow moving Droopy is always there to take him back to jail., Jerry saves a baby duck from Tom as the cat prepares to eat it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621120000 +0000" stop="20250621130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Helter Shelter, Chilly's Cold War, Sh-h-h-h-h-h, Astronut Woody, A Fish Story, Flea For Two, Airlift A La Carte, The Snoozin' Bruin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody and a dog named Happy compete for the affections of an animal-friendly old lady in order to stay in her house during a rain storm., Chilly Willy is cold and hungry and takes shelter in the home of Colonel Pot Shot where Smedley is the caretaker., A jazz musician desperately tries to quiet his nosey neighbors before his volatile condition causes him to blow up., Woody mistakes a rocket headed for the moon for a luxury treehouse., A doctor tells Charlie a pet fish will make him less nervous. After struggling to get the fish tank home, Charlie is forced by Bessie to return it., A country flee must rescue his bride from the playboy flea who kidnapped her., Chilly Willy and friends try to get food from the general store before it closes for the winter., A bear decides to sleep in Woody's tree, and his snoring is so loud that Woody tries everything to wake him up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621130000 +0000" stop="20250621140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Upswept Hare, Daffy Duck And The Dinosaur, Cat Feud, Hare-trimmed, Hook, Line And Stinker, A Pizza Tweety Pie, Bugs Bunny Gets The Boid</sub-title>
    <desc>"Elmer Fudd brings home a rare plant specimen, uprooting all the dirt around it – including the soil containing Bugs Bunny's hole. , The episode takes us far back billions of years to the dinosaur age with Caspar Caveman and his pet dinosaur, Fido. Caspar spots Daffy in a lake and hunts him, but Daffy just keeps outsmarting him. , Marc Anthony, the ferocious guard dog, falls for a cute cuddly little kitty. An evil cat tries to swipe the kitty and it’s up to Marc Anthony to protect the kitty. , Yosemite Sam hears that Granny has inherited fifty million dollars. Good guy Bugs tries to save Granny from Sam's clutches. , Wile E. Coyote faces off against Road Runner again. , Granny takes Tweety to Italy, where he ends up having to save himself from Sylvester. , Beakey Buzzard's mother sends him out on a mission to bring back a rabbit for their nest. He's in for trouble when he chooses Bugs as his target. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621140000 +0000" stop="20250621150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Underground Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>During Mardi Gras, West is grabbed by a Major Hazard, the leader of a gang of crippled Civil War soldiers seeking revenge on the camp's commandant, Mosely. Jim reluctantly agrees to help them, only to have Mosely taken from him by the soldiers. He tracks them to the abandoned camp where Hazard plans on putting Mosely on trial, but it becomes clear that Hazard has another agenda as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621150000 +0000" stop="20250621160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jose Maria Moran Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>The Major and party find a Pawnee Indian strung up and left to die. Back at the wagon train they find he is not who he appears to be. The mystery deepens as the Shoshonees, who hung him there, are still after him and getting closer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621160000 +0000" stop="20250621170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Velvet Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick falls for a woman, not knowing that she is a gunslinger’s lover. She sees this as a perfect opportunity to rid herself of a problem: A pursuer bent on revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621170000 +0000" stop="20250621173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Where'd They Go</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Jonas accuses Clint Dodie of robbing his store, Matt and Chester set out in the bitter cold go to Clint's farm to make an arrest. Once they arrive at Clint's farm, instead of making an arrest, Matt and Chester wind up doing most of Clint's farm chores."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621173000 +0000" stop="20250621180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Crowbait Bob</sub-title>
    <desc>"When the greedy relatives of a dying man (Crowbait Bob)learn that he might be dying, they come to Dodge to grab anything of value they can get from the dying man. When his relatives find out that Bob has willed all of his possessions to Miss Kitty, they show their true hateful feelings about their relative, Crowbait Bob."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621180000 +0000" stop="20250621190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Queen High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Candy haven't a clue of what to do with a stamping mill they won in a poker game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621190000 +0000" stop="20250621193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621193000 +0000" stop="20250621200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward Haskins guns down Joe Flecker, who has evidence that could be used to blackmail him. Haskins thinks the information was given to Lucas because he brought Flecker to the doctor before he died. Stirred up by Haskins behavior, Lucas goes through Flecker's things, finding a wanted poster for Haskins in the sole of Flecker's boot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621200000 +0000" stop="20250621210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of El Toro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Art Fuller is sent to kill a wild bull.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621210000 +0000" stop="20250621213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Campaign Of Billy Banjo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Paladin's, Billy Banjo, sends for him to help with an election.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621213000 +0000" stop="20250621220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Healing Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh embarks on a mission of mercy when he pleads with the parents of a boy with appendicitis to let the doctor operate. The father, embittered against modern medicine, trusts only the local witch to cure his son's sickness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250621220000 +0000" stop="20250622000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Slippery Silks, An Ache In Every Stake, Crash Goes The Hash, Micro-phonies, Bedlam In Paradise, All The World's A Stooge</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are carpenters who inherit a fancy dress boutique.   , The Stooges are icemen who, while delivering ice to a house on the top of a high hill, destroy several cakes that a wealthy man is trying to bring home.  When their antics cause the servants at their customer's house to quit, the boys are hired to take their place and prepare a dinner party.  What they don't know is that the party is for the man whose cakes they wrecked.  When Moe's gas filled cake explodes and the man realizes whom they are, they must leave in a hurry. , The Stooges are window washers who lose their jobs after Moe impersonates the dentist in whose office they were cleaning.  On the run, they are hired by a millionaire to pose as children.  It seems the man's wife wants to adopt some refugees to impress her society friends.  Moe is Johnny, Curly is Frankie and Larry is Mabel.  Everything goes fairly well as the lady shows off the Stooges to her friends, but they finally irritate her husband so much that he goes after them with an ax. , The Stooges are hired as reporters and their first assignment is to get a picture of a visiting prince who is planning to marry a local socialite.  The boys disguise as servants and infiltrate a party being in thrown in the honor of the prince.  The Stooges ruin the party, but save the day as they expose the prince as crook who is planning to rob the house.  Their boss is so grateful for the expose that he gives the boys a bonus and the rich lady decides to marry Curly! , The Stooges are working in a radio station where a pretty girl has just made a recording of "Voices of Spring" under an assumed name.  She wants to hide her singing career from her disapproving society parents while auditioning for Mrs. Bixby's "Krispy Krunchy" radio program.  After a run-in with a pompous violinist, the boys find the record and Curly starts mimicking to it, dressed as a women.  Mrs. Bixby witnesses their performance and is impressed enough to hire "Senorita Cucaracha" (Curly) and Senors "Mucho" and "Gusto" (Moe and Larry) for her radio program.  The boys show up in their disguises to "sing" at a Mrs. Bixby's party but run into trouble when Moe smashes the record over Curly's head.  The real singer tries to help by singing from behind a curtain while Curly mimics, but she is discovered and the Stooges exit to a hail of phonograph records. , Shemp dies but cannot get into heaven until he reforms Moe and Larry.  He returns to earth as an invisible spirit and sets out to prevent the other two Stooges, who are in league with the devil, from selling a phony invention (a fountain pen that writes under whip cream) to a rich couple.  Shemp sabotages Moe and Larry' plans and makes it through the pearly gates. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622000000 +0000" stop="20250622023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Village Of The Damned</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the English village of Midwich, the blonde-haired, glowing-eyed children of uncertain paternity prove to have frightening powers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622023000 +0000" stop="20250622050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <desc>"As the world is overrun by zombies, a group of scientists and military personnel sheltering in an underground bunker in Florida must determine how they should deal with the undead horde."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622050000 +0000" stop="20250622060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Derelict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jupiter 2 is pulled into a giant alien spaceship where there are advanced bubble-like creatures. John and Don look for maps and equipment while Dr. Smith and Will look for trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622060000 +0000" stop="20250622070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Killers Of The Deep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aboard a U.S. destroyer, Nelson wages a harrowing battle with an enemy sub bent on stealing undersea defense missiles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622070000 +0000" stop="20250622080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Genius At Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant boy genius develops a pill that can transform Earthlings into giants. Fitzhugh becomes the first test subject and is eager to take advantage of his newfound status.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622080000 +0000" stop="20250622090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Crack Of Doom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Landing on Krakatoa in 1883, the time travelers try to convince a British scientist that the volcano is about to explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622090000 +0000" stop="20250622100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Condition: Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious recovery leads Vincent to a possible invader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622100000 +0000" stop="20250622110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Italian Caper</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt are tasked to recover stolen and secret Anti-Gravity Device."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622110000 +0000" stop="20250622113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Jessie's Song   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie is under pressure with midterms and her own singing group so she turns to caffeine pills, ignoring Slater's warning that the pills are hazardous to her health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622113000 +0000" stop="20250622120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Fabulous Belding Boys   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>If the gang fails a test in an obnoxious teacher's class, they won't be able to go on a class field trip. On the day of the test, however, the teacher doesn't show, so Belding's brother, Rod, takes over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622120000 +0000" stop="20250622123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Glee Club   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang joins the Glee Club, but soon the friends lose their pep. Jesse catches Lisa's cold, Screech makes a fool of himself in front of his girlfriend's parents and the gang's singing is totally off key.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622123000 +0000" stop="20250622130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Up Is Hard To Undo   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>First, it's splitsville for Zack and Kelly when Kelly goes on a date with her ex-boyfriend. Slater and Jessie are finally a couple, but things get messed up when they disagree on how to celebrate their coupledom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622130000 +0000" stop="20250622133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Video Yearbook   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and the gang decide to make a video yearbook for Bayside, but when Zack uses the opportunity to create the "Girls of Bayside Dating Service," his friends get him back big time!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622133000 +0000" stop="20250622140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Snow White And The Seven Dorks   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang puts together a hip-hop version of 'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs,' and Zack and Jessie get caught in a serious situation when Lisa catches them rehearsing the final scene—the KISS!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622140000 +0000" stop="20250622143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>My Sister, Benedict Arnold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg comes home furious when he is replaced on the basketball team by Warren Mulaney. When he discovers Marcia is dating Warren, he hits the roof and demands that Marcia stop seeing him. When she refuses, Greg tries to get revenge and begins dating the woman who beat Marcia out in cheerleading. Meanwhile, the Bradys prepare a dunking booth for a carnival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622143000 +0000" stop="20250622150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Top Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When an FBI agent makes a visit to check Mike's security clearance, Bobby and Oliver both become convinced that Mike is working on some plans for a top secret project. They later become suspicious of Sam and become convinced that he plans to steal the "secret plans" and pass them on to the Russians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622150000 +0000" stop="20250622153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The Not Making Of The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie goes against Howard and, to get a girl, campaigns for Adlai Stevenson in the 1956 Presidential race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622153000 +0000" stop="20250622160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Note</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne gets upset when she finds a short note from Shirley stating that she and her new husband are moving overseas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622160000 +0000" stop="20250622163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622163000 +0000" stop="20250622170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy's Schedule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky puts Lucy on a rigid time schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622170000 +0000" stop="20250622173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Music Lesson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally makes the baseball team and Ward openly shows how proud he is of him, leaving Beaver feeling inferior. Trying to impress his parents, Beaver tries out for the band and begins practicing the clarinet. However, Beaver soon finds himself with more problems when he's let go from the band.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622173000 +0000" stop="20250622180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>June has Wally stay home from school when he comes down with a sore throat and suddenly Wally is immersed in attention from his parents, friends and doctor. Jealous and feeling left out, Beaver fakes illness, seeking that same attention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622180000 +0000" stop="20250622183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Problem Bear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale has come down with the flu after spending so many nights outside while on the way to Hooterville. Granny wants to help him with her Possum Ridge Penicillin, also known as White Lightening. She leaves Drysdale a jug of it, but he puts it to the side and takes a sleeping pill. However, Elly’s bear Fairchild has taken up drinking Granny’s moonshine and climbs into his room as Drysdale is sleeping and drinks the entire jug.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622183000 +0000" stop="20250622190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny decides to start her own boarding house. The Clampetts put out signs welcoming any incoming boarders and advertising what they offer. When the Drysdale's new butler, Arthur Pinckney, arrives in town he thinks the signs are meant as a welcome for him so he goes to the Clampetts' mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622190000 +0000" stop="20250622193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>It's Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways discover a magician's trunk on the island, using its contents to scare away unfriendly natives from nearby islands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622193000 +0000" stop="20250622200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Old Paint</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous painter who has renounced civilization visits the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622200000 +0000" stop="20250622203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>My Mama, Myself  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama wrestles with the ghost of Grandma Crowley when she finds her mother's broach and realizes it could be worth serious money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622203000 +0000" stop="20250622210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Full House  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama sits in on Vint's poker game when one of his friends cancels, sharing embarrassing stories about Vint's childhood and revealing what he does when bluffing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622210000 +0000" stop="20250622220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Expedition / Julie's Wedding / Mongala / Julie's Replacement / Three Rs / Professor's Wife (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Julie prepares to marry her fiancé Tony Selkirk during a stopover in Sydney, Australia. Meanwhile, New Zealand rancher Ralph Sutton has a secret that he won't share with English teacher and fellow passenger Barbara Carroll, while young beauty Connie Wilker has eyes for him. Gopher and Doc both compete for the affections of new cruise director Yvonne Petty."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622220000 +0000" stop="20250622223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622223000 +0000" stop="20250622230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>David Meinz- Vintage Fitness Fads</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dietician and nutritionist David Meinz has collected a museum's worth of samples, advertising, and more showcasing America's decades-long love affair with quack cures and weird weight-loss schemes. Americana expert Henry Tankersley weighs in on the market value of David's wildest finds, from weight-loss cigarettes to a vitamin mixture made with alcohol, for the whole family!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622230000 +0000" stop="20250622233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250622233000 +0000" stop="20250623000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623000000 +0000" stop="20250623003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>We're Still Having A Heat Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The new neighbors, Irene and Frank Lorenzo, settle into the house next door. Soon Archie is annoyed with both of them, as Irene makes friends with Edith and Archie soon grows jealous of all the time that Edith is spending with her. Meanwhile, Archie also becomes annoyed with Frank, whose constant singing filters into the Bunkers home prompting Archie to buy an air horn to combat the noise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623003000 +0000" stop="20250623010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Finds An Old Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While shopping at the supermarket, Edith befriends a lonely old man, Mr. Quigley, who ran away from the nursing home. Edith swiftly brings him home with her and Archie is less than thrilled to have a constant reminder of his own advancing years hanging around the house. Meanwhile, Mr. Quigley has another problem when he can't get a hold of his uncaring daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623010000 +0000" stop="20250623013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Kiss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>While spending time at the Lorenzo's home, Gloria admires a statue replica of Rodin's 'The Kiss." Seeing the admiration in Gloria's eyes, Irene gives her the statue. However, when she brings it home, Archie is infuriated by it, citing that it's pornography. There is also another problem that arises when Frank wants the statue back and that Irene had no right to give it away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623013000 +0000" stop="20250623020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie The Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home in a great mood, bearing gifts of perfume for Gloria and bubble bath for Edith. However, Edith becomes deeply distrubed to find out Archie won money while playing the horses. It seems that he had promised never to gamble again, twenty years prior, when his addiction got so bad that Edith threatened to leave him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623020000 +0000" stop="20250623023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/14/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623023000 +0000" stop="20250623030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Shirley Jones And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Shirley Jones and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 02/17/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623030000 +0000" stop="20250623033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Odd But True</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The freckles on Rob's back appear to form the Liberty Bell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623033000 +0000" stop="20250623040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Viva Petrie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Petries' former maid asks them to find a job for her matador boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623040000 +0000" stop="20250623043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Please Leave The Premises</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and the Nortons fight a rent increase, though Ralph is the only one who really wants to fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623043000 +0000" stop="20250623053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>He's Alive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Yearning for more power, a small-time neo-Nazi leader takes advice from a shadowy benefactor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623053000 +0000" stop="20250623060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Jonathan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A widower remarries but his son does not take this too kindly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623060000 +0000" stop="20250623070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Hunted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>An extraction mission in South Africa goes suddenly awry when an interrogator arrives unexpectedly. A well disguised member of the IMF is wounded but then aided by an angel of mercy with a secret past and a reward-seeking friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623070000 +0000" stop="20250623080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Brass Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In Santa Monica, California, Kimble is hired by Norma Sessions to help care for her invalid brother Leslie, who was crippled in a car accident. Kimble doesn't realize that Norma, with her boyfriend Lars, are plotting to murder Leslie to collect his insura</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623080000 +0000" stop="20250623090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Lester Two</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kidnapping, smuggling and a double-cross force Harry Orwell to team up with an eccentric young criminologist in an 8000-mile search for stolen diamonds."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623090000 +0000" stop="20250623093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - The Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Other people's credit cards are found in the possession of a forest ranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623093000 +0000" stop="20250623100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday arrests a member of his class for possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623100000 +0000" stop="20250623103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623103000 +0000" stop="20250623110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623110000 +0000" stop="20250623120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Makes A Film Noir</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill stars as a private eye in "The Malty Fountain." Is Toony the "fish fatale," or just a red herring?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623120000 +0000" stop="20250623123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Old Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver are helping Ward clean out the garage when they run across Beaver's old teddy bear, Billy. Beaver reluctantly throws him away after Ward and Wally tell him he's too old for dolls. However, Beaver changes his mind but he's too late: the garbage truck came, which leads Beaver to take drastic measures to get him back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623123000 +0000" stop="20250623130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally jumps at the chance to paint a couple of garbage cans for Ward, who offers 50 cents a piece. However, when Eddie tells Wally that his father was charged $3.00 to have his painted, he becomes disinterested in the job and Beaver takes it over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623130000 +0000" stop="20250623140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Candy Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Claire Armstrong has built a candy empire, but things go sour when her cousin is almost killed by poisoned candy and a man is found dead in his office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623140000 +0000" stop="20250623150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Annihilator  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>At Cassie's request, Matlock reluctantly agrees to represent a famous wrestler accused of killing a long-time rival. The key witness is a young girl whose story might not be completely accurate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623150000 +0000" stop="20250623160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Last Rights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil fears for his Aunt Ruda's safety after several killings occur in the hospital where she is being treated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623160000 +0000" stop="20250623170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Burn Out - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy smokes a pipe and Grandpa leaves a heater plugged in and turned on and a fire breaks out</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623170000 +0000" stop="20250623173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Colleen So Green</sub-title>
    <desc>"A southern belle named Colleen comes to Dodge and charms her way through Dodge. Kitty is not charmed by the woman. She leaves Matt and Doc at Delmonicos in the middle of dinner, and the reason she gives is she's not going to watch them" Moon" over Colleen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623173000 +0000" stop="20250623180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Ex-urbanites</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Doc and Chester are traveling on the prairie, Doc is shot by some wolfers. Doc's gunshot wounds are serious enough where Chester is worried that Doc might die on the prairie. Chester not only has to remove the bullet from Doc, but he also has to fight off an attack by the wolfers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623180000 +0000" stop="20250623190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Yonder Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is asked by an old friend, once an Army scout, to open a cattle ranch in Mira Flores, Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623190000 +0000" stop="20250623193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheridan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Blandon, a man with only one good arm, wanders onto the ranch. Lucas gives Blandon a job to "hire him and Mark a clear conscience." General Sheridan and his patrol wander by and Lucas offers to let them stay the night at the ranch. Blandon once pulled a gun on General Sheridan; as it turns out, Blandon was a Confederate soldier who once had General Sheridan in his gun sight during the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623193000 +0000" stop="20250623200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623200000 +0000" stop="20250623210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Andrew Hale Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>The Major finds an old man in the desert and takes him to the wagon train. He doesn't remember his name but when he's recognized by one of the other passengers, he remembers not just his name but the faith he thought he lost as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623210000 +0000" stop="20250623220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>How Green Was My Thumb?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John rescue a man who swallowed his partial dental plate. Roy takes care of a young woman's plants while she is in the hospital. A young girl's religious parents prevent necessary treatment. The station responds to a fire in a winery, and Dr. Brackett and the paramedics perform backyard surgery on a man with an unexploded grenade in his abdomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623220000 +0000" stop="20250623223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623223000 +0000" stop="20250623230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623230000 +0000" stop="20250623233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250623233000 +0000" stop="20250624000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624000000 +0000" stop="20250624003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624003000 +0000" stop="20250624010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624010000 +0000" stop="20250624013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Drysdale's Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale's father comes to Beverly Hills to visit. When he learns of the Clampetts, he decides he wants to meet them. He visits and ends up playing poker and pool with Jed. But Farquhar loses all his money because his tricks backfire and the Clampetts are better at the games then he could even imagine. In the end, Jed suggests they give up the gambling and just play a friendly game of pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624013000 +0000" stop="20250624020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Glove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is getting the apartment re-decorated for free but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624020000 +0000" stop="20250624023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Funny Thing Happened On The Way To London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winston Chuchill's right-hand man, Group Captain "Robbie" Roberts, is shot down, captured and brought to Stalag 13. The Luftwaffe scheme to assassinate Churchill by keeping Roberts in the cooler while an impostor escapes to England to carry out the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624023000 +0000" stop="20250624030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Casanova Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Burkhalter plans to get Klink to marry his sister, while a Gestapo plant has infiltrated the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624030000 +0000" stop="20250624033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mirror Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman encounters her doppelgänger at a bus terminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624033000 +0000" stop="20250624043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ancient Romeo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della go out for a night at the theatre to see 'Romeo and Juliet.' After the theatre suddenly goes dark during a dueling scene, the audience is horrified to discover that one of the actors has been killed with a sword when the lights are restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624043500 +0000" stop="20250624050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624050500 +0000" stop="20250624053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Better Bargain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A mobster hires a hit man to kill his cheating wife and lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624053500 +0000" stop="20250624060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Rose Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A publisher finds more fact than fiction in an author’s text.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624060500 +0000" stop="20250624070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Ticket To The Eclipse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A member of Mannix's Korean War Army unit is out for revenge for a wrong done to him in the past. But the man's odd confessions lead Mannix to believe he is suffering from combat fatigue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624070500 +0000" stop="20250624080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bitter Legion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A paramilitary troop wants to rob the income of a football stadium. In search of one of the gangsters Cannon approaches the gang and pretends to want to take part in the foray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624080500 +0000" stop="20250624090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Testament Of Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The executors of a millionaire's estate attempt to get rid of a new will putting them out of their jobs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624090000 +0000" stop="20250624093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>I.a.d. - The Receipt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a complaint that two veteran officers stole funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624093000 +0000" stop="20250624100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - The Harassing Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624100000 +0000" stop="20250624103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624103000 +0000" stop="20250624110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624110000 +0000" stop="20250624120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Truckin' Toony</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill hit the road in a big rig, as Bill reminisces about the trucking craze of the 1970s."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624120000 +0000" stop="20250624123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bad Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An incident at the park leads to Beaver ripping the pants on his gray flannel suit. When he's questioned by Ward and June he makes up a wild story that his parents quickly see through. Lectured in telling the truth, Beaver does just that when the pants of his other suit are ripped but Ward and June don't believe him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624123000 +0000" stop="20250624130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Boarding School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Wally's stops by with stories about how great it is at the military school he attends. This leads Wally to decide that he would like to attend military school, despite a wary Ward and June.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624130000 +0000" stop="20250624140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cheating Chancellor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason returns to his college alma mater to receive an award, but there's no rest for the weary when he's called upon to defend Van Fowler for the murder of a professor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624140000 +0000" stop="20250624150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Husband  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock agrees to defend Cassie's friend, Judy, he is shocked to learn that Judy's husband secretly had another wife. As the case continues, Matlock uncovers more shocking facts about Judy's husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624150000 +0000" stop="20250624160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>When The Music Stopped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Singer Eddie Larran returns to Sparta for a concert, but not everyone is a fan. An angry man insists that Eddie owes him money. And their dispute soon ends in violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624160000 +0000" stop="20250624170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Burn Out - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy smokes a pipe and Grandpa leaves a heater plugged in and turned on and a fire breaks out</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624170000 +0000" stop="20250624173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>I Thee Wed</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Sam Hackett physically beats his wife on the streets of Dodge, Matt and Doc try to persuade Mrs. Hackett to prefer charges on her husband, but she refuses to do so. When Mrs. Hackett comes into Doc's office suffering from a beating she received from her husband, Matt decides to go after Sam Hackett."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624173000 +0000" stop="20250624180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady Killer</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Grant Lucas is in Dodge to testify in court against Cy Welch, Grant goes into the Long Branch for a drink. While Grant is at the Long Branch, he sets up a late night meeting with one of Miss Kitty's saloon girls, Mae Talmey. When Grant goes to Mae's house later that evening, Mae shoots Grant clamming that she thought Grant was trying to rob her; however, Matt does not believe Mae's story."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624180000 +0000" stop="20250624190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Mark Of Guilt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hop Sing tries to prove Joe is innocent of a murder by teaching Hoss and Candy the ancient Chinese art of finger printing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624190000 +0000" stop="20250624193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624193000 +0000" stop="20250624200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624200000 +0000" stop="20250624210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Rodney Lawrence Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>After his parents are killed by whites, a boy is raised by a lone indian. Years later, when the wagon train stops nearby, the indian tells the young man to join his people. But his previous experience with the train make him hesitate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624210000 +0000" stop="20250624220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Hard Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Early is diagnosed with a heart condition and undergoes a bypass. A pro football player is embarrassed to admit that his son tackled him too hard. The firemen rescue a boy trapped in his homemade rocket, a woman with her toe stuck in a bathtub faucet and an electrocution victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624220000 +0000" stop="20250624223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624223000 +0000" stop="20250624230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624230000 +0000" stop="20250624233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250624233000 +0000" stop="20250625000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625000000 +0000" stop="20250625003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625003000 +0000" stop="20250625010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625010000 +0000" stop="20250625013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Farquhar Stays On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has taken interest in Mrs. Drysdale’s father, Mr. Farquhar. And Farquhar is trying to get someone to go to Las Vegas with him, first asking Drysdale, who turns him down. He asks Granny to accompany him, and Granny believes this is a marriage proposal. Farquhar tells Drysdale about this, who is against it, and Drysdale tells Jed, who is all for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625013000 +0000" stop="20250625020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to hit the high note on a civil service exam as well as his cornet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625020000 +0000" stop="20250625023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Come, Easy Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and Klink go to England to steal an allied airplane as part of Hogan's plan to expose Nazi spies in London.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625023000 +0000" stop="20250625030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Nights In Shining Armor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan schemes to get a French courier and some Allied bulletproof vests out of Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625030000 +0000" stop="20250625033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Monsters Are Due On Maple Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paranoia strikes the residents of Maple Street when they believe human-looking aliens have invaded the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625033000 +0000" stop="20250625043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Promoter's Pillbox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Aspiring screenwriter Herbert Simms submits a teleplay to unscrupulous producer Charlie Corby, who passes the manuscript off as his own. Corby's scheme dies with him, however, when he is fatally whacked over the head with a whiskey bottle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625043500 +0000" stop="20250625050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625050500 +0000" stop="20250625053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Blanchard's Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A homemaker decides to play investigator when she starts to think that a neighbor is up to no good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625053500 +0000" stop="20250625060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>John Brown's Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has her husband committed to a mental institution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625060500 +0000" stop="20250625070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing his P.I. license in the aftermath of a frame job, Mannix takes an odd case from a mysterious woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625070500 +0000" stop="20250625080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>That Was No Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Lawyer Jane Butler is threatened. She is told to give up the defense of two burglars. When the menace becomes incendiary the lady begins to fret. Jane asks for Cannon's help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625080500 +0000" stop="20250625090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Copy-cat Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband kills his wife's lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625090000 +0000" stop="20250625093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Police search for a safecracker who left his calling card at the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625093000 +0000" stop="20250625100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's cases range from purse snatching to homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625100000 +0000" stop="20250625103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625103000 +0000" stop="20250625110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Million Dollar Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a run-in with a suspected professional jewel thief and fear she will walk due to lack of evidence. They also find themselves in competition with a millionaire vigilante, who provides assistance with apprehending a drunk driver and ending a shootout, but seems destined to soon overstep the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625110000 +0000" stop="20250625120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' Thru The Mountain State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit wild and wonderful West Virginia for a little whitewater rafting!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625120000 +0000" stop="20250625123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An animal is chewing up June's flower bed, so Ward and the boys set a trap to catch it. They soon catch a white rabbit, which Beaver talks Ward and June into keeping. Beaver names him Henry only to later discover Henry is really a Henrietta and she's expecting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625123000 +0000" stop="20250625130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Runs Away</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry gets Beaver into trouble when he goads him into trying out Ward's drill. Discovering that the boys damaged the garage wall, Ward hits the roof and scolds Beaver, who in turn decides to run away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625130000 +0000" stop="20250625140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impetuous Imp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason helps a young woman who believes her aunt was murdered by her husband, but he soon turns up dead, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625140000 +0000" stop="20250625150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Singer  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a producer accused of killing a singer, trying to prove that someone else at the recording studio is guilty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625150000 +0000" stop="20250625160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Flowers From A Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A city councilwoman becomes dangerously obsessed with Bubba.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625160000 +0000" stop="20250625170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy sees a young innocent looking girl who appears to be traveling alone</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625170000 +0000" stop="20250625173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gentlemen's Disagreement</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ed Beaudry comes to Dodge to kill Bert Wells for marrying Jeanne. When Beaudry turns up dead everyone thinks Bert did it. But when Tulsa starts buying drinks and shooting off his mouth Matt thinks different."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625173000 +0000" stop="20250625180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Speak Me Fair</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt, Doc, and Chester are out hunting when Matt finds an Indian boy half beaten to death. Matt and Chester go back out to prairie and split up looking for clues. Matt comes upon and Indian scout (Ken Curtis) and finds out the boy is the Kiowa Chief’s son. Matt and Chester find the men who were rustling Traych’s cattle and takes them by his ranch for identification and winds up finding out who beat up the boy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625180000 +0000" stop="20250625190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A World Full Of Cannibals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben agrees to hide a government witness in a land fraud case at the Ponderosa as part of the witness protection program. However, the witness—who along with eight men committed various crimes in connection with the case—is in constant danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625190000 +0000" stop="20250625193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625193000 +0000" stop="20250625200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart arrives in North Fork in search of renegade indians suspected of the brutal killing of a Texas Ranger and his family. The townspeople are suspicious of him, however, when they discover that he, too, is an indian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625200000 +0000" stop="20250625210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Steele Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Nearing the end of their trip, a mother with four beautiful daughters, all of marrying age, meets the wagon train full of men who are either the same or wanting to be, and not even the Major is off limits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625210000 +0000" stop="20250625220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Floor Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy consider going into the floor cleaning business on the side. A hermit is trapped in his cave home. Dr. Morton treats a famous singer. John is injured on a high rescue, and the station battles a chemical warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625220000 +0000" stop="20250625223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625223000 +0000" stop="20250625230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625230000 +0000" stop="20250625233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250625233000 +0000" stop="20250626000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626000000 +0000" stop="20250626003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626003000 +0000" stop="20250626010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626010000 +0000" stop="20250626013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Military School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro finally decides on his life’s calling again. He decides on being a five-star general. Jethro is hoping to attend West Point, but Drysdale talks him into going to Haven Hurst. Granny is against him joining because he might get hurt, and Drysdale is having trouble getting him in because this military academy is for boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626013000 +0000" stop="20250626020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Head Of The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tells a newspaper that he's head of the house, but then has to prove it to a co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626020000 +0000" stop="20250626023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a counterfeiting operation that has been set up in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626023000 +0000" stop="20250626030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One In Every Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A prisoner offers the Nazis information on Hogan's operation in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626030000 +0000" stop="20250626033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A World Of Difference</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman discovers that life as he knows it doesn't really exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626033000 +0000" stop="20250626043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lonely Eloper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Merle Telford is a naive and maladjusted young woman who is about to turn 21 and receive a substantial inheritance. She plans to run away from her guardians and elope with Danny Pierce as soon as she receives her money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626043500 +0000" stop="20250626050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626050500 +0000" stop="20250626053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Crackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Two newlyweds stay at the same hotel as a man with whom they got into a scuffle with earlier that day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626053500 +0000" stop="20250626060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In 4-d</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband has a vague memory of helping a woman get rid of a corpse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626060500 +0000" stop="20250626070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Fine Day For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>One might think that after waking from a year-long coma, the worst would be in the past. But that is not true for Mannix's client, injured in a hit-and-run accident and now the target of killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626070500 +0000" stop="20250626080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626080500 +0000" stop="20250626090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Simple Case Of Terror, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is tricked into thinking he committed a murder, but the real killer is his own friend who smuggles diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626090000 +0000" stop="20250626093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626093000 +0000" stop="20250626100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A neo-Nazi psycho has planted a bomb somewhere in L.A. Friday and Gannon have to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626100000 +0000" stop="20250626103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandmothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a hype who robbed a hand-made craft store run by elderly women, only to later return the money after robbing an antique store. In the meantime, they engage in a high-speed pursuit, and pull over a priest in possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626103000 +0000" stop="20250626110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Radical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At roll call, Malloy and Reed are asked to look out for a suspected militant and, after spotting him, attempt to follow him to his stash of weapons. Malloy also is asked by a security guard to investigate a possible shakedown and smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626110000 +0000" stop="20250626120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>All Of Our Toons</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony make a very dramatic soap opera."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626120000 +0000" stop="20250626123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all excited to have his friend, Larry Mondello, stay over for the weekend. However, things start off on the wrong foot when Beaver and Larry get into a fight, which ends with Beaver punching Larry in the stomach.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626123000 +0000" stop="20250626130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cat Out Of The Bag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>The neighbors are going away for the weekend and Beaver and Wally have been put in charge of taking care of their lawn and their cat, Puff Puff. When Eddie shows up with his dog, Wolf, chaos erupts and Wolf chases Puff Puff away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626130000 +0000" stop="20250626140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Carefree Coronary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Safeline Insurance Company notices an increase in heart attacks among their policy holders. The company suspects fraud and hires Mason and Paul to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626140000 +0000" stop="20250626150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Juror  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Called to jury duty, Matlock butts heads with the other jurors, who think the defendant is guilty of murder. Matlock implores them to reexamine the evidence before sentencing the man to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626150000 +0000" stop="20250626160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Private Sessions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Virgil's classmates from law school is arrested following the death of his former girlfriend, but the man insists that her death was the result of her relationship with her psychiatrist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626160000 +0000" stop="20250626170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia gets a job in the city as a dressmaker</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626170000 +0000" stop="20250626173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Belle's Back</sub-title>
    <desc>"Belle Ainsley comes back to Dodge after 3 years being with an outlaw. Belle tells Matt she left him for good. Matt gets suspicious when Belle's sister Phyllis goes missing from the Dodge House."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626173000 +0000" stop="20250626180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bobsy Twins</sub-title>
    <desc>"A very bizarre episode about two brothers who have come West to kill Indians."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626180000 +0000" stop="20250626190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet Annie Laurie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss offers to help Annie Laurie run away from her abusive husband, a career criminal who is determined to keep his wife under his control.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626190000 +0000" stop="20250626193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarding House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Reformed card shark Julia Massini now runs a respectable boarding house in North Fork, but Sid Fallon is threatening to reveal her sordid past unless she lets him turn the establishment into a saloon and gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626193000 +0000" stop="20250626200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas puts his life in jeopardy when he agrees to testify in a murder case involving a witness killed before he could testify and a killer still at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626200000 +0000" stop="20250626210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jenny Tannen Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl is injured while on the way to San Francisco to find her famous mother, who abandoned her as a baby. The crew helps the girl with her encroaching blindness and finds her mother, who has her own problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626210000 +0000" stop="20250626220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Propinquity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy spends the night at John's place while his house is being fumigated, which is one night too many. A woman is trapped inside a car while it burns around her; the ambulance carrying Roy and the victim is hit by a car. A man having a heart attack refuses to leave a poker game unless John agrees to play out the man's hand. An explosion at an abandoned refinery injures several workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626220000 +0000" stop="20250626223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626223000 +0000" stop="20250626230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626230000 +0000" stop="20250626233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250626233000 +0000" stop="20250627000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627000000 +0000" stop="20250627003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627003000 +0000" stop="20250627010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627010000 +0000" stop="20250627013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Common Cold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is looking to cure people and learns of Mr. Drysdale’s illness. He has a common cold. Granny says that she has the ability to cure it with one spoonful of “cold cure.” She makes her cold cure to share with Dr. Clyburn, but he turns her down and mean-mouths her. So she decides to start her own doctor’s office and use her cold cure to treat folks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627013000 +0000" stop="20250627020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pal O'mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's feelings are bruised when Ed buys a friendship ring for one of his pals on the sewer crew. Though Ralph gets it stuck on his finger, they eventually make up after Ed survives a sewer explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627020000 +0000" stop="20250627023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Meister Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men pose as Nazi officers to get an American traitor to divulge the names of his German superiors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627023000 +0000" stop="20250627030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Russian Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to get a Russian pilot, who refuses to escape to London, back to Russia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627030000 +0000" stop="20250627033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live Walter Jameson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A history teacher talks about the past as if he had lived it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627033000 +0000" stop="20250627043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bogus Books</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason investigates the murder of an antiquarian bookseller with an interest in forgery. It seems as though someone turned on the gas line to his office while he was taking his afternoon nap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627043500 +0000" stop="20250627050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627050500 +0000" stop="20250627053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother, Richard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man kills his brother’s opponent for the governor’s office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627053500 +0000" stop="20250627060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Manacled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal offers $50,000 to a detective in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627060500 +0000" stop="20250627070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Figures In A Landscape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is stalked by a sniper while searching for a missing woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627070500 +0000" stop="20250627080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Predators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon believes that this time he has accepted a peaceful job. He must protect the bar of a friend, Millie Carroll, against robberies. However, suddenly he finds himself amid a complex love story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627080500 +0000" stop="20250627090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Marathon Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the death of a heavily-insured man that is believed to be an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627090000 +0000" stop="20250627093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapping</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon help an employee rescue her kidnapped boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627093000 +0000" stop="20250627100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627100000 +0000" stop="20250627103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed report to a robbery at a grocery store, where Malloy is required to engage in a high-speed pursuit with one of the suspects while Reed apprehends the other on foot. When Malloy is seriously injured in a rollover accident at a remote location and loses two-way radio communication, Reed and others from the department race against the clock to locate him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627103000 +0000" stop="20250627110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an environmentalist known as "The Ferret" who has been posing as an employee to infiltrate and sabotage industrial complexes he feels are creating too much pollution. In the meantime, they respond to a woman who is nearly comatose and ultimately gives birth to a stillborn baby. They then investigate the witchdoctor who has been convincing her and other women that eating clay will ensure a successful pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627110000 +0000" stop="20250627120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Rival Of The Ages Iv</sub-title>
    <desc>"The battle continues! Two generations face off in the fourth edition of Rival of the Ages."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627120000 +0000" stop="20250627123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Poem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes to Ward for help on the night before a poetry assignment is due. This prompts Ward to totally take over the project and write the whole poem himself. Things get complicated when Beaver wins an award for the poem and Ward is faced with explaining the truth to Beaver's principal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627123000 +0000" stop="20250627130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Eddie swooning over his so-called "girl," Caroline. However, it's obvious Eddie has made up their relationship when Wally and him visit her and she instantly becomes smitten with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627130000 +0000" stop="20250627140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hasty Honeymooner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas Tolliver arrives in California from Oklahoma to meet the woman he was matched up with by a computer dating service. The woman, Miliicent Barton, is supposedly a rich widow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627140000 +0000" stop="20250627150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Network  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Network programming chief Paul J. Bartel is murdered, leaving Hollywood baffled as to the identity of the killer. Matlock comes to town to represent the television producer accused of the crime, and finds more than his fair share of suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627150000 +0000" stop="20250627160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge schemes to get rid of his wife after she tries to blackmail him into giving her a divorce and a generous settlement by revealing a secret from his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627160000 +0000" stop="20250627170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Quilting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen resists joining in on a quilting when she reaches the marrying age</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627170000 +0000" stop="20250627173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Flame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt’s old flame Dolly Winters comes and asks Matt to help her find her husband Rad Meadows. Kitty’s suspicious of Dolly. Matt finds Rad but he’s not like Dolly said he was. Matt tells Dolly to leave town but instead she rides to Rad’s house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627173000 +0000" stop="20250627180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Corporal Janice takes off with the Army payroll after an ambush. Matt has to find his accomplice who no one got a look at. Matt gets a line on Janice and finds him. His father gets the drop on Matt and shoots Chester and holds them hostage at his house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627180000 +0000" stop="20250627190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>My Friend, My Enemy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Candy stands accused of murder, and the only person who can clear his name is an Indian wanted for horse theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627190000 +0000" stop="20250627193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw Sam Morley falls in love with a young woman who has a serious illness. He asks Lucas to turn him in for the reward and then use the money to pay for her medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627193000 +0000" stop="20250627200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>One Went To Denver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas welcomes his old friend, Tom Birch, who once saved his life, unaware that the man is now a bank robber who is on the run with his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627200000 +0000" stop="20250627210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Stagecoach Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The men are returning to St. Louis by stagecoach except for Flint, until he becomes the driver to help a friend. They are forced to take a detour through Mexico by other passengers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627210000 +0000" stop="20250627220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inventions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen enter a contest to invent new firefighting tools. The paramedics handle victims of possible radiation poisoning. A comatose man is suffering from a mysterious ailment. A woman’s overweight son is wedged in her living room ceiling. The firemen respond to a leak at a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627220000 +0000" stop="20250627223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627223000 +0000" stop="20250627230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627230000 +0000" stop="20250627233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250627233000 +0000" stop="20250628000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628000000 +0000" stop="20250628003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628003000 +0000" stop="20250628010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Education Of Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. is back in Mayberry to get his diploma. He is so determined that Andy convinces Helen to allow him to attend class, but Ernest T. isn't exactly classroom material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628010000 +0000" stop="20250628013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Settled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at their new home, but find there aren't any of the conveniences of their old home. Jethro makes a few new discoveries, things they have never seen before, like pink chickens (flamingoes) and a cement pond. When Miss Jane Hathaway arrives, the executive secretary for Mr. Drysdale, she mistakes the clan for a staff of bumbling, insubordinate backwoods servants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628013000 +0000" stop="20250628020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph captures two thugs that followed him home after he witnessed a hold-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628020000 +0000" stop="20250628023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>An Evening Of Generals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as waiters, Hogan and the gang scheme to get rid of a room full of German generals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628023000 +0000" stop="20250628030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Loves A Snowman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys must smuggle a U.S. bomber crew out of camp while under surveillance by Hochstetter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628030000 +0000" stop="20250628033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>People Are Alike All Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When a space exploration crashes on Mars, the surviving passenger is surprised to find that Martians are human-looking, very friendly and apparently just like us.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628033000 +0000" stop="20250628043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Capricious Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When a major financial supporter of an orphanage lapses into a coma and later dies, his nephew pursues plans to shut down the institution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628043500 +0000" stop="20250628050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628050500 +0000" stop="20250628053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Bottle Of Wine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge tries to prove that his wife’s lover is a coward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628053500 +0000" stop="20250628060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Malice Domestic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carl, a newlywed, suspects his wife is trying to poison him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628060500 +0000" stop="20250628070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Mouse That Died</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Out on a routine missing persons case, Mannix uncovers an espionage ring and falls victim to a slow-acting poison for which he must race against time to procure the antidote.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628070500 +0000" stop="20250628080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Long Way Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An illegal immigrant from Mexico has died in a coyote's case. Sheep grower Rita McBain is accused of the deed. Cannon must prove Rita's innocence and deal with a human smuggler ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628080500 +0000" stop="20250628090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of amateur singers commit larceny and murder in an attempt to finance a record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250628090000 +0000" stop="20250628093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Race Against The Stork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe wants to make sure everything is in order when Kate's pregnant friend comes to the Shady Rest to have her baby.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
