<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913170000 +0000" stop="20250913180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chato</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a friend of Matt's dies, he goes to New Mexico to find the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913180000 +0000" stop="20250913190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Time To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben helps an old friend, April Christopher, and her daughter when April is bitten by a rabid wolf while visiting the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913190000 +0000" stop="20250913193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sidewinder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gridley Mau is gunning for Lucas, who killed his father during an attempted robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913193000 +0000" stop="20250913200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteenth Cousin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese nobleman seeks revenge when his servant is insulted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913200000 +0000" stop="20250913210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Damon's Road: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A railroad builder in desperate need of workers tricks Favor's drovers into signing work contracts. To make matters even worse for Favor, he finds himself arrested for "abducting" a showgirl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913210000 +0000" stop="20250913213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Birds Of A Feather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin must contend with other gunfighters as he tries to settle a right-of-way dispute between two railroads in a Colorado town that will die if they go elsewhere.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913213000 +0000" stop="20250913220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Man On Horseback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Charley Red Cloud is blamed for the murder of Will Bascomb. Bascomb's brother, Merv, places a high bounty on Red Cloud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913220000 +0000" stop="20250913230000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Listen, Judge, Goof On The Roof, Hula-la-la</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges becomes servants for the judge that they ran away from., The Stooges are entrusted with taking care of their friend's house while he goes off to get married.  At first they only wreck the place a little bit, but when they try to install a television antenna, total destruction ensues.  When their friend returns with his bride, she's so shocked she walks out on him. , The boys run into trouble with the local witch doctor who wants to add their heads to his collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913230000 +0000" stop="20250914023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Bad Seed</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mother begins to worry that her daughter's sweet exterior may be covering a deadly secret."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914023000 +0000" stop="20250914030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Ring Of Wax</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler smuggles a substance that can eat through anything inside a wax statue of Batman intended for display at Madame Soleil's Wax Museum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914030000 +0000" stop="20250914040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Menagerie, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Spock's court-martial continues as he attempts to justify his abduction of Pike, the theft of the Enterprise, and his heading for a planet declared forbidden by Starfleet.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914040000 +0000" stop="20250914043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl Who Hired Superman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy young lady tries to hire Superman to entertain at a party. Her guardian uses the distraction to steal counterfeit plates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914043000 +0000" stop="20250914050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding Of Superman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois dreams that she gets engaged to Superman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914050000 +0000" stop="20250914060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Attack Of The Monster Plants</sub-title>
    <desc>"Plants grow to huge proportions and can duplicate any item placed in them - but those items are made of plant material and are useless. John Robinson must use the biggest batch of plant killer he's ever mixed up to stop these things from engulfing the spaceship."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914060000 +0000" stop="20250914070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Monster From The Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A creature that is purely brains tries to take over the Seaview.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914070000 +0000" stop="20250914080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Collector's Item</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A nephew schemes against his uncle, a collector, and captures Valerie. He forces her to pretend to be a toy ballerina... unaware that the display cage she's in is rigged with explosives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914080000 +0000" stop="20250914090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Walls Of Jericho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Warrior-prophet Joshua sends Tony and Doug into Jericho as spies before he attacks the Biblical city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914090000 +0000" stop="20250914100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Captive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent is jailed with an alien intruder as a paranoid man decides what to do.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914100000 +0000" stop="20250914110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Dam</sub-title>
    <desc>"A beaver colony dams up the river in Adams' valley, placing his cabin and surrounding wildlife at risk. Should Adams take Mad Jack's advice and destroy the dam and run out the beavers - or is there a more humane solution?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914110000 +0000" stop="20250914113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Swamp Water Safari</sub-title>
    <desc>"Death stalks the Florida Everglades.  Not swift death by predators but a slow, agonizing death caused by drought and floods.  Marlin and Jim visit the Everglades to investigate this problem first hand."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914113000 +0000" stop="20250914120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Exploring Jaguar Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to the high country of northern Mexico to explore the hills where the jaguar roams."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914120000 +0000" stop="20250914123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Giraffe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to Rhodesia to join in a game relocation project with the rangers of Wankie National Park … a game preserve where all kinds of wild animals make their home.  Two animals are on their list:  a zebra and a giraffe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914123000 +0000" stop="20250914130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Partnership</sub-title>
    <desc>"Throughout the wild kingdom there are many examples of animal cooperation, and one of the most remarkable takes place in a picturesque little valley in southern Utah …  home for families of badgers, bobcats, coyotes and golden eagles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914130000 +0000" stop="20250914133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tuskers Below</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to Kruger National Park in the Republic of South Africa to join the rangers there in an exciting wild elephant capture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914133000 +0000" stop="20250914140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cheetah Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Four fuzzy kittens tumble out of their den; they’re baby cheetahs taking those first uncertain steps into a dangerous world.  The rugged bush country of Rhodesia is an excellent training ground for life in the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914140000 +0000" stop="20250914143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Brace Yourself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia is distraught after getting braces, and is convinced that they've made her ugly. Her brothers and sisters try their best to make Marcia feel less self-conscious, but they have little success.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914143000 +0000" stop="20250914150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While shopping at Driscoll's Toy Store, Peter looks up to see a wall about to fall on a little girl, and he saves her by pushing her out of the way. He's called a hero but he lets the newfound attention go to his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914150000 +0000" stop="20250914153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Richie's Flip Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Richie becomes a disc jockey at a local radio station, his boss informs him that he has the potential to become the next Wolfman Jack. Richie begins to develop an inflated ego and neglect his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914153000 +0000" stop="20250914160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Squiggy In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When Squiggy begins dating a beautiful woman, Laverne and Shirley know they must break the news to him that he's being used.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914160000 +0000" stop="20250914163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Ill-gotten Gain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is given a bike after bringing home a report card filled with straight As. He soon discovers that the high marks were a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914163000 +0000" stop="20250914170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy And Bob Hope</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky is opening a new club, and he wants Bob Hope to appear at the grand opening. Lucy fears Hope won't appear because of her widespread reputation for monkey-wrench throwing, and wants to reassure him that this time she's butting out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914170000 +0000" stop="20250914173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Electric Trains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>June runs across Beaver's old electric trains while cleaning and because he hasn't played with them in years, finds someone who will take them, with Beaver's consent. However, Beaver quickly re-discovers the fun of playing with the trains and wants to withdraw from the arrangement, even though the new owners-to-be are expecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914173000 +0000" stop="20250914180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Richard has just gotten, as Beaver describes it, a "keen" new jacket and this prompts Beaver to ask his parents for one exactly like it. June and Ward are hesitant after learning the price but decide to give in. However, when Richard loses his jacket, he coerces Beaver into a plot to trick his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914180000 +0000" stop="20250914183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Revelation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny finally realizes that Mark is not half man/half frog. After learning he is all human, Granny is set on finally getting Elly May married to Mark. Elly and Mark are getting more serious, and Mark is planning to leave the Navy to spend more time with Elly and on his oceanography research. When Drysdale learns all of this, he is dead set on splitting Mark and Elly up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914183000 +0000" stop="20250914190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Grunion Invasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts prepare to go fight the invading Grunion, while Drysdale works to keep the Clampetts believing Mark has turned coward. The Clampetts head to the beach and set up their headquarters. They look out on the water and see a couple of surfers and mistake them for the Grunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914190000 +0000" stop="20250914193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>You've Been Disconnected</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A storm washes up a trans-continental telephone cable into the lagoon. The Professor manages to break into the cable and rig up a telephone so they can dial out for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914193000 +0000" stop="20250914200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Postman Cometh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways hear on the radio that Mary Ann's boyfriend in Kansas is getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914200000 +0000" stop="20250914203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>An Affair To Forget  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama and Naomi suspect Vint of more than a working relationship with his new beautiful, blonde trainee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914203000 +0000" stop="20250914210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Wrong  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>With Naomi pregnant, Iola starts to think she should be married, too. To everyone's surprise, she finds a boyfriend—but the relationship doesn't last through their first dinner with Mama!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914210000 +0000" stop="20250914220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Good Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubing fears a portrait will be too revealing; a woman won't become involved with her neighbor; a new groom sees a face from his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914220000 +0000" stop="20250914223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Date For Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked by Andy and Barney to take Thelma Lou's cousin, Mary Grace Gossage, to the Chamber of Commerce dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914223000 +0000" stop="20250914230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Mark Van Woert- Pop Culture</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mark Van Woert is all about nostalgia. Chances are, if something resonated with him as a child, it's in his collection. Today, Mark will show us Archie Bunker's Grandson Doll, a doll that was almost as controversial as Archie himself, the still-in-box Fembot Action figures, and even Rice Krispy Hand puppets, that were part of his own Mom's childhood. Our toy expert John Ragusa will appraise this special pop culture collection and then try making a trade with our collector. He's brought Mark an oh-so rare collectible that will surely touch his heart, but John's going to ask Mark for something that he remembers from his own childhood. Tune in to see whose heart will win out."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914230000 +0000" stop="20250914233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250914233000 +0000" stop="20250915000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915000000 +0000" stop="20250915003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Very Moving Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>As Mike and Gloria are getting ready to move into their own home, Gloria comes home with news from the doctor that she's pregnant and announces it to an overjoyed Archie and Edith. However, she is a bit nervous about announcing her unexpected pregnancy to Mike because of his stubborn attitudes concerning overpopulation. When Mike does find out he has a mixed reaction, ultimately resulting in him storming out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915003000 +0000" stop="20250915010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Alone At Last?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Teary farewells turn into fireworks when Mike hits Archie with five years of repressed rage, only to discover that he and Gloria can't move out for another week after Mike reveals he forgot to turn on the gas and electricity at his new home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915010000 +0000" stop="20250915013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie, The Donor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie tries impressing his boss by making the maximum contribution to his favorite charity and unwittingly donates his body to medical science.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915013000 +0000" stop="20250915020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie, The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie gets a rude shock when the tall,classy dame whose life he saved in a taxicab turns out to be a man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915020000 +0000" stop="20250915023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll And Jack Jones</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll and Jack Jones. Originally aired on 02/23/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915023000 +0000" stop="20250915030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jane Connell And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Jane Connell and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 03/02/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915030000 +0000" stop="20250915033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sick Boy And The Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob is invited to a party at his boss' house, but Laura doesn't want to go when she senses their son is getting sick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915033000 +0000" stop="20250915040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Blonde-haired Brunette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Worries of a dull marriage turn to worries of Rob's reaction when Mary gets a big make-over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915040000 +0000" stop="20250915043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pal O'mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's feelings are bruised when Ed buys a friendship ring for one of his pals on the sewer crew. Though Ralph gets it stuck on his finger, they eventually make up after Ed survives a sewer explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915043000 +0000" stop="20250915053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Passage On The Lady Anne</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>On a cruise they hoped would rekindle their love, a troubled young couple instead decides to divorce upon their return. The unexpected occurs, however, with the appearance of a certain nightgown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915053000 +0000" stop="20250915060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Insomnia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A man seeks an end to the insomnia that is ruining his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915060000 +0000" stop="20250915070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Kitara (aka The Bigot)</sub-title>
    <desc>"John Darcy, codename "Kitara," leads a liberation movement in the African country of Bocamo and has been inadvertently captured by the ruthless Colonel Kohler. Kohler plans to torture Kitara, who if he confesses his true identity will result in the destruction of the entire movement. Kohler is after a truck full of government gold bullion Kitara stole. Jim and Doug play agents while Barney is captured and gets the location of the bullion from Kitara and gets it to Jim. Before his capture, Barney puts a rigged bulb in Kohler's UV sterilizer and Dana gives the man a drug that causes his skin to blacken, and Kohler soon believes that he's secretly a black native."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915070000 +0000" stop="20250915080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>A.p.b.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble hops onto a freight train and finds himself in the company of three escaped convicts (two of whom are wounded during their escape). One of the convicts dies from his wounds while the second one, a brutal murderer named Neil Pinkerton, forces Kimble</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915080000 +0000" stop="20250915090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Book Of Changes</sub-title>
    <desc>"The owner of a plush gambling club is murdered and private investigator Harry Orwell is hired to find her killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915090000 +0000" stop="20250915093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915093000 +0000" stop="20250915100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915100000 +0000" stop="20250915103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 152 -- A Dead Cop Can't Help Anyone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to shield an impressionable Reed from Officer Ed Wells, a shoot-first-ask-questions-later style officer. Wells' reckless philosophy endangers his own safety when he responds to a sniper, forcing them to come to his rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915103000 +0000" stop="20250915110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 12: He – He Was Trying To Kill Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"Malloy and Reed investigate a case of child neglect."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915110000 +0000" stop="20250915120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Quest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony are on a quest to solve some of history's greatest mysteries."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915120000 +0000" stop="20250915123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Loves Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes convinced that he's ugly and unwanted after constantly being reminded how cute he used to be and from being yelled at by his parents for how messy he is currently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915123000 +0000" stop="20250915130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is rounding up some guys to go to an amusement park and he's one short from getting a discount so he settles on Beaver. However, Beaver begins having second thoughts when he hears stories about one of the roller coasters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915130000 +0000" stop="20250915140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Long-legged Models</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Racketeer George Castle kills Las Vegas hotel owner Glenn Faulkner over a gambling debt and sets his sights on land inherited by Faulkner's daughter, Stephanie. When Castle turns up murdered as well, Stephanie finds herself the number one suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915140000 +0000" stop="20250915150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.a.  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Julie becomes the target of a witness with psychological problems, leaving Matlock and Conrad to learn who is threatening her, and why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915150000 +0000" stop="20250915160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sister, Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A vivacious socialites return to Sparta delights her ailing father and childhood friend Virgil, but her sister is less than thrilled at her homecoming. After their father is poisoned the jealous siblings become suspects in his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915160000 +0000" stop="20250915170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Calling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A cousin of the Baldwin sisters visits</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915170000 +0000" stop="20250915173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doc's Reward</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc kills a man who shoots his horse. The man's brother comes looking for Doc because he thinks Doc killed his brother for reward money."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915173000 +0000" stop="20250915180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Judge</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Matt is away on business, Doc gets threatened by an ex-convict (Brice Harp) who claims that Doc Adams sentenced him to a long term in Prison. Doc tries to explain to the man that he was never a judge and has always been a doctor, but the man does not believe Doc."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915180000 +0000" stop="20250915190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Winter Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When a prized steer belonging to the Cartwrights is killed by the foreman of a neighboring ranch, the man's scheming boss plans to take unfair advantage of the mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915190000 +0000" stop="20250915193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>And The Devil Makes Five</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A snake crawls into Lucas' bed, and Mark must lure it away before it strikes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915193000 +0000" stop="20250915200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of The Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is thrown into jail to stop him from murdering an old enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915200000 +0000" stop="20250915210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Joe Muharich Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>"Polish immigrant Joe Muharich tries to befriend and hopefully straighten out Johnny Kamen, a brash young man who doesn't take well to anyone giving orders to him. Joe has lost his wife and son to thugs, and now he reacts violently to any attempt to harass or intimidate him. When Johnny accidentally shoots a woman while reacting against drunken thugs, Joe tries to defend him. But the thugs who harassed Johnny then harass Joe and start fire to his wagon, causing Joe to react by shooting the men and killing one of them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915210000 +0000" stop="20250915220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>An Ounce Of Prevention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man with chest pains is trapped on a ferris wheel. A child ingests an illegal pesticide. While making a TV appearance to discuss fire prevention, Gage and DeSoto become stars of a real-life emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915220000 +0000" stop="20250915223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915223000 +0000" stop="20250915230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915230000 +0000" stop="20250915233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250915233000 +0000" stop="20250916000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916000000 +0000" stop="20250916003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Barney's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After being kicked out of Mrs. Mendlebright's boardinghouse, Barney becomes suspicious of the man who takes his room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916003000 +0000" stop="20250916010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gives Gomer a ticket for making an illegal U-turn, but then when Barney does it, Gomer has no choice but to make a citizen's arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916010000 +0000" stop="20250916013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Military Career</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is practicing being a Navy Frogman. Granny, who has been testing her flu serum, a.k.a. moonshine, sees Jethro and thinks there is a monster in the pool. When she tells Jed, he thinks it is a result of her moonshine. But Granny finally is shown that it isn’t a monster, but Jethro. Jed decides that Jethro needs some type of guidance, so he calls Miss Jane, who tells Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916013000 +0000" stop="20250916020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit From Cousin Goober</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Goober pays Gomer a surprise visit. Goober says he's through working at the filling station and wants to give the Marines a try for a week to see if he likes it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916020000 +0000" stop="20250916023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Zolle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to detain a German general at camp for 24 hours to allow the Allies to amass troops. Things get complicated when a Gestapo officer comes in search of the reason for Klink's perfect record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916023000 +0000" stop="20250916030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes A Thief... Sometimes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of underground operatives that Hogan and his team begin working with is actually a group lead by a Gestapo captain who's set on capturing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916030000 +0000" stop="20250916033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 03/23/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916033000 +0000" stop="20250916043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ugly Duckling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A prospective heiress to a toy company must soon marry if she wishes to inherit her father's business. When it surfaces that her new boyfriend is being paid to romance her by her uncle, murder is not far behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916043500 +0000" stop="20250916050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Piano In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man discovers that the piano he bought his wife for her birthday possesses magical properties—the music it plays makes people reveal their true essence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916050500 +0000" stop="20250916053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Can Take Care Of Myself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man and his girlfriend run afoul of a gangster, they find their lives in danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916053500 +0000" stop="20250916060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One Grave Too Many</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is ridden with guilt after he takes a wallet from a heart attack victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916060500 +0000" stop="20250916070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>See No Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix takes a case at the request of Peggy on behalf of her friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916070500 +0000" stop="20250916080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin Corner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon gets hired to be a bodyguard for a courier of securities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916080500 +0000" stop="20250916090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916090000 +0000" stop="20250916093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916093000 +0000" stop="20250916100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916100000 +0000" stop="20250916103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 172 -- Boy...the Things You Do For The Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malloy gives a gorgeous wealthy blonde a traffic ticket, she stalks him, affecting him and the police force. Although uninterested in her, Malloy is forced to "take one" for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916103000 +0000" stop="20250916110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 92 -- Tell Him He Pushed Back A Little Too Hard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to repeated calls about an argument between two men and their wives over a boat they co-own. The feud escalates and ends with a fatal conclusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916110000 +0000" stop="20250916120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Age Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony's new podcast sets out to finally uncover the truth about Mr. Quizzer's real age."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916120000 +0000" stop="20250916123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Three Boys And A Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Gilbert and Richard find a burro for sale in Mayfield and they each decide to go in $10 for it. After getting their parent's permission, Richard and Gilbert fight over who gets to keep the burro, which they name Pepe. However, once they get a load of just how destructive a burro can be, they dump the problem of room and board on Beaver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916123000 +0000" stop="20250916130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Quits School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie pompously announces that he's dropping out of school to get a high paying job at a gas station. However, all is not as it seems when Wally and Lumpy get a glance at Eddie's new free spending life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916130000 +0000" stop="20250916140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gilded Lily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Enid Griffin, the secretary of Stewart Brent, attempts to commit suicide after learning her boss has married. Arthur Binney attempts to blackmail Stewart Brent with facts about his new wife having been in jail for fraud. When Binny turns up dead, Brent is framed for his murder, but confesses to protect his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916140000 +0000" stop="20250916150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Blackmailer  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Cartoonist Ron Winfield has been keeping Atlanta enthralled with his recent storyline involving a Senator's affair. But just before the woman in the affair is named in print, the strips disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916150000 +0000" stop="20250916160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Accused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba tries to rescue a woman from a rapist, but she mistakes him for her attacker. Gillespie tangles with an ambitious district attorney who plans to use the case to further his career.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916160000 +0000" stop="20250916170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Moonshiner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Boone Walton returns after he was convicted of moon-shining andJason promises to keep watch on him</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916170000 +0000" stop="20250916180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Baker's Dozen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three baby boys are born on a stagecoach that arrives in Dodge just after being robbed. Their mother dies and Doc fights to keep the boys together instead of going to an orphanage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916180000 +0000" stop="20250916190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Kingdom Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights and Candy are captured by a man known as "The Judge," who turns them into slaves, forcing them to work in his gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916190000 +0000" stop="20250916193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is baffled when the marshal of a neighboring town refuses to hold a gambler who just attempted murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916193000 +0000" stop="20250916200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem At Mission Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark is paralyzed, Lucas attempts to cure him at the mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916200000 +0000" stop="20250916210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Duke Shannon Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>"With his clever tall tales, old prospector Henry Shannon talks Charlie Wooster into coming with him to search for a gold mine. When Hawks finds out about this, he rides out after the two men, along with Shannon's grandson Duke. Also following the old men are three men who hope to grab the gold for themselves."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916210000 +0000" stop="20250916220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Insanity Epidemic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley freaks out when he learns one of his past captains is now his Battalion Chief, causing the others to worry about his increased paranoia. Two men’s carelessness starts a fire at a gas station. A new hospital administrator causes problems. A woman accidentally shoots her husband with a nail gun. Two clowns start a fight at an ice rink. A car leaves an overpass and crashes into a transfer truck filled with pesticides.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916220000 +0000" stop="20250916223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916223000 +0000" stop="20250916230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916230000 +0000" stop="20250916233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250916233000 +0000" stop="20250917000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917000000 +0000" stop="20250917003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And His Merry Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie and his friends find a hungry man in the woods who tells them the story of Robin Hood, the boys begin to steal for the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917003000 +0000" stop="20250917010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Cave Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is the laughingstock of the town after he mistakes the owner of the Mayberry Bank as a robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917010000 +0000" stop="20250917013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Reserve Program</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is getting ready to enter the reserves, and the Clampetts are giving him a party, with gifts, including lady fingers, a squirrel rifle and a Confederate uniform. Jethro heads down to the reserve where they are preparing to shoot a Civil War movie. The men there think Jethro is an actor for the movie. Jethro soon thinks that the Civil War is going to happen again and rushes home to tell Granny and Elly. Granny decides to take up the fight to make sure the South wins, again, since she is convinced they won the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917013000 +0000" stop="20250917020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Groom For Sergeant Carter's Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter objects to the man with whom his sister is engaged, and uses Gomer as a means of breaking them up. Little does he know, the brother-in-law-to-be also is a Marine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917020000 +0000" stop="20250917023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Schultz to portray Klink in order to free three of his men whom the Gestapo has captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917023000 +0000" stop="20250917030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Pizza Parlor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>To get a Italian officer to defect, Hogan and the gang use pizza to tempt him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917030000 +0000" stop="20250917033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 03/30/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917033000 +0000" stop="20250917043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Missing Button</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's campaign to prove his estranged wife an unfit mother is interrupted when he's arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917043500 +0000" stop="20250917050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Rites Of Jeff Myrtlebank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man comes back to life at his own funeral and soon begins to act very strangely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917050500 +0000" stop="20250917053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Party Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman shares a party line with two nosy neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917053500 +0000" stop="20250917060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cell 227</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An innocent man faces death in the gas chamber for the death of a girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917060500 +0000" stop="20250917070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Light And Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix gets involved in the case of a millionaire's wife accused of killing the boyfriend of her stepdaughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917070500 +0000" stop="20250917080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Perfect Fit For A Frame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon gets hired to protect a girl but when her supposed pursuer is found dead he finds himself charged with murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917080500 +0000" stop="20250917090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917090000 +0000" stop="20250917093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917093000 +0000" stop="20250917100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917100000 +0000" stop="20250917103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 22: So This Little Guy Goes Into This Bar, And...</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fur burglary, a family fight and a loud party."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917103000 +0000" stop="20250917110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 15 -- Exactly One Hundred Yards</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On their day off, Malloy and Reed agree to give a talk to a group of fifth grade students, and then offer to let the kids watch them train for the California Police Olympics. But when the tires of their patrol car are slashed and a stopwatch goes missing out of reed's car, the two officers start to suspect one of the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917110000 +0000" stop="20250917120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mysterious Locations</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit some of the most mysterious places on earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917120000 +0000" stop="20250917123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Stays At Lumpy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A communication gap ensues when Wally wants to spend the night at Lumpy's and Beaver wants to have Gilbert spend the night. Beaver asks June and she tells him he can sometime when Wally spends the night somewhere and Wally asks Ward, who tells him he can sometime when Beaver has someone spend the night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917123000 +0000" stop="20250917130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Laundry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver agrees to help Richard cart his family's clothes down to the laundromat; however, half way there they discover that Richard has lost the three dollars his mother gave him. This leads him to ask Beaver if he could use the Cleaver washer. They soon find themselves in another jam when the washing machine overflows after Beaver put in too much soap and starch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917130000 +0000" stop="20250917140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lazy Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Attempting to miss hitting her stepfather's car, Patricia Faxon swerves as she enters her driveway and hits the hedges. After asking her stepfather, Bertrand Allred, to move his car, he finds Bob Fleetwood badly hurt next to the hedges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917140000 +0000" stop="20250917150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Monster  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a cookie mogul is found dead after announcing plans to take over a number of baking companies, Matlock works the defense for another cookie maker suspected in the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917150000 +0000" stop="20250917160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fifteen Forever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Sparta grieves after a drunk driver causes a fatal crash with high school cheerleaders on their way home from a game. While the officers try to find other driver, Althea tries to help the victim's families deal with their loss. The accident brings back painful memories for retired officer Tom Dugan. Meanwhile, district attorney Dutton accuses the department of being inadequate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917160000 +0000" stop="20250917170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen starts taking pills to stay awake, and then to sleep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917170000 +0000" stop="20250917180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Wishbone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt goes after three bandits who robbed a stagecoach and killed the driver and guard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917180000 +0000" stop="20250917190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>An Earthquake Called Callahan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe searches for a professional fighter who can clear the name of an incarcerated Dusty Rhoades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917190000 +0000" stop="20250917193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>New arrival Mario Arsatti becomes very friendly with Lucas, but this turns out to be merely pleasure before business: he's been hired to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917193000 +0000" stop="20250917200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Man Running (aka The Wanted Man)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas, who blames his wife's death on his father-in-law, refuses to help the old man elude gunmen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917200000 +0000" stop="20250917210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Will Santee Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Santee family---Will, his mother, and his younger sister---join the wagon train under a false surname. They have been forced out of town after town because of a terrible thing a family member did. They confide in Hale, Hawks, and Charlie, who agree to keep their secret from the others on the train. But it soon comes out anyway, and things get complicated when Will falls for a young woman from the wagon train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917210000 +0000" stop="20250917220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A sporadic electrical short plagues the squad but Roy and John are convinced they can fix it. A back-to-nature couple is ordered to cut back on their shrubbery; the wife is discovered to have a variant of anthrax. The paramedics rescue a man trapped at the top of a tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917220000 +0000" stop="20250917223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917223000 +0000" stop="20250917230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917230000 +0000" stop="20250917233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250917233000 +0000" stop="20250918000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918000000 +0000" stop="20250918003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie's Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy pays attention to a fatherless new boy in town, which makes Opie jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918003000 +0000" stop="20250918010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Crusader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and most of the women in town rally against Andy when he tries to evict a much-beloved butter and egg man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918010000 +0000" stop="20250918013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is looking for a beau for his gorgeous daughter, so Drysdale and Jane set Elly up with Fred Penrod, a young accountant at the bank. However, no one can seem to get his name straight. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns to plant a paw-paw tree in the back yard, really to look for the Clampett fortune he still believes is buried in the back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918013000 +0000" stop="20250918020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Minds His Sergeant's Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter asks Gomer to drive his car straight home from the airport after dropping him off. But sure enough, the car gets stolen, and Gomer has just one day to find it—or suffer the consequences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918020000 +0000" stop="20250918023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The 43rd, A Moving Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Plans to destroy an anti-aircraft battery are upset by Klink's new executive officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918023000 +0000" stop="20250918030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918030000 +0000" stop="20250918033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Michele Lee</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Michele Lee. Originally aired on 04/13/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918033000 +0000" stop="20250918043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Paper Bullets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is caught between rival political families when the wife of a campaigning senator is accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918043500 +0000" stop="20250918050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>To Serve Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kanamits, nine-foot-tall aliens, arrive on Earth with one lofty goal: To Serve Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918050500 +0000" stop="20250918053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Schartz-metterklume Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a governess at the Wellington household has surprising results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918053500 +0000" stop="20250918060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of Credit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A researcher comes to a small-town bank to find out what happened at a robbery years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918060500 +0000" stop="20250918070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Odds Against Donald Jordan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find missing building contractor Donald Jordan. He gets poor help from the man's partner, wife and sister. Each offers a different reason for his disappearance. When Jordan reappears, he assures Mannix that he's fine and asks him to drop the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918070500 +0000" stop="20250918080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918080500 +0000" stop="20250918090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Desperate Pursuit, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's testimony in a trial puts herself in danger and gives her attention from an impressed reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918090000 +0000" stop="20250918093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918093000 +0000" stop="20250918100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918100000 +0000" stop="20250918103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 153 -- Find Me A Needle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for the "Mulholland Mauler," who has raped six female hitchhikers and left them for dead. They quickly make an arrest of a likely suspect and take him to the location of an abandoned vehicle, after learning its owner never made it to her destination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918103000 +0000" stop="20250918110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 52 -- Good Cop: Handle With Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see a man passed out in an alley and stop to lend assistance, deliver bad news to a young wife, apprehend a mentally ill man who then becomes uncontrollably violent in their patrol car, and respond to a robbery that needlessly becomes a tragedy. All along the way the officers have their every move second guessed by a pair of young, unethical freelance journalists who are determined to document police brutality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918110000 +0000" stop="20250918120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Flavors</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918120000 +0000" stop="20250918123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Car Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows his car to be driven by Lumpy, who must get Eddie, Wally and Beaver to a sporting event in a neighboring town. However, on the way back, Lumpy disobeys Ward's orders and takes a shortcut home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918123000 +0000" stop="20250918130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Baby-sitter</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Wally has a previous engagement and is unable to babysit, Beaver fills in and quickly finds himself the object of a 10-year old's affection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918130000 +0000" stop="20250918140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prodigal Parent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>When Philip Larkin, the owner of an import-export company, is murdered, his step-father, Joseph Harrison, is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918140000 +0000" stop="20250918150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Mother  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A mother confesses to a murder to protect her daughter, but Matlock soon sees through the ruse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918150000 +0000" stop="20250918160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Bug, Lady Bug</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>With the Chief in Quantico Bubba and Virgil try to catch a serial arsonist. Things get complicated after a man dies in one of the fires. And Councilwoman White stirs things up by appointing Tom Dugan acting chief of police in Gillespie's absence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918160000 +0000" stop="20250918170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Portrait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Erin meets a painter who wants to paint her portrait.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918170000 +0000" stop="20250918180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bently</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Chester doubts a man's deathbed murder confession, so he sets out to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918180000 +0000" stop="20250918190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Grand Swing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben takes Jake on an extended tour of the Ponderosa to teach him a lesson after his recklessness destroys a wagon, killing a horse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918190000 +0000" stop="20250918193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Which Way'd They Go?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The notoriously lazy Jackman brothers discover their mortgage has been foreclosed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918193000 +0000" stop="20250918200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Tony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and his girlfriend, Laurie, discover that an old hermit is very lonely.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918200000 +0000" stop="20250918210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jim Bridger Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"An Army general announces he is taking over the wagon train and requiring all members to act as soldiers in helping him rescue a trapped cavalry garrison of 120 men who are otherwise likely to be slaughtered by hostile Utes. Flint, temporarily in charge of the wagon train, has little choice but to agree to the general's demand, as much as he hates it and his passengers want him to fight back. Particularly upsetting to Flint is learning that the man who recommended this takeover was Jim Bridger, a legendary frontiersman and scout who mostly raised Flint and whom he ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918210000 +0000" stop="20250918220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Family Ties</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy's mother-in-law is scheduled for her annual visit. A car runs into the back of a truck. Drs. Brackett and Early argue over attending a convention in Acapulco. An elderly man becomes ill from drinking a quack’s remedy. When a fire breaks out in a hospital room, the occupant goes into cardiac arrest. A boy’s model rocket sparks a house fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918220000 +0000" stop="20250918223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918223000 +0000" stop="20250918230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918230000 +0000" stop="20250918233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250918233000 +0000" stop="20250919000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919000000 +0000" stop="20250919003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919003000 +0000" stop="20250919010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear when he takes it upon himself to turn Ernest T. into a presentable gentleman. The big test comes at Mrs. Wiley's weekly reception, at which Andy passes him off as his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919010000 +0000" stop="20250919013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro In The Reserve</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny still believes she captured the real Ulysses S. Grant, still unsure that he is an actor in a movie. Granny also thinks that Colonel Blake is responsible for starting the second Civil War. Granny is upset at Blake, as well as Drysdale, for running away from battle. Drysdale tries to get in good with Granny by replacing Grant’s picture on the fifty-dollar bill with General Lee and tells her he captured Grant. Of course, she knows better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919013000 +0000" stop="20250919020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, The Peace Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Bunny gets mad once again at Sgt. Carter, he sends Gomer in to explain what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919020000 +0000" stop="20250919023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Psychic Kommandant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink he has ESP in order to get the plans to a new airplane with a silent engine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919023000 +0000" stop="20250919030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Prince From The Phone Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>An African prince comes to Stalag 13 to negotiate with the Germans for the rights to build a submarine base in his country. Hogan replaces him with Kinchloe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919030000 +0000" stop="20250919033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 05/04/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919033000 +0000" stop="20250919043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Scandalous Sculptor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Scandal rocks the art world when a model is found dead, presumably murdered by the jealous wife of a sculptor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919043500 +0000" stop="20250919050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man possessing the power of transformation tries to help a crippled little girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919050500 +0000" stop="20250919053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Escape To Sonoita</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Two kidnappers find a tanker in the middle of the desert and decide to make their escape in it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919053500 +0000" stop="20250919060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hooked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A man schemes with a young woman to get rid of his wealthy wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919060500 +0000" stop="20250919070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Wasn’t There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An old adversary from Mannix's time serving in the Korean War, whom he thought was dead, sets out to kill him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919070500 +0000" stop="20250919080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Missing At Fl307</sub-title>
    <desc>"An ex-convict boards an airplane in Atlanta for a reunion with his daughter but when the plane lands he's nowhere to be found."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919080500 +0000" stop="20250919090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Design For Madness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tries to help her emotionally disturbed niece when she's suspected of murdering her husband and his lawyer during memory lapses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919090000 +0000" stop="20250919093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919093000 +0000" stop="20250919100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919100000 +0000" stop="20250919103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919103000 +0000" stop="20250919110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919110000 +0000" stop="20250919120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Masquerade Ball</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony recieve a mysterious invitation."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919120000 +0000" stop="20250919123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Younger Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to join the basketball team but finds himself trying to live up to Wally's performance. However, after not making the team, Beaver allows his family to believe that he did.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919123000 +0000" stop="20250919130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Typewriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Seeing an ad for typewriters on sale, Beaver talks his parents into letting him get one as long as he learns how to use it. However, Beaver discovers learning to type is not as easy as it looks and soon finds himself making a deal with the shady Eddie Haskell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919130000 +0000" stop="20250919140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Black-eyed Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A visit from an attractive blonde sporting a black eye segues into a case concerning a wealthy man's long-lost grandson and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919140000 +0000" stop="20250919150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Madam  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a blackmailing call girl is charged with murder, Matlock is hired to bring the real killer to justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919150000 +0000" stop="20250919160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Pig Woman Of Sparta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>It seems that a serial killer has been burying his victims in a wooded area owned by a wealthy hermit that Virgil refers to as "Sparta's Howard Hughes". Suspicion immediately falls on an eccentric woman who lives in the woods with her pigs and chases away trespassers with a shotgun. The officers ask the landowner's disturbed son for help and Bubba is surprised to find that a woman he attended high school with is working as the man's "nurse". Also Parker and Sweet compete with one another to solve the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919160000 +0000" stop="20250919170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Captive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth Godsey feels trapped by her unchanging life on Walton's Mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919170000 +0000" stop="20250919180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging Of Newly O'brien</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly attempts to save a hillbilly's life by using drastic measures. The family wants to hang Newly after the man dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919180000 +0000" stop="20250919190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hoss helps send a man to prison, his wife insists that Hoss should be made responsible for their son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919190000 +0000" stop="20250919193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sharpshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain and his son, Mark, arrive in North Fork, New Mexico. Looking to start a new life, they come across a ranch that is to their liking, which is for sale. Lucas enters a Turkey Shoot in hopes of winning the down payment for the ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919193000 +0000" stop="20250919200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Home Ranch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two hired hands of a wealthy cattleman, who has been using the ranch for grazing his cattle, demand that Lucas move out. When Lucas refuses, he is beaten and dragged and then the ranch house is burned down."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919200000 +0000" stop="20250919210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Eleanor Culhane Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>"Flint goes to visit Eleanor Culhane, an old flame of his who had been married to a notorious gunman. He finds everyone in the town she lives in shunning her, and unwilling to discuss her, because they blame her for her husband's misdeeds and the shame he caused the town. When Flint finds her they begin to rekindle their romance. But then her husband, thought dead for the last five years, shows up in town. And Flint realizes there is another side to Eleanor that he was unaware of as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919210000 +0000" stop="20250919220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Bottom Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Paramedics out in the field begin to question the judgment of overcautious Dr. Morton who believes in acting strictly by the book. The firemen respond to a complaint of severe back pain. A man with phosphorous burns on his arm and a boy hit in the head with a baseball are treated at the hospital. While the firemen respond to a case of difficult breathing, the victim’s neighbor drowns in a hot tub. Vince is involved in a traffic accident and goes crazy due to a head injury, pulling his gun on Johnny.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919220000 +0000" stop="20250919223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919223000 +0000" stop="20250919230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919230000 +0000" stop="20250919233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250919233000 +0000" stop="20250920000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920000000 +0000" stop="20250920003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady prisoner woos Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920003000 +0000" stop="20250920010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920010000 +0000" stop="20250920013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cimarron Drip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is hoping to get a part in Dash Riprock’s new TV series, getting a whole new image. Little does Dash know, the show, which is a rehash of every successful show since 1948, didn’t make it, and the female lead, Debbie Dimples, has impossible demands. Drysdale suggests that they use a monkey, Elly’s chimp Cousin, Bessie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920013000 +0000" stop="20250920020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, Pow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>On maneuvers, Sgt. Carter gives Gomer false information, hoping he'll be captured by the enemy camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920020000 +0000" stop="20250920023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920023000 +0000" stop="20250920030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Fat Hermann, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get a trainload of stolen paintings back to London, but things get complicated when Marya uses Schultz to impersonate Reich Marshall Goehring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920030000 +0000" stop="20250920033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/14/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920033000 +0000" stop="20250920043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sleepy Slayer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is accused of killing his employer, who still owed him $50,000 for an accident years before, it's up to Mason to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920043500 +0000" stop="20250920050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>To her parents' horror, a six-year-old girl vanishes into the fourth dimension after rolling under her bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920050500 +0000" stop="20250920053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Young One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenager’s desire to be free leads her to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920053500 +0000" stop="20250920060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Doubtful Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A man relates an unusual situation to his doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920060500 +0000" stop="20250920070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Principle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Two elderly spinster sisters are determined to prosecute a traffic violator. There's only one problem: The man also is a syndicate killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920070500 +0000" stop="20250920080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Set-up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is a victim of mistaken identity and later almost killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920080500 +0000" stop="20250920090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Girl On The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway girl discovers that the glitter of the drug world has a deadly underside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920090000 +0000" stop="20250920093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. government top-secret camera falls out a plane and lands in the Shady Rest. Little does anyone know, the curious device could bring them "explosive" problems.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
