<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309190000 +0000" stop="20250309193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Wrongway Feldman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Gilligan finds an old airplane hidden in the jungle, the castaways discover a long-forgotten aviator who lives on the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309193000 +0000" stop="20250309200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>President Gilligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways hold elections to decide who shall be the leader of the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309200000 +0000" stop="20250309203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher's Pet  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When her home cooking isn't enough to win over her crush, Mama turns to aping Naomi's seductive body language to attract his affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309203000 +0000" stop="20250309210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Child's Play  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The Harper family is asked to watch the grandson of the Reverend and Mrs. Meechum, an eight-year-old brat who pushes Mama over the edge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309210000 +0000" stop="20250309220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Mind My Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend's wife makes passes at Doc; a man records his friend's romances; an engaged woman meets an old school chum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309220000 +0000" stop="20250309223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie's Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy pays attention to a fatherless new boy in town, which makes Opie jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309223000 +0000" stop="20250309230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Props/costumes- Wally Wingert</sub-title>
    <desc>"Voice actor and puppeteer Wally Wingert has a joyful obsession with the pop culture of the '60s through the 1980s, so much so that he's turned his Los Angeles home into what he calls "Wallywood": a virtual musem of treasures including Jack Lord's "Hawaii 5-O" ensemble (complete with height-enhancing boots), the actual passport of Ed McMahon (Wally's predecessor as "Tonight Show" announcer), the very first licensed Kermit puppet (from before he was even a frog), and the iconic stage costume of comedy legend Andy Kaufman... plus so much more! Lisa's invited "Collector's Call" favorite Rob Klein to put a value on Wally's entire collection... then to try to tempt him into a trade, an offer that comes down to a very small piece of colored resin with a very big '60s TV connection!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309230000 +0000" stop="20250309233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp is under fire and is swamped with wounded. They are being attacked by their own artillery in a frightening "friendly fire" incident. After Trapper and Margaret get trapped in the supply tent together, Frank's jealousy of Trapper drives him to propose to Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250309233000 +0000" stop="20250310000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bulletin Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Camp activities include Henry's nervous delivery of a sex lecture, with Hawkeye and Trapper heckling, a Shirley Temple movie and a cookout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310000000 +0000" stop="20250310003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Gives Blood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike is set to go down to the blood bank to donate some blood and asks Archie if he would like to donate. Dead set against it, Archie refuses to donate blood because he's afraid that his vital fluids might get mixed in with those of a different race. After some coaxing, Mike gets Archie to come to the blood bank, but Archie takes one look at some blood and passes out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310003000 +0000" stop="20250310010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Judging Books By Covers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roger, a friend of Mike and Gloria's, stops by for a visit. Archie takes one look at him and labels him as gay due to what Archie considers effeminate behavior, even though Mike insists that he isn't. Mike soon makes a realization that one of Archie's drinking buddies, Steve is actually a well-adjusted, sports loving, straight-acting, gay man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310010000 +0000" stop="20250310013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Has A Belly Full</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria comes home from the doctor with some news: she's pregnant. This leads to a big argument between Archie and Mike so Mike decides to quit school and move out. Archie doesn't believe him, that is until Mike gets a job in Detroit and plans on moving there. However, plans for a move are suddenly halted when Gloria suffers a miscarriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310013000 +0000" stop="20250310020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Hippie Friends Come To Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Just before leaving on a flight to Europe, Mike's hippie friends need a place to stay for the night. Mike invites them to stay in the Bunker's living room, however, Archie objects citing that no unmarried couple will spend the night together under his roof. But a night of arguing begins to take its toll on everyone, as the fighting begins to stretch into the early morning hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310020000 +0000" stop="20250310023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Torchy Song</sub-title>
    <desc>In Torchy Song, the gang parodies the classic film, with Carol playing a demanding Joan Crawford on a warpath.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310023000 +0000" stop="20250310030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Stop Grabbing My Jewels</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball plans a secret party for Mrs. Wiggins, who per usual, doesn't understand. Then, in Stop Grabbing My Jewels, Tim tries to steal a priceless diamond, with explosive results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310030000 +0000" stop="20250310033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Two Show-offs And Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob, Buddy and Sally let their egos get the best of them when a reporter is going to interview them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310033000 +0000" stop="20250310040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stretch Petrie Vs. Kid Schenk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An opportunistic old friend causes problems for Rob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310040000 +0000" stop="20250310043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310043000 +0000" stop="20250310050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jeopardy Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A former KGB officer trying to defect finds himself trapped in a room with a bomb—and three hours before it detonates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310050000 +0000" stop="20250310060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Forecast: Low Clouds And Coastal Fog  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A lady is plunged into a nightmare after she refuses to help a man and his badly beaten girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310060000 +0000" stop="20250310070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The propaganda minister of Suroq, Vassier, is preparing to pardon Ismet El Kabir, a ruthless terrorist whom he secretly supports. The IMF must make sure El Kabir is never released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310070000 +0000" stop="20250310080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Chariot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble happens to watch a TV debate in which a once-renowned attorney, named G. Stanley Lazer, claims that he could reverse Kimble's criminal conviction if the case went back to trial. Lazer once a respected lawyer, had his license revoked after getting i</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310080000 +0000" stop="20250310090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Material Witness</sub-title>
    <desc>"Pressed into service by the police, Harry Orwell must protect an eyewitness against attempts to assassinate her before she can testify against a murderer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310090000 +0000" stop="20250310093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310093000 +0000" stop="20250310100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310100000 +0000" stop="20250310103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up One L-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While transporting a burglar to the station with Malloy's assistance, Sgt. MacDonald strikes and kills a jaywalker with his cruiser, but unfortunately all of the witnesses on the sidewalk inexplicably claim she was in the crosswalk. With the burglar unmotivated to testify on MacDonald's behalf, Malloy has to take it upon himself to clear his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310103000 +0000" stop="20250310110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Who Won?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed try to curb a chronic street racing problem by befriending the club leaders and working with a racing promoter to open a legitimate drag strip. Their efforts, along with a highly anticipated race between reed and officer wells, are put in</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310110000 +0000" stop="20250310120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The North Star State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony continue their Trekkin' All 50 tour of the United States with a visit to Minnesota."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310120000 +0000" stop="20250310123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While his class is reciting a poem about trees, Beaver remembers a tree that Ward had given him for his birthday when they lived at their old house. Wanting "his" tree back, Beaver and Larry go to Beaver's old home and promptly dig it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310123000 +0000" stop="20250310130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Comes To Dinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a surprise when June invites Miss Landers over for dinner and Larry convinces him that something bad might happen. This leads Beaver to become a nervous wreck as he tries to make sure his parents don't do anything to embarrass him. Meanwhile, Larry charges a quarter to anyone who wants to spy on Miss Landers eating dinner at the Cleavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310130000 +0000" stop="20250310140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of Constant Doyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After the death of her husband and partner, Joe Doyle, Constant Doyle takes on a case involving a young man who knew her husband. She asks for Mason's help and he suggests she hire the Paul Drake Detective agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310140000 +0000" stop="20250310150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Final Affair: Part 1  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to figure out whether the archbishop was meant to die in a plot involving an ex-football player, his wife, her lover and the mafia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310150000 +0000" stop="20250310160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Pig Woman Of Sparta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>It seems that a serial killer has been burying his victims in a wooded area owned by a wealthy hermit that Virgil refers to as "Sparta's Howard Hughes". Suspicion immediately falls on an eccentric woman who lives in the woods with her pigs and chases away trespassers with a shotgun. The officers ask the landowner's disturbed son for help and Bubba is surprised to find that a woman he attended high school with is working as the man's "nurse". Also Parker and Sweet compete with one another to solve the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310160000 +0000" stop="20250310170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy falls in love with Jenny Pendelton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310170000 +0000" stop="20250310173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Obie Tater</sub-title>
    <desc>"An old prospector named Obie Tater causes trouble for himself, his bride, and Matt when he refuses to tell where his fortune of gold is hidden."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310173000 +0000" stop="20250310180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Night Incident</sub-title>
    <desc>"Little Timmy Wyatt witnesses a series of bizarre murders. He has a habit of telling tall tales, so no one will believe him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310180000 +0000" stop="20250310190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Her Brother's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben falls for Claire Amory but her invalid brother might end up tossing a monkey wrench into the romance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310190000 +0000" stop="20250310193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of A Young Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is forced to give refuge to Will Fulton, a young bank robber who was injured while saving Mark's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310193000 +0000" stop="20250310200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310200000 +0000" stop="20250310210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Richard Bloodgood Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"A blind man called Sangre has joined the wagon train along with his guide. He is actually Coop's boyhood blood brother Richard Bloodgood, and he openly states his plan to kill Coop. Coop gets very hostile and refuses to discuss it whenever Charlie or Barnaby ask the reason Richard wants to kill him, but they know it has to do with the death of a beautiful woman long ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310210000 +0000" stop="20250310220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Ends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny tries to win a ticket-selling contest. Dr. Backett blames himself when he is involved in a car accident that leaves the other driver dead and The driver's daughter refuses to speak. While repairing the squad, the paramedics find themselves in the middle of a shootout and treat a policeman with heart trouble. A boxcar full of ammonia complicates a fire on a pier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310220000 +0000" stop="20250310223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Consultant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Borelli visits the 4077th to demonstrate his artery transplant technique. Unfortunately, being so close to the front at the 4077th causes Borelli's drinking problem to interfere at the worst time—when a patient needs the transplant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310223000 +0000" stop="20250310230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>House Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye hits Major Burns and Houlihan is a witness. Despite Hawkeye and Trapper's claims that it wasn't intentional, Frank makes allegations against Hawkeye, and he is put in house arrest facing court martial. A female colonel is sent to inspect the nurses. When she cries "Rape!" when Burns visits her tent, Houlihan recants her story, and Burns, not Hawkeye, ends up under house arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310230000 +0000" stop="20250310233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Aid Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye, Houlihan and Klinger go to an aid station at the front. Working closely together under heavy fire and unsanitary medical conditions, the three return to camp with new found respect for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250310233000 +0000" stop="20250311000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love And Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper prevent a GI from marrying a call girl who has TB, while trying to help a Korean soldier join his pregnant wife. Radar, of course, provides his usual invaluable help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311000000 +0000" stop="20250311003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Crusader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee and most of the women in town rally against Andy when he tries to evict a much-beloved butter and egg man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311003000 +0000" stop="20250311010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311010000 +0000" stop="20250311013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Diner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed thinks that it is time for Jethro to start in the business world, and Jethro decides to become a fry cook and open his own restaurant. Jed is okay with this, but when he tells Drysdale, he is unsure because he is afraid of losing some of the Clampett money. The banker does end up buying Jethro a place on Restaurant Row, but the building is a wreck, with rent only thirty-five a month. Jethro is just glad to have a place of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311013000 +0000" stop="20250311020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is pleased when asked to be one of three busboys for a visiting colonel. But his attention is turned to the officer's sad little daughter, who is lonely and needs a playmate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311020000 +0000" stop="20250311023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Axis Annie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use a propaganda radio announcer to get information to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311023000 +0000" stop="20250311030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>What Time Does The Balloon Go Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A basket-weaving and a kite-flying contest are part of Hogan's plan to transport an agent to England in a balloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311030000 +0000" stop="20250311033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Madeline Kahn</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Carol plays Eunice, who is determined to star in a local production, despite lacking the talent of her drama teacher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311033000 +0000" stop="20250311043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bartered Bikini</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally Dunbar seeks Mason's help in securing ownership of his new summer line of swimwear, but the sketches are stolen and, worse yet, chief designer Rick Stassi is murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311043500 +0000" stop="20250311050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover In A Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Having had a little too much to drink the night before, a young couple wakes up in a strange house in a strange town called Centerville, a place where no one lives, the trees are props and the food is plastic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311050500 +0000" stop="20250311053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Special Delivery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A little boy's hobby of growing mushrooms in his cellar turns into a nightmare.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311053500 +0000" stop="20250311060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Road Hog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman is responsible for a death when he refuses to allow a truck to pass him on a narrow road.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311060500 +0000" stop="20250311070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Hardball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A drug dealer and his gang take several hostages, hoping to force Mannix to locate and retrieve another gang member who betrayed them. Mannix fears someone's going to die no matter what he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311070500 +0000" stop="20250311080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Voice From The Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>"Reverend" Will can heal the sick by the power of faith. Or can he? Either way, his "powers" won't keep a witness to murder from coming forward, and that means... another murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311080500 +0000" stop="20250311090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Stand In For Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband kills a man he thought was his wife's lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311090000 +0000" stop="20250311093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311093000 +0000" stop="20250311100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311100000 +0000" stop="20250311103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a six-year-old boy who was apparently abducted while walking home from school, and later fear that an elderly witness's wildly inaccurate account may actually pertain to a different crime. They also respond to a barking dog complaint and become suspicious of the dog's owner, mediate a domestic dispute caused by a husband's obsession with watching football, respond to a very creative college prank and pursue armed robbery suspects through a crowded train depot with the aid of a police helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311103000 +0000" stop="20250311110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Wednesday Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed becomes preoccupied with the well being of a friend, an electrical engineer by profession, who has just qualified as a reserve police officer and has the bad luck of drawing Officer Wells as his partner. On patrol, Reed and Malloy help out a group of distrusting young adults who are planning to illegally camp in a public park after a rock concert, pull over a young couple in a stolen car and aid wells and the reservist in the foot chase of a heavily armed man who has been coercing innocent strangers into committing bank robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311110000 +0000" stop="20250311120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Take A Hike</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill braves a treacherous hike with the illusory help of Toony."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311120000 +0000" stop="20250311123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his fortune read by a machine and becomes convinced nothing but good luck is headed his way. However, he doesn't feel that way when Larry sets it up so that Beaver will have to fight a 5th grader, Sonny Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311123000 +0000" stop="20250311130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Makes A Loan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward loans Beaver 25 cents but gives him a dollar, expecting 75 cents as change. However, Larry manages to convince Beaver to loan him the 75 cents. When Larry doesn't pay him back when he said he was going to, a feud erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311130000 +0000" stop="20250311140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Libelous Locket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance student is charged with murder when her instructor is found dead after they had a physical altercation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311140000 +0000" stop="20250311150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Final Affair: Part 2  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to figure out whether the archbishop was meant to die in a plot involving an ex-football player, his wife, her lover and the mafia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311150000 +0000" stop="20250311160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie is kidnapped and Virgil believes that Tom Dugan is involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311160000 +0000" stop="20250311170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The family sets up their cousin Cody, a 64-year-old bachelor, on a date with Cordelia Hunnicutt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311170000 +0000" stop="20250311173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Smoking Out The Nolans</sub-title>
    <desc>"Clay Young is trying to evict Josh Nolan. Josh tells Matt he paid Clay for the property. Clay denies it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311173000 +0000" stop="20250311180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kites Reward</sub-title>
    <desc>"Andy Travis shoots a guy. Matt tells him you're real good with the gun, but you have a choice either put it down or you will have to constantly prove yourself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311180000 +0000" stop="20250311190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Trouble With Jamie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A visit by the Cartwrights' spoiled Eastern cousin disrupts life at the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311190000 +0000" stop="20250311193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311193000 +0000" stop="20250311200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311200000 +0000" stop="20250311210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clay Shelby Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>"With Hawks ill and Comanches threatening to attack, an Army troop meets up with the wagon train. The Indians appear to greatly outnumber the soldiers, so to give the train hope the troop's lieutenant falsely tells Hale and Coop that there is also a relief column headed their way. Complicating matters even more, a sergeant from the troop recognizes Clay Shelby, a young man on the wagon train traveling with his pregnant wife, as a deserter from back in the Civil War whom he blames for the death of his brother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311210000 +0000" stop="20250311220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>An Ounce Of Prevention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man with chest pains is trapped on a ferris wheel. A child ingests an illegal pesticide. While making a TV appearance to discuss fire prevention, Gage and DeSoto become stars of a real-life emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311220000 +0000" stop="20250311223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311223000 +0000" stop="20250311230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311230000 +0000" stop="20250311233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250311233000 +0000" stop="20250312000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Abyssinia, Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry finally gets his discharge. While he is tying things up, Burns prepares for his new command. Henry bids a tearful adieu, but not before Klinger turns up in an outrageous tropical outfit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312000000 +0000" stop="20250312003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Fair Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear when he takes it upon himself to turn Ernest T. into a presentable gentleman. The big test comes at Mrs. Wiley's weekly reception, at which Andy passes him off as his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312003000 +0000" stop="20250312010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Rod Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has Mayberry worried when he buys a car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312010000 +0000" stop="20250312013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Chickadee Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is still hoping to marry burlesque dancer Chickadee Laverne, and she is still hoping for a dance engagement from the Clampetts. Chickadee returns to the mansion, making Jethro very happy. However, her plan to show them her new act, Little Red Riding Hood, goes haywire thanks to a meddling raccoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312013000 +0000" stop="20250312020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Star Is Born</sub-title>
    <desc>"Carter becomes the star of a documentary about the Marine Corps."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312020000 +0000" stop="20250312023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lebeau And The Little Old Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau tells the others he is taking messages to a little old lady, when really she is a beautiful lady he has fallen for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312023000 +0000" stop="20250312030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Escape From Prison Camp Without Really Trying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hides 30 prisoners in order to keep the SS busy while the Allies build reinforcements.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312030000 +0000" stop="20250312033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Dinah Shore</sub-title>
    <desc>In Went with the Wind, Carol and the gang parody the classic "Gone with the Wind", with Carol playing Scarlet O'Hara.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312033000 +0000" stop="20250312043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Artful Dodger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Allen Sheridan has more enemies than you can shake a stick at, even though he's due to inherit the healthy sum of $162,000. When Allen turns up dead his killer could be anyone, but his cousin, Sarette, becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312043500 +0000" stop="20250312050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Garrity And The Graves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A man arrives in the Old West town of Happiness, Arizona, proclaiming he can revive the dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312050500 +0000" stop="20250312053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Specialty Of The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A restaurant is specialized in "serving" its costumers very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312053500 +0000" stop="20250312060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>An Occurrence At Owl Creek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A Southerner is about to be hanged for attempting to destroy a bridge vital to the Union's advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312060500 +0000" stop="20250312070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Name Is Mannix</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired by former crime boss Sam Dubrio when his daughter is kidnapped. His plan is to set up a ransom and then pay off the pickup man to turn in his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312070500 +0000" stop="20250312080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady In Red</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young dancer who teaches at a lonely hearts club winds up dead. One of his clients hires Cannot to find out who killed him. It isn't long before Frank discovers the dancer was also a con man who had bilked several women out of their life savings. And that lengthens the list of suspects considerably.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312080500 +0000" stop="20250312090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Black Art Of Dying, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tries to determine if a psychic had anything to do with a lawyer's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312090000 +0000" stop="20250312093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312093000 +0000" stop="20250312100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312100000 +0000" stop="20250312103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Dirt Duel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of purse snatching leads Malloy and Reed to investigate a motorcycle gang. Determined to convince the gang he has not prejudged them, Malloy challenges their leader to a motocross duel at Indian Dunes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312103000 +0000" stop="20250312110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy finds himself attracted to the new girl in the steno pool, and decides to ask her on a date after learning she's Officer Wells' 25-year-old niece. Out on patrol, he and Reed investigate a report of a prowler in a heavily wooded neighborhood, make a deal with a flower vendor before booking him for unpaid tickets, engage in a high-speed pursuit with a green corvette and investigate a suspicious gardener.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312110000 +0000" stop="20250312120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Rival Of The Ages Iii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two generations face off in the third edition of Rival of the Ages."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312120000 +0000" stop="20250312123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Magician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a common magic trick but is disappointed by everyone's "that's nice" reaction. He gets a totally different reaction out of Bengie, however, when Larry and Beaver convince him that Beaver has been turned into a rock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312123000 +0000" stop="20250312130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>June's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June's birthday has Wally and Beaver fighting over what to buy with the $5 dollars that Ward gave them. Wally buys her a wallet while Beaver buys an ugly blouse that June kindly thanks him for, but she has a hard time bringing herself to wear it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312130000 +0000" stop="20250312140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Two-faced Turnabout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Balkan dictator with ties to an American businessman dies, the race is on to destroy papers belonging to him that may implicate the businessman in corruption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312140000 +0000" stop="20250312150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.j.  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When radio disk jockey, and Michelle's new boyfriend, Arthur Saxon is accused of murdering a rival, Matlock agrees to defend him. Michelle swears he's the kindest, most gentle man she's ever known, but Matlock soon learns otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312150000 +0000" stop="20250312160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After being released by his captors, the chief discovers that his abduction is part of a plot to assassinate a visiting civil rights leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312160000 +0000" stop="20250312170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gypsies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A band of gypsies are traveling through Walton's Mountain when they become stranded</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312170000 +0000" stop="20250312173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunter</sub-title>
    <desc>"A buffalo hunter, Jase Murdock, is warned by Ross the storekeeper to stay out of Indian Territory."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312173000 +0000" stop="20250312180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <desc>"After two bullies cut off Chen's pig-tail (queue), the man vows vengeance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312180000 +0000" stop="20250312190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Shining In Spain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe falls for a girl whose filled with stories of her absent father and his many adventures.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312190000 +0000" stop="20250312193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Italian count arrives in North Fork, his strange attire attracts the attention of Groder, a town bully. Groder, trying to have fun with this stranger, destroys some of the count's currency, mocks him and tries to humiliate him. Eventually the count challenges Groder to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312193000 +0000" stop="20250312200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Floyd Doniger comes to North Fork, looking to start a new life. He's got a steady job as the guard at the new bank and he's entertaining ideas of settling down on a spread of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312200000 +0000" stop="20250312210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>"A little girl, crying each night, appears to be a ghost from The Donner Party. Many people hear her, but she appears each night to Charlie, who questions his own sanity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312210000 +0000" stop="20250312220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Insanity Epidemic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley freaks out when he learns one of his past captains is now his Battalion Chief, causing the others to worry about his increased paranoia. Two men’s carelessness starts a fire at a gas station. A new hospital administrator causes problems. A woman accidentally shoots her husband with a nail gun. Two clowns start a fight at an ice rink. A car leaves an overpass and crashes into a transfer truck filled with pesticides.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312220000 +0000" stop="20250312223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp. On the way back, BJ is introduced to the Korean War.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312223000 +0000" stop="20250312230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312230000 +0000" stop="20250312233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Command</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank settles in as commanding officer, only to have a new one appointed over his head, one that, to his chagrin, fits in very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250312233000 +0000" stop="20250313000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>It Happened One Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It happened one night: freezing cold, an artillery barrage that's coming too close, a patient going downhill and Frank's searching Hot Lips' tent for his letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313000000 +0000" stop="20250313003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Song Festers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's singing voice surprises everyone, especially Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313003000 +0000" stop="20250313010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313010000 +0000" stop="20250313013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Are Overdrawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing the pool man putting chlorine in the pool, thinking it is poison, and getting a letter they are overdrawn, the Clampetts think that they are broke and Drysdale is trying to get rid of them. However, this is all a misunderstanding, since the letter Jed got was meant for another J.D. Clampett, Jake, who is an out-of-work actor. When Jake gets Jed’s letter, he takes advantage of the notice that he has $36 million dollars, buying a new car and other things.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313013000 +0000" stop="20250313020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Phone Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries to repay the $40 he received at a pay phone to the phone company, but gets arrested instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313020000 +0000" stop="20250313023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Collector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a fortune in paintings from winding up in the collection of a general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313023000 +0000" stop="20250313030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Ultimate Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send German defenses to the wrong target by "giving" Schultz ESP so that the Allies can bomb an important target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313030000 +0000" stop="20250313033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Sammy Davis Jr.</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Slave Ship, a carpetbagger stages a revolt against the tough gallery master. Then, in Her Majesty and the Mob, Queen Carol announces a 128 percent tax increase to the locals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313033000 +0000" stop="20250313043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lucky Legs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Marjorie Cluny wins a contest for best-looking legs sponsored by Frank Patton of Stellar Productions. Her prize is a trip to Hollywood and a role in Patton's next picture. Unfortunately, there was fine print in Marjorie's contract that she didn't read.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313043500 +0000" stop="20250313050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Brain Center At Whipple's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A heartless CEO completely automates his factory, laying off all of his employees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313050500 +0000" stop="20250313053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Graduating Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A teacher gets too involved in the life of one of her students.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313053500 +0000" stop="20250313060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Wet Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A vulnerable man is pinned with a murder he did not commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313060500 +0000" stop="20250313070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Skid Marks On A Dry Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>People begin to be killed off after Mannix is hired to drub up information that could hurt a politician's chances of being elected governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313070500 +0000" stop="20250313080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Kathy Ackers hires Cannon to find out why her father, a banker, committed suicide at a Caribbean resort. She thinks he was murdered, and wants Cannon to prove it. But the man was embezzling from his own bank, so maybe he did have a motive to kill himself...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313080500 +0000" stop="20250313090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The prime suspect in a jewel heist is robbed of his gems, his spouse and his life by his own lawyer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313090000 +0000" stop="20250313093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313093000 +0000" stop="20250313100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313100000 +0000" stop="20250313103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Airdrop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While on duty in a rural area, Reed and Malloy request the assistance of the DEA to build a case against the smug pilot of a light plane whom they suspect is involved in a drug smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313103000 +0000" stop="20250313110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lost And Found</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed transport an unconscious 8-year-old boy to Rampart General Hospital and help him and his parents cope with the ordeal. Afterwards, they assist a child welfare hotline operator locate a 15-year-old girl who has intentionally overdosed on pills, and then race to find the boy they brought in earlier after he escapes from the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313110000 +0000" stop="20250313120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Art Of The Con</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony look at some of the biggest cons and conartists of all time!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313120000 +0000" stop="20250313123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tire Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants to raise chinchillas and begins building a cage in the garage. However, when Beaver changes his mind, Ward tries his best to get Wally and Beaver to clean up the mess. Things get worse when Ward unknowingly runs over some of the wood and nails left laying around with the car, causing the boys to try to patch a flat tire before Ward finds out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313123000 +0000" stop="20250313130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry Hides Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver is staying at the Mondellos, Larry sneaks a peak at his sister's diary and his mother discovers him and yells at him right in front of Beaver. This prompts Larry to run away to Beaver's house, where Beaver secretly hides him in his bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313130000 +0000" stop="20250313140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Surplus Suitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a wealthy heiress' uncle is found dead, she is charged with the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313140000 +0000" stop="20250313150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Play  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an actress is murdered, Matlock represents her director in a community theatre play—on the grounds that Matlock won't be cut from his role in the production!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313150000 +0000" stop="20250313160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Rape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil struggles to help Althea after she is raped by a fellow teacher. Darnell does not think they can get a conviction because the man's wife has given him an alibi. Virgil tries to control his anger - until the man returns to intimidate Althea. And Gillespie tries to convince the wife to tell the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313160000 +0000" stop="20250313170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Deed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The validity of the Waltons' claim to their land is questioned when they cannot produce a legal deed to the property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313170000 +0000" stop="20250313173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>General Parcley Smith</sub-title>
    <desc>"Old-timer Smith is a former Army officer considered a butcher. He arrives in Dodge City spreading rumors about the new Banker, Drew Holt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313173000 +0000" stop="20250313180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Magnus</sub-title>
    <desc>"Chester is concerned when his nomadic and "uncivilized" brother pays a Christmas visit to Dodge, but Magnus Goode proves worldlier and more adaptable to town life than anyone thought possible."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313180000 +0000" stop="20250313190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss tries to help an alcoholic poet stay on the wagon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313190000 +0000" stop="20250313193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313193000 +0000" stop="20250313200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiffauges, a wealthy and sadistic Frenchman who is used to getting whatever he wants, decides he wishes to purchase the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges' lead man, Xavier, proclaims Lucas to be muy macho, and does not believe Lucas will give in so easily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313200000 +0000" stop="20250313210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hector Heatherton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"Charlie has finally found someone else who shares his dream of man being able to fly, henpecked inventor Hector Heatherton, who has been working on an idea for building a flying machine so Charlie volunteers to build a machine for Hector."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313210000 +0000" stop="20250313220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A sporadic electrical short plagues the squad but Roy and John are convinced they can fix it. A back-to-nature couple is ordered to cut back on their shrubbery; the wife is discovered to have a variant of anthrax. The paramedics rescue a man trapped at the top of a tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313220000 +0000" stop="20250313223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Captain Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye's father is notified that he's dead, he finds it's no easy matter either to get word to him or to establish otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313223000 +0000" stop="20250313230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Doc</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Its quid pro quo at the 4077th: two bottles of Scotch for secret surgery, and a tank to scare off snipers for an unauthorized shot of penicillin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313230000 +0000" stop="20250313233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving back from a medical conference, Radar, Hawkeye, B.J., Sherman and Frank find themselves lost. When they decide to turn around, the bus does not want to start. And when Radar goes off in the middle of the night for the latrine, he does not immediately return.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250313233000 +0000" stop="20250314000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Mildred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Potter's anniversary. While Potter writes home, Frank and Hot Lips have a wood carving made for him, and Radar rescues a horse and makes him a present of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314000000 +0000" stop="20250314003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314003000 +0000" stop="20250314010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314010000 +0000" stop="20250314013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Opal Clampett are continuing to stay at the Clampett mansion, and Elly and Jethro are more than happy to serve them. But Granny isn’t impressed by Jake at all, and isn’t even sure if Jake is related to Jed. Jethro and Elly both decide they want to get into the movie business, and the two get help from Jake and Opal. Jethro turns into a Marlon Brando-type and Elly fancies herself a glamorous movie star, taking the name Venus Adore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314013000 +0000" stop="20250314020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Church Organ</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clara and Andy get everyone in Mayberry to promise to pledge money for a new church organ, no one wants to pay up when the pledges come due.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314020000 +0000" stop="20250314023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets a stray chimpanzee to deliver radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314023000 +0000" stop="20250314030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Drums Along The Dusseldorf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan mines a bridge, he learns that a truck of Allied prisoners would be the first to cross it and a new plan is born which includes a flaming arrow from Sioux Indian Carter, aka Little Deer Who Goes Swift And Sure Through Forest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314030000 +0000" stop="20250314033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary, Quite Contrary, Carol and the gang parodies "Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman". Then, in Do Not Disturb, a dog-tired Tim just wants to sleep, but his noisy neighbors fight next door.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314033000 +0000" stop="20250314043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Violent Village</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On a fishing trip in a small Sierra Nevada town with his old friend, Sheriff Gene Norris, Mason gets sidetracked into a murder case when Phil Beecher returns from jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314043500 +0000" stop="20250314050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Come Wander With Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A singer searches for an authentic folk song.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314050500 +0000" stop="20250314053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Ikon Of Elijah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's dream of wealth takes form when he learns of a treasure buried in the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314053500 +0000" stop="20250314060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A South American native helps his boss' wife when it's evident that she needs a shrink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314060500 +0000" stop="20250314070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing Ever Works Twice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an old flame is found dead, Mannix is named the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314070500 +0000" stop="20250314080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Private eyes so rarely get a vacation free of peril, and Cannon is no exception. He goes fishing, little knowing that someone from his police past is hunting him: a murderer determined on revenge for the time he spent in prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314080500 +0000" stop="20250314090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a plane crash that resulted in a corporation president's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314090000 +0000" stop="20250314093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314093000 +0000" stop="20250314100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314100000 +0000" stop="20250314103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After completing a hazardous driving refresher course, Sgt. MacDonald assigns Malloy and Reed to a nighttime undercover bicycle patrol to test Officer Wells' idea on how to deal with a rash of residential car break-ins. The next day, they pull over a hippie with an obnoxious passenger, and then put their refreshed driving skills to the test when called to a burglary in progress at a new car showroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314103000 +0000" stop="20250314110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Badge Heavy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed puts his reputation on the line when he decides to file a formal complaint against a fellow officer after witnessing him use excessive force. On patrol, he and Malloy search for suspects in two separate robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314110000 +0000" stop="20250314120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Do The Math</sub-title>
    <desc>"It's Pi Day! Bill signs up for a trial that makes him a super genius... or something like that."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314120000 +0000" stop="20250314123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Pet Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pet fair at school has Beaver feeling left out because he doesn't have a pet, but he tells everyone he does, a parrot. Meanwhile, Ward tries to find a pet for Beaver and buys him a hamster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314123000 +0000" stop="20250314130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An upcoming test in history, Wally's weakest subject, has Wally studying all weekend and has Larry and Eddie coming up with a plan that will give them good grades on the test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314130000 +0000" stop="20250314140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Oranges</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason goes to the dogs when his defense of a murder suspect hinges on a surprise witness—a dog named Hard Tack. It seems as though Hard Tack holds the key to the murder of a developer who planned to bulldoze orange groves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314140000 +0000" stop="20250314150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Police Officer Jim Shanley is found dead, Sergeant Jerry Reese is charged with the crime. Everyone thinks he's guilty, especially Shanley's partner. In defending Reese, Matlock begins to realize that an old cop buddy of his isn't the man he used to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314150000 +0000" stop="20250314160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fairest Of Them All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A beauty contest is marred by blackmail and the ambitious mother of a contestant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314160000 +0000" stop="20250314170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Scholar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Verdie Grant learns her daughter is graduating from college, she feels embarrassed by the fact that she never learned to read or write.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314170000 +0000" stop="20250314173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Reed Survives</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucy also professes her love for handsome Booth Rider, and concocts a scheme in which Ephram is the intended victim. Booth becomes the unwitting pawn in a homicide that culminates in an ironic twist of fate."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314173000 +0000" stop="20250314180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Professor Lute Bone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc is so angered by a traveling medicine man and his opium elixir that he wants to get a gun and shoot him. When a fellow comes to town trying to kill Professor Lute Bone because his father died drinking his elixir, Bone decides that it's time to give up the patent medicine business."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314180000 +0000" stop="20250314190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Unwritten Commandment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben tries to bring an estranged father and son back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314190000 +0000" stop="20250314193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Apprentice Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Willard is filling in as temporary marshal while Micah is away. Some Texas cowhands are in North Fork looking for some fun and relaxation, but Dan keeps coming down hard on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314193000 +0000" stop="20250314200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark, returning from selling their herd, share the stagecoach trip with a Marshal and his prisoner, Johnny Cotton. Johnny's gang arrives to free their partner and steal the contents of the stage's strongbox, as well as Lucas' money and rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314200000 +0000" stop="20250314210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Echo Pass Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>"While out looking for water Coop and Charlie are stopped by a gang of five, including two women, who are on the run after robbing a bank and killing three lawmen. The leader of the gang shoots Charlie after tying him up, and they take Coop to lead them through a mountain pass to get to California."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314210000 +0000" stop="20250314220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Family Ties</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy's mother-in-law is scheduled for her annual visit. A car runs into the back of a truck. Drs. Brackett and Early argue over attending a convention in Acapulco. An elderly man becomes ill from drinking a quack’s remedy. When a fire breaks out in a hospital room, the occupant goes into cardiac arrest. A boy’s model rocket sparks a house fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314220000 +0000" stop="20250314223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th plays host to kids bombed out of their orphanage, and at the same time has to deliver a baby and care for battle casualties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314223000 +0000" stop="20250314230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Peggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. writes home to his wife, Peg, reporting Klinger's escape attempts, the visit of a formidable chaplain and one of Frank's goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314230000 +0000" stop="20250314233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Of Moose And Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tangles with a tough Army colonel, Colonel Spiker; B.J. helps Zale, who's received a Dear John letter; and Frank looks endlessly for Korean saboteurs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250314233000 +0000" stop="20250315000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Soldier Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has a fever and makes a will, leaving all his money to his wife and all his clothes to Hot Lips.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315000000 +0000" stop="20250315003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315003000 +0000" stop="20250315010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315010000 +0000" stop="20250315013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Turkey Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May makes a pet out of the Thanksgiving turkey Drysdale gives the family, making it impossible for "Herman" to be killed. And to celebrate in her own way, Mrs. Drysdale organizes a picture to represent the first Thanksgiving, enlisting two actors portraying Native Americans. But when they head over to the Clampetts' mansion to get the turkey for the picture, Elly and Granny think they are being attacked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315013000 +0000" stop="20250315020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Vacation In Vegas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer wins a vacation for two to Las Vegas and Sgt. Carter joins him. Gomer doesn't want to gamble as much as he wants to see the sights, but the sergeant is committed to gaming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315020000 +0000" stop="20250315023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Clearance Sale At The Black Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing something he shouldn't have, Schultz is ordered to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315023000 +0000" stop="20250315030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink Vs. The Gonculator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan leads Klink to believe a rabbit trap is a secret electronic device in order for Klink to bring an electronics expert, who wants to defect, to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315030000 +0000" stop="20250315033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Kitchen Commercials, Carol and the gang parody classic kitchen commercials. Then, in Fire At Will, Private Tim can't detonate the cannon successfully. Finally, in The Comic, Carol cheers up her comedian husband by heckling him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315033000 +0000" stop="20250315043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Frantic Flyer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A double cross, a double murder, a plane crash, missing money and an innocent widow charged with crimes she didn't commit are the elements of this case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315043500 +0000" stop="20250315050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Two people in a remote cabin find signs of an extraterrestrial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315050500 +0000" stop="20250315053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Backward, Turn Backward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is murdered, suspicion falls on his daughter's suitor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315053500 +0000" stop="20250315060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Not The Running Type</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man has an interesting way of making a small fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315060500 +0000" stop="20250315070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Woman In The Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After inheriting the original manuscript of the first chapter of Marx's "The Capital," Lisa Ralph turns up murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315070500 +0000" stop="20250315080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Avenger</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon takes on a missing person's case which leads to the death of a policeman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315080500 +0000" stop="20250315090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Of The Dunes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A weekend motorcyclist witnesses a gangster burial, then pays for it with his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315090000 +0000" stop="20250315093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bedloe Strikes Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe, an executive with the C&amp;W Railroad makes a second attempt at shutting the Hooterville Cannonball down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315093000 +0000" stop="20250315100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Joe's Replacement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>General store clerk Herbie Bates is name assistant general manager of the Shady Rest by Kate, making Uncle Joe feel like he is being replaced.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315100000 +0000" stop="20250315103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Plays Solomon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny's plan to stop Pearl's yodeling backfires when the police she called find her illegal still.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315103000 +0000" stop="20250315110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Comes Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly shows Granny an article about an old school mate getting engaged after having a coming out party. Granny tells Jed about this, and the clan decides to give Elly May a coming out party. Drysdale isn’t happy about hearing this, especially the spare-no-expense part and seeing the Clampetts’ country decorations. Drysdale decides to get someone to help with the task so the Clampetts don’t embarrass themselves, getting his wife to tend to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315110000 +0000" stop="20250315113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Customers Wanted, Abusement Park, Popeye The Sailor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye tries to lure customers into his penny arcade at Coney Island., Popeye takes Olive to the carnival where he starts demonstrating his prowess on the bell-ringing machine. Bluto appears and proceeds to outdo him., Popeye and Olive Oyl go to a carnival and Bluto follows."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315113000 +0000" stop="20250315120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Johann Mouse, Droopy Leprechaun, Million Dollar Cat</sub-title>
    <desc>"A narrator tells the story of a waltzing mouse who lived in the home of Johann Strauss. Academy Award for Best Short Subject, Droopy gets mistaken for a leprechaun while visiting Ireland., Tom will inherit a million dollars if he doesn't harm any living thing, including Jerry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315120000 +0000" stop="20250315130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tree's A Crowd, Musical Moments From Chopin, Pesky Pelican, Billion Dollar Boner, Bugged In A Rug, Fowled Up Party, His Better Elf</sub-title>
    <desc>"A wealthy estate owneer sends his cat after Woody to stop him pecking at his priceless trees., A Musical Miniature cartoon. Andy and Woody play a flawless Chopin piano concert in a barn, not missing a note even when a horse accidentally sets fire to the barn., Chilly contends with a pelican trying to steal his fishing catch., A man will receive one billion dollars but only if he doesn't harm Woody Woodpecker who won't stop pestering him., Charlie Beary struggles to replace a rug in his family's house., Maggie and Sam find trouble on their way to a Halloween costume party when a dog mistakes him for a real rooster., Woody finds a four-leafed clover that transforms into a small green woodpecker claiming to be a leprechaun named "Clancy." As his three wishes to become rich go awry, Woody realizes this was all a lesson to get him to work to earn a fortune."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315130000 +0000" stop="20250315140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare Do, Soup Or Sonic, Shamrock And Roll, High Diving Hare, Wearing Of The Grin, Hare Lift</sub-title>
    <desc>"Elmer Fudd hunts for Bugs with an army surplus wabbit detector but it doesn't seem to work when Bugs leads him off a cliff. , The Coyote chases the Roadrunner all over the desert and ends up tiny. , Merlin the magic mouse and his assistant decide to take a trip to Ireland where they meet a leprechaun. , Sam forces Bugs into a high diving position but unlucky for him Bugs tricks Sam into doing the high dives., Porky Pig is a weary traveler who must stay the night in a foreboding castle. There, the castle's caretaker warns Porky about the leprechauns that roam the grounds tricking wayward travelers. , Bugs takes the 50-cent tour of a giant plane which Sam hijacks and Bugs is forced to fly at gun-point. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315140000 +0000" stop="20250315150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Jack Of Diamonds</sub-title>
    <desc>"James and Artemus arrive in Mexico with a present for the Mexican president - a beautiful Arabian horse. However, after their arrival the horse is stolen by a group of outlaw bandits, endangering the relationship between the two countries."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315150000 +0000" stop="20250315160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Chottsie Gubenheimer Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale finds his old flame Chottsie Gubenheimer (played by John McIntire's real-life wife Jeanette Nolan) working in a gambling house and in an argument with the owner, so he asks her to come with him and join the wagon train. He comes to realize that he's getting more problems than he bargained for."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315160000 +0000" stop="20250315170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Hazard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Gil Anders, once a friend of Heath’s, is ambushed by bounty hunters. The Barkleys hide him, and Jarrod seeks to discover the truth about the crime of which Anders has been accused, despite the fact that Heath believes Anders deserves death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315170000 +0000" stop="20250315173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>No Handcuffs</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a dishonest Deputy Sheriff takes a prisoner from Matt's jail without Matt's approval or knowledge, Matt and Chester go after the Deputy Sheriff and the Prisoner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315173000 +0000" stop="20250315180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Reward For Matt</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt kills a man and his widow posts a $1,000 reward for his death. Everyone in the country from sodbusters to gunslingers is out to get the reward."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315180000 +0000" stop="20250315190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Big Shadow On The Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Immigrant winemakers decide to plant their grapes on Ponderosa land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315190000 +0000" stop="20250315193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315193000 +0000" stop="20250315200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315200000 +0000" stop="20250315210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Wild Deuces</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mushy wins $1,500 from saloon-owner Lorelie Mears, his troubles begin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315210000 +0000" stop="20250315213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ledge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin and four others debate what to do after a man falls off a ledge and it is uncertain whether he is alive or dead. Unresponsive and out of reach, the fallen man may be on the receiving end of a mercy killing if no one can find a way to get to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315213000 +0000" stop="20250315220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Ballot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Randall comes to assist a war buddy in his bid for the town's mayoralty, quickly running afoul of the established political machine and its corrupt mayor and sheriff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250315220000 +0000" stop="20250316000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Ants In The Pantry, We Want Our Mummy, Boobs In Arms, Baby Sitters Jitters, Sweet And Hot, Yokes On Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are pest exterminators who drum up business by planting vermin in a ritzy mansion where a party is going on.  They are hired, but must pose as guests to work unobserved.   , The stooges go to Egypt in search of the mummy of king Rootin-Tootin for which a museum will pay a $5000 prize., Rejected by the armed services, the Stooges decide to "do their bit" by becoming farmers.  After paying $1000 and throwing in their car, the boys are owners of a run down farm, which lacks any livestock.  After capturing an escaped ostrich, they decide to carve jack-o- lanterns for profit and then must contend with some Japanese who have escaped from a relocation center.  The Stooges become heroes by capturing the escapees, with the help of explosive eggs laid by the ostrich who had swallowed some blasting powder. , The Stooges are greeting card salesmen who are mistakenly inducted into the army after escaping from the jealous husband of one of their customers.  In boot camp their sergeant turns out to be the same man, whom they constantly vex and bewilder.  When the boys are sent to the front lines and the sergeant is captured they must rescue him, which they do after doping themselves with laughing gas.  At the end they get shot off into the sunset on a cannon shell. , The Stooges are facing eviction and decide to raise some money by becoming baby-sitters.  Their first client is a women separated from her husband, who entrusts her son "Junior" to the boys' care.  When the husband steals the baby, the Stooges set out to find their missing charge and return him to his mother.  The boys confront the husband and find Junior, and in the process the estranged couple is re-united. , Nightclub performer Larry wants Joe and his sister Tiny to join the act.  The only problem is that Tiny is afraid to sing in front of people.  They take her to a psychiatrist (Moe) who cures her, and the act is a success. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316000000 +0000" stop="20250316023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost World</sub-title>
    <desc>"A professor leads an expedition into the Amazonian jungle to find dinosaurs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316023000 +0000" stop="20250316050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Puppet Master</sub-title>
    <desc>"An evil puppeteer targets psychics using his deadly marionettes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316050000 +0000" stop="20250316060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>A Day At The Zoo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A cave boy appears and attempts to lure Penny away, but she refuses and is instead caught in a net. She is transported to an intergalactic zoo, were she will be put on show. Meanwhile Dr. Smith tries to take over the zoo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316060000 +0000" stop="20250316070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Jonah And The Whale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to salvage information about a destroyed underwater laboratory, Admiral Nelson and Russian scientist Katya Markhova are swallowed by a whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316070000 +0000" stop="20250316080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict stumbles across the Spindrift and takes it with him, leaving half the group stranded and the other half trapped inside the ship, as the man falls into quicksand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250316080000 +0000" stop="20250316090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Billy The Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers find themselves being hunted by Billy the Kid.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
