<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530220000 +0000" stop="20250530223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530223000 +0000" stop="20250530230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530230000 +0000" stop="20250530233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250530233000 +0000" stop="20250531000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Abyssinia, Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry finally gets his discharge. While he is tying things up, Burns prepares for his new command. Henry bids a tearful adieu, but not before Klinger turns up in an outrageous tropical outfit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531000000 +0000" stop="20250531010000 +0000">
    <title>Me-TV Special Presentation</title>
    <sub-title>The Andy Griffith Show Reunion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cast members from "The Andy Griffith Show" gather to reminisce about the classic 1960s TV series."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531010000 +0000" stop="20250531013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Versus Automation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts befriend Leroy Lester, an unappreciated accountant being replaced at the bank by a computer, and give him the rest, relaxation and vacation he deserves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531013000 +0000" stop="20250531020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Life And Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ralph thinks he's dying and sells the story to a magazine, he discovers it was a dog who was sick instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531020000 +0000" stop="20250531023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds In The Rough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A German officer threatens to expose Hogan unless he is paid a million dollars in diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531023000 +0000" stop="20250531030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531030000 +0000" stop="20250531033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531033000 +0000" stop="20250531043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Brazen Bequest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Cromwell, the president-elect of Euclid College, worries that some less than stellar moments from his past will be exposed when Maisie Freitag arrives at the college.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531043500 +0000" stop="20250531050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531050500 +0000" stop="20250531053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Bullet For Baldwin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Benjamin Stepp turns into a cold-blooded murderer after being fired from his job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531053500 +0000" stop="20250531060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Switch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man buys an alibi so he can murder his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531060500 +0000" stop="20250531070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mannix tracks down an assassin, he is shot and seriously injured. Having a breakdown, Mannix is diagnosed with psychosomatic blindness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531070500 +0000" stop="20250531080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Stone Cold Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The reopening of the cold case of a salesgirl reveals that a bicycle she sold may be a clue to her death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531080500 +0000" stop="20250531090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dangerous Gambit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigation a fatal automobile accident, Barnaby uncovers a complex scheme to defraud a bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531090000 +0000" stop="20250531093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Days At Shady Rest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Norman Curtis, the railroad president, sends his basset hound to the Shady Rest for a change of scenery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531093000 +0000" stop="20250531100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>A Millionaire For Kate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe believes an old schoolmate of Kate's is a con artist, rather than the millionaire he claims to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531100000 +0000" stop="20250531103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Sonny Drysdale Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny predicts that Elly will get married, but Jed doesn’t believe her. However, when Jethro tells them Sonny Drysdale is returning, Granny believes that this will be Jed’s future son-in-law. Drysdale believes the same thing, and has Sonny and Elly set up to be married. Drysdale makes Sonny get a job, selling beauty products door-to-door.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531103000 +0000" stop="20250531110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Drysdale stops the clan from going back home to deliver a baby, the Clampetts try to help the Brewsters with their baby, while Jethro unsuccessfully tries to open his own version of the Kitty Kat Club. Of course, the Brewsters don't need the help because they are adopting, though after hearing the explanation given, the Clampetts believe they really need help and advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531110000 +0000" stop="20250531113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Quick On The Vigor, Crystal Brawl, Nurse-mates</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye must save Olive from strongman Bluto at the county fair., When Bluto takes Olive to the fair, Popeye disguises himself as a fortune teller to get her attention., Popeye and Bluto vie with each other over caring for Swee'pea while Olive visits the beauty parlor."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531113000 +0000" stop="20250531120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Jekyll And Mr. Mouse, The Field Mouse, Salt Water Tabby</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry drinks a potion that makes him grow to the size of a giant and decides to go after Tom this time. Academy Award nominee for 1948 Best Short Subject., A lazy field mouse proves his worth to his grandfather by rescuing him from a thresher., Tom's efforts to impress a female cat at the beach are foiled by Jerry and a crab."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531120000 +0000" stop="20250531130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Beach Nut, Sliphorn King Of Polaroo, Little Woody Riding Hood, Lighthouse Keeping Blues, Woodpecker In The Rough, Window Pains, Romp In A Swamp</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody Woodpecker ruins Wally's day at the beach., A trombone playing, merchant-marine sailor is shipwrecked in the far north, and the animals like his playing so much that he is named Sliphorn King of Polaroo., Woody tells the story of Little Red Riding Hood, but Gabby tries to steal the wolf's part., Chilly breaks the bright light bulbs of a lighthouse that are keeping him awake. But lighthouse keeper Smedley keeps replacing them., A power player challenges Woody to a high stakes golf game., Charlie tries to clean the house's windows himself., Woody and Ali Gator try to trap and eat each other."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531130000 +0000" stop="20250531140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Baseball Bugs, A Pest In The House, Patient Porky, Box Office Bunny, Zoom At The Top, Walky Talky Hawky, Tortoise Beats Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs takes on a team of Gorillias in this baseball comedy. , A tired businessman goes to Elmer's hotel for some peace and quiet. The only problem is that Daffy is a bellman who doesn't know how to be quiet., Porky enters a hospital with a stomach ache and contends with a crazy cat patient posing as a doctor. , Bugs takes a peek inside a movie theater that was built directly over his rabbit hole. Elmer and Daffy complicate matters. , The chase continues between the Coyote and the Road Runner. This time the Coyote relies on bear traps, an icicle maker and a boomerang. , Henery goes out to fulfill his destiny: hunting chickens. Foghorn Leghorn is fighting with a dog and uses the naive Henery against his enemy. , Bugs Bunny challenges Cecil Turtle to a race. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531140000 +0000" stop="20250531150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Arrow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Strong Bear's Sioux Indians are making noises about breaking the peace treaty. President Grant's first three messengers failed to return from meetings with the Indian leader. Now it's up to Jim and Artemus to find Strong Bear and to keep peace in the territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531150000 +0000" stop="20250531160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunter Malloy Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hunter Malloy and his partner get jobs as drivers on the wagon train as part of their plan to rob the boss. Striking gold instead while stopping to repair their wagons, the fever is high as some stop to strike it rich and uncover more than just a few nuggets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531160000 +0000" stop="20250531170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Pursuit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A young Payute indian flees back to his tribal encampment when he learns he has measles, believing that only his medicine man will be able to save him. Victoria goes after him, knowing that if he reaches his people the disease may wipe them out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531170000 +0000" stop="20250531173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Renegade White</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt goes after Ord Spencer for murder. He gets thrown by his horse and hits his head then gets kidnapped by the Cheyene."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531173000 +0000" stop="20250531180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Warrant</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lee Prentice is shot by Jake Harbin who has a dead or alive bogus murder warrant for him. Matt has to try and figure a way to keep him and Sherriff Ben Goddard from taking Lee back."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531180000 +0000" stop="20250531190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>In Defense Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E27</episode-num>
    <desc>When a love triangle involving a Yute ranch hand leads to murder, a treaty between the white man and the Yutes is threatened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531190000 +0000" stop="20250531193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531193000 +0000" stop="20250531200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531200000 +0000" stop="20250531210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Hourglass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The herd needs to get through Hourglass pass where the army is preparing to blast for a dam. Favor's hometown friend is married to the Post Adjutant. When she kills an officer, she lies to get Favor convicted of the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531210000 +0000" stop="20250531213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Black Sheep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Huttner is a fugitive wanted for manslaughter. He is also the illegitimate son of a very wealthy man and stands to inherit his five million dollar estate, but he must first come back and stand trial. Paladin is hired to find him and either bring him back to stand trial or get him to sign a paper giving up his inheritance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531213000 +0000" stop="20250531220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Conquerors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A concerned father hires Josh to retrieve his son, a passionate young ideologue whose gift for rousing rhetoric is being used by plunderers to recruit freedom fighters for a phony liberation of Baja California.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250531220000 +0000" stop="20250601000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Little Pigskins, Cookoo Cavaliers, Gents In A Jam, Three Dark Horses, Hoi Polloi, So Long Mr. Chumps</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are mistaken by a gangster for the "Three Horsemen of Boulder Dam", famous football players , The Stooges are three fish peddlers who, looking for a new business opportunity, open a beauty salon south of the border.  Their first customers are some chorus girls from a local nightclub.  After the Stooges completely ruin the girl's hair, and their manager finds out, the boys must leave on the run. , Larry, Moe and Curly are on a quest to find an honest man. And they finally find one - in jail!  , Shemp's rich Uncle Phineas comes to visit the Stooges who are broke and about to be evicted.  The boys convince their landlady Mrs. McGruder not to toss them out as Shemp is set to inherit a fortune.  The boys also have trouble with a circus strongman after Shemp accidentally rips off his wife's dress.  Uncle Phineas gets in the middle of the fight, and Mrs. McGruder ends it by knocking out the strongman.  It turns out that Uncle Phineas and the landlady were childhood sweethearts and he marries her, leaving the Stooges out of the bucks once again. , The Stooges escape from jail to prevent their newly rich dad from marrying Daisy, a gold-digger after his money.  Shemp looks like dad, so he impersonates him and marries Daisy.  What the Stooges don't know is that Daisy is in cahoots with some crooks, and they plan to bump off her new husband.  The boys foil the crook's plan and take Pa home to Ma. , A professor bets that he can turn the Stooges into gentlemen.   "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601000000 +0000" stop="20250601023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted Strangler</sub-title>
    <desc>"A researcher investigating a notorious serial killer who was hanged 20 years earlier seemingly becomes possessed by the long dead strangler."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601023000 +0000" stop="20250601030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Penguin's A Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman and Robin accompany a bored actress, fearful the Penguin will kidnap her, something he only plans to do after eavesdropping on the Dynamic Duo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601030000 +0000" stop="20250601040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>All Our Yesterdays</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk, Spock and McCoy become trapped in the past of another world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601040000 +0000" stop="20250601050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Ripper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kolchak argues that a serial killer is actually Jack the Ripper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601050000 +0000" stop="20250601060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Vegetable Rebellion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith uses the Space Pod to land on a planet that the Jupiter 2 is passing by. It turns out that the planet has evolved in such a way that plants are the highest form of life, and some of them are quite intelligent. One of these plants, a large carrot, captures Smith and tries to change him into a plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601060000 +0000" stop="20250601070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Machines Strike Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Unmanned submarines inexplicably aim their devastating arsenal toward the United States.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601070000 +0000" stop="20250601080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of Thrombeldinbar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitzhuge pretends to be a magical holiday elf to entertain two orphan children. But the ruse turns deadly when he discovers that the giants ritually throw Thrombeldinbar into a fire to celebrate the holiday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601080000 +0000" stop="20250601090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>End Of The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In a 1910 mining town, Tony and Doug try to rescue 200 miners trapped by a cave-in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601090000 +0000" stop="20250601100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Moonshot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A planned moon mission causes Vincent and an astronaut to suspect danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601100000 +0000" stop="20250601110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Daredevil</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Matthew's friend decides to become a stuntman, Star has to intervene with his powers to protect him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601110000 +0000" stop="20250601113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Close Encounters Of The Nerd Kind   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Looking for a way to make a quick buck, Slater and Zack have Screech dress up as an alien from outer space to trick a tabloid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601113000 +0000" stop="20250601120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Slater's Friend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater unwittingly dooms his chameleon when he leaves it with Screech.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601120000 +0000" stop="20250601123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Save That Tiger   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack and Slater's prank war against rival school Valley High escalates, Screech gets kidnapped!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601123000 +0000" stop="20250601130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Birthday   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After the gang forgets Screech's birthday, he gets revenge by sending them all to detention, not knowing they're planning a surprise party in Mr. Belding's office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601130000 +0000" stop="20250601133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Dates   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack agrees to go on a date with Mr. Belding's niece, Penny, but when Kelly invites him to her birthday party, he sends Screech instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601133000 +0000" stop="20250601140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Prom   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When her dad loses his job, Kelly chooses to cancel prom with Zack in order to save money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601140000 +0000" stop="20250601143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Kelly's Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Brady's friends, the Kellys, adopt three boys, all of different ethnic backgrounds, and soon find themselves dealing with racist neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601143000 +0000" stop="20250601150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Driver's Seat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg bets Marcia that she can't beat his score on her driver's test. However all the pressure gets the best of Marcia. Meanwhile, Jan must also deal with the pressure of speaking in front of a large group of people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601150000 +0000" stop="20250601153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At The Circus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to get Ashley's young daughter, Heather, to warm up to him, Fonzie takes her to the circus. Meanwhile, K. C., Howard's niece, moves in with Howard and Marion while her parents look for a new boarding school. Marion asks Howard to consider letting her stay permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601153000 +0000" stop="20250601160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While Laverne is at a funeral home with pregnant Sgt. Plout, her baby decides it's time to come into the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601160000 +0000" stop="20250601163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Mends A Broken Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy shows up for a date with Peggy McMillan only to learn her old friend, Don, has arrived unexpectedly, leading to a string of misunderstandings and Barney's attempts at help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601163000 +0000" stop="20250601170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Men Are Messy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"Men are nothing but a bunch of messcats," insists Lucy Ricardo while Ricky concludes that "a man's home is his castle." To make a point, Lucy divides the apartment in half so that Ricky can be as messy as he likes on his side, but when Ricky's press agent, Kenny Morgan, lines up a publicity spread in Halfbeat Magazine, Lucy decides to teach her sloppy husband a lesson by turning the Ricardo apartment into a regular pig pen. Little does Lucy know that this photographer is not from the musician's journal, but is actually from Look magazine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601170000 +0000" stop="20250601173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Summer In Alaska</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie is happy to break the news that he plans to spend his summer on a fishing boat in Alaska and this prompts Wally and Lumpy to think about signing up to do the same thing. However, they all get a dose of reality when they discover just what kind of conditions they would be living in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601173000 +0000" stop="20250601180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>It's come down to the final week before junior high school graduation and Beaver is having a ball and even skips a class with Gilbert. However, Beaver becomes convinced he won't graduate after Gilbert and him take a peek at the diplomas on Mrs. Rayburn's desk and find Beaver's diploma to be missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601180000 +0000" stop="20250601183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Goes To Hooterville</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after the Clampett's return from London, Granny gets a letter saying she is needed in Hooterville. The problem is that nobody knows where it is. Granny tries to find out, but doesn’t have much luck. Jethro, who isn't getting fed because Granny is focusing on Hooterville, is desperate for food and accidentally eats Elly's grits and rocks for her critters. Granny has to “doctor” him back to health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601183000 +0000" stop="20250601190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Italian Cook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has been staying in Petticoat Junction, and her family is hungry. Elly May decides to take over the cooking, though her dishes are worse than eating nothing. The clan asks Granny to come home, but she says she can’t. So Jane suggests to Jethro that he hire a cook, and he ends up getting a gorgeous cook that only speaks Italian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601190000 +0000" stop="20250601193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>They're Off And Running</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Howell wins all of the Skipper's possessions betting on turtle races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601193000 +0000" stop="20250601200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Three To Get Ready</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The Skipper insists a stone found by Gilligan will grant the finder three wishes before sundown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601200000 +0000" stop="20250601203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Naomi's New Position  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Naomi's boss sexually harasses her, Mama marches down to the store and gives him a taste of his own medicine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601203000 +0000" stop="20250601210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Really Loud Family  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Bubba turns in an unflattering video of his family for a school project, Mama ends up excused from organizing a charity event she didn't even want to organize.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601210000 +0000" stop="20250601220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Tony And Julie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Julie falls for a veterinarian; a divorced couple must share quarters; Vicki is offered a part in a TV series.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601220000 +0000" stop="20250601223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Lawman Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's ability to be a lawman is put to the test with some peddlers and he fails. His confidence is shattered until Andy steps in behind the scenes and warns the peddlers of "Fife the Fierce."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601223000 +0000" stop="20250601230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Claire Peterson- Transformers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Claire Peterson is not your typical Transformers collector, most are male. But as the daughter of an engineer, she loved working with her hands, and she became enamored with Transformers when she was still a child. That was in the early 1990s, during what is called the Generation 2, or G2, Transformers era. Generation one started in the 1980s. Now, Claire collects everything from G one and G two to the B Wars, the Beast machines, and beyond. Claire also buys and sells Transformers at local and regional conventions as well as online. She has about 1,100 on display and a little more than 2000 in storage, each of them unique. Out of all the cartoon, TV shows, and movies that have come out of the franchise, the 1986 animated film “Transformers” is one of her favorites. She says she is devastated, though, that she still does not have the full Devastator combiner set. She and our expert, Ben Talmage, had already crossed paths, having met at a local Michigan toy convention."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601230000 +0000" stop="20250601233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp. On the way back, BJ is introduced to the Korean War.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250601233000 +0000" stop="20250602000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602000000 +0000" stop="20250602003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith gets an invitation to attend her 30th high school class reunion, but when Archie refuses to escort her, she decides not to go. When her Cousin Amelia shows up to question Edith about her decision, Edith learns that an old flame, Buck, will be attending the reunion. Suddenly, Archie decides that he would like to go. However, when Buck does finally show up, Archie is in for a surprise since the once good looking track star seems to have lost his good looks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602003000 +0000" stop="20250602010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home with a brand new watch and claims that he got a bargain on it, since he was told that it was a $300 watch and he got it for $25. Later, Archie is crestfallen when he discovers that the watch is broken. Meanwhile, Mike is convinced that the watch is stolen and encourages Archie to be careful, since the serial number may lead the jeweler to discover that indeed Archie has a hot watch. Thus, Archie scrambles to find a jeweler who will fix it with no questions asked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602010000 +0000" stop="20250602013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Is Branded</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>One morning Archie gets up, goes to his front door to get the newspaper and is shocked to discover that someone has painted a swastika on his front door. Archie soon gets into a debate with Mike as to who could have painted it and why. As Archie is calling the police to report it, the Bunker home gets a visit from a man from a Hebrew vigilante group who wants to plan some retaliation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602013000 +0000" stop="20250602020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Tells The Truth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie, Edith, Mike and Gloria go out to a French restaurant and recall the events of the day. Each one of them has a vastly different version of the day's events. It seems that the Bunker's refrigerator is on the fritz and a pair of repairmen enter the scene. However, in the end, the fridge doesn't get repaired and it's Edith's version of the day that explains why it didn't get fixed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602020000 +0000" stop="20250602023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 03/30/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602023000 +0000" stop="20250602030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Art Carney</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Art Carney. Originally aired on 02/19/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602030000 +0000" stop="20250602033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Ugliest Dog In The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob tries to find a home for an unattractive dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602033000 +0000" stop="20250602040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>No Rice At My Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recalls a time when Laura almost married someone else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602040000 +0000" stop="20250602043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Sleepwalker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton is sleepwalking and Ralph gets stuck looking after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602043000 +0000" stop="20250602053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>In His Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A scientist creates an android that has the qualities which he feels he's lacking.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602053000 +0000" stop="20250602060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Got To Have Luck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man holds a woman hostage in her farmhouse while he plans his escape from the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602060000 +0000" stop="20250602070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF is up against a contract killer who makes decisions at random at the last minute to ensure his moves are unpredictable. As Barney stands in for the intended victim, the IMF prepares for every contingency to thwart his plans and stop the killing spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602070000 +0000" stop="20250602080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Iron Maiden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An industrial accident traps Kimble and some government workers underground. A member of the trapped group wants to turn Kimble in as soon as they are rescued. To add to Richard's problems, Lt. Gerard is waiting above at the only exit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602080000 +0000" stop="20250602090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Street Games</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell seeks to find and protect a teenage dope addict before she is killed by a ruthless narcotics overlord."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602090000 +0000" stop="20250602093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602093000 +0000" stop="20250602100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602100000 +0000" stop="20250602103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 94 -- Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy fears that a boxer who has just been paroled after serving a murder sentence is going to seek revenge against him. Out on patrol, they try to save a man who has been crushed while working under a stolen car, apprehend a liquor store robber who swears revenge against reed, change a flat tire on their patrol car, locate a four-year-old child who locked himself in a refrigerator and become the targets of an ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602103000 +0000" stop="20250602110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 104 -- The Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspect who frames an employee of a manufacturing plant for theft and then plants a powerful bomb on the premises. They also apprehend two criminals after questioning a suspicious man who is carrying heavy bags down the street, and protect an innocent motorist from a street race that still ends in tragedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602110000 +0000" stop="20250602120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin Racing</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602120000 +0000" stop="20250602123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Practical Joke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie fall prey to Lumpy's practical joking after he plants cherry bombs under the hoods of Eddie's car and Wally's car. Both Eddie and Wally want to get him back but their plan goes awry when they destroy Lumpy's car after chaining it to a tree. All fingers point to Wally after Fred finds that the chain has Ward's name printed on it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602123000 +0000" stop="20250602130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The All-night Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E36</episode-num>
    <desc>After graduation, an all-night party is set to begin, which has June and Ward very wary. They aren't sure if they should allow Wally to attend. Meanwhile, Wally's date for the party has the same problem. This leads her to invite Wally to meet her folks and put their worries to rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602130000 +0000" stop="20250602140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tell-tale Tap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When the niece of the head of an investment firm is found dead, the company's financial comptroller is charged with her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602140000 +0000" stop="20250602150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Chef  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a wife is accused of poisoning her ex-husband during the taping of a television cooking show, Matlock is hired to uncover the truth in this seemingly open-and-shut case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602150000 +0000" stop="20250602160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Odessa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Racists target a ceremony honoring a civil rights pioneer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602160000 +0000" stop="20250602170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fighter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A prize fighter arrives searching for work, living and training in the Waltons' barn</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602170000 +0000" stop="20250602173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Heart</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bella Grant is brought to Dodge by Brisco Cass (Ken Curtis) to get Jerry Cass away from his ranch so his brother, Brisco, can claim the ranch as his own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602173000 +0000" stop="20250602180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Buffalo Hunter</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a Buffalo hunter dies from injuries from burning lead, Matt and Doc think that their boss (Jim Gatluf) might have had something to do with the man's dying."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602180000 +0000" stop="20250602190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>To Die In Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A man convicted on Ben's testimony seeks revenge, luring Ben and Candy to an abandoned mineshaft and then trapping them there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602190000 +0000" stop="20250602193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602193000 +0000" stop="20250602200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Assailants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An assassination plot unfolds as four gunmen disguised as cavalrymen enter North Fork. Their target: Sen. Jim Borden. Their weapon: a Gatling gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602200000 +0000" stop="20250602210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ben Courtney Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The sheriff of Bitter Springs feels he has lots of reasons to hate. When settlers from the South want to live there, he accuses them of enslaving a black child, but his reasons for keeping them from the town go much deeper than that.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602210000 +0000" stop="20250602220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Alley Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stray cat decides to have her kittens on John's bed at the station. A family is trapped in a downed airplane. An old man gets his foot caught in a bear trap. A stage actress suffers an anxiety attack. A school develops a gas leak. Roy and John rescue the victim of a boating accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602220000 +0000" stop="20250602223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Command</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank settles in as commanding officer, only to have a new one appointed over his head, one that, to his chagrin, fits in very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602223000 +0000" stop="20250602230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>It Happened One Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It happened one night: freezing cold, an artillery barrage that's coming too close, a patient going downhill and Frank's searching Hot Lips' tent for his letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602230000 +0000" stop="20250602233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Captain Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye's father is notified that he's dead, he finds it's no easy matter either to get word to him or to establish otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250602233000 +0000" stop="20250603000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Doc</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Its quid pro quo at the 4077th: two bottles of Scotch for secret surgery, and a tank to scare off snipers for an unauthorized shot of penicillin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603000000 +0000" stop="20250603003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Mayberry Band</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Stoner declares the town's marching band a disgrace and refuses to allocate money for its annual trip to the state competition. Andy takes matters into his own hands, with help from Bobby Fleet and his Band with a Beat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603003000 +0000" stop="20250603010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Floyd The Gay Deceiver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Madeline Grayson, a rich widow that Floyd has been "pen-palling" with, announces in her next letter that she wants to meet him face-to-face. Of course, the whole time Floyd has been pretending in his letters to be a wealthy entrepreneur.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603010000 +0000" stop="20250603013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Luke's Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Luke Short's boy, Beau, comes to town, and Granny has him set up with Elly. But Elly wants no part of this and tries to turn him off, first as a Hollywood siren, then as a scrubwoman. When this doesn't work, Jane convinces Beau and Jethro they should become international playboys and belong to all women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603013000 +0000" stop="20250603020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Better Living Through Televison</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton go on T.V. to sell a kitchen utensil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603020000 +0000" stop="20250603023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Two German officers interfere with Hogan's operations when one tries to turn Stalag 13 into an officer's retirement home the other wants to use the facilities to interrogate the citizens of the local town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603023000 +0000" stop="20250603030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Rise And Fall Of Sergeant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is stymied in the rescue of a captured member of the underground until a potential diversion appears in the form of an old WWI buddy of Sgt. Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603030000 +0000" stop="20250603033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Escape Clause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hypochondriac exchanges his soul for immortality and indestructibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603033000 +0000" stop="20250603043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Renegade Refugee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A journalist is murdered while tracking an ex-Nazi war criminal who may be posing as an executive at a company called Space Associates, Ltd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603043500 +0000" stop="20250603050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603050500 +0000" stop="20250603053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Older Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter discovers the truth about the infamous Lizzie Borden murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603053500 +0000" stop="20250603060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Shopping For Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Two retired sales clerks test their theory that people become killers at 92 degrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603060500 +0000" stop="20250603070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Who Killed Me?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Bradley Everett crashes his small plane into the sea. After an intensive search turns up no sign of the man, he suddenly appears at Mannix's door, babbling about a murder attempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603070500 +0000" stop="20250603080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is A Double Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired to be a bodyguard for the daughter of a broker and his grandchildren, but is drawn in when the broker reveals that he believes his son in law is involved in a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603080500 +0000" stop="20250603090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Wipeout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the death of a girl who was a supposedly skilled surfer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603090000 +0000" stop="20250603093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603093000 +0000" stop="20250603100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603100000 +0000" stop="20250603103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 74 -- Light Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed spend a night shift on desk duty after Malloy breaks his wrist and another office worker calls in sick. With the assistance of a new female recruit, they deal with a homesick elderly woman who refuses to identify herself, help a lenient father bail out his son and become suspicious of a man who walks in looking for a wanted fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603103000 +0000" stop="20250603110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 114 -- The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed witness a young hispanic man save a trapped watchman from a burning warehouse, but become suspicious when he resists numerous attempts of private and public commendation. They also try to prevent a drunken man from falling out a window, and resuscitate a man with a heart condition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603110000 +0000" stop="20250603120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Campfire Stories</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603120000 +0000" stop="20250603123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Sees America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has the chance to travel around the country for six weeks during the summer and he's all excited about it. However, he quickly realizes when he's gone Gilbert will go after the girl Beaver has a crush on, Mary Margaret. But he quickly realizes, there's more to life than Mary Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603123000 +0000" stop="20250603130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clothing Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's school is having a clothing drive and whoever brings in the most clothes will be awarded 1,000 school points. June, Ward and Wally round up all the old clothes they can find and put them in a box. However, next to the box are three good suits of Ward's that are to be cleaned, and, of course, Beaver mistakes them as items for the clothing drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603130000 +0000" stop="20250603140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impatient Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Paint manufacturer Amory Fallon suspects that his partner, Ned Thompson, is behind a mysterious fire and explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603140000 +0000" stop="20250603150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Author  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a scurrilous book leads to murder, Matlock finds himself defending the suspected killer, soon realizing that the case is not at all what it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603150000 +0000" stop="20250603160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Time To Trust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea fears for one of her students after her mother's boyfriend is linked to a criminal operation that has resulted in the deaths of several truckers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603160000 +0000" stop="20250603170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Prophecy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>John's 25th high school reunion is being planned; he thinks he is not successful, but at the reunion, everyone thinks he is the winner</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603170000 +0000" stop="20250603173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Choice</sub-title>
    <desc>"Andy Hill comes to Dodge looking for a job. Matt finds out he's wanted for robbery but decides to take a chance on him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603173000 +0000" stop="20250603180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>There Never Was A Horse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gunman Kin Creed comes to Dodge and tries everything to get Matt into a gunfight."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603180000 +0000" stop="20250603190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Bottle Fighter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hoss is accused of stabbing a man to death, his hopes for acquittal rest on the skills of Barney Sturgess, a once great lawyer who has crawled inside a bottle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603190000 +0000" stop="20250603193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mark's Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharpshooter Marty Blair tries to persuade Lucas to buy Mark a rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603193000 +0000" stop="20250603200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Amazing Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Fast-draw artist Wade Randall is less than anxious to display his prowess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603200000 +0000" stop="20250603210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ella Lindstrom Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ella Lindstrom loses her husband on the wagon train ride west from Boston. With her seven children she decides to stay the course against the wishes of Major Adams. It gets more complicated when she thinks she is expecting number eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603210000 +0000" stop="20250603220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>An English Visitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A paramedic from England has a stint with Station 51 observing Roy and John, whose rescues include a fire, a wild-west performer, a car accident and a man trapped in heavy machinery. The visitor saves John's life. At the hospital Dr Brackett treats a rock singer in a diabetic coma and Dr. Early has problems with a defiant nurse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603220000 +0000" stop="20250603223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving back from a medical conference, Radar, Hawkeye, B.J., Sherman and Frank find themselves lost. When they decide to turn around, the bus does not want to start. And when Radar goes off in the middle of the night for the latrine, he does not immediately return.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603223000 +0000" stop="20250603230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Mildred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Potter's anniversary. While Potter writes home, Frank and Hot Lips have a wood carving made for him, and Radar rescues a horse and makes him a present of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603230000 +0000" stop="20250603233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th plays host to kids bombed out of their orphanage, and at the same time has to deliver a baby and care for battle casualties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250603233000 +0000" stop="20250604000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Quo Vadis, Captain Chandler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Intelligence officer Colonel Flagg and psychiatrist Sidney Freedman grapple over the fate of a wounded officer, Captain Chandler, who claims to be Jesus Christ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604000000 +0000" stop="20250604003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Rival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is afraid that Andy's new girlfriend, Peggy, will take his place in his father's heart, and sets out to sabotage their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604003000 +0000" stop="20250604010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bed Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bea longs for a special present: a blue bed jacket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604010000 +0000" stop="20250604013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Brewsters Return</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>The Brewsters come to Beverly Hills to build their new home on a vacant lot they purchased, and they request the Clampetts don't learn of this. But the Clampetts are planning to move back home to the Hills. When they tell Drysdale, he reveals the secret. Drysdale tells Brewster what he has done, but explains it was to save the Clampett oil account, and because of this, he has to visit the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604013000 +0000" stop="20250604020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pal O'mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's feelings are bruised when Ed buys a friendship ring for one of his pals on the sewer crew. Though Ralph gets it stuck on his finger, they eventually make up after Ed survives a sewer explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604020000 +0000" stop="20250604023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses a broken water main under the camp to aid the escape of captured resistance fighters by creating a health spa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604023000 +0000" stop="20250604030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Klink, A Bomb And A Short Fuse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>General Burkhalter wants Hogan to defuse a bomb that has landed in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604030000 +0000" stop="20250604033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604033000 +0000" stop="20250604043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unwelcome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Walter Frazer has always blamed his daughter-in-law, Sue Ellen, for the failures of his son, Gregson. You can only imagine how he feels when Sue Ellen is accused of Gregson's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604043500 +0000" stop="20250604050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604050500 +0000" stop="20250604053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Derelicts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is having monetary problems and his wife has just bought a mink coat. To make matters worse, two bums are blackmailing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604053500 +0000" stop="20250604060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>And So Died Riabouchinska</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist with a very lifelike puppet is accused of a murder at a vaudeville theater.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604060500 +0000" stop="20250604070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Missing: Sun And Sky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A valuable racehorse has disappeared on the way to Florida. Mannix is hired to retrieve the noble animal learn why it was abducted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604070500 +0000" stop="20250604080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An accountant wants to teach the world a lesson about the production of a deadly nerve gas when he steals a can of the substance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604080500 +0000" stop="20250604090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Eyes Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of a small town being terrorized by a rapist falsely accuse a stutterer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604090000 +0000" stop="20250604093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604093000 +0000" stop="20250604100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - Dr-33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Crosby plays a hippie whose wife has been persuaded—by other hippies—to pass bad checks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604100000 +0000" stop="20250604103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 134 -- Child Stealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has to deal with the consequences of forgetting to roll up the window on the patrol car before he left it. Back on patrol, Malloy and Reed search for an estranged husband who kidnaps his own child, deal with an elderly man who tries to pay for a meal with trading stamps, engage in a shootout with an escaped prisoner caught napping on a city bus and pull over a hijacked delivery van full of booze.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604103000 +0000" stop="20250604110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 144 -- Bank Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are in for a rude awakening when they report to the home of a former professional wrestler on a domestic abuse call. Later, they become suspicious of an apartment burglary victim after they find one of the suspects dead, deal with a man who discovers car parts that were stolen from him installed on another car and become involved in a shootout responding to a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604110000 +0000" stop="20250604120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Gangbusters</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604120000 +0000" stop="20250604123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Family Scrapbook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While cleaning, June runs across an old family scrapbook and gathers the family together to reminisce about the past six years. The Cleavers recall scenes from previous episodes including: 'Beaver Gets 'Spelled,'' 'New Neighbors,' 'My Brother's Girl,' 'The Shave,' 'Beaver Runs Away,' 'Larry Hides Out,' 'Teacher Comes to Dinner,' and 'Wally's Election.'</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604123000 +0000" stop="20250604130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets "spelled"</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver's teacher, Miss Canfield, sends a note home with Beaver and the other kids convince him that it's news that he's getting kicked out of school. So Beaver and Wally take steps to hide the note from Ward and June."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604130000 +0000" stop="20250604140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lover's Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An art critic is found dead in his bedridden wife's bed, yet his wife is nowhere to be found. The woman's caretaker is charged with murder, and it's up to Mason to find the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604140000 +0000" stop="20250604150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Rat Pack  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a Beverly Hills cookie entrepreneur charged with murdering his girlfriend. While the case against the man looks bleak, Matlock eventually uncovers a secret love triangle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604150000 +0000" stop="20250604160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>By Means Most Foul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A restaurateur and her mechanic boyfriend plot to eliminate her husband, but their scheme backfires. Gillespie takes heat over a string of mailbox bashings. And Virgil soon regrets ignoring Parker's theory regarding where the vandals would strike next.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604160000 +0000" stop="20250604170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Boondoggle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A traveling reporter visits the mountain to write story about Judge Baldwin</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604170000 +0000" stop="20250604173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Print Asper</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lawyer Jay Rabb tries to cheat Print Asper out of his ranch. Print threatens to kill him unless he makes it right. When Rabb is shot he tells the Marshall that Print did it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604173000 +0000" stop="20250604180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Constable</sub-title>
    <desc>"The businessmen of Dodge tell the Marshall to stay out of the town affairs while Texas cowboys come to town and hire a constable to deal with things."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604180000 +0000" stop="20250604190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrival Of Eddie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss finds himself in trouble when he tries to help the son of a criminal he shot and killed years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604190000 +0000" stop="20250604193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Squeeze Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A speculator will stop at nothing to grab Lucas's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604193000 +0000" stop="20250604200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark blames himself for a friend's accidental death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604200000 +0000" stop="20250604210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Scouting for a better pass, Flint finds a mountain man, hungry and half out of his mind. With no memory, his strange behavior may endanger the entire wagon train, especially when everyone begins to think they know who he is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604210000 +0000" stop="20250604220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Heavyweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>At a fire, the paramedics rescue a pregnant woman and Johnny injures his shoulder. After going into labor, the guilt-ridden mother is determined to abandon her deformed baby. Dr. Morton treats Johnny and gives him a bad time about his physical condition, sending Johnny on a fitness kick. Dr. Early treats an electrocuted child whose mother is on drugs. The son of a stabbing victim is more determined to shoot the assailant than get his father to the hospital. Roy and Johnny rescue a hang glider pilot trapped in a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604220000 +0000" stop="20250604223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Peggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. writes home to his wife, Peg, reporting Klinger's escape attempts, the visit of a formidable chaplain and one of Frank's goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604223000 +0000" stop="20250604230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Of Moose And Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tangles with a tough Army colonel, Colonel Spiker; B.J. helps Zale, who's received a Dear John letter; and Frank looks endlessly for Korean saboteurs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604230000 +0000" stop="20250604233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Soldier Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has a fever and makes a will, leaving all his money to his wife and all his clothes to Hot Lips.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250604233000 +0000" stop="20250605000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605000000 +0000" stop="20250605003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605003000 +0000" stop="20250605010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605010000 +0000" stop="20250605013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed, The Bachelor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is tired of Beverly Hills and heads home for the Hills. But she never makes it back home and ends up in Las Vegas. And Jethro is having no luck being an international playboy and ends up getting arrested. Granny comes back that night, but with a story to tell about Vegas the next day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605013000 +0000" stop="20250605020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Ralph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, after making a suggestion at work, is laid off. Alice decides to take a job as a secretary, but tells her boss that Ralph is her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605020000 +0000" stop="20250605023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Tanks For The Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to photograph and destroy a model for a radio-controlled tank that is being tested at camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605023000 +0000" stop="20250605030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Adolf Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>With camp security raised, Hogan and his men are desperate to smuggle top-secret German fortifications information to the Allies. The solution? Make liberal use of Carter's remarkable impersonation of Adolf Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605030000 +0000" stop="20250605033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605033000 +0000" stop="20250605043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Roving River</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Working to settle a land dispute in the Manzana Valley, Mason soon finds himself defending his client against a murder charge when the key witness is blown up by a homemade bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605043500 +0000" stop="20250605050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605050500 +0000" stop="20250605053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Safe Conduct</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Suspense and romance fill the travel of an American reporter returning after a visit to an Iron Curtain nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605053500 +0000" stop="20250605060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Place Of Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man looking for revenge goes undercover in a monastery but things do not turn out the way he planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605060500 +0000" stop="20250605070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Tooth Of The Serpent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe Mannix must trace the missing son of a policeman. The mother fears that he might be involved in a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605070500 +0000" stop="20250605080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flight Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A political refugee gets a unwilling helping hand from Frank when he creates a change of identity to help flee the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605080500 +0000" stop="20250605090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Stalking Horse, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney poses as the brother of an eccentric millionaire he's hired to protect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605090000 +0000" stop="20250605093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605093000 +0000" stop="20250605100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605100000 +0000" stop="20250605103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 44 -- Attempted Bribery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy businessman openly offers malloy and reed security jobs at three times their current salaries if reed agrees to withhold damaging testimony against his troubled son. In the meantime, they have to deal with an elderly man who has strangled his ch</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605103000 +0000" stop="20250605110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 173 -- Shoplift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed track down a young shoplifter who escapes custody and hides at the lair of an eccentric spiritualist whom she worships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605110000 +0000" stop="20250605120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>We're Having A Party</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill &amp; Toony help Mr. Quizzer plan a Junaween Bash!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605120000 +0000" stop="20250605123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally send away for an alligator and they secretly keep it in the bathroom. When the alligator falls ill, the boys get some advice from Captain Jack, an owner of an alligator farm. However, keeping him a secret is going to be hard; the alligator is growing and they need a new place to keep him without June and Ward finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605123000 +0000" stop="20250605130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with a black eye and Ward is upset when he learns that Beaver didn't fight back. This leads Ward to teach Beaver how to defend himself. Little does Ward know, the person who punched Beaver is a girl, Violet Rutherford, the daughter of one of Ward's co-workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605130000 +0000" stop="20250605140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fetish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a pin-prick to a voodoo doll seemingly results in a stab wound through the chest, Mason is called to determine a more down-to-Earth cause of death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605140000 +0000" stop="20250605150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Nurse  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A private nurse accused of murdering her patient barters her engagement ring in exchange for Matlock's renowned defense services.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605150000 +0000" stop="20250605160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Trundel's Will Be Done</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>V.J. Trundel's widow takes Harriet to court to gain custody of Eric. But Harriet is determined that her nephew will not be raised in the home of the man who ordered the murder of her sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605160000 +0000" stop="20250605170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason spends too much time playing with a band</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605170000 +0000" stop="20250605173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blue Horse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Chester are taking a prisoner across the prairie when Matt's horse goes down and breaks Matt's leg. Chester rides for Dodge to get Doc leaving Matt alone with the prisoner. When the prisoner overpowers Matt, Blue Horse comes to Matt's rescue."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605173000 +0000" stop="20250605180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cheyenne's</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Chester come across a family murdered by renegade Cheyennes. The Cavalry arrests Matt by mistake then let him go. Matt goes after the gunrunners who sold the guns to the Indians."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605180000 +0000" stop="20250605190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Stronghold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When the crooked Farrell brothers pay Joe and Candy for a herd with a worthless bank draft, the Cartwrights turn to a bitter enemy of the Farrell's to help get the money owed to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605190000 +0000" stop="20250605193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Anvil Chorus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nils Swenson, North Fork's blacksmith, volunteers to take the marshal's place for a few days while Micah attends a wedding in another town. To help maintain peace, Nils institutes a policy that anyone coming into town must turn in their weapons, getting them back when they leave. This plan backfires on Nils when some dishonest men come to town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605193000 +0000" stop="20250605200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas's self-confidence begins to slip away when he misses an easy shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605200000 +0000" stop="20250605210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man Charvanaugh Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint leaves the train to escort a wagon to its occupants' new home. When they meet an old man with a wagonload of uncured buffalo skins he's trying to sell, they invite him along as he appears friendly enough. But Flint feels he's too friendly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605210000 +0000" stop="20250605220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Snakebite</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Returning from a fishing trip, Roy, John and Chet help the victims of a car accident. On duty, after rescuing some joyriders whose car went off a cliff, John is bitten by a rattlesnake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605220000 +0000" stop="20250605223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605223000 +0000" stop="20250605230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605230000 +0000" stop="20250605233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Ma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes home to his mother, as Hawkeye conducts the camp foot inspection, and Colonel Potter gets some shrapnel in his backside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250605233000 +0000" stop="20250606000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Der Tag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter decides Frank would be less of a pain if the others were friendlier to him; they oblige, with some startling results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606000000 +0000" stop="20250606003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606003000 +0000" stop="20250606010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606010000 +0000" stop="20250606013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Art Center</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale has a new plan to get rid of the Clampetts and add culture to Beverly Hills. She gets the Clampetts to donate their home as an art gallery. Of course, they misunderstand this and think they have to provide the art. They go on and sculpt and paint up a storm for this new art center and end up filling their mansion with their homemade creations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606013000 +0000" stop="20250606020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606020000 +0000" stop="20250606023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Purchasing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and crew are ordered to deliver airdropped ammo to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606023000 +0000" stop="20250606030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Tiger Hunt In Paris: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While trying to free the underground agent "Tiger" in Paris, Hogan seeks help from a Parisian fortune teller and also enlist the aid of a man who is a lookalike for Nazi Police Chief Heinrich Himmler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606030000 +0000" stop="20250606033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is terrified of falling asleep for fear he might die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606033000 +0000" stop="20250606043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shapely Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Naive secretary Janice Wainwright carries out her boss' orders, placing a briefcase containing more than $100,000 in a train station locker. Then she waits for the arrival of his ex-wife but is met by an arrest warrant instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606043500 +0000" stop="20250606050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606050500 +0000" stop="20250606053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Back For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to get rid of his nagging wife — permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606053500 +0000" stop="20250606060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Two twisted brothers scheme to speed up their inheritance by killing their aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606060500 +0000" stop="20250606070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Madonna</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When an actress is the target of a strange murder attempt, Mannix is called on the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606070500 +0000" stop="20250606080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A former motorcycle officer who was disabled when a thief tried to steal the payroll from an armored car, seeks Frank's help for the purpose of exacting his revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606080500 +0000" stop="20250606090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby sets out to avenge his cousin's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250606090000 +0000" stop="20250606093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
