<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017220000 +0000" stop="20241017223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017223000 +0000" stop="20241017230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017230000 +0000" stop="20241017233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017233000 +0000" stop="20241018000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018000000 +0000" stop="20241018003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Sam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is suspicious of Mayberry's mysterious new farmer (William Schallert).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018003000 +0000" stop="20241018010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Gets His Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict vows revenge on the man who sent him back to prison: none other than Deputy Barney Fife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018010000 +0000" stop="20241018013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Italian Cook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has been staying in Petticoat Junction, and her family is hungry. Elly May decides to take over the cooking, though her dishes are worse than eating nothing. The clan asks Granny to come home, but she says she can’t. So Jane suggests to Jethro that he hire a cook, and he ends up getting a gorgeous cook that only speaks Italian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018013000 +0000" stop="20241018020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Exodus To Bleedwell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of Hooterville flock to nearby Bleedswell for jobs at the new defense plant. To keep people from leaving, Hooterville reopens its old airplane factory to fulfill its contract with the Army--signed during WWI.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018020000 +0000" stop="20241018023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The General Swap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan captures a German general to trade for an American general who dislikes Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018023000 +0000" stop="20241018030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018030000 +0000" stop="20241018033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Lynde And Nanette Fabray (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Paul Lynde and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/29/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018033000 +0000" stop="20241018043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Captain's Coins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Historian Phillip Andrews argues that his fiancée, Evelyn Faraday, is entitled to a share of a shipping company fortune. Phillip then finds himself accused of murdering the company's top man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018043500 +0000" stop="20241018050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteen-millimeter Shrine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging former movie star lives and dreams in the past, constantly watching her old movies alone in isolation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018050500 +0000" stop="20241018060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Lonely Place  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Dread stalks a ranch occupied by a farmer, his wife and a strange hired hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018060500 +0000" stop="20241018070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Crime That Wasn't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Dennis Coverly fears he and his family are in danger when a missing corpse is linked to a crime hit set for Mannix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018070500 +0000" stop="20241018080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018080500 +0000" stop="20241018090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Copy-cat Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband kills his wife's lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018090000 +0000" stop="20241018093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Store</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a masked gunman holds up several supermarkets, Dan Mathews sets an unusual trap to catch him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018093000 +0000" stop="20241018100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018100000 +0000" stop="20241018103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Man Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed, who is an optimist and still has faith in the human race, is subjected to ridicule from Officer Wells after he is swindled twice. On patrol, he and Malloy come to the aid of a woman whose baby has been kidnapped by a heavily armed man seeking a large ransom. Afterward, wells once again questions Reed's judgment during the search for an intoxicated sniper at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018103000 +0000" stop="20241018110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 165 -- Once A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The search for a stabbing suspect leads to a bitter ex-cop who has just moved into the area. Afterward, Malloy and Reed deal with a naive and frustrated starlet who shoots up a telephone booth and loses her suitcase containing a live rattle snake. The officers then become involved in shootout at a train station that leads to another unfortunate run-in with the ex-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018110000 +0000" stop="20241018120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Alum Chums</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer and Bill head back to campus for their college homecoming."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018120000 +0000" stop="20241018123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver spends the weekend at Larry's but the first night there they get into a terrible argument and Beaver goes home angry. After Ward tells Beaver a story about Damon and Pythias, Beaver and Larry swear to die for each other. Larry then promptly demands that Beaver give him his homework to prove himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018123000 +0000" stop="20241018130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Dance Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets an invitation to attend a cotillion with Mary Ellen Rogers. At first he wants to turn down the invitation, but then decides to go anyway, despite the fact that Mary Ellen has signed them up to do the cha-cha in a dance contest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018130000 +0000" stop="20241018140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lame Canary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ruth Prescott wants to divorce Walter Prescott so she can be with her true love, Jimmy MacLaine. After a brush with death, Ruth becomes convinced that Walter is trying to kill her, but then Walter turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018140000 +0000" stop="20241018150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.j.  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When radio disk jockey, and Michelle's new boyfriend, Arthur Saxon is accused of murdering a rival, Matlock agrees to defend him. Michelle swears he's the kindest, most gentle man she's ever known, but Matlock soon learns otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018150000 +0000" stop="20241018160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Paper Castles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil soon regrets telling an old friend that his new business partners are being investigated by the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018160000 +0000" stop="20241018170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Festival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>In spring of 1940, Jason practices his music for a town festival</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018170000 +0000" stop="20241018180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chato</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After a friend of Matt's dies, he goes to New Mexico to find the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018180000 +0000" stop="20241018190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Samuel Bellis is accused of desertion, murder and selling guns to the Indians. Bellis insists that he's innocent, and Candy believes him, but before he can clear Bellis' name, he must elude the Army patrol hot on the fugitive sergeant's heels.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018190000 +0000" stop="20241018193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Actress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A deathbed request from an old friend sends Lucas to a neighboring town in search of the man's long-lost sweetheart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018193000 +0000" stop="20241018200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Closer Than A Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for answers when recovering alcoholic Micah Torrence returns to the bottle—and turns in his badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018200000 +0000" stop="20241018210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charlene Brenton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby girl sure has a rough start when she arrives on the stage with her dead mother. Plague is what people think killed her and then Charlie Wooster steps in to try to help—and, well, you can imagine where it goes from there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018210000 +0000" stop="20241018220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dilemma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An elevator gets stuck between floors, and then the brake drum fails; inside, a man has a heart attack. A nursing student is in awe of Dr. Brackett; a fireman buff develops a crush on John, who tries to get rid of her. A man is injured in his junkyard. An industrial accident takes place at a railroad yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018220000 +0000" stop="20241018223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018223000 +0000" stop="20241018230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018230000 +0000" stop="20241018233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241018233000 +0000" stop="20241019000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019000000 +0000" stop="20241019003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry guitarist Jim Lindsey (James Best), a success as a solo artist, returns to a hero's welcome. However, Andy suspects trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019003000 +0000" stop="20241019010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bringing Up Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, believing that the jailhouse environment is adversely affecting Opie, forbids the lad to spend time at work with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019010000 +0000" stop="20241019013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Cook-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Even though the Clampetts are enjoying Maria’s cooking, Granny is upset that there is another cook in her kitchen. She wants Maria to leave, and Jed knows Maria leaving is the best thing to make everything right. However, Jethro is in love with Maria, hoping to marry her. Jane figures out a way to get Maria in good with Granny. She arranges a meeting between the two cooks, and Jane tells Maria to answer "Yes" to everything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019013000 +0000" stop="20241019020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>It's Human To Be Humane</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bored and looking for a project, Lisa becomes the head of the "Hooterville Human Humane Committee". She takes her cause to the extreme, declaring everything from duck hunting to selling chicken eggs off limits. Soon, the Douglases house is a zoo and the locals are ready to run her out of town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019020000 +0000" stop="20241019023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019023000 +0000" stop="20241019030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019030000 +0000" stop="20241019033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Lynde And Nanette Fabray (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Paul Lynde and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/29/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019033000 +0000" stop="20241019043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Carefree Coronary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Safeline Insurance Company notices an increase in heart attacks among their policy holders. The company suspects fraud and hires Mason and Paul to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019043500 +0000" stop="20241019050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Walking Distance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man decides to visit his hometown, he finds it exactly as it was when he was a child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019050500 +0000" stop="20241019060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Mcgregor Affair  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Dopey McGregor makes his living carrying boxes to a medical college, unaware that they contain the remains of murder victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019060500 +0000" stop="20241019070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Gathering Of Ghosts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange college reunion for Mannix's old football squad at a ghost town ends in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019070500 +0000" stop="20241019080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Conspiracy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank Cannon and Barnaby Jones team up for an investigation of a murder at a big corporation in which a deliveryman was charged with the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019080500 +0000" stop="20241019090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Simple Case Of Terror, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is tricked into thinking he committed a murder, but the real killer is his own friend who smuggles diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019090000 +0000" stop="20241019093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo becomes jealous of her sweetheart, aviator Steve Elliott, and her youngest sister, Betty Jo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019093000 +0000" stop="20241019100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>That's Max???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Billie Jo is stunned when Steve Elliott all but announces that he is about to marry a former girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019100000 +0000" stop="20241019103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Race For Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May enters a Beverly Hills beauty contest, Queen of Beverly Hills, and the Drysdales and Miss Jane try to make sure that she'll win. And when Granny hears it is a race, she is set on entering, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019103000 +0000" stop="20241019110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is looking for a beau for his gorgeous daughter, so Drysdale and Jane set Elly up with Fred Penrod, a young accountant at the bank. However, no one can seem to get his name straight. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns to plant a paw-paw tree in the back yard, really to look for the Clampett fortune he still believes is buried in the back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019110000 +0000" stop="20241019113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Too Weak To Work, My Pop, My Pop, Peep In The Deep</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bluto thinks he needs a complete rest; Popeye, however, soon teaches him that honest toil is best as he puts him through a workout in a rest hospital., Popeye is building a boat when his daddy, Poopdeck Pappy, insists on helping., When Popeye searches for treasure, Bluto tries to beat him to it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019113000 +0000" stop="20241019120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Calypso Cat, Out Foxed, Just Ducky</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom falls for a female cat but she quickly loses interest in him when they arrive at an island and Jerry torments him., Droopy is a member of a hunting kennel of dogs and must catch a fox to get a steak., When a duckling becomes separated from his mama duck, Jerry rescues the duckling from a hungry Tom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019120000 +0000" stop="20241019130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Woody Woodpecker Polka, The Mouse And The Lion, Chilly And The Woodchopper, Practical Yolk, The Flying Turtle, Case Of The Cold Storage Yegg, Woody Meets Daveycrewcut</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody disguises himself as a lovely lady to woo Wally Walrus and get into the dance for free., A Foolish Fable Cartoon. A mouse captures a Lion, the King of the Jungle, to have him perform a tight-rope act in a US circus., Chilly stows away in a woodchopper's bag. When Chilly arrives at Smedley's Rest Home, Smedley attempts to get rid of the stowaway., In Egypt, Woody eats and destroys the ancient Egyptian eggs that famous explorer Miss Meany is trying to collect., A Foolish Fable Cartoon. Herman the Turtle tries everything to learn how to fly only to get killed in the processs and turned into an angel with wings., Inspector Willoughby follows bank robber Yeggs Benedict around the world in an attempt to capture him., A bear convinces Davy Crewcut (a parody of Davy Crockett) to hunt woodpecker instead."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019130000 +0000" stop="20241019140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare Brush, Mouse-taken Identity, Touché And Go, Jack-wabbit And The Beanstalk, Lumber Jerks, Roadrunner A Go-go, Now Hare This</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs believes he’s a human and goes hunting for Elmer Fudd who believes he’s a rabbit. , Sylvester takes his son, Junior, to work with him for the first time. To show off to his son he must chase Hippetty Hopper, who has escaped from the zoo, all over the museum trying to catch him., Pepe LePew believes he has found a female skunk, but she is really a black cat who accidentally got a white stripe painted across her back., The Giant catches Bugs Bunny in the act of chopping carrots in his victory garden. Instead of running, Bugs slaps the dopey giant with his glove and challenges him to a duel with pistols. , As the Gophers prepare for winter, their tree is moved to a local saw mill., The Road Runner is at it again! , In this parody of Little Red Riding Hood and Goldilocks, Bugs faces off against a big bad wolf."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019140000 +0000" stop="20241019150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Skulls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim goes on the run from the government when he shoots and kills Artie. But a criminal organization captures him and puts him on trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019150000 +0000" stop="20241019160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sam Livingston Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Abigail has lost her driver to the better paying mines. Her new driver says he owns a bank and a pig. The ride west reveals another side of him, one that takes at least the pig to change both heart and mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019160000 +0000" stop="20241019170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Young Marauders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Audra is saved from serious injury by a young man who says he is a mustang hunter. She falls in love with him; her brothers find him a suspicious character.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019170000 +0000" stop="20241019180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Noose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty is held hostage in a ghost town as bait to get Matt to attempt a rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019180000 +0000" stop="20241019190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Way Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam finds shelter overnight at a stagecoach way station. There he meets others ranging from a beautiful girl to a dangerous outlaw on the run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019190000 +0000" stop="20241019193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas agrees to take a job as a federal undercover agent and goes to Wyoming to investigate rumors of sales of arms to renegade indians. His life is endangered by the town drunk, who stumbles onto his true identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019193000 +0000" stop="20241019200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark stays with Miss Milly, while Lucas is in Wyoming on the trail of a gang illegally selling weapons to the Indians. Mark suffers from loneliness and doubt while his father is away for two months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019200000 +0000" stop="20241019210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Married Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In Calvin, Miss Abigail owns The Silver Slipper Salon, a very posh saloon. There Rowdy sees the picture of the dead war hero, Gil Favor, Abigail's husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019210000 +0000" stop="20241019213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>First, Catch A Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Two of the three men who brought in and helped to hang an outlaw have been killed by an assassin. The third man, Paladin, is staying at a hotel where one of the guests is the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019213000 +0000" stop="20241019220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Bounty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A reclusive old man with an Apache bodyguard is wanted for a crime committed long ago. Randall tags along with an overeager bounty hunter to ensure the man is brought back alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241019220000 +0000" stop="20241020000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Loot, Hot Stuff, Flagpole Jitters, Rumpus In The Harem, Oils Well That Ends Well, Snitch In Time</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are willed a lot of dough from a rich uncle, but the executor of the estate, Icabob Slipp, is a crook who absconds with the money.  The Stooges trail him to a theater where they engage in a wild chase and ultimately recover their inheritance.  [ the opening scenes are taken from "Hold that Lion".  ] , The Stooges are government agent entrusted with protecting professor Sneed, who has invented a super rocket fuel.  Larry is mistaken for the professor by foreign agents who kidnap the trio and take them to the country of Anemia where they are ordered to produce the rocket fuel or be executed.  The boys come up with a concoction they try to pass of as the real stuff, but are exposed when the real professor and his daughter are also kidnapped.  The Stooges help them escape, using their secret formula to fuel a jeep. , The Stooges are carpenters who are re-staining some furniture they've delivered to a boarding house.  The plot gets complicated when the boys confront some crooks who are hiding out there.  They defeat the bad guys with the help of the varnished furniture, which sticks the head crook to a chair. , The Stooges are taking care of their invalid friend Mary who is confined to wheelchair.  At their jobs in a theater, where they hope to earn money for an operation for Mary, they witness a hypnotist, doing his act.  The Stooges become subjects for his show and are hypnotized into walking out on a flagpole high above the ground.  When they come out of their trance and realize their predicament they fall into a window and foil a robbery in progress thus earning reward money to pay for Mary's operation.  [ A remake of "Hocus Pocus".] , Set in a desert land where the Stooges run a restaurant, the boys need money to pay their fiancee's taxes, or the girls will be sold as slaves.  Some crooks come into their restaurant and convince the boys to recover the stolen Rootin Tootin diamond.  The Stooges decide to return the diamond to the government and get the reward money.  They learn that the Emir of Shmo has absconded with the contraband jewel.  They journey to the stronghold of Shmo where they disguise as Santa Clauses and scare the ruler into giving them the diamond. , The Stooges need money for their father's operation, so they head for the country to prospect for uranium.  Instead of uranium, they discover oil on their father's property and all their troubles are solved. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020000000 +0000" stop="20241020023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>House Of Wax (1953)</sub-title>
    <desc>"An associate burns down a wax museum with the owner inside, but he survives only to become vengeful and murderous."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020023000 +0000" stop="20241020050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Labyrinth</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sixteen-year-old Sarah must solve a labyrinth to rescue her baby brother when he is taken by the Goblin King."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020050000 +0000" stop="20241020060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Spanish Moss Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A dreaming host conjures up the Creole legend of Père Malfait ("Father of Evil"), a moss-monster willing to kill anyone who threatens its survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020060000 +0000" stop="20241020070000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Werewolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In snowy Chicago the INS Christmas party is to send off Tony Vincenzo, but he gets audited instead, and it is Carl who gets to go on the singles cruise, where a werewolf goes on a killing spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020070000 +0000" stop="20241020080000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. R.i.n.g.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>An android murders anyone that threatens its survival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020080000 +0000" stop="20241020090000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Vampire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An overlooked victim of the Las Vegas vampire makes her way to Los Angeles and begins killing anew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020090000 +0000" stop="20241020100000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Ripper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kolchak argues that a serial killer is actually Jack the Ripper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020100000 +0000" stop="20241020110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Hand</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matthew and Walt go to Las Vegas to investigate rigged games."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020110000 +0000" stop="20241020113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Cut Day   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's senior cut day. Zack does his best not to get caught by Belding. Meanwhile, Jessie protests the use of plastic cups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020113000 +0000" stop="20241020120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>School Song   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang decides to write a new school song together for a Bayside competition. Zack schemes to get them to compete against one another, and when they find out it's time for revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020120000 +0000" stop="20241020123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Senior Prom   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's up to the gang to raise the funds needed for the senior prom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020123000 +0000" stop="20241020130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Graduation   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On graduation day, Zack discovers that he is one credit short of getting his diploma, and the only way he can earn it is by doing the unbelievable—BALLET!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020130000 +0000" stop="20241020133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Time Capsule   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mr. Belding and the class of 2003 find a video time capsule from the class of 1993. The video shows the funny and the touching moments Zack and the gang shared with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020133000 +0000" stop="20241020140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>King Of The Hill   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack starts high school ready to woo longtime crush Kelly, but A.C. Slater stands in his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020140000 +0000" stop="20241020143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Driver's Seat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg bets Marcia that she can't beat his score on her driver's test. However all the pressure gets the best of Marcia. Meanwhile, Jan must also deal with the pressure of speaking in front of a large group of people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020143000 +0000" stop="20241020150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of This World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After meeting an astronaut, Bobby and Peter begin wondering about life on other planets. Their wonder turns to excitement when they claim to have spotted a UFO and camp out in the backyard to get it on film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020150000 +0000" stop="20241020153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Father &amp; Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie goes to a Leopard Lodge convention with Howard in Chicago despite wanting to go to a Bears game with Potsie and Ralph.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020153000 +0000" stop="20241020160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Note</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne gets upset when she finds a short note from Shirley stating that she and her new husband are moving overseas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020160000 +0000" stop="20241020163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Bully</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolboy bully makes life miserable for seven-year-old Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020163000 +0000" stop="20241020170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Ricardos Change Apartments</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Now that they have Little Ricky, Lucy insists they need more room and wants to change apartments with one of the other tenants (Mrs. Benson) She convinces a reluctant Ricky by cluttering their apartment with baby things and assorted junk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020170000 +0000" stop="20241020173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Fund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry have been put in charge of the class cookie fund and are taking turns guarding the money. A new kid takes advantage of them and cons Beaver and Larry out of three dollars from the fund.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020173000 +0000" stop="20241020180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Forgotten Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Beaver's, David Manning, invites him to a birthday party and Beaver promises to attend, but as the week passes Beaver forgets all about it. When the day arrives, June, Ward and Wally scramble to find the Beaver, who is spending the day with Larry, wandering around town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020180000 +0000" stop="20241020183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Son Of Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May and her new beau, Fred Penron, are getting rather serious. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns, this time with his son, Dub. He plans to set Dub up with Elly, to once again try to get some of Jed's money. Jed and Jethro try to hide this from Granny because the Cricks really rile her up. She sees the Cricks, but Jed tries to convince her that she is having visions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020183000 +0000" stop="20241020190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Fishing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale and Jane try to get the Clampetts interested in deep-sea fishing, but face an obstacle: Granny. She has a fear of water and refuses to go on a boat. So, Jane comes up with the idea of letting them visit Marineland. They decide to go right away and are impressed by the giant fishing holes. And Granny sees the fish of fishes, a giant whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020190000 +0000" stop="20241020193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan Vs. Gilligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan meets his double, a foreign spy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020193000 +0000" stop="20241020200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Pass The Vegetables, Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan finds a crate of radioactive vegetable seeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020200000 +0000" stop="20241020203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Cat's Meow  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Iola has her dead cat freeze-dried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020203000 +0000" stop="20241020210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Gets The Bird  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama's crazy old Uncle Oscar passes on, he leaves her his talking parrot, Captain Petey, who convinces the family that treasure is hidden somewhere in the house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020210000 +0000" stop="20241020220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Eyes Of Love / Masquerade / Hollywood Royalty (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 2. Thieves eye a honeymooning actress's gems; a man encounters his blind childhood love; a wife meets her spouse's mistress."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020220000 +0000" stop="20241020223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Replacement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy is grooming a new man to replace him as deputy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020223000 +0000" stop="20241020230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Larry Strothe- Creature From The Black Lagoon</sub-title>
    <desc>"There may be no one more enthusiastic and energetic about the Creature from the Black Lagoon than Larry Strothe. A devoted collector ever since he was a kid, Larry’s monster-sized collection features everything from a life-sized Creature to a hard-to-get-Christmas ornament to some Monster Magazine cover art. Larry’s brought along his good buddy and Monster Party podcast sparring partner, Matt Weinhold to step up the fun. Joining Lisa today--much to our collector’s delight, is our expert John Gilbert, AKA The Arizona Gill-man, who will appraise Larry’s collection and then try to pull off a seemingly impossible trade that means a lot to both our collector and expert."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020230000 +0000" stop="20241020233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241020233000 +0000" stop="20241021000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021000000 +0000" stop="20241021003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Saga Of Cousin Oscar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is furious with his houseguest, Cousin Oscar. It seems when they were kids, Oscar bullied Archie and now Oscar is taking full advantage of his visit at the Bunkers. Archie wants to throw him out, but Oscar makes an exit of his own when he turns up dead. This leaves Archie left with the funeral arrangements which drives him up the wall after looking over the costs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021003000 +0000" stop="20241021010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's refusal to particpate in a chain letter triggers a string of unlikely events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021010000 +0000" stop="20241021013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Beverly Rides Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>As a practical joke, Archie fixes up one of his drinking buddies with female impersonator Beverly La Salle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021013000 +0000" stop="20241021020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Teresa Moves In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers take in a boarder to help revive their battered budget.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021020000 +0000" stop="20241021023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Barbara Mcnair And Sid Casesar</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Barbara McNair and Sid Casesar. Originally aired on 05/06/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021023000 +0000" stop="20241021030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/15/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021030000 +0000" stop="20241021033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Who And Where Was Antonio Stradivarius?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob gets amnesia from a violin!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021033000 +0000" stop="20241021040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle George is on the search for wife and can't help but fall for Sally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021040000 +0000" stop="20241021043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Oh My Aching Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph hurts his back at a bowling tournament the night before his physical exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021043000 +0000" stop="20241021050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Escape Clause</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hypochondriac exchanges his soul for immortality and indestructibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021050000 +0000" stop="20241021060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Misadventure  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An outsider forms a wobbly coalition with an insatiable woman bent on murdering her rich husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021060000 +0000" stop="20241021070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare At Northoak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble is injured while helping save some children from a fiery crash. While recuperating at a local home, he learns that his caretakers are the local sheriff and his wife. As if this weren't bad enough, a news article describing Kimble's heroic deed goes</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021070000 +0000" stop="20241021080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Agent Norvan Kruger knows about his country's plans to launch some kind of attack that will devastate the world. He's been captured by a second country unfriendly to the U.S. The IMF must spirit Norvan away from his captors in order to learn how to stop the attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021080000 +0000" stop="20241021083000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Double Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wrongly-convicted parolee becomes coldly determined to get revenge on his former business partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021083000 +0000" stop="20241021090000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021090000 +0000" stop="20241021093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021093000 +0000" stop="20241021100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - Dr-33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Crosby plays a hippie whose wife has been persuaded—by other hippies—to pass bad checks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021100000 +0000" stop="20241021103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 76 -- The Militants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed participate in the search for two black militants who ambush and critically wound two officers in their patrol car. When one of the suspects subsequently dies in custody, a bitter public relations battle begins with the militant group as the search for the other suspect continues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021103000 +0000" stop="20241021110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 164 -- The Poachers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young employee at the city garage steals a patrol car and engages in a high speed pursuit. Afterward, Malloy and Reed arrest a young woman trying to cash an old-age benefits check she found on the ground, report to an apartment complex garage that had its security camera stolen, investigate a break-in at a mortuary and arrest a couple of pill pushers at a warehouse in Officer Ed Well's territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021110000 +0000" stop="20241021120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Transylvania Mania</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit the vampire mecca."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021120000 +0000" stop="20241021123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Athlete</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting a poor grade in gym class on his report card, Beaver becomes determined to prove to everyone that he is a good athlete, so he signs up to play baseball—where it's the boys versus the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021123000 +0000" stop="20241021130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Found Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry invites Beaver to the carnival and tells him that his mother will treat him. However, when Mrs. Mondello refuses to give Larry money, Larry decides to find some. So Larry throws some of his mother's money out the window and when Beaver comes over, Larry pretends as if he's found it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021130000 +0000" stop="20241021140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spurious Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Chapman returns home early from a business trip to find that his wife, Marie, wants a divorce. Chapman is shocked at this turn of events because he thought his wife had recently been strangled to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021140000 +0000" stop="20241021150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Police Officer Jim Shanley is found dead, Sergeant Jerry Reese is charged with the crime. Everyone thinks he's guilty, especially Shanley's partner. In defending Reese, Matlock begins to realize that an old cop buddy of his isn't the man he used to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021150000 +0000" stop="20241021160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Laid To Waste</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Parker protects a blind woman who heard her neighbors murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021160000 +0000" stop="20241021170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Olivia celebrate their 25th wedding anniversary</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021170000 +0000" stop="20241021180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Stark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam, the son of one of Dodge City's revered citizens returns. But upon arriving someone takes a shot at him. The man who shot him, Stark, is a bounty hunter. It seems that Adam was in jail in Texas and broke out, and Stark aims to bring him back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021180000 +0000" stop="20241021190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The War Comes To Washoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Adam's differences in politics lead to unrest in the house. When Joe is picked to go to a convention on the statehood of Nevada, will his relationship with a admitted Confederate's daughter weigh his decision?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021190000 +0000" stop="20241021193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Treasure Of Canyon Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In a ghost town, Lucas, Mark and Micah tangle with the Newman family and learn the secret of the town's 20-year-old mystery of a lost gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021193000 +0000" stop="20241021200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Day At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in an explosion, Lucas fights despair as he prepares for a meeting with a gun-toting enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021200000 +0000" stop="20241021210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Shadrack Bennington Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Shadrack Bennington has been a cavalier of the open road, not wanting to be tied down until he joins the wagon train, heading for San Francisco and a future even he couldn't anticipate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021210000 +0000" stop="20241021220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Hang-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A jewel thief is trapped in an air-conditioning duct. Two battered men continue their brawl in the hospital. A man ruins his cast by going surfing. Dr. Brackett treats a woman with a neurological disorder. Radioactivity impedes the rescue of a lab worker. Johnny misses the end of an 'Adam-12' episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021220000 +0000" stop="20241021223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021223000 +0000" stop="20241021230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021230000 +0000" stop="20241021233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241021233000 +0000" stop="20241022000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022000000 +0000" stop="20241022003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022003000 +0000" stop="20241022010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Bankrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Myers is about to get evicted by the city council when he discovers an old bond that the city of Mayberry issued 100 years ago. Mayberry now owes him $350,000 and can't pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022010000 +0000" stop="20241022013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is very excited about graduating from the sixth grade. But in order to prevent embarrassment, Mrs. Potts gets help from Drysdale and Diana to get Jethro to miss his sixth grade graduation. She schemes to turn Jed and Jethro’s watches back 45 minutes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022013000 +0000" stop="20241022020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Never Take Your Wife To A Convention</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The only thing Oliver learns at a farming convention is how to get a hangover. He and Lisa meet up with Charlie, a former gangster-turned-farmer, and Wanda, his floozy dancer wife. The more Charlie talks about his farm, the more Oliver's convinced that his shady days are not in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022020000 +0000" stop="20241022023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022023000 +0000" stop="20241022030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022030000 +0000" stop="20241022033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022033000 +0000" stop="20241022043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hasty Honeymooner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas Tolliver arrives in California from Oklahoma to meet the woman he was matched up with by a computer dating service. The woman, Miliicent Barton, is supposedly a rich widow.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022043500 +0000" stop="20241022050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A convict serving time isolated on an asteroid receives a gift: a robot that looks, sounds and acts like a real woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022050500 +0000" stop="20241022060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Triumph  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When two missionaries arrive at a remote medical mission in the Indian jungle, jealousy leads to murder and a coverup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022060500 +0000" stop="20241022070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Day Filled With Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When a basketball star disappears, his family hires Mannix to hunt him down—before the syndicate does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022070500 +0000" stop="20241022080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Medicine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates a doctors claim that he is innocent of a death he was charged with concerning a patient he was treating that had slipped into a diabetic coma. Cannon becomes involved in a medical malpractice suit when a young resident physician is charged with making the wrong diagnosis on a woman in an apparent diabetic coma who dies after his treatment. Hired by the hospital facing a two million dollar suit, Cannon hears testimony of the accused Dr. Jeff Reston, played by guest star David Birney, that the woman he treated wore a diabetic's bracelet. She was, in fact, suffering from hypoglycemia. But the bracelet disappeared and none of the nurses attending with Reston can back up his story. Reston then gives Cannon a motive for a possible conspiracy against him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022080500 +0000" stop="20241022090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Marathon Murders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the death of a heavily-insured man that is believed to be an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022090000 +0000" stop="20241022093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hideout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews rushes to the scene when a woman kills a wanted thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022093000 +0000" stop="20241022100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022100000 +0000" stop="20241022103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022103000 +0000" stop="20241022110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022110000 +0000" stop="20241022120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Our Worst Nightmares</sub-title>
    <desc>"A wicked fish gives Bill, Toony, Quizzer, Simon Shock, and Teddy bad dreams!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022120000 +0000" stop="20241022123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Most Interesting Character</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers assigns Beaver's class to write a short essay about the most interesting character they know. While Judy writes about her dad, Beaver debates over whom he should write about. Beaver finally decides to write about Ward, but Beaver isn't sure if Ward is interesting enough.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022123000 +0000" stop="20241022130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Date Committee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally becomes the chairman of the blind date committee for an upcoming dance. However, Wally quickly wants to resign from the position when he can't find anyone to go with the new girl, Jill Bartlett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022130000 +0000" stop="20241022140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Watery Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lorna Thomas is a has-been actress who once gave up her baby for adoption and lived to regret it. George Clark discovers that his wife might be Lorna's long-lost daughter and begins to see dollar signs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022140000 +0000" stop="20241022150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022150000 +0000" stop="20241022160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>First Deadly Sin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial rapist stalks Sparta.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022160000 +0000" stop="20241022170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason helps Verdie research her family tree</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022170000 +0000" stop="20241022180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sam Mctavish, M.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of the first woman doctor in Dodge City, Dr. Sam McTavish, riles Doc Adams. However, she soon wins his confidence and that of his patients, and the two physicians make a startling medical discovery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022180000 +0000" stop="20241022190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss picks up a mail order bride for a friend, but problems arise when the bride decides she has fallen in love with Hoss and has no interest in her husband to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022190000 +0000" stop="20241022193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Two ex-Confederate officers seek revenge on Lucas. McCain was a lieutenant in the 8th Indiana, which defeated the 12th Cavalry 15 years earlier at the Battle of Fort Donaldson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022193000 +0000" stop="20241022200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Assault</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman can't talk his way out of an assault charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022200000 +0000" stop="20241022210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Wagons Ho!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While preparing to return to St. Joseph, the men read the story "Wagon Ho" written and printed by Samuel T. Evans about his trip as a naive young Irishman headed west and his experiences and adventure on the trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022210000 +0000" stop="20241022220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Crash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy bring in a football player who was tackled too hard. A burglar has a heart attack. John wants Roy to apologize for calling him "some kind of nut." Dr. Early treats a hypochondriac. A babysitter brings in a child who has swallowed some pills. Roy and John rescue the occupants of a light plane that crashed in a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022220000 +0000" stop="20241022223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022223000 +0000" stop="20241022230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022230000 +0000" stop="20241022233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241022233000 +0000" stop="20241023000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023000000 +0000" stop="20241023003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney On The Rebound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After a tiff with Thelma Lou, Barney is victimized by a scheming young couple.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023003000 +0000" stop="20241023010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023010000 +0000" stop="20241023013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Homer Noodleman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts leave Hooterville after spending Thanksgiving there. They return to their mansion, telling Drysdale and Jane about the boy Elly started dating. When Drysdale hears of this, he decides to get a country boy to come and court Elly. He employs Dash Riprock to play country boy Homer Noodleman. After the Clampetts are introduced to Homer, Granny wants to meet his father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023013000 +0000" stop="20241023020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Computer Age</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate Ralph Monroe joins a computer dating service to meet a husband. Oliver thinks it's a great idea since computers are always right. Lisa thinks they can't possibly take the place of romance, so she challenges Oliver to test their match-up on the electric brain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023020000 +0000" stop="20241023023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everyone Has A Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plot to destroy an ammunition train is foiled by Burkhalter's brother-in-law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023023000 +0000" stop="20241023030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses an incredibly original ruse to get Schultz a weeklong furlough in Heidelberg. While there, Schultz is to deliver needed radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023030000 +0000" stop="20241023033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023033000 +0000" stop="20241023043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The 12th Wildcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Burt Payne coaches and owns 10% of a professional football team. His rich wife, Ellen, owns the remainder. Knowing that he's washed up and needing some quick cash, Burt tries to sell his share of the team to a group of investors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023043500 +0000" stop="20241023050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023050500 +0000" stop="20241023060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From Purgatory  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>In a Brooklyn slum, an aspiring author joins a gang of hoodlums to collect material for a book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023060500 +0000" stop="20241023070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Voices In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A former championship diver, now disabled, believes she is going to be murdered after receiving death threats.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023070500 +0000" stop="20241023080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Iceman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon reopens an investigation when he discovers a convicted man may be innocent, but then refuses parole. Robert Foxworth is the villain. He plays a murderer, an ex-Green Beret who served in Vietnam with overtones of CIA activity. The murdered man was Cannon's friend, and that brings him into the case. When the convicted murderer turns down a parole, Cannon becomes very curious."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023080500 +0000" stop="20241023090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A blind girl is Barnaby's only lead in his search for a missing coed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023090000 +0000" stop="20241023093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's March</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews investigates when a local beautician is blamed for a crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023093000 +0000" stop="20241023100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023100000 +0000" stop="20241023103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023103000 +0000" stop="20241023110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023110000 +0000" stop="20241023120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Murder Mystery...</sub-title>
    <desc>"Someone has killed Mr. Quizzer! Can you solve the mystery? (Don't worry, it's just a game.)"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023120000 +0000" stop="20241023123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Bath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June allow Wally to babysit Beaver one evening while they attend a party. However, things go awry when Beaver gets ready to take a bath. He accidentally lets the bathtub overflow, causing the water to leak onto the bathroom floor and into the downstairs ceiling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023123000 +0000" stop="20241023130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A new school year has the bus service being extended to those students living in town. However, after not even a week, Beaver gets suspended from riding the bus after getting into a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023130000 +0000" stop="20241023140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Garrulous Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry Benton is a hard-luck guy. He gets in an argument in a poker game and knocks Mike Granger out cold. Then he is informed him that Granger is dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023140000 +0000" stop="20241023150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Crook</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Wally McDaniels, a fellow choir member, after he is arrested for killing the man who had turned him in to the police for stealing rare books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023150000 +0000" stop="20241023160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Just A Country Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to Los Angeles to arrest an arsonist. When the man is murdered to keep him from talking Bubba teams up with a pretty insurance investigator to solve the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023160000 +0000" stop="20241023170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023170000 +0000" stop="20241023180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gentry's Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A baron gives Matt trouble when Matt wants the man's sons in jail for a crime they committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023180000 +0000" stop="20241023190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Beginning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe befriends a young man, Billy Horne, a white man captured and raised by the Shoshones. Meanwhile, Milton Tanner goes after a third of the Ponderosa. Seeing that his new friends are in trouble, Billy takes matters into his own hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023190000 +0000" stop="20241023193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Short Rope For A Tall Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are in another town to sell a bull to Joe Lovering. While there, Mark buys two horses from Mr. Schneider. Neither Mark nor his father knows that the horses have been illegally bought and resold to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023193000 +0000" stop="20241023200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Bibs Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor-turned-gunfighter's reputation hangs on one lucky shot—and a lot of gall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023200000 +0000" stop="20241023210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Horace Best Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Adams' "distant" cousin Horace arrives hoping to be a wagon master. His trading skills allow him to steal the crew and vendors from Adams, but when Adams confronts him with the decisions he must make on the trail, there are second thoughts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023210000 +0000" stop="20241023220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Decision (a.k.a. Problem)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John rescue a man whose engine has fallen on him during his car repair work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023220000 +0000" stop="20241023223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023223000 +0000" stop="20241023230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023230000 +0000" stop="20241023233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241023233000 +0000" stop="20241024000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024000000 +0000" stop="20241024003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Crime-free Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are honored for achieving the lowest crime-rate in the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024003000 +0000" stop="20241024010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy learns a great deal about Thelma Lou's cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024010000 +0000" stop="20241024013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Hot-rod Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro wants a new car, embarrassed by the truck. He buys two new cars for two different images he is trying. But Jed tells him to just get a few new parts for the truck. Granny, who is celebrating her birthday, believes that they are planning to replace her. But she learns the truth, and wants the truck to stay the way it was. Jethro ends up getting a whole new front for the truck, and when Jed tells him to fix it, he gets a whole new back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024013000 +0000" stop="20241024020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Liberation Movement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lisa hears a women's liberation speaker, she demands that Oliver share the household chores while she runs the farm. While he meets with nothing but red tape while trying to build a tool shed, Lisa gets the permit and completes the building with ease. A skeptical Oliver is in disbelief that his wife is so successful at "men's work".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024020000 +0000" stop="20241024023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reverend Kommandant Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan sneaks a French pilot's girl into camp and gets Klink to marry them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024023000 +0000" stop="20241024030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Escape-proof Camp I've Ever Escaped From</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Klink's "no escape" record is jeopardized when Malcom Flood, a British escape artist, lands in Stalag 13 and intends to continue his impressive escape record, a plan likely to endanger Hogan's scheduled rendezvous with an OSS agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024030000 +0000" stop="20241024033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024033000 +0000" stop="20241024043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wrathful Wraith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Louise Self finds herself in the unfortunate position of having to stand trial for the murder of her husband twice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024043500 +0000" stop="20241024050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is terrified of falling asleep for fear he might die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024050500 +0000" stop="20241024060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Consider Her Ways  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A physician tries to stop her hallucinatory vision of an all-female society from becoming a reality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024060500 +0000" stop="20241024070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Color Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A witness against a crime boss is murdered just before he can reveal the syndicate's plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024070500 +0000" stop="20241024080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024080500 +0000" stop="20241024090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Circle Of Treachery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>As a thief awaits trial, his accomplice puts out a contract on the only witness to the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024090000 +0000" stop="20241024093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Slain Cabby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews uses taxi drivers as bait for criminals.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
