<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104000000 +0000" stop="20250104003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104003000 +0000" stop="20250104010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104010000 +0000" stop="20250104013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104013000 +0000" stop="20250104020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie goes to the carnival and blows all his money on a game to win a birthday gift for Andy. The game, however, is rigged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104020000 +0000" stop="20250104023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Grunion Invasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts prepare to go fight the invading Grunion, while Drysdale works to keep the Clampetts believing Mark has turned coward. The Clampetts head to the beach and set up their headquarters. They look out on the water and see a couple of surfers and mistake them for the Grunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104023000 +0000" stop="20250104030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Learns A Bully</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A troublemaker transfers into the platoon and decides to make Pyle his patsy. Gomer handles him with kindness, but soon learns that he needs to stand up to the brute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104030000 +0000" stop="20250104033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Meister Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men pose as Nazi officers to get an American traitor to divulge the names of his German superiors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104033000 +0000" stop="20250104040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>That's No Lady, That's My Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk poses as a general's wife to get penicillin to an ill underground leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104040000 +0000" stop="20250104043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Joel Grey And Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol meets Vicki's mama's-boy boyfriend. Then, in The Switchboard, Carol plays a nosey operator who eavesdrops on the romantic entanglements of the hotel guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104043000 +0000" stop="20250104053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fiery Fingers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When wealthy Louise Gordon is poisoned to death her nurse is charged with the crime. Mason does some digging and discovers that the first wife of the victim's husband also died of poisoning. Is the husband really the culprit or could it be someone else?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104053500 +0000" stop="20250104060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Before he died, notorious gunslinger Pinto Sykes put a curse on hired gun Conny Miller. When Miller returns to town, he is challenged to visit Sykes' grave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104060500 +0000" stop="20250104063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Vicious Circle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A hit man has to choose between his childhood sweetheart and obeying his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104063500 +0000" stop="20250104070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Three Dreams Of Findlater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband dreams constantly of a beautiful woman who prompts him to kill his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104070500 +0000" stop="20250104080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Way To Dusty Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix ruffles some feathers in a small town when he arrives in search of a missing youth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104080500 +0000" stop="20250104090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Predators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon believes that this time he has accepted a peaceful job. He must protect the bar of a friend, Millie Carroll, against robberies. However, suddenly he finds himself amid a complex love story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104090500 +0000" stop="20250104100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Target Of A Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An heiress doesn't know that the fortune hunter she's fallen for has murdered her benefactor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104100000 +0000" stop="20250104103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>A Horse On You, Mr. Bedloe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad executive Homer Bedloe shows up again with a new scheme to get the Cannonball discontinued.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104103000 +0000" stop="20250104110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Kate's Day In Court</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate decides to contest a jaywalking ticket she receives in Pixley.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104110000 +0000" stop="20250104113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Common Cold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is looking to cure people and learns of Mr. Drysdale’s illness. He has a common cold. Granny says that she has the ability to cure it with one spoonful of “cold cure.” She makes her cold cure to share with Dr. Clyburn, but he turns her down and mean-mouths her. So she decides to start her own doctor’s office and use her cold cure to treat folks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104113000 +0000" stop="20250104120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed The Heartbreaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale is tired of the Clampetts, especially Granny, who keeps scraping with her. When Miss Jane tells her of a beautiful movie starlet who threw herself at Jed and how Jed stopped going to his movie studio when he found out she was married, she plans a scheme herself. Mrs. Drysdale decides to throw herself at Jed to get him and his family to move away from Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104120000 +0000" stop="20250104123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Wimmin Hadn’t Oughta Drive, Flies Ain’t Human, Olive Oyl For President, Nearlyweds</sub-title>
    <desc>"There's plenty of excitement when Popeye takes Olive Oyl out for a driving lesson., A stubborn fly causes problems for Popeye., Tired of political rhetoric, Olive lays out her platform., Popeye and Bluto both plan to marry Olive Oyl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104123000 +0000" stop="20250104130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Catty Cornered, Poor Little Me, Jerry's Diary</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom and another cat compete against one another to claim the prize, which is Jerry., Bunnies, turtles, and other small woodland animals play., Tom gets tired of chasing Jerry so he takes a seat and finds Jerry's Diary which he checks out."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104130000 +0000" stop="20250104140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Coo Coo Nuts, Mousie Come Home, Plywood Panic, Careless Caretaker, Under Sea Dogs, Candyland, Sleep Happy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody is stranded on an island with a hungry castaway that likes woodpeckers., Andy Panda and Milo move to avoid a mouse., Milford the pig wins Maw &amp; Paw a new house, but they have to build it themselves., Smedley is a caretaker of the trees in a park, and gets angry when Woody starts pecking at the eldest tree. Woody tries to convince Smedley that he tree is sick., Maxie decides to mess with a submarine explorer when his vessel crashes into their igloo., The Sandman takes a boy and his puppy to Candyland., Woody takes advantage of a vacancy in Wally Walrus' house and keeps him up all night with his unusualy snoring."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104140000 +0000" stop="20250104150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Case Of The Missing Hare, Believe It Or Else, Hare-um Scare-um, You Were Never Duckier, By Word Of Mouse, Prince Violent</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs ruins a magician's theatre act. , A montage of believe-it-or-not gags. , Bugs battles with a hunter appearing in various guises and making doors appear that lead to nowhere. , Daffy dresses up to win a Rooster Contest and gets grabed by Henery Hawk. , A foreigner mouse comes to America and is amazed by its economic system. He goes to a mouse professor who explains how it works while they are being chased by Sylvester. , Bugs tries to protect a castle by kicking Sam the Terrible out and not letting him back in. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104150000 +0000" stop="20250104160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Surreal Mccoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Agents West and Gordon are guarding a museum containing the famous Herzberg jewels but someone still manages to steal the gems. Afterwards, a famous painting of a Western scene is removed from the museum by its wealthy rancher-owner. Gordon becomes suspicious and notifies West who discovers that the rancher is partners with Miguelito Loveless, the evil inventor-doctor. His latest invention is a machine that moves real people in and out of paintings. Miguelito's plan is to transpose murderers into famous paintings, distribute the paintings to the rulers of the world and have them all killed!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104160000 +0000" stop="20250104170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cole Crawford Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>"The young Crawford couple is trying to leave their past behind but having difficulty doing it. The wagon train is crossing a massive ranch and the owner's son refuses to let Mrs. Crawford leave nor will the train members help them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104170000 +0000" stop="20250104180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Brawlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of Irish immigrants settles on Barkley land, believing they have bought the land from a reputable agent. Nick thinks of them purely as squatters, while they refuse to believe they've been scammed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104180000 +0000" stop="20250104190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Whelan's Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A former lawman that Dillon put out of business years earlier comes back with a group of men to gun him down. Since Dillon is out of town, they settle in at the Long Branch to play poker and wait.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104190000 +0000" stop="20250104200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Wild One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Jessup doesn't really want to be married, and now he's about to be a father! The horse wrangler finds a fight with Hoss at his reluctance to perform his duties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104200000 +0000" stop="20250104203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple moves to North Fork under an assumed name to hide the fact that they are the parents of a vicious killer. The plan backfires when the son shows up at their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104203000 +0000" stop="20250104210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After foiling a girl's attempt to rob the general store, Lucas finds that she and her brother are plotting the murder of their abusive stepfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104210000 +0000" stop="20250104220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of Iron Bull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Joseph, a Comanche, is hired after returning the remuda. Colonel Macklin and Sergeant Grogan are accompanying the herd as far as Waycross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104220000 +0000" stop="20250104223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Champaigne Safari</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gravely, an old friend of Paladin, asks Paladin to help when a member of his hunting party is killed in an Indian attack. Gravely arranged a phony attack to provide excitement for his clients and doesn't believe the killing was an accident."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104223000 +0000" stop="20250104230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Of Red Rock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is bushwhacked by bounty hunters in cahoots with the local sheriff, who now must keep Josh from blowing the whistle on their illegal but lucrative "bounty game."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250104230000 +0000" stop="20250105010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Disorder In The Court***, Beer Barrel Polecats, Three Loan Wolves, Three Hams On Rye, Three Dark Horses, Pardon My Clutch</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are witnesses at a trial where their friend, a dancer at a nightclub where they are musicians, is accused of murder.   , The Stooges make a whole batch of homemade beer, but get tossed in jail when Curly sells some to a cop.  Their minor indiscretion turns into a forty-year sentence when a keg of beer Curly has hidden under his coat explodes while the boys are being photographed.  In prison the Stooges get into more trouble with the warden and wind on the rockpile when they try to escape.  Released as old men with long gray beards, the first thing Curly wants is a bottle of beer. , The stooge's friend Claude sells them his old lemon of a car so they can take Shemp, who is sick with a toothache, camping.  The car won't work and the boys are apparently out a bundle, when a car collector happens on the scene and offers to buy it at a premium.  Claude backs out on the deal and gives the Stooges their money back, only to discover the "collector" is an escaped lunatic. , Told in flash back, the Stooges tell their son how he came to have three fathers.  The Stooges, owners of a pawnshop, owed money to the gashouse protection society, a bunch of loan sharks.  To complicate matters, a lady leaves a baby in the shop as part of a plan to sell a phony diamond and the Stooges wind up caring for the kid.  The Stooges manage to defeat the crooks and when they finish telling the story, the kid goes off to find his real mother. , The Stooges are stagehands who also have small parts in a big play.  They quickly get on the bad side of the producer.  First they fail to prevent a famous critic from sneaking into the audience.  Then Shemp accidentally adds a potholder into a cake they bake as a prop.  During the play the Stooges (as southern gentlemen) and the rest of the cast spit up feathers during what was supposed to be a serious scene.  The critic thinks it's a hilarious satire and the boys are redeemed , The Stooges escape from jail to prevent their newly rich dad from marrying Daisy, a gold-digger after his money.  Shemp looks like dad, so he impersonates him and marries Daisy.  What the Stooges don't know is that Daisy is in cahoots with some crooks, and they plan to bump off her new husband.  The boys foil the crook's plan and take Pa home to Ma. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105010000 +0000" stop="20250105033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Abbott And Costello Meet Dr. Jekyll And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <desc>"Police officers Bud and Lou encounter the infamous shape-changing scientist while on assignment in London."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105033000 +0000" stop="20250105040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>He Meets His Match, The Grisly Ghoul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman and Robin track a female student who joined Joker's gang, but Joker poisons her perfume to cover his tracks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105040000 +0000" stop="20250105050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Dove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Enterprise brings aboard Klingon prisoners, an alien entity pits both sides against each other in an ever-escalating struggle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105050000 +0000" stop="20250105060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Werewolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In snowy Chicago the INS Christmas party is to send off Tony Vincenzo, but he gets audited instead, and it is Carl who gets to go on the singles cruise, where a werewolf goes on a killing spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105060000 +0000" stop="20250105070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Visit To A Hostile Planet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Jupiter 2 is sucked through a time warp, the Robinsons find themselves near Earth. Upon arrival to their planet, however, they discover the year is 1947.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105070000 +0000" stop="20250105080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Saboteur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Commander Crane is electronically brain washed by enemy agents and ordered to abort an important mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105080000 +0000" stop="20250105090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>A Small War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A sadistic child discovers the Earthlings and unleashes his mechanical toys against them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105090000 +0000" stop="20250105100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1861, Tony and Doug are involved in a plot to assassinate President-elect Abraham Lincoln.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105100000 +0000" stop="20250105110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Organization</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While searching for alien debris, Vincent finds himself caught in a narcotics ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105110000 +0000" stop="20250105120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Genius</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt temporarily loses his powers to something unknown."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105120000 +0000" stop="20250105123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Fight   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zach and Slater might turn back into rivals when they fall for a new girl from Idaho. Who'll be the one to have a date with her?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105123000 +0000" stop="20250105130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Rockumentary   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Casey Kasem hosts a biography of Zack's rock group,The Zack Attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105130000 +0000" stop="20250105133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Sats   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie's self-esteem takes a dive when she gets a lower score on her SAT than Zack, hurting her chances at getting into Stansbury College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105133000 +0000" stop="20250105140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Bayside Triangle   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Screech realizes that Zack and Lisa have fallen for each other while Zack helps her put on a fashion show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105140000 +0000" stop="20250105143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Student-teacher Week   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's student-teacher week. Belding and Zack switch places while Kelly becomes Slater's teacher. When Kelly gives a test and everyone in her class fails, Zack faces a hard decision: to either be their friend or their leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105143000 +0000" stop="20250105150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Teacher's Strike   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>To go on a ski trip, the gang conjures up a teacher's strike only to learn that it could affect the academic bowl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105150000 +0000" stop="20250105153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Power Of The Press</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter comes home with the great news that he's been given his own column in the school newspaper. He quickly becomes popular with his classmates when they find their names in his newspaper column. This newfound popularity goes to Peter's head, however, as he tries to improve a poor grade in biology by flattering his teacher in the column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105153000 +0000" stop="20250105160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Emma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice has decided to take a well deserved vacation, but feels like she's deserting the Brady family. She calls in her cousin, Emma to take her place and the Brady family is not prepared for Emma's military-styled approach.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105160000 +0000" stop="20250105163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Two Angry Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie takes Howard to court after Fonzie's pigeon cage falls through the roof of his apartment during a blizzard. Fonzie claims the weight of the snow caused the roof to collapse while Howard claims it was the pigeon cage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105163000 +0000" stop="20250105170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Watch The Fur Fly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shirley yells at Rhonda for wearing a coat made of animal fur, Laverne unknowingly sets Shirley up on a date with a furrier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105170000 +0000" stop="20250105173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banjo-playing Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When former carnival man Jerry Miller becomes deputy to Sheriff Taylor, he finds himself jeopardizing Mayberry, making him question his decision to become a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105173000 +0000" stop="20250105180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood At Last!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Ricardos and the Mertzes arrive in Hollywood, Lucy goes to the Brown Derby restaurant where her sighting of actor William Holden turns catastrophic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105180000 +0000" stop="20250105183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Mustache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's on-again off-again girlfriend, Julie Foster, seems to have thrown him over for a new guy in school who just happens to have a mustache. Wally's ego is bruised when Eddie tells him that Julie thinks he's naive and immature. This is the last straw and Wally decides to grow a mustache, much to the dismay of his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105183000 +0000" stop="20250105190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Buys A Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend has a car for sale and Wally is interested; however, Ward and June are, as usual, hesitant about the whole thing. Ward decides to give in to Wally and allow him to buy the used car, with the condition that he inspect it first. Ward quickly finds problems with the car and he helps Wally look elsewhere giving Wally tips on the process of used car shopping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105190000 +0000" stop="20250105193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Trotting Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny needs to get around Beverly Hills and is having no luck with a driving lesson. When she hears that the Drysdale are looking at the horses, Granny decides she needs a trotter and buggy. Drysdale learns that the Clampetts want a horse, and after he learns of its potential winnings, the Clampetts acquire Ladybelle, a racehorse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105193000 +0000" stop="20250105200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Buggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a buggy for her horse Ladybelle and gets the same thing for Mrs. Drysdale so they can have buggy races. But the horse she buys for her neighbor is known around the stables as "Old Gluepot." She tries to cheat to win, but ends up with Lightening, the poor horse, after Jed tries to teach her a lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105200000 +0000" stop="20250105203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous big-game hunter lands on the island in search of new game to hunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105203000 +0000" stop="20250105210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Our Vines Have Tender Apes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An loin-cloth-clad ape-man comes to the island, and makes off with their food and supplies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105210000 +0000" stop="20250105213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Have It Mama's Way  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama and Bubba get a job at the same fast-food restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105213000 +0000" stop="20250105220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Birthright  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An anonymous letter convinces Vint that he's adopted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105220000 +0000" stop="20250105230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Musical Cabins</sub-title>
    <desc>A young bachelor must marry within the week in order to claim a $3 million inheritance; meanwhile, a drab widow poses as a glamorous adventuress and captures the heart of the captain. Also, a confirmed male chauvinist angers his fiancee, who finds comfort in sick bay with Doc. And, a scandal sheet reporter sets out to compile material for a sins-at-sea story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105230000 +0000" stop="20250105233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Housekeeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose, the former housekeeper, gets married and Opie is unhappy at her departure. Aunt Bee comes to live with Andy and Opie, and Opie is not exactly thrilled with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250105233000 +0000" stop="20250106000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Kevin Hermann- Movie Props And Costumes</sub-title>
    <desc>"Driven by his “completist” mentality, Kevin Hermann has built an impressively vast collection of movie props and costumes from his favorite films - including one of the most complete costume collections from the hit franchise, Underworld.  Kevin collects what he loves -  from rare Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom props to the original puppets from the animated series, Gumby - and that love has turned into a hefty investment. In this episode of Collector’s Call, expert Mark Short places a seven-figure value on Kevin’s massive collection. With Kevin’s appetite for complete costumes - including the accessories - Mark comes prepared to trade two costumes and a prop from a popular television series in hopes of taking home one of Kevin’s more gruesome rarities. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106000000 +0000" stop="20250106003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106003000 +0000" stop="20250106010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106010000 +0000" stop="20250106013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Iola's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie refuses to let Edith's elderly aunt move into their spare bedroom, even after she's been turned away by every other relative.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106013000 +0000" stop="20250106020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Love Comes To The Butcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is jealous when a lonely butcher lavishes attention on Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106020000 +0000" stop="20250106023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Two's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Archie have a long talk after they find themself locked in the storeroom of Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106023000 +0000" stop="20250106030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Stalemates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Gloria are sure the romance has gone out of their marriage when even a weekend in the Poconos fails to reignite the spark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106030000 +0000" stop="20250106033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Wrong Number / Saturday Night / Recital, The / Vacuum Salesman</sub-title>
    <desc>In Wrong Number, Carol questions a strange phone call for her husband. Then, in Saturday Night, Carol tries to get invited to a party next door. Next, in The Recital, four talentless musicians perform a showcase. Finally, in Vacuum Salesman, Tim has an emotional breakdown while trying to sell a vacuum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106033000 +0000" stop="20250106040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>In As the Stomach Turns, Carol's sweet niece visits, only to discover she's possessed, in this parody of "The Exorcist". Then, in Two-Man Sub, two sailors must complete their mission: sink Cleveland.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106040000 +0000" stop="20250106043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Edwin Carp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob decides to do a program honoring great radio comedians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106043000 +0000" stop="20250106050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>October Eve</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura's past comes back to haunt her in form of a naked painting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106050000 +0000" stop="20250106053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to hit the high note on a civil service exam as well as his cornet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106053000 +0000" stop="20250106060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Good Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of a small town are terrorized by a young boy who has the ability to read minds and make anything he wishes a reality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106060000 +0000" stop="20250106070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>House Guest  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>John Mitchell gets more than he bargained for when he offers a young man a new start in life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106070000 +0000" stop="20250106080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>King Selim of Qamadan, an American ally, has been secretly imprisoned by his brother, Prince Samandal, who controls the oil reserves and is brutalizing his people. The IMF must restore Selim to power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106080000 +0000" stop="20250106090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Angels Travel On Lonely Roads (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"After escaping the police in Nevada, Dr. Kimble comes upon Sister Veronica, who convinces him to accompany her on her trip to Sacramento despite his protests that he's heading in another direction."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106090000 +0000" stop="20250106100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Gertrude</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell joins forces with a woman whose search for her missing brother involves a dangerous assortment of characters -- and a half-million dollars in diamonds."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106100000 +0000" stop="20250106103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106103000 +0000" stop="20250106110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106110000 +0000" stop="20250106113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 71 -- I Feel Like A Fool, Malloy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It is a shift of conflicts forcing Malloy and Reed to use their wits to keep control and make the right decisions end on a low note.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106113000 +0000" stop="20250106120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 72 -- El Presidente</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy teases Reed about calculating the cost of a new house while their first baby is still six months away. In the meantime they settle a domestic dispute between arguing neighbors and help a taxi driver who was just robbed as well as a local man mistaken as the president by a group of rural Mexicans. Finally, they must arrest a psychotic shooter holed up in his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106120000 +0000" stop="20250106130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Cowboy State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony travel to Wyoming for their Trekkin' All 50 tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106130000 +0000" stop="20250106133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Parking Attendants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The social event of the season, according to Fred Rutherford, is a big party that a wealthy family is throwing and he rubs it in due to the fact that June and Ward didn't get an invitation. However, Wally and Eddie will be there after they get jobs parking the guest's cars. However, trouble ensues when Eddie parks Fred's car in a no parking spot and the car gets towed away by the city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106133000 +0000" stop="20250106140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>More Blessed To Give</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert go to a carnival and Beaver surprisingly wins a fourteen caret gold locket in one of the carnival games. Beaver thinks about giving it to June but, thanks to Gilbert, decides to give it to a girl whom he has a crush on. However, soon it becomes apparent that this was a mistake when the girl's parents discover Beaver's gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106140000 +0000" stop="20250106150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Jealous Journalist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The drowning death of a newspaper executive during a fishing trip sets off all kinds of repercussions at the newspaper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106150000 +0000" stop="20250106160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Parents  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a woman who was planning to give her unborn baby to couple Howard and Amy has second thoughts and is soon found dead, the couple in question are the natural suspects. Matlock sets out to prove that someone else may have had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106160000 +0000" stop="20250106170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Brewer's Pond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A night of revelry at a local pond turns deadly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106170000 +0000" stop="20250106180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Remembrance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Zadok Walton visits the mountain. He seems eccentric, but turns out he is held in esteem by Boatwright University for his work</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106180000 +0000" stop="20250106190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kimbro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt runs into his former mentor, Adam Kimbro, and decides to build his self-confidence by deputizing him as a deputy marshal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106190000 +0000" stop="20250106200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Thanks For Everything, Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After falling into a river, Adam is rescued by Tom Wilson. Wilson has feelings for Sue Miller, which bring him into trouble after her father is killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106200000 +0000" stop="20250106203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A condemned killer being transported by train murders a marshal and takes Mark hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106203000 +0000" stop="20250106210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark discovers that the new preacher and his wife are impostors planning a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106210000 +0000" stop="20250106220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Levi Hale Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>"Chris Hale is traveling to the Wyoming prison to pick up his brother Levi---who's about to be released from prison. Chris assumed Levi was pardoned but he was paroled to Chris. He must keep Levi out of Wyoming or he will be hanged."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106220000 +0000" stop="20250106230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Firehouse Four</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The station enters the fireman's barber shop quartet contest. A man keeps requiring rescue while trying various ways to exercise. A woman overdoses on sleeping pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106230000 +0000" stop="20250106233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250106233000 +0000" stop="20250107000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107000000 +0000" stop="20250107003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107003000 +0000" stop="20250107010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107010000 +0000" stop="20250107013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The state police arrogantly ask Andy and Barney to step aside while they search for an escaped convict in Mayberry, believing that the Mayberry sheriff's department is not capable of doing "real" police work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107013000 +0000" stop="20250107020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Lindsey is a young guitarist that lives in Mayberry. When the famous musician Bobby Fleet and his band arrive in Mayberry, Andy and Barney scheme to arrest Bobby and his band so that Jim can get an audition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107020000 +0000" stop="20250107023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girls From Grun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finish dining with their Grunion, a surfer boy and a girl, and tell the captives they will let them go. Jethro wants to keep his captured girl, but Jed let’s the two go. At the bank, Drysdale, who tells Helen she must take the blame for his stupid mistakes, decides to get his former secretary back. Helen goes to the beach to try to get Jane back, and finds out the Clampetts still believe Grunion are people, a poor excuse, but people nonetheless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107023000 +0000" stop="20250107030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Pay Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced he has been a goldbrick and stubbornly refuses to accept part of his paycheck. The Pentagon orders him to do so, but Gomer still refuses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107030000 +0000" stop="20250107033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>To Russia Without Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for a beautiful Russian spy to convince Klink that the Kommandant should volunteer for service at the Russian front. Hogan's payoff: some secret papers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107033000 +0000" stop="20250107040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink For The Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is appointed defense counsel for a German officer on trial for treason who has secret plans intended for London. Hogan helps Klink prove the officer's innocence in order to secure the plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107040000 +0000" stop="20250107043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Vic Voyeur Show, Carol discovers her husband is cheating on her while listening to a radio program. Then, in The Thin Man, a parody on the hit series,  the husband-wife detective duo search for a murder among dinner guests. Finally, in The Interrogator, a captured American solider meets the toughest interrogator yet -- a Hitler puppet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107043000 +0000" stop="20250107053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Substitute Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della are traveling on a cruise ship returning to Los Angeles from Vancouver. Carl Houser jumps overboard and is presumed drowned. Houser later turns up on shore but with a bullet wound in his body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107053500 +0000" stop="20250107060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Deaths-head Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A former Nazi SS captain returns to the ruins of Dachau and begins reminiscing on the power he enjoyed there, until he finds himself on trial by those who died at his hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107060500 +0000" stop="20250107063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night The World Ended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of newspapermen plays a joke on a man who in return decides to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107063500 +0000" stop="20250107070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hands Of Mr. Otterhole</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial killer uses the heavy London fog to confuse the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107070500 +0000" stop="20250107080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Climb A Deadly Mountain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Forced to crash land a plane, Mannix gets rescued by an escaped convict who's being pursued by corrupt law enforcement officers out to silence him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107080500 +0000" stop="20250107090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Long Way Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An illegal immigrant from Mexico has died in a coyote's case. Sheep grower Rita McBain is accused of the deed. Cannon must prove Rita's innocence and deal with a human smuggler ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107090500 +0000" stop="20250107100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Temptation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>As a police lieutenant ends up falling for the ex-girlfriend of a murderer in trying to make her a witness to have the murderer convicted, he's framed for the murder of a second witness, so Barnaby and J.R. try to clear him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107100000 +0000" stop="20250107103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107103000 +0000" stop="20250107110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107110000 +0000" stop="20250107113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 101: Someone Stole My Lawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed wants an early dinner when his wife puts him on a low-cal diet. However, one after another events prevents them from going code 7 all night long. Events include the theft of a man's sod, stolen credit cards and a suspected car theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107113000 +0000" stop="20250107120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 132 -- Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed tries to pawn off his new litter of puppies to co-workers, strangers and even victims. The officers work a silent alarm, rescue a boy with his head stuck in a fence and track down a prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107120000 +0000" stop="20250107130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Time Capsule Trivia Hour</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony cheer up Mr. Quzzer by showing lost Time Capsule Tiriva footage.                                    "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107130000 +0000" stop="20250107133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Good Deed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver seems to be on a selfish streak after backing out of a babysitting and later not wanting to do a simple favor for Wally. Ward gives Beaver a stern lecture and he soon takes Ward's advice when a tramp comes to the door wanting some kindness. However, the tramp quickly takes advantage and helps himself to more than a glass of water.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107133000 +0000" stop="20250107140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Credit Card</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie brags about getting a credit card to his high school friends. When Wally's battery dies on his car, Eddie comes to the rescue by getting him a brand new battery. Everything is fine until Mr. Haskell finds out that Eddie charged it on their charge account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107140000 +0000" stop="20250107150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impatient Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Paint manufacturer Amory Fallon suspects that his partner, Ned Thompson, is behind a mysterious fire and explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107150000 +0000" stop="20250107160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Of The Year  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is all set to be honored as the man of the year, but when his car breaks down and he's forced to ask his housekeeper for a ride, a simple 20-minute trip turns into a flat tire, hostage situation and afternoon in jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107160000 +0000" stop="20250107170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Love Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lana's ex-boyfriend comes to see her and brings a load of stolen rifles with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107170000 +0000" stop="20250107180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspiration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mamie Balwin has a cataract, but does not want an operation</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107180000 +0000" stop="20250107190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Jesse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus runs into Jesse Dillard who is wanted for shooting a black man. Festus wants to find out more and takes his friend to prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107190000 +0000" stop="20250107200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Logan's Treasure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Logan is released from jail after serving his 20-year sentence for stealing $100,000 worth of gold dust. He is followed by a bounty hunter who believes Sam will lead him to where the gold is buried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107200000 +0000" stop="20250107203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance get into trouble with the Army when they try to help a wounded young soldier who deserted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107203000 +0000" stop="20250107210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mark contracts typhoid fever and has a vision of his dead mother, he no longer seems interested in getting well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107210000 +0000" stop="20250107220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Terry Morrell Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>"After the Sheriff escorts Ben Morrell and his son Terry to the wagon train, the members find Ben Morrell and his son very antisocial: the two can't even tolerate each other. One woman wants to adopt Terry believing he is being mistreated."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107220000 +0000" stop="20250107230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a call, Roy and John witness a pedestrian being struck by a car. A woman is badly burnt in a fire. John thinks about settling down. A belly dancer overdoses on diet pills. A child bites a dog and the dog bites back. At a burning building, Roy and John must jump to safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107230000 +0000" stop="20250107233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250107233000 +0000" stop="20250108000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108000000 +0000" stop="20250108003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108003000 +0000" stop="20250108010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108010000 +0000" stop="20250108013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie Walker, the local pharmacist's niece, comes to Mayberry to replace him on a temporary basis. Her "new" approach to dispensing medicine shakes things up in Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108013000 +0000" stop="20250108020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Irresistible Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy comes to believe that Ellie is a "deadly female hunter" out to marry him so he tries to put her onto other quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108020000 +0000" stop="20250108023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Women's Lib</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Elly have decided to support the women’s lib movement, since Jethro treats them like servants. Each time Jed tries to make it better, Jethro ends up messing it up and upsetting the women even more. At the bank, the secretaries continue to fight for liberation, but Drysdale has decided to challenge them as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108023000 +0000" stop="20250108030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Loves A Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer drives Sgt. Carter crazy by liking him, no matter what the sergeant does to make Gomer dislike him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108030000 +0000" stop="20250108033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kamikazes Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys find a new rocket that has landed near camp. They are at a loss on how to get it back to England for study when Marya and her rocket-designing husband enter camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108033000 +0000" stop="20250108040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Gertrude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a U.S. general out of Stalag 13, while Klink plans to move the camp's fence line and Gertrude arrives with her fiancé.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108040000 +0000" stop="20250108043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hit, Carol puts a "hit" on her husband, then worries she's in danger being around him. Then, in P.T.A. Auditions, a Russian director must cope with a bad leading lady. Finally, in Daughter of Houdini, a fake magician finds herself trapped in a sinking box.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108043000 +0000" stop="20250108053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Long-legged Models</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Racketeer George Castle kills Las Vegas hotel owner Glenn Faulkner over a gambling debt and sets his sights on land inherited by Faulkner's daughter, Stephanie. When Castle turns up murdered as well, Stephanie finds herself the number one suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108053500 +0000" stop="20250108060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Midnight Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earth's orbit has been changed, drawing ever closer to the sun and promising imminent destruction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108060500 +0000" stop="20250108063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Greatly Beloved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A newcomer refuses to allow his garden to be used for a church activity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108063500 +0000" stop="20250108070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Martha Mason, Movie Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>After years of being teased by her husband, a woman discovers that she looks very similar to movie star and decided to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108070500 +0000" stop="20250108080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to help a girl who witnessed her father's murder and was driven over the edge mentally by the event.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108080500 +0000" stop="20250108090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Rip-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Simeon is accused by orderly Duran of stealing drugs in the Metropolitan Hospital . Cannon has to find out whether this is right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108090500 +0000" stop="20250108100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Man On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby works with a claims adjuster in an arson-and-murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108100000 +0000" stop="20250108103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108103000 +0000" stop="20250108110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108110000 +0000" stop="20250108113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 111: Snake In The Trunk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A ditzy young woman reports her 1958 Ford convertible stolen while she went into a liquor store. She left the keys in the car, has no paperwork, doesn't know the license number or other details but she needs it by 6 PM for a date. She finally tells the officers that her eight-foot boa constrictor is in the trunk as she was coming from the vet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108113000 +0000" stop="20250108120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 61: The Runaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Walters and Brinkman are on a roll lately and like to brag, much to the irritation of Reed. He and Malloy help them out by finishing one of their calls, then rescue a sick teenage girl and arrest the young man who took her in. Back on patrol, they meet an informant who gives them a tip on a big drug buy scheduled for 11 PM. They give the info to Sgt. Miller who asks them to help in the bust.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108120000 +0000" stop="20250108130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Advice For Life</sub-title>
    <desc>"Do you need advice? Bill,Toony, and a special guest comedian are here to help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108130000 +0000" stop="20250108133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Caddie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver has gotten a job as a caddy and is quickly running around the golf course chasing balls. However, all innocence is broken when one of the guys, Beaver is caddying for cheats in order to win a bet. Soon, Beaver begins wrestling with his conscience over whether or not to tell anyone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108133000 +0000" stop="20250108140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with the news that he applied to appear on a local television show called 'Teen Forum' and has been accepted. Beaver gets out of classes for the taping and all his classmates are treated to being able to watch him on TV during class. However, what Beaver, his friends and family don't know is that the show tapes each episode a week in advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108140000 +0000" stop="20250108150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Romantic Rogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After con man Stacey Chandler and Helen Harvey are married in Vegas, Chandler's former associate and scheming con woman, Irene Wallace, is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108150000 +0000" stop="20250108160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Arsonist  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of two business partners planning to hire an arsonist and collect insurance money is found dead, the surviving business man is pinned as the likely killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108160000 +0000" stop="20250108170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Singin' The Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Luann moonlights as a singer at a nightclub and finds romance with the clubs owner. Her happiness is short-lived when she realizes that the bartender is dealing drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108170000 +0000" stop="20250108180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Straw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John thinks about giving up the lumber mill when it seems like everything is going wrong</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108180000 +0000" stop="20250108190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Talbot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Talbot falls in love with Katherine after shooting her husband in self-defense. But when Katherine learns of Talbot's plans to rob a bank, she puts her life in danger by telling him she will leave him if he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108190000 +0000" stop="20250108200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Scapegoat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss hires Waldo as a ranch hand after keeping Waldo from killing himself. Hoss soon learns that Waldo is lousy at his job and only causes problems for everyone else because of his clumsiness. Although Hoss is willing to defend him, he soon discovers a secret about Waldo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108200000 +0000" stop="20250108203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Lucas's returns to town in the company of a shady gambler and is accused of cheating at cards.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108203000 +0000" stop="20250108210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men are vying for a rancher's daughter's affections. When she is found dead, one of them becomes the prime suspect in her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108210000 +0000" stop="20250108220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jud Steele Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bill Hawks returns the horse and belongings of a horse thief he shot to the local town sheriff. These identify the thief as a long dead war hero with a monument in the middle of town who was declared dead after a payroll robbery."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108220000 +0000" stop="20250108230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John finally restore their old fire engine to ride in the California Fire Fighters Parade. A man with heart problems causes an accident for which the other driver blames herself. Dr. Early treats a patient who has a seizure in the waiting room. A man on a date passes out and has difficulty breathing. A child's medical condition causes an argument between his divorced parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108230000 +0000" stop="20250108233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250108233000 +0000" stop="20250109000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109000000 +0000" stop="20250109003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109003000 +0000" stop="20250109010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109010000 +0000" stop="20250109013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie becomes friends with an eight-year-old runaway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109013000 +0000" stop="20250109020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy The Matchmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, trying to lift Barney's spirits, stages a minor robbery and tries to match his deputy with a shy seamstress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109020000 +0000" stop="20250109023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro Proposes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has heard that Miss Jane has never been proposed to and wants to help out. She tries to get Jed to propose, but has no luck with that plan. Granny then settles to have Jethro propose to her. Jethro asks Miss Jane out, and she accepts. While at the bank, Jethro also meets the gorgeous new night guard, Ilse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109023000 +0000" stop="20250109030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Dragon Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While in town on a pass, Sgt. Carter decides to play a joke on Gomer by setting him on a quest to get a kiss from "The Dragon Lady." But in order for it to work he will need Duke's help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109030000 +0000" stop="20250109033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Double Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan is identified as a saboteur, he impersonates a German officer in front of the very Gestapo agent who could take him down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109033000 +0000" stop="20250109040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Funny Thing Happened On The Way To London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winston Chuchill's right-hand man, Group Captain "Robbie" Roberts, is shot down, captured and brought to Stalag 13. The Luftwaffe scheme to assassinate Churchill by keeping Roberts in the cooler while an impostor escapes to England to carry out the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109040000 +0000" stop="20250109043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Roddy Mcdowall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Bus Stop, strangers at a bus stop rush to answer the phone, which may be a quiz show. Then, in Brief Encounter, a film parody, Carol and Roddy have a romantic encounter using only one-word responses. Finally, in The Family, Eunice's successful brother returns home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109043000 +0000" stop="20250109053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gilded Lily</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Enid Griffin, the secretary of Stewart Brent, attempts to commit suicide after learning her boss has married. Arthur Binney attempts to blackmail Stewart Brent with facts about his new wife having been in jail for fraud. When Binny turns up dead, Brent is framed for his murder, but confesses to protect his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109053500 +0000" stop="20250109060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Still Valley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A Confederate soldier wanders into a town and finds a group of Union soldiers frozen in time. An old man with a black book implores the soldier to use the book's powers to win the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109060500 +0000" stop="20250109063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>West Warlock Time Capsule</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A taxidermist uses his art to dispose of his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109063500 +0000" stop="20250109070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Father And Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam needs the money his father will not give him so his girlfriend can marry him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109070500 +0000" stop="20250109080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Gang’s All Here</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix becomes the target of a vicious street gang known as the Nomads.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109080500 +0000" stop="20250109090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Paul Stubber taps the computer of the railroad company to be able to rob cars with valuable goods. However, nothing can be proved against him. Cannon finds Stubber's weak spot: The crook fights for the right to keep his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109090500 +0000" stop="20250109100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109100000 +0000" stop="20250109103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109103000 +0000" stop="20250109110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109110000 +0000" stop="20250109113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 81: The Long Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After roll call, Reed and Malloy provide backup at a robbery, help a lost man return home, handle a call about a prowler and respond to a silent alarm. Malloy demonstrates for Reed the importance of "officer presence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109113000 +0000" stop="20250109120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Jimmy Eisley's Dealing Smack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy spot TJ, an informant, who tells them about a possible drug house. They spot a woman and girl at the same bus stop an hour apart. When they stop to talk to her, she tries to run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109120000 +0000" stop="20250109130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1989</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony flash back to the rad year of 1989, a year of flashy hammer pants, lip-syncing scandals, and the end of an era for a cartoon legend."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109130000 +0000" stop="20250109133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Box Office Attraction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward have noticed the Wally has been spending quite a bit of his time at the movie theater but it's not to see the movies. He's been eyeing the pretty young lady who works in the box office. Thanks to Eddie, Wally works up enough courage to ask her out but quickly sees another side to the young lady that is a bit too mature for Wally's taste.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109133000 +0000" stop="20250109140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Scholarship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is let down when he learns that he didn't get the sports scholarship from State University. However, he does learn that Lumpy did get one and this leads him to throw a party in Lumpy's honor. However, half way through the party, Fred calls with some unfortunate news for Lumpy, the scholarship is no longer available due to Lumpy's grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109140000 +0000" stop="20250109150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Malicious Mariner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>During a terrible storm at sea, First Officer Jerry Griffin dumps a million dollars worth of goods overboard to lessen the chances of his cargo freighter sinking. Once on shore, Jerry is hauled before a maritime court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109150000 +0000" stop="20250109160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Formula  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A young acquaintance of Matlock's asks for his expertise when accused of murder and the theft of a secret formula.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109160000 +0000" stop="20250109170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Virgil Tibbs: Attorney At Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Attorney Virgil Tibbs returns to Sparta and is soon assigned his first case as a defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109170000 +0000" stop="20250109180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Travelling Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A former boyfriend and dance partner of Rose's comes to visit</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109180000 +0000" stop="20250109190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Women For Sale: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt becomes involved in investigating the disappearance of female settlers and travelers in the region. He links it to a band of renegade Native Americans, who plan to sell the women as sex slaves to a band of ruthless white mercenaries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109190000 +0000" stop="20250109200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Dime's Worth Of Glory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An author is inspired to write about the heroic Cartwrights after watching first-hand as they fight off an attempted robbery of a stage. As Ben and Adam see no use for the glory of such a novel, they turn the writer down forcing him to turn to the sheriff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109200000 +0000" stop="20250109203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Shotgun man John Beaumont, who Lucas sent to prison, returns with vengeance on his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109203000 +0000" stop="20250109210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting a man in self-defense, Andy Moon turns to Lucas for protection from his vengeful brothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109210000 +0000" stop="20250109220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Beckett Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"A Frenchman arouses strong---and polarized---emotions among the wagon train members: men distrust him, women adore him. He owes a substantial gambling debt and plans to pay it off by convincing a woman to pay it until he is killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109220000 +0000" stop="20250109230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Bash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is trapped on a film set with a bear. When Roy and John rescue him, they are invited to a "thing" that the man is giving later that week. John talks Roy into getting overdressed for the event. Dr. Brackett treats a man suffering from trichinosis. A bomb blast injures two men. The paramedics resuscitate a musician at the party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109230000 +0000" stop="20250109233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250109233000 +0000" stop="20250110000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110000000 +0000" stop="20250110003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110003000 +0000" stop="20250110010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110010000 +0000" stop="20250110013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes upset when Opie contributes a measly three cents to the Underprivileged Children's drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110013000 +0000" stop="20250110020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Feud Is A Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy strives to end a long-running feud between two neighboring families.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110020000 +0000" stop="20250110023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lib And Let Lib</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Troubles are following everyone after the women’s lib movement ended. Elly and Granny return home to the mansion, while Jethro still believes he is Japanese and the women should serve him because women should wait on man. And at the bank, the secretaries are working on better working conditions, but get bullied by Banzai, who is trying to get new girls from Japan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110023000 +0000" stop="20250110030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Survival Of The Fattest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>It's survival training for the platoon, meaning that for five days partners have to rough it. Thinking Gomer will bring down the rating for the platoon, Sgt. Carter takes Pyle as his own partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110030000 +0000" stop="20250110033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Rockets Or Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan becomes the partner of a beautiful underground agent when he and his men team up with the underground to destroy a guided missile battery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110033000 +0000" stop="20250110040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110040000 +0000" stop="20250110043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests John Byner And Francine Beers</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Diner, two robbers pose as cook and waitress when the police interrupt their hold-up at a restaurant. Then, in Carol and Sis, Carol and Harvey's anniversary is ruined by a house guest. Finally, in Humanoids, two female robots compete to see which is better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110043000 +0000" stop="20250110053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lazy Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Attempting to miss hitting her stepfather's car, Patricia Faxon swerves as she enters her driveway and hits the hedges. After asking her stepfather, Bertrand Allred, to move his car, he finds Bob Fleetwood badly hurt next to the hedges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110053500 +0000" stop="20250110060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jungle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a business man plans to build a dam in Africa, a witch doctor puts a curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110060500 +0000" stop="20250110063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Indestructible Mr. Weems</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An apparently dying man is offered the first plot at a brand-new cemetery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110063500 +0000" stop="20250110070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Little Sleep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Two brothers, one of them a murderer, share a cabin with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110070500 +0000" stop="20250110080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hires Mannix to investigate the disappearance of her husband's plane in the Rockies, but then the detective learns that she is not the missing man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110080500 +0000" stop="20250110090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Shadow Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon is hired to search missing rancher Dale Lucas following his wife's order. He notes that the guard service of the ranch has been replaced.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110090500 +0000" stop="20250110100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In Hawaii (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In Hawaii, J.R. is framed for murder and thrown in jail by a vengeful cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250110100000 +0000" stop="20250110103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
