<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206140000 +0000" stop="20251206150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>My Bunny Lies Over The Sea, Tweety And The Beanstalk, I Gopher You, Pre-hysterical Hare, Clippety Clobbered, Porky's Cafe, Wild And Wooly Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"In Scotland, Bugs gets into a fight with McCrory, and they decide to settle it over a game of golf. , Sylvester is up to his old tricks but this time he is in a giant world and against a giant Tweety. , The Goofy Gophers are about to harvest their ripe looking vegetables when vandals confiscate the produce and truck it off to a food-processing plant. , Running from Elmer, Bugs is wondering why there is an annual rabbit hunting season. Bugs looks back in time to 10,000 B.C. and sees that even back then there was a rabbit hunting season. , Wile E. Coyote tries to use invisible paint, rubber paint, and a rocket to try and catch the Road Runner. , Porky attempts to wait tables in his cafe while his friend, Conrad Cat, has problems cooking in the kitchen. , Only Bugs Bunny has nerve enough to stand up to Yosemite Sam in the wild west. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206150000 +0000" stop="20251206160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Sabatini Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim meets with crime czar Sabatini, who asks him to travel to Calliope, MO to protect a lady and give a man called Swanson a key. Accompanied by government chemist Ned Brown, Jim travels to Calliope where an Army finance officer died after stealing half a mil. Everyone in Calliope wants the hidden loot... and someone is willing to kill to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206160000 +0000" stop="20251206170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Annie Duggan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"An elderly couple and then a young girl become ill with typhoid fever on the wagon train. A young servant girl has attended to them all in isolation. One of the women on the train has an idea about the cause but no one wants to listen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206170000 +0000" stop="20251206180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Court Martial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Armed men occupy the Barkley house, bent on punishing Nick’s former general for the destruction of an innocent town during the war. Jarrod convinces them to let the general and Nick give their side of the story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206180000 +0000" stop="20251206190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Warden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus protects a young Indian maiden from a farmer who bought her from her father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206190000 +0000" stop="20251206200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Escape To Ponderosa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam is bushwhacked by three men, who turn out to be Army deserters. When Ben pursues them, he finds himself hindered by a Captain Bolton, who is also after the three men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206200000 +0000" stop="20251206203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Tinhorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A professional card player, John Keeler, has set up business in North Fork, but local Jesse Phillips claims that this tinhorn is a cheat. Lucas starts playing poker with Keeler to draw him out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206203000 +0000" stop="20251206210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>None So Blind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark befriends singer-banjoist Lafayette Bly, a blind man with an acute sense of hearing—and a very strong grip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206210000 +0000" stop="20251206220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Moment In The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Shaw arrests Reed McCuller, who is known by locals as a type of Robin Hood, but in fact is a murderer and thief. He tries to use Favor's herd as cover to get out of the area, and the locals, led by his brother, are on to Shaw's plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206220000 +0000" stop="20251206223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>24 Hours At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>When a blight kills all the crops except for one farmer's, Paladin must protect him from a greedy storekeeper who wants his farm and his hired gun who has a personal grudge against Paladin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206223000 +0000" stop="20251206230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>A House Divided</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is hired by an attractive woman to find and clear the name of her father wrongly accused of murder. The real killer hires Jason to find the same man, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251206230000 +0000" stop="20251207010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Hoi Polloi, Movie Maniacs, Matri-phony, Stone Age Romeos, Merry Mavericks, Shivering Sherlocks</sub-title>
    <desc>"A professor bets that he can turn the Stooges into gentlemen.   , The Stooges arrive in Hollywood hoping to make it in the movie business. , The Stooges witness an armed robbery and are brought in by the cops as suspects.  After passing a lie detector test, the boys are freed but are now the only ones who can identify the crooks.  Meanwhile, their friend Gladys has inherited a house in the country and the boys go with her to inspect it so she won't be gypped when it's sold.  The house turns out to be the crook's hideout, and when they abduct Gladys, the Stooges must rescue her. , The Stooges are potters in ancient Rome during the reign of Emperor Octopus Grabus.  When the emperor orders all beautiful redheaded women to be brought before him so he can select a wife, Diana, a pretty redhead, seeks refuge with the Stooges.  Some soldiers find Diana's hiding place and they are all brought to the palace where the Stooges escape and try to pass of Curly as Diana, having broken the emperor's glasses.  Their ruse fails and they're caught by the palace guards as they try to escape. , The Stooges hope to collect a reward by proving to a museum that cavemen still exist.  They return from their expedition with a film purporting to show some stone age Stooges defending their women from other cavemen.  The museum curators are about to pay they reward, until they overhear the Stooges talking about how they faked the film, with themselves playing the cavemen. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are mistaken for lawmen and manage to capture a gang of crooks.  The boys then get the job of guarding some money in an old house reputed to be haunted by the ghost of an Indian Chief.  The crooks escape and go after the money disguised as ghosts, but Shemp, disguised as the Indian Chief, manages to knock them out. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207010000 +0000" stop="20251207030000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Mummy's Tomb</sub-title>
    <desc>"An Egyptian priest and his mummified slave arrive in America bent on avenging the desecration of their master's tomb."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207030000 +0000" stop="20251207033000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Fine Finny Fiends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>The Penguin kidnaps Alfred Pennyworth and brainwashes him to help rob the Multimillionaires' Annual Award Dinner. Later, Batman and Robin are puzzled by Alfred's behavior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207033000 +0000" stop="20251207040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Batman Makes The Scene</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Believing the Dynamic Duo has been finished off, the pudgy purveyor of perfidy and his finks quickly dash to establish their "alibis." Meanwhile, Batman has been able to reach the emergency tank of Batoxygen in his utility belt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207040000 +0000" stop="20251207050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Arena</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Capt. Kirk is pitted against the reptilian captain of an alien ship by a superior alien race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207050000 +0000" stop="20251207053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Disappearing Lois</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois disguises herself as a maid to get an interview with a gangster. He orders his henchman to dispose of her and Jimmy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207053000 +0000" stop="20251207060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Money To Burn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Daily Planet's newsprint warehouse has a fire, and the payroll disappears. Perry White is accused of embezzlement and arson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207060000 +0000" stop="20251207070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>All That Glitters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith is given a ring that turns anything he touches into platinum, but his joy soon becomes terror when even his food turns into the precious metal. In danger of starving to death because he cannot remove the ring, Smith scrambles to discover how to get the device off his finger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207070000 +0000" stop="20251207080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An enemy sub battles with the Seaview for an activated super bomb that threatens to explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207080000 +0000" stop="20251207090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret City Of Limbo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings stumbles upon a miniature teleporter which gives access to the secret city of Limbo, whose inhabitants have hidden from the dictatorship of the surface people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207090000 +0000" stop="20251207100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Attack Of The Barbarians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In 13th-century Asia, Tony and Doug aid Marco Polo in defending a fort against Mongols led by Genghis Khan's grandson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207100000 +0000" stop="20251207110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursued</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien reaches out to Vincent with the intention of defecting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207110000 +0000" stop="20251207120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Woman In The Wilderness</sub-title>
    <desc>"The men meet a lady, Mrs. Jackson. Who asks about black bears. She's writing a book about them. Adams finds out she's really after a bear who killed her father, to end its life. Can she be convinced revenge against nature isn't the solution?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207120000 +0000" stop="20251207123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bears Of The High Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim follow a pair of black bear cubs in Yellowstone National Park; track a large black bear to tag for future reference."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207123000 +0000" stop="20251207130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bundu Rescue</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go on a thrilling adventure in South Africa to catch lions, hippos and elephants for scientific and conservation purposes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207130000 +0000" stop="20251207133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Raccoon Valley</sub-title>
    <desc>"With Marlin and Jim you follow the raccoon family in their adventures in a remote valley amid the scenic splendor of southern Utah."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207133000 +0000" stop="20251207140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Crocodile Is King</sub-title>
    <desc>"To Marlin and Jim, Africa’s waters mean the chance to film the most exciting dramas and most unusual animals ever captured by the camera.  Crocodiles are among the largest reptiles in the world and the most feared!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207140000 +0000" stop="20251207143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>El Tigre</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the hostile mountains and deserts of Mexico roams one of the world’s most beautiful and dangerous cats…El Tigre the jaguar. Marlin and Jim track this predator through miles of inhospitable terrain."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207143000 +0000" stop="20251207150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Survival Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to every corner of the globe to capture and tag wild animals to be studied and for conservation purposes.  Some are taken to restock old ranges, others moved to new ranges where they will have a better chance to survive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207150000 +0000" stop="20251207153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Jan Brady Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan is upset when her friend, Lucy Winters, sends a birthday party invitation but accidentally addresses it to Marcia. Tired of being the middle blonde girl of the family, Jan tries to alter her appearance by buying a black wig, which she intends to wear to Lucy's upcoming birthday party. Meanwhile, Peter is horrified that Margie will be attending the party, a girl who has a major crush on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207153000 +0000" stop="20251207160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Drummer Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter, Jan and Cindy rush home from school with the news that they've joined the glee club. Bobby feels left out, but Mike and Carol let him test out his musical ability on a set of drums. Bobby's enthused, but is he talented?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207160000 +0000" stop="20251207163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Goin' To Chicago</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie, Potsie and Ralph go on a trip to Chicago with the school choir. Not wanting to stay in their hotel room all night, they decide to sneak out and see a show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207163000 +0000" stop="20251207170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, Come All Ye Bums</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The gang works to raise money for Frank's annual hobo Christmas dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207170000 +0000" stop="20251207173000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>A Christmas Carol</sub-title>
    <desc>"An adaption of A Christmas Carol.  An old bitter miser is given a chance for redemption when spirits visit him on Christmas Eve. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207173000 +0000" stop="20251207180000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>Little Rascals Christmas Special</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Little Rascals try to raise money to get Spanky's mom a new coat for Christmas."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207180000 +0000" stop="20251207183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After leaving the cap off the ink, Beaver is grounded to the house for a whole day after spilled ink ruins some of Ward's papers. However, Larry and Beaver sneak out to the movies and when Beaver wins a bike, he must find a way to keep it a secret from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207183000 +0000" stop="20251207190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's class holds a "Most Beautiful Baby" contest in which each student is supposed to bring in a baby picture. To make the deadline, June picks out a cute picture of Beaver at the last minute and sends it to Miss Landers, not realizing that the cute picture may cause Beaver embarrassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207190000 +0000" stop="20251207193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Get Culture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are having no success getting acquainted with their neighbors. Not to mention, the clan is having trouble with Mrs. Drysdale and Mrs. Potts. They decide to go back home to the hills, and when they go see Drysdale, they feel they are not wanted. Drysdale tries to clear everything up, and even has his Italian suit maker create a full suit for Jed, though Jed thinks the suit maker is trying to tie him up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207193000 +0000" stop="20251207200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Hair-raising Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor blows the whistle on Granny's mountain-medicine practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207200000 +0000" stop="20251207220000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>The Homecoming: A Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <desc>"On Christmas Eve 1933, the Waltons prepare for the holiday, but they are becoming increasingly worried because John Walton, who was forced to take work in another part of the state, has not yet returned home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207220000 +0000" stop="20251207230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Lonely At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>In a Christmas-themed cruise, a group of orphans and a man convicted for a crime he didn't commit are among those aboard the ship. Florence Henderson, Donna Mills and Shecky Greene guest star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207230000 +0000" stop="20251207233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251207233000 +0000" stop="20251208000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Kirk Kirkand- Classic Scifi Tv Props</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kirk Kirkland has been spent many years creating a work of art out of his science fiction props and costumes. He has built an office adjacent to his home to house his collection, and unlike collectors who find an item and then look for a place to display it, Kirk finds a spot he wants to fill and looks for the perfect collectible to display. Also, unlike collectors who will never part with their prized possessions, Kirk plans to sell some of his larger pieces so he and his wife can travel when their daughter goes to college. His fascination with all things sci-fi began when he was just nine years old and watched famed producer and director Irwin Allen's Lost in Space and Star Trek on television. Ever since moving from Appalachia to Los Angeles, Kirk has had a successful career in the entertainment industry himself, working in post-production. Kirk is joined by pop culture expert Rob Klein, who has an extensive collection of sci-fi memorabilia of his own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208000000 +0000" stop="20251208003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208003000 +0000" stop="20251208010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208010000 +0000" stop="20251208013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike The Pacifist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Stranded in a subway train with different personalities, Mike is shocked when he punches a man for the very first time in his life after the man had pushed Gloria aside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208013000 +0000" stop="20251208020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers and Teresa wake up with their bathroom on fire! Archie expects money cashing in from the insurance company, until he finds out he's guilty for starting the fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208020000 +0000" stop="20251208023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria Split</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Before bedtime, Mike and Gloria have a game of Scrabble in which Mike ends up winning. He uses this game as an opportunity to rub Gloria's nose in the fact that he has to be better at everything, leading to an argument between the two.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208023000 +0000" stop="20251208030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie, The Liberal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Archie and the guys at the lodge are being called bigots in the papers because they are only white, Archie suggests to initiate a black jewish guy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208030000 +0000" stop="20251208033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Marie And Frank's New Friends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra devise a plan to push Frank and Marie into making friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208033000 +0000" stop="20251208040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Alone Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray finds it hard to understand why Debra needs her "alone time."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208040000 +0000" stop="20251208043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Talented Neighborhood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Alan Brady Show" announces a talent contest, and Rob deals with a flood of children and their stage mothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208043000 +0000" stop="20251208050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Word A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie has an expanding vocabulary which includes a bad word.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208050000 +0000" stop="20251208053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to hit the high note on a civil service exam as well as his cornet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208053000 +0000" stop="20251208060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Monsters Are Due On Maple Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paranoia strikes the residents of Maple Street when they believe human-looking aliens have invaded the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208060000 +0000" stop="20251208070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Star Juror  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Killer George Davies finds himself in a unique situation: He's on the jury that's trying an innocent man for the crime he committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208070000 +0000" stop="20251208080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Invasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An earthquake damages the U.S.'s Distant Early Warning (DEW) system and a Defense Department advisor, Whitmore Channing, steals plans from the Air Force identifying the weak spots. Channing has hid the information for pick-up by an enemy agent the next day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208080000 +0000" stop="20251208090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Landscape With Running Figures (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dr. Kimble helps a temporarily blinded Marie Gerald, Lieutenant Gerald's wife, not knowing she's trying to set a trap for him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208090000 +0000" stop="20251208100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Coinage Of The Realm</sub-title>
    <desc>"The carnival atmosphere of an amusement park adds a bizarre twist to Harry O's attempt to save a little girl's life and prevent a gangland murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208100000 +0000" stop="20251208103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208103000 +0000" stop="20251208110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208110000 +0000" stop="20251208113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Taking It Easy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed gets stuck manning the front desk after spraining his wrist, where he must deal with a caller who claims to have planted a bomb at the station, a young man who wants to file a claim of police brutality and an elderly man who walks in with a shotgun. Meanwhile, Malloy is assigned a partner who is a first-day rookie, and they deal with three young children from Oklahoma who are abandoned by their mother, and engage in a high-speed pursuit that ends in a most unexpected way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208113000 +0000" stop="20251208120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Krash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's brand new car gets dinged up when he has to bail out to chase down a purse snatcher, but Sgt. MacDonald promises him his kid brother in Beverly Hills can fix it on the cheap. Out on patrol, he and Reed search for a drunk man accused of randomly shooting arrows, respond to a robbery at a deli that results in tragedy and search for a drug store robbery suspect who gets away after being shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208120000 +0000" stop="20251208130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking Bill</sub-title>
    <desc>"This is a big year for breakdancing, but will Bill survive the celebration in one piece."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208130000 +0000" stop="20251208133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward saves an old pedometer from being thrown out and gives it to Beaver, but not before telling him a story about when he was a kid he would walk 20 miles a day. Taking the story literally, Beaver makes a bet with Whitey that he, too, can walk 20 miles in a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208133000 +0000" stop="20251208140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Borrowed Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver spend the day at the lake, which is where they encounter two kids who let them borrow their boat. However, little do Larry and Beaver know, the boat is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208140000 +0000" stop="20251208150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ominous Outcast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a notorious bank robber's son returns to his hometown it seems as though everyone is interested in missing loot supposedly hidden by the man's father. This leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208150000 +0000" stop="20251208160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsession  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Even from his hospital bed Matlock can't get the case of a TV star accused of killing a therapist out of his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208160000 +0000" stop="20251208170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Landlord</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A drug dealing slumlord is murdered by his accomplices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208170000 +0000" stop="20251208180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Stanley Perkins is retired and returns to the mountain to see Rose</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208180000 +0000" stop="20251208190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>The ex-husband of Hector Lowell's wife claims that the Lowells' home, land and business belong to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208190000 +0000" stop="20251208200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Avenger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Adam are in the Virginia City jail waiting to be hanged. Last minute bids by Joe and Hoss to get them out are hindered by another rancher who wants to see Ben dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208200000 +0000" stop="20251208203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Jealous Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Fay Owens, old friends of Micah, are the McCain's new neighbors. Jake quickly develops an unreasoning jealousy of Lucas with Fay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208203000 +0000" stop="20251208210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Conscience</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>No one's more surprised than Micah when newcomer Leota Carraway claims he's her long-lost husband and the father of her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208210000 +0000" stop="20251208220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Michael Mcgoo Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"When four brothers are orphaned, no one on the train wants all four. Charlie is determined to find a home for the four together and even proposes to a spinster who wants the boys but turns him down so he looks for a husband for her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208220000 +0000" stop="20251208230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>An English Visitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A paramedic from England has a stint with Station 51 observing Roy and John, whose rescues include a fire, a wild-west performer, a car accident and a man trapped in heavy machinery. The visitor saves John's life. At the hospital Dr Brackett treats a rock singer in a diabetic coma and Dr. Early has problems with a defiant nurse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208230000 +0000" stop="20251208233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251208233000 +0000" stop="20251209000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209000000 +0000" stop="20251209003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209003000 +0000" stop="20251209010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209010000 +0000" stop="20251209013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Spoiled Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Arnold the spoiled kid moves to town, he thinks he can walk all over the townsfolk, including Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209013000 +0000" stop="20251209020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Filling Station Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is accused of being the mysterious crook who's been robbing Wally's filling station. Andy and Barney try to determine his guilt or innocence in a variety of methods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209020000 +0000" stop="20251209023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Someone's Cranky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is driving everyone crazy with his nasty behavior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209023000 +0000" stop="20251209030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Moon Rising</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray's attempts to alleviate Debra's PMS moodiness only make her more irritable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209030000 +0000" stop="20251209033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Standing Room Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to save Klink from an officer who plans on turning him in for not having balanced books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209033000 +0000" stop="20251209040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses a broken water main under the camp to aid the escape of captured resistance fighters by creating a health spa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209040000 +0000" stop="20251209043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Charo</sub-title>
    <desc>In Uni-Sex Salon, a hairdressing Carol drives Tim up the wall. Then, in Boring Speech, a member of the Garden Club can't stay awake for their meeting. Finally, in Interview with Chiquita, Tim interviews Charo and meets her equally feisty mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209043000 +0000" stop="20251209053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crafty Kidnapper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alex Tanner and his wife, Patricia, inherent her father's global media empire, things get messy when an obnoxious newspaper man is found dead and the couple's toddler is kidnapped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209053500 +0000" stop="20251209060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A World Of Difference</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman discovers that life as he knows it doesn't really exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209060500 +0000" stop="20251209070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Silence  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Cory Manson is paralyzed, and terrified that her husband will discover she is slowly recovering.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209070500 +0000" stop="20251209080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Name Is Mannix</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired by former crime boss Sam Dubrio when his daughter is kidnapped. His plan is to set up a ransom and then pay off the pickup man to turn in his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209080500 +0000" stop="20251209090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Moonlight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A young convict is being harassed by a prisoner who is running a gambling operation inside of the lock up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209090500 +0000" stop="20251209100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Challenge, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As Barnaby attempts to uncover the motives for a man's alleged suicide, another detective tries to cover up the facts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209100000 +0000" stop="20251209103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209103000 +0000" stop="20251209110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209110000 +0000" stop="20251209113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Routine Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by responding to a call of a drunken woman threatening the patrons of a bar with a handgun. Afterwards, they search for a group of four carjackers who go on a robbery spree after targeting a man with a cache of guns in his trunk, and investigate the suspicious death of a mentally disabled man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209113000 +0000" stop="20251209120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed returns from vacation with a full-body sunburn, making for a miserable work day. Out on patrol, he and Malloy respond to a fiery traffic accident, use an informant's tip to track down a drug dealer, search for an armed robbery suspect based on a vehicle description and attempt to rescue two boys after their rowboat capsizes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209120000 +0000" stop="20251209130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Living Legends Of Tv</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209130000 +0000" stop="20251209133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While his class is reciting a poem about trees, Beaver remembers a tree that Ward had given him for his birthday when they lived at their old house. Wanting "his" tree back, Beaver and Larry go to Beaver's old home and promptly dig it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209133000 +0000" stop="20251209140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Comes To Dinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a surprise when June invites Miss Landers over for dinner and Larry convinces him that something bad might happen. This leads Beaver to become a nervous wreck as he tries to make sure his parents don't do anything to embarrass him. Meanwhile, Larry charges a quarter to anyone who wants to spy on Miss Landers eating dinner at the Cleavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209140000 +0000" stop="20251209150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Irate Inventor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>James Frazer wants a divorce and his cheating wife refuses to give him one. She's also stealing the plans to his invention in order to bait her engineer lover into staying around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209150000 +0000" stop="20251209160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Divorce  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Duncan and Clara Farmington want to have the perfect divorce. What starts out as a simple division of property turns nasty as Leanne represents the wife and Matlock the husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209160000 +0000" stop="20251209170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fool For Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor plots to eliminate his wife -- and his mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209170000 +0000" stop="20251209180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Beginning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Another new minister begins at Walton's Mountain. The church is in disarray, but he gets the community involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209180000 +0000" stop="20251209190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Other Half</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A love triangle between a girl and twin brothers turns tragic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209190000 +0000" stop="20251209200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Trophy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lord and Lady Dunsford arrive at the Ponderosa to visit their old friend, Ben. Adam finds himself the object of Lady Dunsford's attentions when she deems him to be a braver man than her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209200000 +0000" stop="20251209203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Reckoning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is torn by conflicting emotions when he meets the town's new preacher—a former outlaw whom he vowed to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209203000 +0000" stop="20251209210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Town Slept</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The town of North Fork becomes a haven for outlaws when suave Ben Judson smooth-talks his way into the marshal's job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209210000 +0000" stop="20251209220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Adam Mackenzie Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>"The Perez family is run out of town because people believe their daughter Juana is a witch. The family joins the wagon train, and after Juana's brother Felipe is mauled by a cat, the old world is pitted against the new world of medicine."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209220000 +0000" stop="20251209230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Heavyweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>At a fire, the paramedics rescue a pregnant woman and Johnny injures his shoulder. After going into labor, the guilt-ridden mother is determined to abandon her deformed baby. Dr. Morton treats Johnny and gives him a bad time about his physical condition, sending Johnny on a fitness kick. Dr. Early treats an electrocuted child whose mother is on drugs. The son of a stabbing victim is more determined to shoot the assailant than get his father to the hospital. Roy and Johnny rescue a hang glider pilot trapped in a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209230000 +0000" stop="20251209233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251209233000 +0000" stop="20251210000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210000000 +0000" stop="20251210003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210003000 +0000" stop="20251210010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210010000 +0000" stop="20251210013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Discovers America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie doesn't like his new teacher, "Old Lady Crump," because she gives too much homework. Andy comments on the teacher, words which Opie twists in his retelling to Ms. Crump, and she is furious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210013000 +0000" stop="20251210020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Medicine Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, saddened by the death of a friend, is feeling old and tired. She stumbles across a medicine man's presentation and is intrigued by his bottle of elixir, which she believes to add pep to her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210020000 +0000" stop="20251210023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Confronting The Attacker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing his nerve, Robert quits the police force.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210023000 +0000" stop="20251210030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Divorce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barones reminisce about the demise of Robert's marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210030000 +0000" stop="20251210033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Sergeant's Analyst</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After Burkhalter finds him sleeping on the job, Schultz is ordered to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210033000 +0000" stop="20251210040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Klink, A Bomb And A Short Fuse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>General Burkhalter wants Hogan to defuse a bomb that has landed in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210040000 +0000" stop="20251210043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Helen Reddy And John Byner</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nora Desmond, Carol plays a has-been actress, who's so sure she's dying, she plans a death scene. Then, in Rona Rumor, a Hollywood gossip columnist ruins a happy marriage by twisting their words. Finally, in TV Commercials, the gang parodies classic TV commercials, including Shaving, Dirt Around the Collar, Sludge, Improper Margarine, Left-Guard Deodorant, Minnie Made Orange Juice, and Ritalls Dry Control.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210043000 +0000" stop="20251210053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Final Fadeout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After an unscrupulous television star decides not to continue with his hit show, the producer is in hot water. It's not surprising that a murder soon occurs, but nothing goes as expected after that.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210053500 +0000" stop="20251210060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live Walter Jameson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A history teacher talks about the past as if he had lived it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210060500 +0000" stop="20251210070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>An Out For Oscar  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Weighed down by an adulterous partner and her money-mad lover, a shy bank teller schemes to free himself via the "perfect crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210070500 +0000" stop="20251210080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Skid Marks On A Dry Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>People begin to be killed off after Mannix is hired to drub up information that could hurt a politician's chances of being elected governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210080500 +0000" stop="20251210090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Cats And Sudden Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Public prosecutor Mike Arnold needs Cannon's help. He is suspected of the murder of his wife. His problem: Dubious friends want him to finish a corruption investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210090500 +0000" stop="20251210100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Conspiracy Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Pulitzer Prize-winning author ends up dead after he gains a prisoner's confession of innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210100000 +0000" stop="20251210103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210103000 +0000" stop="20251210110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210110000 +0000" stop="20251210113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program to help ground based officers better understand the abilities and limitations of helicopter assistance, malloy and reed are selected to be observers on several air support division missions. This morning's missions include a sea</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210113000 +0000" stop="20251210120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed take flight in separate helicopters to provide assistance in the search of a light plane stolen from the los angeles airport by a distraught man. Afterwards, they search for a group of robbery suspects who flee in separate cars, then reed</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210120000 +0000" stop="20251210130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bills, Bills, Bills</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sitcom superstar Billy Gardell (Mike &amp; Molly, Bob Hearts Abishola) hangs out with Bill and Toony!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210130000 +0000" stop="20251210133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his fortune read by a machine and becomes convinced nothing but good luck is headed his way. However, he doesn't feel that way when Larry sets it up so that Beaver will have to fight a 5th grader, Sonny Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210133000 +0000" stop="20251210140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Makes A Loan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward loans Beaver 25 cents but gives him a dollar, expecting 75 cents as change. However, Larry manages to convince Beaver to loan him the 75 cents. When Larry doesn't pay him back when he said he was going to, a feud erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210140000 +0000" stop="20251210150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Flighty Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When eighteen-year-old Trudy Holbrook's mother dies leaving her $10 million, two men blow into town claiming to be her long-lost father. Then the only person who could identify the real father, a blind uncle, is killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210150000 +0000" stop="20251210160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Final Affair: Part 1  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to figure out whether the archbishop was meant to die in a plot involving an ex-football player, his wife, her lover and the mafia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210160000 +0000" stop="20251210170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Love, Honor, And Obey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Parkers investigation into a purse snatching reveals an abused woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210170000 +0000" stop="20251210180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pearls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth returns to her family home to help a dying aunt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210180000 +0000" stop="20251210190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Journey For Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A stranger accompanies two brothers on their trip to California.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210190000 +0000" stop="20251210200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>San Francisco</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben, Hoss, Joe and Hop-Sing go to San Francisco to sell their cattle. They get shanghaied, but are able to break up the racket with the help of some of Hop-Sing's many cousins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210200000 +0000" stop="20251210203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Milly's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran returns with tales of heroism and the fate of Milly's brother in the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210203000 +0000" stop="20251210210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A head wound wipes out Lucas' memory, leaving him with only one clue: he's wearing an outlaw's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210210000 +0000" stop="20251210220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tom Tuesday Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>"While scouting in Wyoming territory, Duke is forced by outlaw Tom Tuesday to act as his guide to an important rendezvous in Ruby City, Idaho. Tuesday is going blind from a gunshot wound, and Duke is able to turn the tables on him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210220000 +0000" stop="20251210230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Snakebite</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Returning from a fishing trip, Roy, John and Chet help the victims of a car accident. On duty, after rescuing some joyriders whose car went off a cliff, John is bitten by a rattlesnake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210230000 +0000" stop="20251210233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251210233000 +0000" stop="20251211000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211000000 +0000" stop="20251211003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211003000 +0000" stop="20251211010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211010000 +0000" stop="20251211013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darlings Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry is visited by an unusual family from the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211013000 +0000" stop="20251211020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's English Valet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A tourist from England has to do chores to pay off a fine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211020000 +0000" stop="20251211023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Italy: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie surprises the family with the news that she's treating them all to a vacation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211023000 +0000" stop="20251211030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Italy: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie surprises the family with the news that she's treating them all to a vacation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211030000 +0000" stop="20251211033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Crittendon's Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon is the only one to avoid capture when he and his commandos parachute into the area during a mission to capture Rommel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211033000 +0000" stop="20251211040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to think he is about to capture a POW escape ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211040000 +0000" stop="20251211043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>In Yung Fool, Carol and the gang parody the classic TV hit "Kung Fu", with Harvey as the Chinese Master, Jim as the Student.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211043000 +0000" stop="20251211053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Restless Redhead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman claims she was menaced by a car driven by a hooded assailant, whom she shot at with a revolver. When the police find a body in a car wreck with a bullet wound, she is wanted for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211053500 +0000" stop="20251211060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>People Are Alike All Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When a space exploration crashes on Mars, the surviving passenger is surprised to find that Martians are human-looking, very friendly and apparently just like us.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211060500 +0000" stop="20251211070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Death And The Joyful Woman  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The secretary of a wine baron is driven to murder when her dream of marrying the man is shattered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211070500 +0000" stop="20251211080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing Ever Works Twice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an old flame is found dead, Mannix is named the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211080500 +0000" stop="20251211090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Sky Above, Death Below</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A trade union boss dies in the mountains of Colorado. His daughter believes it was murder and hires Cannon to investigate. While the detective is inspecting of the scene someone pursues him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211090500 +0000" stop="20251211100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Odd Man Loses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An industrialist is accidentally killed in a holdup before he's able to close a shady deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211100000 +0000" stop="20251211103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211103000 +0000" stop="20251211110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211110000 +0000" stop="20251211113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>L.a. International</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed barely get acquainted with their fill-in assignment at LAX when a security camera spots a car being stolen from a parking structure. While on foot-beat as Zebra-12 inside the airport, they find a surprise inside of a stolen suitcase, deal with a man who picks the pocket of a returning soldier, chase down a man buying airline tickets with stolen credit cards, escort a runaway boy back to his mother and track down a suspect who robbed a parking structure attendant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211113000 +0000" stop="20251211120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clinic On 18th St</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Abe Strayhorn and his assistants from the major fraud and consumer protection division of the Los Angeles District Attorney's Office launch an investigation into a local doctor following the death of one of his patients, who was found wearing a strange belt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211120000 +0000" stop="20251211130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Prepare For Take Off</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony board an old Cleam Jet to relive the Golden Age of air travel."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211130000 +0000" stop="20251211133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Magician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a common magic trick but is disappointed by everyone's "that's nice" reaction. He gets a totally different reaction out of Bengie, however, when Larry and Beaver convince him that Beaver has been turned into a rock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211133000 +0000" stop="20251211140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>June's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June's birthday has Wally and Beaver fighting over what to buy with the $5 dollars that Ward gave them. Wally buys her a wallet while Beaver buys an ugly blouse that June kindly thanks him for, but she has a hard time bringing herself to wear it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211140000 +0000" stop="20251211150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Treacherous Toupee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tyrannical company president Hartley Bassett returns from the dead after two years. His first act is to fire Peter Dawson, which makes Dawson the prime suspect when Bassett is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211150000 +0000" stop="20251211160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Final Affair: Part 2  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to figure out whether the archbishop was meant to die in a plot involving an ex-football player, his wife, her lover and the mafia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211160000 +0000" stop="20251211170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Odessa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Racists target a ceremony honoring a civil rights pioneer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211170000 +0000" stop="20251211180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor is being beaten by her drunken husband and the Waltons help</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211180000 +0000" stop="20251211190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blue Heaven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man and a fugitive team up as they run from their respective pursuers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211190000 +0000" stop="20251211200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Bitter Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights find themselves resorting to the unthinkable when a neighbor wants to destroy the Ponderosa and will stop at nothing to do so.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211200000 +0000" stop="20251211203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Executioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A former neighbor of the McCain's is released from jail after serving his sentence for stage coach robbery, but the money was never found. Lucas agrees to let the man work for him, but the new work hand holds a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211203000 +0000" stop="20251211210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Lou Mallory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Mallory has arrived in North Fork and quickly purchases land, which includes the hotel and Milly Scott's store. She pays higher prices than the sellers feel their properties are worth. Everyone is happy until they find out that Lou really is an astute businesswoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211210000 +0000" stop="20251211220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Heather And Hamish Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>"Samuel MacIntosh picks Hamish Browne to marry his daughter Heather before the two have met. Heather is a naive young girl who thinks she can talk to animals, while Hamish is a backwoods boy who cares for his livestock more than for women."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211220000 +0000" stop="20251211230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Promotion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy passes the engineer's test, but accepting the promotion will mean leaving the paramedics. A bad fog leads to a multi-car accident on the San Diego Freeway. A young crash victim has a heart murmur. The paramedics have difficulty responding to an attempted suicide. At a fire, Johnny is injured and Roy must rescue both him and a security guard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211230000 +0000" stop="20251211233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251211233000 +0000" stop="20251212000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212000000 +0000" stop="20251212003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212003000 +0000" stop="20251212010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212010000 +0000" stop="20251212013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's First Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney uses his life savings of $300 to buy a car, which almost immediately begins to break down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212013000 +0000" stop="20251212020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rivals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his first crush, who ignores him. Barney steps in and tries to give him advice about women, which leads to Opie developing a crush on Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212020000 +0000" stop="20251212023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Wallpaper, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray kicks his parents out of his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212023000 +0000" stop="20251212030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Meant To Be</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert finds himself choosing between three women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212030000 +0000" stop="20251212033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cuisine A La Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau decides to escape leaving the camp without a chef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212033000 +0000" stop="20251212040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Experts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan saves a German radio expert whom the Nazis want to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212040000 +0000" stop="20251212043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Ham Actor, Carol loses her contact lenses moments before she must go on stage. Then, in Airline Security, Tim detains Harvey, determined to search through his briefcase before he boards the plane. Finally, in The Old Flame, Carol dreams up the perfect meeting when she runs into a former love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212043000 +0000" stop="20251212053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sleepwalker's Niece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When his stepbrother is found dead, a man is charged with murder and is accused of using his sleepwalking as a cover-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212053500 +0000" stop="20251212060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Just before being hanged for murder, a man in 1880 is transported to the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212060500 +0000" stop="20251212070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Last Seen Wearing Blue Jeans  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A 17-year-old girl is inadvertently driven to Mexico by a dangerous car thief, who is unaware she is sleeping in the back seat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212070500 +0000" stop="20251212080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>One Step To Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to protect the granddaughter of an exiled mobster. It seems as though she's being stalked by hoods who want to get to her grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212080500 +0000" stop="20251212090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bitter Legion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A paramilitary troop wants to rob the income of a football stadium. In search of one of the gangsters Cannon approaches the gang and pretends to want to take part in the foray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212090500 +0000" stop="20251212100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Forfeit By Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When a bondsman's client fails to deliver stolen valuables in exchange for bail, the bondsman kills him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212100000 +0000" stop="20251212103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212103000 +0000" stop="20251212110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212110000 +0000" stop="20251212113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy invites a troubled boy along on an upcoming week-long group camping trip in the mountains after apprehending him during a burglary, but soon discovers the kid might be too much for him to handle. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a high-speed chase with a taxi, investigate a motorcycle versus pedestrian accident in a parking lot and respond to an armed robbery call.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212113000 +0000" stop="20251212120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Officers Malloy and Woods take a group of children to a youth camp, but Malloy becomes preoccupied with the 14-year-old boy he reluctantly brought along, who continues to compensate for his small stature by getting into trouble. Meanwhile, Reed goes on patrol alone, and deals with a woman who uses a unique weapon to fend off an attacker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212120000 +0000" stop="20251212130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Cleam's Dungeon Plungers</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212130000 +0000" stop="20251212133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tire Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants to raise chinchillas and begins building a cage in the garage. However, when Beaver changes his mind, Ward tries his best to get Wally and Beaver to clean up the mess. Things get worse when Ward unknowingly runs over some of the wood and nails left laying around with the car, causing the boys to try to patch a flat tire before Ward finds out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212133000 +0000" stop="20251212140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry Hides Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver is staying at the Mondellos, Larry sneaks a peak at his sister's diary and his mother discovers him and yells at him right in front of Beaver. This prompts Larry to run away to Beaver's house, where Beaver secretly hides him in his bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212140000 +0000" stop="20251212150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Credulous Quarry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends Richard Hammond, charged with killing his former girlfriend by running over her with his car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212150000 +0000" stop="20251212160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Magician  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a night at the magic show with Julie, Matlock agrees to defend magician Daniel Fontaine when he's charged with the murder of his assistant and lover, Sandy Farrell, a woman who was as devious as she was beautiful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212160000 +0000" stop="20251212170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Time To Trust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea fears for one of her students after her mother's boyfriend is linked to a criminal operation that has resulted in the deaths of several truckers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212170000 +0000" stop="20251212180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Threshold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy needs a job. At the university, he convinces them to let him set up a television media program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212180000 +0000" stop="20251212190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Crooked Mile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's whip-wielding father does not approve of her romance with Quint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212190000 +0000" stop="20251212200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Feet Of Clay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights take in young Billy Allen following the death of his mother. Hostile at first, the boy eventually befriends Hoss. When Billy's father breaks out of prison, Hoss knows he must do whatever is necessary to protect the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212200000 +0000" stop="20251212203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212203000 +0000" stop="20251212210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212210000 +0000" stop="20251212220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Blane Wessels Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke and three women under attack by Cheyenne Indians are helped by a stranger who has a fatalistic attitude toward life. They take refuge in a relay station where the stranger slowly relays his past to the others while they hope for help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212220000 +0000" stop="20251212230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Insomnia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A boat has an explosion en route to the marina. John obsesses about the lack of night runs and can't sleep. A man and his son are injured when they swerve to avoid a dog. Doctors race against time to save a marijuana smoker dying of an unidentifiable malady. A worker is pinned in a loading dock by a semi. A man and child fall into a gravel pit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212230000 +0000" stop="20251212233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251212233000 +0000" stop="20251213000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213000000 +0000" stop="20251213003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213003000 +0000" stop="20251213010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213010000 +0000" stop="20251213013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Wife For Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy should be getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213013000 +0000" stop="20251213020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dogs, Dogs, Dogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Visiting officials take pause when they visit Mayberry and find that the courthouse is full of dogs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213020000 +0000" stop="20251213023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Pet Cemetery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray inadvertently commits "petslaughter" on Ally's hamster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213023000 +0000" stop="20251213030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Author, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The competition between Ray and Robert reaches an all-time high.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213030000 +0000" stop="20251213033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An English traitor, who could pass for Colonel Crittendon's twin brother, parachutes into camp with information for Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213033000 +0000" stop="20251213040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan becomes convinced that Crittendon can't fool Hitler, things get complicated when Chitterly escapes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213040000 +0000" stop="20251213043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Gloria Swanson</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, the elevator boy has a crush on Carol. Then, in The Guilty Man, Carol plays a sweet housewife who understands her husband's martial indiscretions... at first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213043000 +0000" stop="20251213053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nervous Accomplice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sybil Granger hires Mason to help her buy stock in her estranged husband's oil company on the sly. By this, Sybil hopes to force her husband's latest girlfriend, Roxy Howard, out of the company and his life altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213053500 +0000" stop="20251213060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Tall Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy who believes in magic thinks he is helping a boxer win with his "big, tall wish."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213060500 +0000" stop="20251213070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Pool  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After her adopted son drowns, a woman is blackmailed by a stranger claiming to be the boy's birth mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213070500 +0000" stop="20251213080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Make Like It Never Happened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to get an innocent man, and father of a young girl, off death row. Meanwhile, he romances the mistress of a wealthy industrialist he is investigating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213080500 +0000" stop="20251213090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>That Was No Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Lawyer Jane Butler is threatened. She is told to give up the defense of two burglars. When the menace becomes incendiary the lady begins to fret. Jane asks for Cannon's help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213090500 +0000" stop="20251213100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blueprint For A Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Recently released from prison, the leader of a burglary ring murders his partner for taking his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213100000 +0000" stop="20251213103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Crowded Wedding Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Kate's old flames pays a visit, but his efforts to rekindle their romance are thwarted by his dominating sister.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
