<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025130000 +0000" stop="20251025140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Broom-stick Bunny, The Night Of The Living Duck, D' Fightin' Ones, Invasion Of The Bunny Snatchers, Each Dawn I Crow, Buccaneer Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs makes a visit to Witch Hazel who is infatuated with her own ugliness and needs a rabbit for her stew... , While reading monster comic books Daffy dreams that he is in a nightclub performing for various monsters. , Sylvester and a bulldog are handcuffed together on the way to the pound. They break loose, but they're stuck together with cuffs. , Alien pod people have captured Daffy Duck, Yosemite Sam, and Elmer Fudd and taken their places. Bugs must escape before he is the next victim. , It's about time for Elmer Fudd to behead the chicken on his farm. It's just too bad for him that the chicken gets wise to the plot, thus starting the cartoon chase., Bugs infuriates Pirate Yosemite Sam by stealing his treasure and chases Bugs onto the pirate ship. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025140000 +0000" stop="20251025150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of Miguelito's Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Agent West is summoned by a note from agent Gordon to the local barbershop. While waiting for Gordon, West decides to have a shave and is promptly anesthetised by a hot towel from one of Dr. Loveless's assistants, working in disguise. When he wakes up, he finds himself in a carnival funhouse where he encounters dazed-looking Justice Alonzo Fairlie. Before he can get any information from the judge, he is attacked by a quartet of gunmen. He quickly dispatches his adversaries but Justice Fairlie disappears in the confusion, leaving behind a strange clue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025150000 +0000" stop="20251025160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The George B. Hanrahan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"An ousted Ute medicine man rescued by Duke who knows Chris predicts the future of wagon train passengers but he tries to withhold the deadly fortune of the man who takes him in but is a shyster himself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025160000 +0000" stop="20251025170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Down Shadow Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria is eyewitness to the murder of a saloon girl: A murder committed by her godson, the only child of a local judge. When the boy admits the crime to his father, the judge turns to desperate means to protect him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025170000 +0000" stop="20251025180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Jubal Tanner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A saloon girl and a drifter team up to find the man who did them both wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025180000 +0000" stop="20251025190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>New Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben brings parolee Griff King to the Ponderosa to work, but the newly freed man has a hard time adjusting to life outside of prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025190000 +0000" stop="20251025193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple moves to North Fork under an assumed name to hide the fact that they are the parents of a vicious killer. The plan backfires when the son shows up at their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025193000 +0000" stop="20251025200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After foiling a girl's attempt to rob the general store, Lucas finds that she and her brother are plotting the murder of their abusive stepfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025200000 +0000" stop="20251025210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>No Dogs Or Drovers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After a long, hard cattle drive, Gil Favor and his drovers arrive at a town only to find that the townsfolk aren't receptive to cattle drivers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025210000 +0000" stop="20251025213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Hey Boy's Revenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hey Boy's brother is killed for protesting the working conditions on a Chinese railroad gang in Utah, Paladin must get the boy out of jail and bring the killer to justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025213000 +0000" stop="20251025220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is determined to debunk the dire menace posed by a marauding monster that has smashed mining camps, decimated an indian village and has the residents of Nugget City hiding behind locked doors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025220000 +0000" stop="20251026000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Restless Knights, Ants In The Pantry, Bubble Trouble, Flying Saucer Daffy, Three Arabian Nuts, In The Sweet Pie And Pie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Set in Medieval times, the Stooges learn they are of royal blood and vow to save the kingdom.   , The Stooges are pest exterminators who drum up business by planting vermin in a ritzy mansion where a party is going on.  They are hired, but must pose as guests to work unobserved.   , The Stooges are convicts about to be executed for some murders they didn't commit.  The day before the execution they are tricked into marrying three rich girls who need husbands to collect a legacy.  At the last minute the real murderers confess and the Stooges are pardoned.  The girls are now stuck with the Stooges so they plot to get rid of them by making them become gentlemen.  The girl's lawyer convinces them to throw a big party in the hope that the Stooges will humiliate them and they can get a divorce.  The boys do just that as the party degenerates into a wild pie fight.  But the girls decide to keep the Stooges and give their lawyer the boot. [Dance teacher footage from "Hoi Polloi"] , The Stooges are pharmacists who invent a fountain of youth formula that can turn old people young.  They turn an old lady into a beautiful young woman, but when her husband takes the formula it turns him into a gorilla. , Joe accidentally takes a picture of a paper plate, which Moe and Larry submit to a magazine as an authentic picture of a flying saucer.  Moe and Larry collect a big prize, but when the picture is proven to be phony, they're hauled off to Jail.  Joe then gets a picture of a real spaceship and this time he gets the fame and fortune, while Moe and Larry wind up in a sanitarium. , The Stooges find themselves in the crosshairs of thieves who want a magic lamp."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026000000 +0000" stop="20251026023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Fly</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mad scientist's invention leaves him forever changed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026023000 +0000" stop="20251026043000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Return Of The Fly</sub-title>
    <desc>"Years after his father's dangerous experiments, a son continues his work, hiring a criminal in disguise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026043000 +0000" stop="20251026050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Wolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lumberjacks leave their job, fearing a werewolf. A forest fire enlivens the plot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026050000 +0000" stop="20251026060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Ghost In Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith holds a seance to contact his Uncle Thaddeus. Instead a spirit creature is contacted and creates havoc for the Robinsons. It is later discovered that the "spirit creature" is a physical creature, rendered invisible by the properties of the "ionized gas" in the bog from which it came.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026060000 +0000" stop="20251026070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Shipwrecked on a mysterious island, Nelson, Sharkey and a geologist are terrorized by a giant lizard and then by hallucinations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026070000 +0000" stop="20251026080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings work with a sympathetic Giant college student to get a reactor for their spaceship, but when it malfunctions they are plagued by hallucinations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026080000 +0000" stop="20251026090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of Nero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1915, the travelers try to keep the ghost of Nero from taking revenge on a descendant of Nero's rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026090000 +0000" stop="20251026100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Pit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A professor diagnosed with delusions tells Vincent aliens are experimenting with dreams.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026100000 +0000" stop="20251026110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial</sub-title>
    <desc>"Grizzly 'Ben' is accused of eating a bucket of fish from an Indian tribesman,after a young brave named Tumaqua takes of with it to hide his failure at catching fish. Will Ben be found guilty or can Adams save his furry friend?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026110000 +0000" stop="20251026113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of Quaking Earth</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the southeastern coastal plain of the United States in Georgia, there exists one of the world’s truly unique jingle swamps named by the Indians OKEEFENOKEE (land of floating islands).  Here in this intricate maze of river-ways with its ferns, grasses and cane growths, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore a fairytale jungle that is one of the last strongholds of the alligator.  The jungle suddenly becomes marshland, also called wet prairies, with water 1 to 4 feet deep.  Here in profusion fly hundreds of American egrets, the swamp fisherman.  Jim uses the Indian soap plant to wash his hands, and Marlin tries to balance on one of the floating hammocks or floating islands of “quaking earth.”  We witness the lassoing, from a boat, of a bear that has moved in too close to civilization.  After being caged, he is moved into the interior on an island that can support him, and we follow his encounters with an alligator, a skunk, and an alligator snapping turtle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026113000 +0000" stop="20251026120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Trailing The Midnight Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Winter is night, summer is day, and you need your wits to survive in the forbidding land north of the Arctic Circle.  In this story you go by walrus skin boat, dogsled, airplane and helicopter.  You hunt seal with Eskimos, find polar bear and beluga whale.  You round up a large herd of reindeer and tag them for conservation officials. And you watch Jim Fowler discover a far-north version of a popular rodeo event:  bulldogging moose from a helicopter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026120000 +0000" stop="20251026123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cattail Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin visits the Grand Teton Mountains in the U.S. and the wilderness north of Canada to show us the territorial fight, the rescue of a baby moose and to see the sandhill cranes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026123000 +0000" stop="20251026130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>The Philmont Trail</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim make a fascinating climb up the Philmont Trail with a troop of Explorer Scouts at the famous Boy Scout ranch near Cimarron in northern New Mexico."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026130000 +0000" stop="20251026133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Kalahari region of southern Africa, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler study the life and habits of the graceful and cunning leopard by establishing a camp near a hidden leopard den."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026133000 +0000" stop="20251026140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim continue their investigation into the home life of the leopard."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026140000 +0000" stop="20251026143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Call Me Irresponsible</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Soon to be 16 and anxious to start saving for a car, Greg gets his first job as an office boy at Mike's architectural firm. However, he places his job in jeopardy when he carelessly loses some important designs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026143000 +0000" stop="20251026150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Treasure Of Sierra Avenue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>While playing in a vacant lot, the boys discovers a wallet containing $1,100. The girls learn about the boys' find, and they decide they want a cut of the money. The result is another boys-against-girls fight in the Brady household.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026150000 +0000" stop="20251026153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The Apartment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie, Potsie and Ralph get an apartment of their own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026153000 +0000" stop="20251026160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The girls get engaged to Richie and Fonzie to avoid a shotgun wedding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026160000 +0000" stop="20251026163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy is chosen to be the sole judge of a local beauty pageant. The entrants include Floyd's niece, the mayor's daughter and Ellie Walker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026163000 +0000" stop="20251026170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Camping Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy fears that she and Ricky don't have enough in common, so she decides to pursue one of his interests: camping. Ricky and Fred don't want her (or Ethel for that matter) horning in on their summer retreat, so Ricky decides to take Lucy on a "trial run" in the woods and make her life miserable. But Lucy is wise to his plan; guess whose life is made miserable in the end?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026170000 +0000" stop="20251026173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Short Pants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When June goes on a trip to visit her sister, Peggy, June's Aunt Martha steps in and stays with Ward and the boys. They do their best not to hurt Martha's feelings, but Beaver has the hardest time, when she buys him a suit, knee socks, a cap and short pants and makes him wear the outfit to school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026173000 +0000" stop="20251026180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfume Salesmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to win a fancy film projector and in order to get it they have to sell 24 bottles of perfume. However, the appalling aroma of the perfume quickly leads to zero sales and has Ward trying to think up a sales gimmick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026180000 +0000" stop="20251026183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly's Animals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Elly's animals converge on the Clampett estate when Pearl starts giving yodeling lessons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026183000 +0000" stop="20251026190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro has an idea of starting a new business, a five-second car wash. But Jed and Granny don’t care for the idea and think that Jethro and Elly need jobs to fill their time. At the bank, Milburn is taking care of his nephew, little Milby. Jane doesn’t want to take care of the sneaky child and Drysdale doesn’t have the time. When Jed visits asking for jobs for Elly and Jethro, he says that Elly May can take care of Milby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026190000 +0000" stop="20251026193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Allergy Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>The Skipper begins to itch and sneeze whenever he is around Gilligan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026193000 +0000" stop="20251026200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Friendly Physician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A mad scientist lands on the island and takes the castaways to his castle to perform strange experiments on them. Soon they are locked in a dungeon and trapped in the wrong bodies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026200000 +0000" stop="20251026203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Cat's Meow  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Iola has her dead cat freeze-dried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026203000 +0000" stop="20251026210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Gets The Bird  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama's crazy old Uncle Oscar passes on, he leaves her his talking parrot, Captain Petey, who convinces the family that treasure is hidden somewhere in the house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026210000 +0000" stop="20251026220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Eyes Of Love / Masquerade / Hollywood Royalty (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 2. Thieves eye a honeymooning actress's gems; a man encounters his blind childhood love; a wife meets her spouse's mistress."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026220000 +0000" stop="20251026223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol And Old Lace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney, on a spree of destroying illegal stills, are surprised when a trail leads them to two spinster sisters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026223000 +0000" stop="20251026230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>David Kostman- Sci-fi/horror Props + Costumes</sub-title>
    <desc>"David Kostman is proud of his home “dungeon,” where he keeps his vast collection of props and costumes from horror, sci-fi, and fantasy movies. David grew up with a magazine called Famous Monsters of Filmland and became hooked. Even today, he says the films continue to stretch his imagination. In addition to props and costumes, David also collects movie posters and autographs. He will show some of his favorite items, ranging from arachnids to vampire teeth to our expert Mark Short, who has his own collection of movie memorabilia."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026230000 +0000" stop="20251026233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251026233000 +0000" stop="20251027000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027000000 +0000" stop="20251027003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Brief Encounter (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith leaves Archie when she finds out he a dated a flirtatious waitress while she was volunteering at the Sunshine Home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027003000 +0000" stop="20251027010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Brief Encounter (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith forgives Archie's indiscretions after Mike and Gloria bring the two together for an emotional reunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027010000 +0000" stop="20251027013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Brief Encounter (part 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith forgives Archie's indiscretion after Mike and Gloria bring the two together for an emotional reunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027013000 +0000" stop="20251027020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Beverly Rides Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>As a practical joke, Archie fixes up one of his drinking buddies with female impersonator Beverly La Salle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027020000 +0000" stop="20251027023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Father Knows Least</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray gets to use the "active technique" he and Debra learned in parenting class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027023000 +0000" stop="20251027030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray takes his brother, Robert, out for a night on the town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027030000 +0000" stop="20251027033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Uhny Uftz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Did Rob see a UFO?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027033000 +0000" stop="20251027040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Long Night's Journey Into Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura tries to spend the night alone while her family is on a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027040000 +0000" stop="20251027043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph cuts a record to sweet talk Alice after insulting her mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027043000 +0000" stop="20251027050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare At 20,000 Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While aboard a commercial aircraft, a man believes he is seeing a gremlin on its wing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027050000 +0000" stop="20251027053000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In 4-d</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband has a vague memory of helping a woman get rid of a corpse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027053000 +0000" stop="20251027060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a terrible accident leaves a man completely paralyzed, people who encounter him think he is dead, though he is very much alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027060000 +0000" stop="20251027070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Tram</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Two underworld leaders, Hatcher and Thorne, have called a conference of Syndicate leaders to form a massive holding/laundering company. The IMF must obtain their joint Swiss bank account number.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027070000 +0000" stop="20251027080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Trial By Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble's sister Donna summons him home with a possible break in the case: a letter from James Eckhardt, a former U.S. Army captain who also saw the one-armed man fleeing from the Kimble's house on the night of Helen's murder. Kimble meets with Eckhardt, w</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027080000 +0000" stop="20251027090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Mysterious Case Of Lester And Dr. Fong</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mishaps and murders abound when boy-wonder private eye Lester Hodges and his mentor Dr. Creighton Fong join forces with Harry Orwell."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027090000 +0000" stop="20251027093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027093000 +0000" stop="20251027100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027100000 +0000" stop="20251027103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Radical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At roll call, Malloy and Reed are asked to look out for a suspected militant and, after spotting him, attempt to follow him to his stash of weapons. Malloy also is asked by a security guard to investigate a possible shakedown and smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027103000 +0000" stop="20251027110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed report to a robbery at a grocery store, where Malloy is required to engage in a high-speed pursuit with one of the suspects while Reed apprehends the other on foot. When Malloy is seriously injured in a rollover accident at a remote location and loses two-way radio communication, Reed and others from the department race against the clock to locate him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027110000 +0000" stop="20251027120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Headless Horseman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Washington Irving's classic tale is retold with a Toony twist."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027120000 +0000" stop="20251027123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward make Wally and Beaver promise that they won't go see a scary movie. However, Wally and Beaver are talked into seeing it, thanks to Wally's so-called best friend, Eddie Haskell. The movie has quite an influence on Beaver, who makes a voodoo doll, names it Eddie Haskell and sticks it with pins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027123000 +0000" stop="20251027130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Part Time Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After taking an IQ test, Beaver scores the highest in his class and Mrs. Rayburn suggests that it would be best if Beaver went to a special school, where his abilities can be challenged. However, little does anyone know, everything is not as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027130000 +0000" stop="20251027140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Calendar Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A building contractor is charged with the murder of a wealthy political Mr. fix-it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027140000 +0000" stop="20251027150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Dame  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While out at dinner, a chance encounter prompts Matlock to relate the story of a case from years earlier in which Matlock's father believed his friend was murdered by his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027150000 +0000" stop="20251027160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lessons Learned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie sends Parker to confirm suspicions that a local truck stop is really a front for a prostitution business. When a young prostitute is found dead Gillespie is shocked at her father’s reaction. Parker is dismayed when he recognizes one of the ladies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027160000 +0000" stop="20251027170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver Wings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob delivers a package to a woman whose husband is in the war</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027170000 +0000" stop="20251027180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Jeb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A man buys an allegedly stolen horse from a farm boy, which proves to be a big mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027180000 +0000" stop="20251027190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush At Rio Lobo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws lie in wait, ready to waylay a stagecoach carrying Ben and a young pregnant woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027190000 +0000" stop="20251027193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A condemned killer being transported by train murders a marshal and takes Mark hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027193000 +0000" stop="20251027200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark discovers that the new preacher and his wife are impostors planning a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027200000 +0000" stop="20251027210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Swamp Devil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>"A section of the wagon train splits to attempt a crossing of a dangerous swamp. On the way they hear stories from the local Indians of a strange creatures living in the swamp. Flint has a secret worry as he leads them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027210000 +0000" stop="20251027220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nurses Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A store owner shoots an armed robber and is filled with remorse. Sparks fly between Johnny and a nurse. Dr. Early treats an alcoholic. A dog delays the rescue of an unconscious woman. Dr. Morton assumes an unconscious hippie is on drugs. The firemen rescue a man trapped at a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027220000 +0000" stop="20251027223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Kim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye operates on a five-year-old Korean boy, and Radar can't find his family. Henry plans to send him to the orphanage, and the camp enjoys his company while they can. Trapper decides to adopt him after consulting his wife, and has to rescue him after he wanders into the minefield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027223000 +0000" stop="20251027230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>L.i.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporal Walker is being sent home, and he wants to marry his Korean girl so she and their baby can return with him. CID sends Lt Willis to investigate, but when he refuses Hawkeye and Trapper frame him. Hawkeye is upset that a nurse he was pursuing does not approve of the marriage between "a gook" and "one of us."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027230000 +0000" stop="20251027233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Of Henry Blake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Majors Houlihan and Burns press charges against Colonel Blake to get him arrested and put Frank in charge. They also put Hawkeye and Trapper under arrest so that they can't help Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251027233000 +0000" stop="20251028000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad... Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Once more Hawkeye writes home to his father: the doctors operate on a soldier with a grenade shot into his body; Hawkeye and Trapper color the skin of a racist patient, who demanded the right color blood, while he is asleep; Henry gets a movie of his daughter's birthday from home; the officers hold the monthly staff meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028000000 +0000" stop="20251028003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy, The Marriage Counselor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy counsels a Mayberry couple who are constantly bickering with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028003000 +0000" stop="20251028010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes suspicious when a record promoter comes to town to gather material for a folk music album.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028010000 +0000" stop="20251028013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Mozart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray tries to teach Ally an important lesson about not quitting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028013000 +0000" stop="20251028020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Golf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray's guilt manifests itself in an anxiety attack on the golf course.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028020000 +0000" stop="20251028023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Two Nazis For The Price Of One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A Gestapo agent knows about Hogan's operation and tries to leverage this knowledge to find out information about the Manhattan Project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028023000 +0000" stop="20251028030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Doctor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink's illness causes problems for one of Hogan's plots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028030000 +0000" stop="20251028033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bing Crosby And Paul Lynde</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bing Crosby and Paul Lynde. Originally aired on 11/03/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028033000 +0000" stop="20251028043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mischievous Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady private investigator and his pawn die mysteriously, the woman who may have been his intended target is charged with their murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028043500 +0000" stop="20251028050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Hitch-hiker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Alone on a cross-country trip, a woman keeps seeing the same hitch-hiker everywhere she looks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028050500 +0000" stop="20251028053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of Mr. Pelham</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Albert Pelham is slowly being replaced at home and at work by a double.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028053500 +0000" stop="20251028060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Crime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous criminologist discovers that he has sent an innocent man to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028060500 +0000" stop="20251028070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When a little girl turns up dead and unidentified, Mannix sets out to discover who she was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028070500 +0000" stop="20251028080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Quasar Kill</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates the mysterious death of a scientist who was killed by a laser beam."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028080500 +0000" stop="20251028090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Go Round</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>It's one killing after another as Barnaby investigates a hit-and-run accident while wealthy townspeople plot his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028090000 +0000" stop="20251028093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028093000 +0000" stop="20251028100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028100000 +0000" stop="20251028103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an environmentalist known as "The Ferret" who has been posing as an employee to infiltrate and sabotage industrial complexes he feels are creating too much pollution. In the meantime, they respond to a woman who is nearly comatose and ultimately gives birth to a stillborn baby. They then investigate the witchdoctor who has been convincing her and other women that eating clay will ensure a successful pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028103000 +0000" stop="20251028110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Truant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After apprehending a couple of juvenile delinquents who are ransacking a house, Reed is inspired to submit an idea on how to deal with truants, which ultimately gets implemented on a trial basis by the captain, but draws the ire of Officer Wells. Back on patrol, they apprehend a couple of high-level drug dealers who run into bad luck, and nearly get run over by two men using stolen automobile parts to build a high-powered go cart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028110000 +0000" stop="20251028120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Scariest Places On Earth</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit a few of the world's scrariest places."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028120000 +0000" stop="20251028123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Party Invitation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is invited to Linda Dennison's birthday party and quickly discovers that he is the only boy that she invited. Fearing for his reputation, Beaver tries his best to get out of attending but June and Ward are insistent, not aware of the situation Beaver's in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028123000 +0000" stop="20251028130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy Rutherford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The local bully, Lumpy Rutherford, has been picking on Beaver and Wally and, thanks to a story Ward tells them, the boys decide to play a joke on Lumpy. However, their ploy catches the wrong person: Lumpy's father and Ward's co-worker, Fred Rutherford, is caught in the trap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028130000 +0000" stop="20251028140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Petulant Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret was a much younger woman on the make who entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028140000 +0000" stop="20251028150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Suspect: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a wealthy widow charged with the murder of her husband, while Michelle defends a father accused of murdering the drug dealer who got his child hooked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028150000 +0000" stop="20251028160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Perversions Of Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A mild mannered school teacher is accused of child molestation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028160000 +0000" stop="20251028170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Wager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A run (on foot) and ride (on horse) race is being held. Mary Ellen and Erin bet two guys that they will win</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028170000 +0000" stop="20251028180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Quest For Asa Janin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Convinced that Dave Ingalls is innocent of murder, Matt sets out to find the real killer before Ingalls is wrongfully hanged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028180000 +0000" stop="20251028190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Twenty-sixth Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Samuel Clemens (a.k.a. Mark Twain) comes nosing around town investigating the mysterious death of miners, he starts an uprising with accusations of claim jumping and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028190000 +0000" stop="20251028193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance get into trouble with the Army when they try to help a wounded young soldier who deserted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028193000 +0000" stop="20251028200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mark contracts typhoid fever and has a vision of his dead mother, he no longer seems interested in getting well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028200000 +0000" stop="20251028210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cole Crawford Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>"The young Crawford couple is trying to leave their past behind but having difficulty doing it. The wagon train is crossing a massive ranch and the owner's son refuses to let Mrs. Crawford leave nor will the train members help them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028210000 +0000" stop="20251028220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Publicity Hound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John is envious of the publicity given to another paramedic. After Roy and John rescue a man trapped in ship's rigging, John gets seasick. Dr. Brackett clashes with a tycoon over a diagnosis. The paramedics rescue a horse from a ditch and a child stuck in a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028220000 +0000" stop="20251028223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A lone sniper has the 4077th pinned down—including Radar and Henry in the shower. The poor boy thinks he's firing on McArthur's headquarters, and a chopper finally comes by and wounds him with gunfire from above, ending the siege. Hawkeye walks out to into the bush to tend to the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028223000 +0000" stop="20251028230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Carry On Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp succumbs to the Asian flu, except for Hawkeye and Margaret, who have to do everything themselves. As the others start to recover, Hawkeye falls ill but he still manages to operate when wounded arrive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028230000 +0000" stop="20251028233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251028233000 +0000" stop="20251029000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029000000 +0000" stop="20251029003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Barney's Morale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's overzealous policing enrages the people of Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029003000 +0000" stop="20251029010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Gentleman Crook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An infamous con artist, held temporarily in Mayberry, manages to enchant everyone except Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029010000 +0000" stop="20251029013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond is shocked to learn that his parents were once separated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029013000 +0000" stop="20251029020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Working Late Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra asks Ray to start working from home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029020000 +0000" stop="20251029023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered home and Colonel Crittendon is sent to replace him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029023000 +0000" stop="20251029030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket Newkirk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk unknowingly sneaks a beautiful Gestapo agent he has fallen for into camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029030000 +0000" stop="20251029033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Mel Torme And Nanette Fabray</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Mel Torme and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 11/17/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029033000 +0000" stop="20251029043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Laughing Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman being held in prison pending her trial sees the woman whom she believes committed the crime with which she has been charged on a televised gala.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029043500 +0000" stop="20251029050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mirror Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman encounters her doppelgänger at a bus terminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029050500 +0000" stop="20251029053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Jury Of Her Peers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A sheriff suspects the wife of a murdered man to be his killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029053500 +0000" stop="20251029060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Coming, Mama</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman begins to realize that her mother has no intentions of cutting her from her apron strings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029060500 +0000" stop="20251029070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Figures In A Landscape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is stalked by a sniper while searching for a missing woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029070500 +0000" stop="20251029080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Shot</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates when a former hitman seems to now be on someone's wanted list."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029080500 +0000" stop="20251029090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>To Denise, With Love And Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A philanderer murders his mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029090000 +0000" stop="20251029093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029093000 +0000" stop="20251029100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Parolee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon retrace a 14-year-old investigation to determine whether charges can be brought against a man up for parole.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029100000 +0000" stop="20251029103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are ambushed by two men who want to silence the prisoner they are transporting from Malibu to Los Angeles. Their problems are compounded by the lack of radio communication in Malibu Canyon, which ultimately results in Reed being taken hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029103000 +0000" stop="20251029110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed brainstorm what to get Sgt. MacDonald for his anniversary, subdue an understandably belligerent wrestler in a bar and get followed by a man with a recent streak of bad luck. Afterward, they investigate an unethical used car salesman and liquor store robbery and also thwart an attempted camper theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029110000 +0000" stop="20251029120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Zombie Makeover</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill make a zombie movie, with some unbelievable, undead makeup."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029120000 +0000" stop="20251029123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Paper Route</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to get brand-new bikes so they ask Ward for some money; however, he suggests that they earn the money. This leads Wally and Beaver to get a job delivering papers. Later, while trying to help the boys out, Ward and June inadvertently almost get Wally and Beaver fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029123000 +0000" stop="20251029130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Child Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After Ward's bragging about Wally and Beaver being responsible, Herb and Janet Wilson assume that it would be alright to leave their four-year-old daughter in Wally and Beaver's care while they go out to a party with Ward and June. However, the trouble begins when the youngster locks herself in the bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029130000 +0000" stop="20251029140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dangerous Dowager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Matilda Benson is a tough old broad who rules her children with an iron hand and the promises in her will. When Benson and her brood become involved in a gambling scandal and the death of a nightclub owner, Mason looks into the matriarch's matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029140000 +0000" stop="20251029150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Suspect: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a wealthy widow charged with the murder of her husband, while Michelle defends a father accused of murdering the drug dealer who got his child hooked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029150000 +0000" stop="20251029160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>...and Justice For Some</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie and his officers are outraged when a drug courier who ran down the son of Virgil's next door neighbor makes a deal with the F.B.I. to avoid prosecution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029160000 +0000" stop="20251029170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fastidious Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth tries to sell a book at the store about being a perfect wife</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029170000 +0000" stop="20251029180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kate Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man commits murder and ambushes Matt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029180000 +0000" stop="20251029190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Stallion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble follows when Ben purchases a beautiful black stallion for Joe's birthday gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029190000 +0000" stop="20251029193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Lucas's returns to town in the company of a shady gambler and is accused of cheating at cards.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029193000 +0000" stop="20251029200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men are vying for a rancher's daughter's affections. When she is found dead, one of them becomes the prime suspect in her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029200000 +0000" stop="20251029210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Levi Hale Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>"Chris Hale is traveling to the Wyoming prison to pick up his brother Levi---who's about to be released from prison. Chris assumed Levi was pardoned but he was paroled to Chris. He must keep Levi out of Wyoming or he will be hanged."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029210000 +0000" stop="20251029220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Weird Wednesday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A parachutist lands in a tree, an obese man collapses while jogging, an 80-year-old woman breaks her ankle while dancing, a man can't stop the hiccups, a boy tries to cryogenically freeze himself, a golfer is bitten by a snake, a prostitute brings in a customer suffering from chest pains, and John is injured during the rescue of a drunk driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029220000 +0000" stop="20251029223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029223000 +0000" stop="20251029230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029230000 +0000" stop="20251029233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251029233000 +0000" stop="20251030000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030000000 +0000" stop="20251030003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to help Barney express his lovestruck feelings for Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030003000 +0000" stop="20251030010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Housekeepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie go to great lengths to show Aunt Bee what a mess they'd be without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030010000 +0000" stop="20251030013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Children's Book, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides to try her hand at writing a children's book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030013000 +0000" stop="20251030020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Gift, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is feeling guilty about only getting his dad a card for his 65th birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030020000 +0000" stop="20251030023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>War Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to get the Gestapo to release its prisoners, Hogan tricks Klink and Hochstetter into thinking the war is over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030023000 +0000" stop="20251030030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan prepares Klink to flee to Argentina with information for the Allies after Klink is challenged to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030030000 +0000" stop="20251030033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eydie Gorme, Shecky Green, And Improv Group</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eydie Gorme, Shecky Green, and Improv Group. Originally aired on 11/24/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030033000 +0000" stop="20251030043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune teller gives a series of accurate predictions regarding a woman's future. But something goes wrong when she's charged with murdering her new husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030043500 +0000" stop="20251030050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Masks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A dying man demands that his family wear masks he's given them at a Mardi Gras party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030050500 +0000" stop="20251030053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night The World Ended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of newspapermen plays a joke on a man who in return decides to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030053500 +0000" stop="20251030060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Door Without A Key</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man with amnesia and a young boy with no one find each other in a police station.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030060500 +0000" stop="20251030070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Mouse That Died</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Out on a routine missing persons case, Mannix uncovers an espionage ring and falls victim to a slow-acting poison for which he must race against time to procure the antidote.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030070500 +0000" stop="20251030080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Point After Death</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates the shooting death of the girlfriend of a former basketball star."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030080500 +0000" stop="20251030090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Little Glory, Little Death, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A blackmailing actress gets pushed off a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030090000 +0000" stop="20251030093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030093000 +0000" stop="20251030100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Bunco - $9,000</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The search is on for a swindler who conned an old vaudevillian out of $9,000 he found on a sidewalk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030100000 +0000" stop="20251030103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Assassination</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed become the repeated targets of an unidentified sniper who has them called to fake disturbances and follows them to some of their real calls, which include a special deliver, a suicide threat at a gas station and a reported prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030103000 +0000" stop="20251030110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Dinosaur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Eight years after an act of heroism put him out of commission, an officer returns to active duty, only to find that the changes made to the job that limit an officer's power and increase suspects' rights are too much to handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030110000 +0000" stop="20251030120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>House Monster</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony take a spooky field trip to get into the Halloween spirit."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030120000 +0000" stop="20251030123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Account</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward tries to teach Wally and Beaver the importance of saving by giving them a piggy bank. The boys quickly save up a handful of change and are all ready to spend it on some baseball equipment. However, unknown to their parents, they change their minds and decide to spend the money on a most unselfish gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030123000 +0000" stop="20251030130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lonesome Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally goes away on a trip with the Boy Scout troop that he belongs to, leaving a lonesome Beaver behind. Finding his friends to be busy, Beaver takes up other means to make the time go by.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030130000 +0000" stop="20251030140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Toy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Selkirk is a major league rotter who wants Claire Allison in the worst way, even though she's dating Dirk Benedict. Selkirk has Dirk's jaw broken and begins sending Claire threatening mail. Then Selkirk is murdered in his beach house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030140000 +0000" stop="20251030150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Defense  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends teenager Danny Hayes, who is accused of murdering his father. Danny insists that his father was going to kill his mother, but the testimony of his father's best friend damages the young man's story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030150000 +0000" stop="20251030160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Heart Of Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba is reunited with his high school sweetheart, but his happiness is short lived after she resorts to murder to silence an attorney who was threatening to stop her from inheriting her late husband's estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030160000 +0000" stop="20251030170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Walker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An unknown person is walking around Walton's Mountain at nights and causing worry</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030170000 +0000" stop="20251030180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Lover Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A ladies' man takes up with a married woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030180000 +0000" stop="20251030190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Hidden Enemy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A new doctor in Virginia City is secretly fighting the demons of a morphine addiction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030190000 +0000" stop="20251030193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Shotgun man John Beaumont, who Lucas sent to prison, returns with vengeance on his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030193000 +0000" stop="20251030200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting a man in self-defense, Andy Moon turns to Lucas for protection from his vengeful brothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030200000 +0000" stop="20251030210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Terry Morrell Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>"After the Sheriff escorts Ben Morrell and his son Terry to the wagon train, the members find Ben Morrell and his son very antisocial: the two can't even tolerate each other. One woman wants to adopt Terry believing he is being mistreated."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030210000 +0000" stop="20251030220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dilemma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An elevator gets stuck between floors, and then the brake drum fails; inside, a man has a heart attack. A nursing student is in awe of Dr. Brackett; a fireman buff develops a crush on John, who tries to get rid of her. A man is injured in his junkyard. An industrial accident takes place at a railroad yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030220000 +0000" stop="20251030223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030223000 +0000" stop="20251030230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030230000 +0000" stop="20251030233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As You Were</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While there are no casualties, Hawkeye and Trapper crate up Frank while he sleeps and receive gorilla suits through the mail. Henry gets a tan and gives another sex orientation lecture. When the wounded start pouring in again, their own side shells the camp, hitting the generator, and Radar tries to get through to tell someone to stop the shelling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251030233000 +0000" stop="20251031000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The supply lines to the camp are cut. Radar, the housing officer, starts doubling people up to save fuel and Klinger is thrown out of the nurse's tent. People start burning everything to stay warm while Frank wears his heated socks. The toilet paper supply is worst hit, and then wounded start arriving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031000000 +0000" stop="20251031003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a handsome new doctor arrives in town, his friendship with Ellie arouses suspicion in Aunt Bee and Barney and jealousy in Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031003000 +0000" stop="20251031010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Plaque For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Pike (Dick Elliott) and the townspeople are shocked to discover that the last living descendant of Revolutionary War hero Nathan Tibbs is Mayberry's town drunk, Otis Campbell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031010000 +0000" stop="20251031013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>High School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray reluctantly takes Deborah to his 20th high school reunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031013000 +0000" stop="20251031020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Letter, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides to tell Ray's mom she can't stand her being so critical.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031020000 +0000" stop="20251031023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Axis Annie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use a propaganda radio announcer to get information to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031023000 +0000" stop="20251031030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>What Time Does The Balloon Go Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A basket-weaving and a kite-flying contest are part of Hogan's plan to transport an agent to England in a balloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031030000 +0000" stop="20251031033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol suspects her sister is pregnant and tries to figure out who the father is. Then, in George and Zelda, Carol sabotages a poker game on a riverboat. Finally, in Salute to Horror Movies, the gang parodies classic films, including "The Mummy", "The Wolf Man", and "The Bride of Frankenstein".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031033000 +0000" stop="20251031043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Candy Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Claire Armstrong has built a candy empire, but things go sour when her cousin is almost killed by poisoned candy and a man is found dead in his office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031043500 +0000" stop="20251031050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Living Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is displeased when his wife buys an expensive doll for his step-daughter. He becomes even more displeased when the doll tells him it doesn't like him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031050500 +0000" stop="20251031053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Greatest Monster Of Them All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A horror-film actor plans payback after an incompetent director ruins his comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031053500 +0000" stop="20251031060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Sorcerer's Apprentice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfaithful woman plans to get rid of her husband with the help of a stranded young man. (This episode was deemed too horrifying by a sponsor and was not broadcast until the series was sold into syndication.)</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031060500 +0000" stop="20251031070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Question Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young boy asks Mannix to prove that his hero did not die from a hit-and-run accident but rather was murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031070500 +0000" stop="20251031080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Well Remembered Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mobsters kidnap Judge Hayes's daughter, on the orders of their boss who is on trial in Hayes's courtroom. Cannon must find and rescue her before the judge is forced to preside over a miscarriage of justice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031080500 +0000" stop="20251031090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty Million Alibis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A jewel thief writing his memoirs accidentally kills a butler while making off with a diamond necklace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031090000 +0000" stop="20251031093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031093000 +0000" stop="20251031100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031100000 +0000" stop="20251031103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pick-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed actively search for a serial rapist/murderer who hasn't left behind any solid clues, which causes Malloy to vent about what he perceives to be over-reliance on computers at the expense of old-fashioned police logic. In the meantime, they deal with a kid who crashes his friend's dirt bike, engage in a futile high-speed pursuit of a porsche and search for an armed suspect of a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031103000 +0000" stop="20251031110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizens All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed deal with a surly victim of a purse snatching and search for her assailant, who is driving a vehicle that should be easy to spot. In the meantime, they surveil a disabled vehicle with a suspicious driver, respond to a loud music call at a residence that's been transformed into a hippie party house by its recently widowed owner, and break up a fist fight at a lunch stand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031110000 +0000" stop="20251031120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Scientist</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031120000 +0000" stop="20251031123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cleaning Up Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins to outgrow his "sloppy" phase and becomes much neater. This is noticed by Ward and June who try to encourage Beaver to undergo the same transformation. However, Beaver changing like that just seems too extraordinary of a task.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031123000 +0000" stop="20251031130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward becomes a bit jealous when Wally and Beaver begin spending time playing basketball at Willie Dennison's house after Willie's dad put up a backboard and a basket. This prompts Ward to do the same thing but it just seems like things are working against him in his quest to be the perfect father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031130000 +0000" stop="20251031140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spanish Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Jimmy Morrow can't seem to catch a break. Already on probation for car theft, he's charged with stealing a valuable Spanish cross and killing its owner. Mason feels sorry for the kid and decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031140000 +0000" stop="20251031150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Game Show  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the producer of a popular gameshow is murdered, Matlock is hired to defend the show's aging host while Michelle goes undercover as a contestant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031150000 +0000" stop="20251031160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Quick Fix</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The investigation into the death of an abandoned infant leads to a mentally handicapped teenager.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031160000 +0000" stop="20251031170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Changeling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth is turning 13 years old - not quite a child, not quite a woman</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031170000 +0000" stop="20251031180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Legends Don't Sleep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting out of prison, an infamous gunman meets a cocky young man eager to cash in on his reputation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031180000 +0000" stop="20251031190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Sadness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely old man wants to adopt a pair of orphans, but he will need to get past bureaucratic red tape first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031190000 +0000" stop="20251031193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prodigal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep his invalid mother happy, an outlaw forces Lucas and Mark to go along with a masquerade that he is the owner of Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031193000 +0000" stop="20251031200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Fourflusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A sharecropper enters his colt in a horse race, hoping to win enough money to buy his farm from the owner, who has bet on Mark McCain's entry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031200000 +0000" stop="20251031210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jud Steele Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bill Hawks returns the horse and belongings of a horse thief he shot to the local town sheriff. These identify the thief as a long dead war hero with a monument in the middle of town who was declared dead after a payroll robbery."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031210000 +0000" stop="20251031220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Hang-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A jewel thief is trapped in an air-conditioning duct. Two battered men continue their brawl in the hospital. A man ruins his cast by going surfing. Dr. Brackett treats a woman with a neurological disorder. Radioactivity impedes the rescue of a lab worker. Johnny misses the end of an 'Adam-12' episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031220000 +0000" stop="20251031223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Burns tries to slap a dishonorable discharge on a decorated soldier who admits to being a homosexual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031223000 +0000" stop="20251031230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a new batch of mail leaves Trapper depressed, and thinking of desertion, despite Hawkeye's efforts to dissuade him. Meanwhile, Hawkeye learns that he has successfully tricked Frank into buying stocks in a fictitious company, Pioneer Aviation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031230000 +0000" stop="20251031233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Smattering Of Intelligence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A classic episode in which Colonel Flagg and another secret agent from another intelligence agency come to the 4077th to keep their eyes on the camp. Hawkeye and Trapper trick them both into thinking that Burns is a traitor—one thinks he's a fascist, the other thinks he's a communist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251031233000 +0000" stop="20251101000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General Flipped At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The MASH 4077th is visted by General Steele. He wishes to move the camp five miles down the road. Hawkeye and Henry are charged with mutiny. And Hawkeye also is charged with impersonating a reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101000000 +0000" stop="20251101003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A by-the-book courthouse inspector condemns Andy and Barney's lack of proper procedure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101003000 +0000" stop="20251101010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Saves A Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie encourages and helps a female farmhand to express her femininity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101010000 +0000" stop="20251101013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Halloween Candy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray decides to make the drastic move of "cutting the wires."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101013000 +0000" stop="20251101020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>All I Want For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>All Ray wants for Christmas is a little loving from his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101020000 +0000" stop="20251101023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lebeau And The Little Old Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau tells the others he is taking messages to a little old lady, when really she is a beautiful lady he has fallen for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101023000 +0000" stop="20251101030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Escape From Prison Camp Without Really Trying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hides 30 prisoners in order to keep the SS busy while the Allies build reinforcements.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101030000 +0000" stop="20251101033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Dionne Warwick And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Dionne Warwick and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 12/15/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101033000 +0000" stop="20251101043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dodging Domino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Phil Schuyler is a two-bit songwriter who comes to a bad end on Halloween night. Someone enters his bungalow while Phil is taking a bath and tosses an electric heater into his tub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101043500 +0000" stop="20251101050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Eye Of The Beholder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A bandaged young woman awaits the outcome of an experimental treatment that has been administered to her in a last-ditch effort to make her appear normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101050500 +0000" stop="20251101053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One More Mile To Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>With the dead body of his wife in the trunk of his car, a man is hassled by police for a burnt-out taillight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101053500 +0000" stop="20251101060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Creeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A serial killer known as “the strangler” terrorizes a New York neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101060500 +0000" stop="20251101070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Trap For A Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to find a stolen briefcase containing bribery money in a mob murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101070500 +0000" stop="20251101080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired to investigate when an Army researcher seems to have gone insane for no obvious reason. Another cry for help comes out of Cannon's past. A girl he once knew is concerned about her husband's -he's a research scientist- fits of irrational behavior. they touch on mind-boggling drugs here, a topical subject."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101080500 +0000" stop="20251101090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A blind girl is Barnaby's only lead in his search for a missing coed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251101090000 +0000" stop="20251101093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>There's No Business With Show Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Circus owner Harry Harmon concocts a plan for he and his staff to stay at the Shady Rest without paying.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
