<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802090000 +0000" stop="20250802093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Sneaky Ways Of A Woman Who Is Both Beautiful And Smart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Janet Craig, rebuffed as a physician by the local males, sets out to win them over as a woman—and a good cook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802093000 +0000" stop="20250802100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Strange Case Of Joseph P. Carson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to get rid of lady Dr. Craig, Uncle Joe fakes an illness that becomes real.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802100000 +0000" stop="20250802103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Private Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro continues his fantasy of being a double naught spy by getting an office at the bank. When two bank robbers arrive, who are interested in that office because it is above the vault, they make Jethro believe they are from London headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802103000 +0000" stop="20250802110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Shorty, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Jethro stay out all night, not to Granny's approval, Shorty is forced to chop wood in the early morning and do other chores the rest of the day so he will want to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802110000 +0000" stop="20250802113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthdaze, Penny Antics, The Marry-go-round</sub-title>
    <desc>"In order to prevent fellow sailor Shorty's suicide attempts, Popeye invites him to a birthday party at Olive's home, but Shorty's clumsiness causes lots of mishaps., Popeye and Bluto run competing penny arcades., Popeye wants to propose to Olive, but can't work up the nerve. His fellow sailor, Shorty, helps him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802113000 +0000" stop="20250802120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Orphan, Bah Wilderness, Vanishing Duck</sub-title>
    <desc>"An orphan mouse joins Tom and Jerry for Thanksgiving Dinner., Barney Bear decides to spend a quiet night in the wild during a camping trip but, unfortunately for him, there are plenty of nocturnal animals that do their best to deny him any sleep. , Jerry and his singing duck friend discover the delights of vanishing cream while Tom suffers because of it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802120000 +0000" stop="20250802130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banquet Busters, Chilly And The Woodchopper, Coming Out Party, Wild And Woody, Corny Concerto, Moochin Pooch, The Loan Stranger</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody and Andy are true starving musicians who agree to a gig in a fancy mansion in the hopes of nabbing some food., Chilly stows away in a woodchopper's bag. When Chilly arrives at Smedley's Rest Home, Smedley attempts to get rid of the stowaway., Inspector Willoughby repeatedly foils Crash's attempts to escape Sing Song prison., Sheriff Woody attempts to capture bandit Buzz Buzzard and blows him up and sends him to hell in the process., Doc and Champ inadvertently develop a famous "act" in which Doc hits Champ's foot with a mallet., Charlie offers to babysit his boss' dog while he's out of town., A wolf in loan officer's clothing pursues Woody after he forgets to repay a loan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802130000 +0000" stop="20250802140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Oily Hare, Baby Bottleneck, Wabbit Twouble, From A To Z-z-z-z, Horton Hatches The Egg, Show Biz Bugs</sub-title>
    <desc>"A Texas oilman and his assistant, Maverick, try everything to get Bugs to move his hole from their oil fields. , A post-war baby-boom era overworks the stork, and faulty deliveries are made. Daffy Duck and Porky Pig are then hired as assistants but this leads to more problems than good. , While camping, Elmer Fudd runs into the menacing Bugs Bunny. , Another episode with Ralph Phillips and all his daydreaming fantasies. He fights math problems on the chalkboard, becomes part of the pony express escaping Indians and flies like a bird., A cartoon based on Dr. Seuss, about Horton, the elephant who promised he'd babysit a bird's eggs. , Daffy is jealous that Bugs' show is more popular than his own. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802140000 +0000" stop="20250802150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Big Blackmail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While President Grant attends an event at the German Consulate, Baron Hinterstoisser invites him to a special reception, explaining he has something interesting for the president to see. Suspicious, agent James West retrieves the mysterious box the Baron refers to and finds a kinetoscope of a fake depiction of President Grant signing a secret agreement with the unscrupulous government of another nation. If the film is shown for the heads of other countries, Grant will suffer terrible indignation and upset international relations. If the film is not replaced, however, the Baron will accuse the U.S. of stealing on consulate soil, a far greater crime. Agent Artemus Gordon decides that the only alternative is to make a duplicate kinetoscope - with some changes - and return it to the consulate before it is discovered missing. West and Gordon finish just as the president arrives. The Baron announces that he has proof of President Grant's connection with the corrupt foreigh officials. But as the film is shown before an attentive crowd, it's not quite what Hinterstoisser expects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802150000 +0000" stop="20250802160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Jarvis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy hurt in a crippling accident and his domineering mother meet a runaway boy, who she feels is making her son do things outside his capabilities. Another accident reveals something unexpected because it may pit two friends against each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802160000 +0000" stop="20250802170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Hide The Children</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When he accuses some gypsy workers of stealing his brandy and injures one of them in a fight, Nick is volunteered by his brothers to escort the other gypsies and their dowry wagon to a wedding. On the way there, he becomes smitten with the bride-to-be and learns some lessons about intolerance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802170000 +0000" stop="20250802180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Dan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc tries to keep an alcoholic off the bottle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802180000 +0000" stop="20250802190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Trouble With Amy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben comes to the aid of Amy Wilder, an eccentric animal lover whose mental competency is questioned when a neighbor declares an interest in her land for mining.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802190000 +0000" stop="20250802193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Schoolmaster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and his friend become trapped in an old mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802193000 +0000" stop="20250802200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Promoter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark attempt to reform a con man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802200000 +0000" stop="20250802210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>The Race</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The race is on when a disgruntled Rowdy signs as trail boss for another drive and pulls all the stops to beat Favor's herd to market.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802210000 +0000" stop="20250802213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher blames Paladin when a practical joke goes awry and his wife is crippled in a riding accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802213000 +0000" stop="20250802220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Against better judgment, Josh serves as guide for a dandified East Coast gun salesman who comes west to retrieve and replace a defective gun he sold to notorious outlaw Curly Bill Brocius.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250802220000 +0000" stop="20250803000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Mutts To You, Wee Wee Monsieur, I Can Hardly Wait, Wham Bam Slam, Merry Mix Up, Out West</sub-title>
    <desc>"When the stooges find a baby they take it back to their dog laundry business, but wind up in the dog house when they are accused of kidnapping the baby. , Paris is for loveres, and for the Three Stooges, as struggling artists who paint themselves into a cornerwhenthey try to rescue a military captain from kidnappers. , The wild west will never be the same again! The Stooges turn a frontier upside down in this wild, wild comedy gem! , The Stooges are defense workers who have trouble getting to sleep when Curly gets a toothache.  Moe and Larry try various ways to remove the offending tooth, but nothing works so they take Curly to the dentist.  While Moe gets in the chair to show Curly how easy it's going to be, the dentist enters and pulls Moe's tooth by mistake.  Curly then wakes up and realizes its all been a dream and a punch to the mouth from Moe dislodges the tooth. , Shemp is a sick man with a bad case of nerves.  The stooge's friend Claude, a self-taught healer, tries to cure Shemp with various home- made remedies.  When nothing seems to work, Claude suggests they buy his old lemon of a car so they can take Shemp on a trip to the country.  The car won't start, and the trip never gets off the ground, but not to worry, Shemp is cured by all the excitement. , The Stooges appear in triplicate as three sets of triplets who were separated a long time ago.  Their reunion causes confusion and troubles for various wives and sweethearts, but it all works out in the end. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803000000 +0000" stop="20250803023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Scorpion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Volcanic activity frees giant scorpions from the earth who wreak havoc in the rural countryside and eventually threaten Mexico City."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803023000 +0000" stop="20250803030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Purr-fect Crime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After Catwoman steals one of two priceless golden cat statuettes, Batman and Robin race to protect the other. However, Catwoman captures Boy Wonder and sics a tiger on Batman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803030000 +0000" stop="20250803040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>What Are Little Girls Made Of?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Christine Chapel is reunited with her old fiancé on Exo III, but the scientist has plans for Captain Kirk and the Federation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803040000 +0000" stop="20250803043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois writes an article about the discovery of an ancient necklace that is said to protect its wearer from harm. A gangster reads the article and kidnaps Lois.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803043000 +0000" stop="20250803050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Bully Of Dry Gulch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois and Jimmy visit a rodeo. Jimmy gets on the bad side of a gunfighter who warns him to leave town by sundown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803050000 +0000" stop="20250803060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Invaders From The Fifth Dimension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Luminous aliens capture Dr. Smith with the plan to replace their burnt out computer with his brain. Smith bargains with them, and they attempt to use Will's brain instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803060000 +0000" stop="20250803070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Men's Doubloons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The flying sub is attacked by a ghostly, underwater pirate ship—which fires a live bombardment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803070000 +0000" stop="20250803080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Mechanical Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways agree to help a professor fix his robot creation in exchange for help returning to Earth. But the professor proves to be less than trustworthy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803080000 +0000" stop="20250803090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1861, Tony and Doug are involved in a plot to assassinate President-elect Abraham Lincoln.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803090000 +0000" stop="20250803100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Spores</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Aliens plot to make a new resilient race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803100000 +0000" stop="20250803110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Howdy-do, I'm Mad Jack</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mad-Jack disappears down a river on a raft. Adams later finds some of his belongings. Thinking he may have perished,it causes him to reflect back on the time he first met the mountain man. Will James Capen Adams bid farewell to his friend?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803110000 +0000" stop="20250803113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Motion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Oddities of animal motion include mammals that fly, birds that climb with their shoulders, lizards that dive and snakes that travel sideways."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803113000 +0000" stop="20250803120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Sahara South</sub-title>
    <desc>"A horseback safari into the wilds of Rhodesia where Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore the vast grasslands, rivers and forests and observe an amazing variety of rare animals.  In this episode, the forming waters swirl around tons of struggling hippo in a dangerous project to tranquilize and capture one of the largest members of the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803120000 +0000" stop="20250803123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Against The Clock</sub-title>
    <desc>"Man loves speed and this episode answers some of the most pertinent inquiries as to what animals hold the records."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803123000 +0000" stop="20250803130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Monarchs Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the wild kingdom each animal owns a territory…and one animal rules every habitat.  A visit to each domain reveals why each is called a Monarch of the Wild."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803130000 +0000" stop="20250803133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tusker Territory</sub-title>
    <desc>"Of all the behemoths that once roamed the earth, only the elephant is left for us to marvel about.  And marvel we should for here’s an animal that weights 10 tons, yet leaves an imprint only a half-inch deep when walking on soft sand…can eat 200 pounds of hay a day, drink 50 gallons of water at one go, grow to be 13 feet tall at the shoulder, yet can use its trunk so delicately it can pick a flower off the ground without crushing it.  But many questions about this animal remain unanswered.  By literally living with a family of elephants in Bechuanaland, Africa, we observe their fascinating life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803133000 +0000" stop="20250803140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>To Rope A Grizzly</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan are invited to help capture one of the most feared animals on four legs, a livestock marauding grizzly.  They plan to use the only capture method suited to the animal and the country – roping the fierce and powerful bear."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803140000 +0000" stop="20250803143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Kitty Karry-all Is Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Cindy's doll, Kitty Karry-All, turns up missing, she accuses Bobby. This leads to a mock trial with Alice as judge to determine Bobby's guilt or innocence. Later, Bobby's kazoo turns up missing and he blames Cindy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803143000 +0000" stop="20250803150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby bets Greg that he can't do twice as many chin-ups as him. Greg is a tad too confident and sees no need to train, a decision that comes back to bite him. Meanwhile, Mike prepares for his high school reunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803150000 +0000" stop="20250803153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Cruisin'</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie, Postie and Ralph are forced to go cruising for girls in Howard's DeSoto after Marion dents Richie's car at the supermarket. They find three girls but, later, find their boyfriends—who are members of street gang the Dragons!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803153000 +0000" stop="20250803160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Angels Of Mercy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley become hospital volunteers, or "candy stripers," and have a hard time as newbie nurses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803160000 +0000" stop="20250803163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry guitarist Jim Lindsey (James Best), a success as a solo artist, returns to a hero's welcome. However, Andy suspects trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803163000 +0000" stop="20250803170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ricky Asks For A Raise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ricky asks for a raise, but his boss (Gale Gordon) turns him down, prompting Lucy to prove just how popular a performer he is. Her scheme involves making a lot of bogus reservations at the club on the night that somebody else is playing, then show up in various guises (including Fred in drag) feigning indignation that Ricky's not performing and leave in a huff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803170000 +0000" stop="20250803173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Alma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After drawing Alma's name for a school picnic, Wally finds himself meeting her parents and her mother takes an immediate liking to Wally, setting him and Alma up on numerous dates, but then turns around and accuses Wally of monopolizing Alma's time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803173000 +0000" stop="20250803180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver asks his parents if he could ride his new bike to school instead of the bus, and after some hesitating they finally agree to it. However, on the first day, a naive Beaver gets his bike stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803180000 +0000" stop="20250803183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny tries to conjure a man for Elly May, but accidentally attracts Miss Jane's man, who is actually a hired escort Mr. Drysdale got for Elly. When the Clampetts find out, they work to get rid of him so Miss Jane can have her man back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803183000 +0000" stop="20250803190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Our Hero, The Banker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lance Bradford has started working as vice president at the Commerce Bank, though he really isn’t doing anything helpful. Everyone at the bank, except Drysdale, is excited to get Jet Stream working at the bank. Jethro sees how the girls at the bank react to Lance’s Air Force uniform, so he goes out to get a four-star general uniform. When Lance visits, needing a new account, Jethro tells him he’ll put his whole allowance in the bank if he sets him up with the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803190000 +0000" stop="20250803193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Castaways Pictures Presents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways make a silent movie in the hopes that it will lead to their rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803193000 +0000" stop="20250803200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Agonized Labor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan and the Skipper hear a radio broadcast telling of the collapse of the Howell financial empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803200000 +0000" stop="20250803203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama In One  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama finally gets the house to herself when everyone goes away for the weekend. But the peace and quiet is far from the paradise she expects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803203000 +0000" stop="20250803210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>There's No Place Like… No Place  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama accidentally leaves home without her identification, ending up arrested during a rally by the homeless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803210000 +0000" stop="20250803220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Farnsworth's Fling / Three In A Bed / I Remember Helen / Merrill, Melanie &amp; Melanesia / Gopher Farnsworth Smith (part 2)  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The crew is in Australia to work on one of the cruise lines ships based there. And a wealthy man named Fransworth has decided to invite his whole family for a reunion. But in actuality he wants to see who among them he should keep in his will.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803220000 +0000" stop="20250803223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bringing Up Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, believing that the jailhouse environment is adversely affecting Opie, forbids the lad to spend time at work with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803223000 +0000" stop="20250803230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Neil La Sala- G.i. Joe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Former Marine Corps Reservist Neil LaSala may have retired from duty, but his devotion to the armed forces continues in his expansive collection of the original, 12-inch G.I. Joe action figure. Neil’s home is a virtual museum of the iconic toy’s early years and rare interim incarnations, and he shares with Lisa some of his most desirable items, including an African American soldier, Joe as a State Trooper complete with motorcycle and accessories, and a complete (and pristine!) run of the super-rare Photobox series. Joining Lisa is Collector’s Call favorite Joel Magee a.k.a “America’s Toy Scout.” Joel appraises Neil’s meticulously curated collection, then offers him a trade for something he ends up already owning, but with an unexpected, Joel Magee twist. And when Lisa learns it's also Neil's birthday, she rises to the occasion with a final, G.I. Joe-themed surprise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803230000 +0000" stop="20250803233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250803233000 +0000" stop="20250804000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804000000 +0000" stop="20250804003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At The Pta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith develops laryngitis on the eve of her singing debut at Stephanie's PTA recital, Archie steps in to understudy the duet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804003000 +0000" stop="20250804010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Girl Like Edith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith invites butcher Klemmer and his new sweetheart, a Russian who is the spitting image of Edith, she notices that Klemmer might have the hots for Edith and not for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804010000 +0000" stop="20250804013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Appendectomy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith and Archie rush Stephanie to the hospital for an emergency appendectomy on the eve of her 10th birthday. Luckily, the surgery goes perfectly, so they celebrate both Stephanie's birthday and the success of her operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804013000 +0000" stop="20250804020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Stephanie &amp; The Crime Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie and Edith are shocked when they discover that Stephanie has been stealing some of her favorite teacher's (and the Bunkers') belongings. But Stephanie admits that she stole these things so that when she returns to her dad's, she'll have something to remember them by.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804020000 +0000" stop="20250804023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bernadette Peters And Donald O'connor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bernadette Peters and Donald O'Connor. Originally aired on 10/26/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804023000 +0000" stop="20250804030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nancy Wilson And Nanette Fabray</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nancy Wilson and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 01/12/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804030000 +0000" stop="20250804033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Remember The Alimony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura recall a rough trip to Mexico where a divorce is only $10.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804033000 +0000" stop="20250804040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sally Rogers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A gag on live TV leaves Sally with many suitors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804040000 +0000" stop="20250804043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Dog's Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph feeds his boss dog food, thinking that it is an appetizer that Alice made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804043000 +0000" stop="20250804053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Parallel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An astronaut arrives back on Earth, noticing several differences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804053000 +0000" stop="20250804060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Canary Sedan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hears voices in her car when she arrives in Hong Kong to join her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804060000 +0000" stop="20250804070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Takeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Phelps must stop Charles Peck from using violence, created by professional provocateur Billy Walsh, to elevate his puppet, Mayor Steven Tallman, to the governorship. Dana is a provocateur herself, arrested by Barney, the current governor's representative.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804070000 +0000" stop="20250804080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Moon Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble arrives in a small town where women are being murdered by an unknown serial killer and a vigilante mob mistakes Kimble (a stranger in town) of being the killer. Kimble hides out with a mentally retarded young woman named Joanne Mercer, a 'moon chil</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804080000 +0000" stop="20250804090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Apb Harry Orwell</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell is framed for murder and must break out of jail to prove his innocence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804090000 +0000" stop="20250804093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804093000 +0000" stop="20250804100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804100000 +0000" stop="20250804103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a new dispatcher on today's day watch, and while Reed can't stand her voice, Malloy sees the situation much differently. On patrol, they search for a hit and run driver who left a small girl in serious condition, investigate a break-in at a synagogue, deal with a drunk woman who is searching for her daughter and become part of a SWAT team attempting to neutralize a sniper terrorizing the movie studio from which he was just fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804103000 +0000" stop="20250804110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Northeast Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has full faith that an Explorer Scout volunteering at the station can repair his television set in time to watch 'King Kong,' but Malloy thinks he's crazy for letting a teenager work on expensive electronics. On today's patrol, they engage in a high-speed chase with a teenager on a modified dirt bike, investigate a report of a woman who may have buried her husband in their backyard, search for a female bank robber, deal with a group of women illegally protesting outside a supermarket and respond to a call of a robbery in progress at a coffee shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804110000 +0000" stop="20250804120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Summer Fit</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony get their summer bods ready with the help of a few guests."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804120000 +0000" stop="20250804123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Orchid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks out a rich girl who drops hints that she would like an orchid for her corsage. Wally quickly discovers that getting one is going to be more difficult then he originally thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804123000 +0000" stop="20250804130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward's cherished autographed baseball becomes the object that Larry and Beaver just can't keep their hands off of. They decide to play catch with it and it ends up getting run over by a truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804130000 +0000" stop="20250804140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nervous Accomplice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sybil Granger hires Mason to help her buy stock in her estranged husband's oil company on the sly. By this, Sybil hopes to force her husband's latest girlfriend, Roxy Howard, out of the company and his life altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804140000 +0000" stop="20250804150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Dare  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An eccentric millionaire tells Matlock that he wouldn't be able to solve the perfect murder if it were handed to him on a silver platter. To prove his point, he kills Matlock's friend and successfully frames another man for the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804150000 +0000" stop="20250804160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Ches And The Grand Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lonnie must protect his Aunt Cordelia when her cherished friendship with Ches Collins angers one of his cousins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804160000 +0000" stop="20250804170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Go-getter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Ben again come to blows about work at the mill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804170000 +0000" stop="20250804180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Catawomper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman tries to make her boyfriend jealous when she's had enough of his attitude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804180000 +0000" stop="20250804190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady And The Mark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It seems as though everyone wants a piece of a ranch hand who makes a gold strike—including a beautiful woman who may have ulterior motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804190000 +0000" stop="20250804193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Illustrator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas encourages a drunken artist charged with murder to use his talents to identify the true killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804193000 +0000" stop="20250804200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Knife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark try to persuade a persecuted young mute to return stolen money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804200000 +0000" stop="20250804210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dr. Swift Cloud Story</sub-title>
    <desc>"The wagon train runs into their old pal Swift Cloud who's on his way back to his Native American village after studying medicine in China. However, the aspiring physician faces resentment from both whites and his own people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804210000 +0000" stop="20250804220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The station becomes aware of the Battalion Chief's impending inspection. A wife is convinced that her husband's heart transplant means he no longer loves her. Paramedics aid a parachutist snagged on a radio tower. Dr. Brackett treats a veterinarian. An accident victim goes into shock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804220000 +0000" stop="20250804223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804223000 +0000" stop="20250804230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804230000 +0000" stop="20250804233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250804233000 +0000" stop="20250805000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805000000 +0000" stop="20250805003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Bully</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolboy bully makes life miserable for seven-year-old Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805003000 +0000" stop="20250805010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Replacement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy is grooming a new man to replace him as deputy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805010000 +0000" stop="20250805013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny's Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny wants to plough the front lawn of the mansion to grow vegetables.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805013000 +0000" stop="20250805020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Here Comes The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's advice to a lodge brother on how to be head of the household has his wife (Alice's sister) in tears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805020000 +0000" stop="20250805023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must prevent the Germans from getting ahold of a secret device that was aboard a plane shot down near camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805023000 +0000" stop="20250805030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Defector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a defecting field marshal to England, whom Hochstetter has followed to Stalag 13.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805030000 +0000" stop="20250805033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Dingle, The Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Martians give Luther Dingle the strength of 300 men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805033000 +0000" stop="20250805043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Witless Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge is accused of murdering a government witness who planned to expose him as a crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805043500 +0000" stop="20250805050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805050500 +0000" stop="20250805053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Impromptu Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer decides to murder one of his clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805053500 +0000" stop="20250805060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Little White Frock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E39</episode-num>
    <desc>A producer is surprised when an actor announces his retirement plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805060500 +0000" stop="20250805070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Run Till Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Little League coach goes missing, Mannix investigates and soon discovers that the man went into hiding after a mobster made an attempt on his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805070500 +0000" stop="20250805080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Lady's Tears</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a plane carrying three million in negotiable securities vanishes, the insurance carrier hires Cannon to find out what happened to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805080500 +0000" stop="20250805090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Judgment (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby comes to suspect that the wrong man was convicted in an 11-year-old kidnapping case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805090000 +0000" stop="20250805093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805093000 +0000" stop="20250805100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805100000 +0000" stop="20250805103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>If The Shoe Fits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While Reed is having his shoes fixed at the repair shop, the squeakiness of his replacement shoes is driving Malloy crazy. On patrol, they deal with a deranged homeowner destroying his own possessions, stop a cargo van whose driver misunderstands the meaning of double jeopardy, search for a young boy hiding in an industrial building about to be demolished and create a hostage situation after shooting a bank robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805103000 +0000" stop="20250805110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Southwest Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a baseless complaint against an elderly artist, Malloy decides to buy a random painting out of pity and makes Reed envious. Meanwhile, they question a man attempting to break into a gumball machine while his son looks on, get a big surprise after tracking down a suspected peeping tom, deal with a man who comes up with a creative way to avoid having his furniture repossessed and engage in a game of cat-and-mouse inside the Los Angeles Coliseum with a former football player turned suspected robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805110000 +0000" stop="20250805120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' Big Sky Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony trek Montana!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805120000 +0000" stop="20250805123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Monkey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a pet and Ward and June object to his latest one, a mouse. They tell him they can have a sensible pet, so when Beaver and Larry see an ad at the market giving away a free monkey, Beaver jumps at the chance and Ward and June find their house the new home for Stanley, the Monkey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805123000 +0000" stop="20250805130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Finds A Wallet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry find a wallet that contains $89 while on their way to the grocery store to pick up some groceries for June. Surprisingly, Beaver and Larry decide to turn it in at the police station and Beaver finds himself waiting an agonizing week to see if he can keep the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805130000 +0000" stop="20250805140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drowning Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Donald Briggs is an unscrupulous private investigator hired by Clyde Waters to uncover information about Marv Adams, his daughter's fiance. Briggs learns that Marv Adams' father was Ben Devereaux, who was convicted of murder 18 years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805140000 +0000" stop="20250805150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Other Woman  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend psychiatrist Lucas Forbes when he's arrested for killing the husband of one of his patients with whom he was reportedly having an affair. Matlock soon realizes that the patient in question has a host of deep-rooted psychiatric problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805150000 +0000" stop="20250805160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Conspiracy Of One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil accepts a position at a prominent law firm. But as a former police officer he feels conflicting emotions when he realizes that one of their clients is guilty of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805160000 +0000" stop="20250805170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Achievement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy sent his novel to a publisher and does not hear anything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805170000 +0000" stop="20250805180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Half Straight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt is stalked by a hired killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805180000 +0000" stop="20250805190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Is There Any Man Here...?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman walks out of her wedding with the intention of marrying another man—Ben Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805190000 +0000" stop="20250805193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bertie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A lively old lady arrives in town hot on the trail of a notorious bandit—and the reward money for capturing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805193000 +0000" stop="20250805200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Six Years And A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor seeks revenge on the man he blames for ruining his practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805200000 +0000" stop="20250805210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Luke Grant Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Luke Grant is found wandering the desert with one wish on his mind—kill me! Turned over to the wagon train by some friendly Chiracawa indians, they slowly discover his identity and learn there are Apaches on the warpath and nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805210000 +0000" stop="20250805220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Indirect Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A hard-nosed female trainee is assigned to Roy and John. Freeway construction threatens an old couple's house. A man tries to commit suicide by gas, but then changes his mind. A man suffers a heart attack and the paramedics are unable to revive him. Roy is electrocuted trying to save an invalid at a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805220000 +0000" stop="20250805223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805223000 +0000" stop="20250805230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805230000 +0000" stop="20250805233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250805233000 +0000" stop="20250806000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Showtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kaplan is to be shipped home, but becomes paranoid that something will happen to him before he leaves. He takes the wheel of the jeep to drive to Kimpo himself, but crashes and ends up in plaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806000000 +0000" stop="20250806003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Woman Speeder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A stubborn but charming lady speeder makes life difficult for Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806003000 +0000" stop="20250806010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Bankrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Myers is about to get evicted by the city council when he discovers an old bond that the city of Mayberry issued 100 years ago. Mayberry now owes him $350,000 and can't pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806010000 +0000" stop="20250806013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampett Look</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are getting ready for Mrs. Fenwick and Cynthia to come to share a meal with them, hoping to give them a better life than what the Clampetts believe they are leading. Jed and Jethro head to visit the Fenwick house, still thinking the gardener’s place is their house, and after seeing the little building decide to get the Fenwicks to move into the Clampett mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806013000 +0000" stop="20250806020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806020000 +0000" stop="20250806023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Parachute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets the Germans to look for an allied agent by planting an opened parachute in camp. This gives him the opportunity to get at the briefcase that was handcuffed to a courier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806023000 +0000" stop="20250806030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Antique</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to open an antiques business selling "rare" cuckoo clocks, a business venture that is actually a ruse enabling the POWs to smuggle information out in the timepieces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806030000 +0000" stop="20250806033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Mover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man discovers that his business partner has the ability to control objects with his mind, the pair head to Vegas to win big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806033000 +0000" stop="20250806043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nebulous Nephew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A scam to swindle elderly relatives and a pang of conscience leads to a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806043500 +0000" stop="20250806050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806050500 +0000" stop="20250806053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to cheat an insurance company out of a large amount of money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806053500 +0000" stop="20250806060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Interrupt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A little boy on a train tries desperately to tell someone a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806060500 +0000" stop="20250806070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Glass Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Police Detective Ross Santini begins acting suspiciously after taking custody of drug baron Brastow, starting Mannix on a case of kidnapping and blackmail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806070500 +0000" stop="20250806080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Limping Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer confined to a psychiatric hospital escapes. He's looking for his wife, whom he believes framed him for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806080500 +0000" stop="20250806090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Judgment (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby comes to suspect that the wrong man was convicted in an 11-year-old kidnapping case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806090000 +0000" stop="20250806093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806093000 +0000" stop="20250806100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806100000 +0000" stop="20250806103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Sweet Smell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy elderly woman spills a large bottle of perfume in Malloy and Reed's patrol car, resulting in a most unpleasant work day. Meanwhile, a reported burglar in a church office results in a comical case of mistaken identity, a well-meaning man is accused of kidnapping his granddaughter and a young boy asks for help locating his stolen bicycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806103000 +0000" stop="20250806110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Trouble In The Bank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a quiet patrol, Reed decides to spend part of his lunch break doing business at his bank while Malloy waits in the patrol car. Unfortunately, he walks into the clutches of a pair of ruthless robbers who take him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806110000 +0000" stop="20250806120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Detectives</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Diver Guy goes missing, Detectives Tank and Clicker are on the case!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806120000 +0000" stop="20250806123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's Day Composition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver must write a composition about his mother but soon finds himself the only one with a seemingly "boring" mother while Richard, Larry and Judy have colorful mothers. Beaver decides to make his mother colorful, too, even if it means making up things.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806123000 +0000" stop="20250806130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Violet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver finds himself in a most uncomfortable situation when Fred Rutherford practically plays matchmaker and pairs Beaver up with his daughter, Violet. Fred organizes a picnic and invites the Cleavers, which is where the situation culminates into Beaver getting kissed by Violet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806130000 +0000" stop="20250806140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sulky Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An impetuous niece who demands her trust fund be released comes to Mason for help. But it's her boyfriend who needs defending when he is charged with murdering her controlling uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806140000 +0000" stop="20250806150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Confession  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a former snitch calls Julie to the jailhouse and admits that she had lied about a murder suspect, Julie convinces Matlock to defend the man accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806150000 +0000" stop="20250806160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Rabbi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A Rabbi returns to Sparta after many years. Racists vandalize his synagogue and soon after their Torah is stolen. Forbes investigates but the Rabbi refuses to trust Bill because of his inaction while investigating a hate crime many years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806160000 +0000" stop="20250806170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A hawk is attacking the Waltons' chickens</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806170000 +0000" stop="20250806180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>He Learned About Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt goes after a band of comancheros that raided a camp and kidnapped a girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806180000 +0000" stop="20250806190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Law And Billy Burgess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The widow of a teacher demands immediate punishment of the student she blames for her husband's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806190000 +0000" stop="20250806193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Flowers By The Door</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas unmasks a killer posing as a door-to-door seed salesman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806193000 +0000" stop="20250806200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Trek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance run into trouble transporting a captured killer back to face trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806200000 +0000" stop="20250806210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charlene Brenton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby girl sure has a rough start when she arrives on the stage with her dead mother. Plague is what people think killed her and then Charlie Wooster steps in to try to help—and, well, you can imagine where it goes from there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806210000 +0000" stop="20250806220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure 165</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets ribbed about his cooking. The paramedics go to Catalina to help a diver, where John and a doctor treat the patient in a hyperbaric chamber. Roy and John help a famous chef with a kitchen fire. A youth suffers a serious gunshot wound. The firemen deal with a dust explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806220000 +0000" stop="20250806223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Divided We Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brought on by Frank and Margaret's negative reports, General Clayton assigns a psychiatrist, Captain Hildebrand, to examine the 4077th M*A*S*H unit to see if it should be disbanded. Henry tells them to be on their best behavior, or else they will be split up. But the 4077th soon begins to act in their traditional, insane way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806223000 +0000" stop="20250806230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806230000 +0000" stop="20250806233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250806233000 +0000" stop="20250807000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807000000 +0000" stop="20250807003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney On The Rebound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After a tiff with Thelma Lou, Barney is victimized by a scheming young couple.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807003000 +0000" stop="20250807010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Hobo Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A ne'er-do-well vagrant has a bad influence on Opie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807010000 +0000" stop="20250807013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Woodchucks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is desperate to meet a girl, planning to mail himself to Paris. However, Jed talks him out of it. When the Biddle Bird Watchers come to visit for a recruitment gathering, Granny suggests he tries to date one of those girls, but Jed knows that the female bird lovers aren’t exactly his type—attractive. But Jed sees one girl, Athena, that he knows Jethro will like. And sure enough, he does. Jethro spends the afternoon trying to impress Athena, but she isn’t interested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807013000 +0000" stop="20250807020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Please Leave The Premises</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and the Nortons fight a rent increase, though Ralph is the only one who really wants to fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807020000 +0000" stop="20250807023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807023000 +0000" stop="20250807030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Zolle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to detain a German general at camp for 24 hours to allow the Allies to amass troops. Things get complicated when a Gestapo officer comes in search of the reason for Klink's perfect record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807030000 +0000" stop="20250807033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Hundred Yards Over The Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1847 an American pioneer sets out to find medicine for his dying son—and stumbles into modern-day New Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807033000 +0000" stop="20250807043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Verdict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason loses a case when Janice Barton is convicted of murdering her aunt and subsequently sentenced to death. After the verdict, Mason continues investigating to find the real killer among the old lady's heirs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807043500 +0000" stop="20250807050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807050500 +0000" stop="20250807053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Crooked Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple passing through a small town falls victim to its crooked officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807053500 +0000" stop="20250807060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The $2,000,000 Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate man makes a deal with his defense lawyer in order to get acquitted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807060500 +0000" stop="20250807070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Choice Of Evils</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When his secretary, Peggy, is abducted, Mannix finds a note from her captors. He must track down an FBI undercover agent within 72 hours or she will die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807070500 +0000" stop="20250807080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Trial By Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The victim of a burglary hires Cannon. He's sure he knows who stole $50,000 from his wall safe and only needs Cannon to prove it. The problem is, the suspect was in jail at the time of the robbery!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807080500 +0000" stop="20250807090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Terror On A Quiet Afternoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The heir to a fortune makes trouble for the woman who jilted him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807090000 +0000" stop="20250807093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807093000 +0000" stop="20250807100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807100000 +0000" stop="20250807103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>North Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed volunteers to write a profile on Malloy for the LAPD's magazine to honor his 10th anniversary on the force, but soon discovers he may be in over his head. Out on patrol, an apparent gas station armed robbery gets turned on its head when they question the parties after a long chase, a man goes to extreme lengths to get his neighbor's poodle to stop barking, a woman's plan to get her husband arrested backfires and a liquor store robbery suspect barricades himself inside a house's garage after a high-speed chase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807103000 +0000" stop="20250807110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Taking It Easy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed gets stuck manning the front desk after spraining his wrist, where he must deal with a caller who claims to have planted a bomb at the station, a young man who wants to file a claim of police brutality and an elderly man who walks in with a shotgun. Meanwhile, Malloy is assigned a partner who is a first-day rookie, and they deal with three young children from Oklahoma who are abandoned by their mother, and engage in a high-speed pursuit that ends in a most unexpected way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807110000 +0000" stop="20250807120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Forgotten Inventions</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony discuss long-lost and forgotten inventions like Roman Concrete and the Antikythera mechanism."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807120000 +0000" stop="20250807123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Spot Removers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>For an upcoming dance, Wally is ready to wear a grey suit but when Beaver brings his new friend, Richard, over to the house, he accidentally spills oil on it, leaving a big stain. This leads Richard and Beaver to try to bleach the stain out with disastrous results. Beaver finds himself with another problem, when later Eddie discovers what Beaver is hiding from Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807123000 +0000" stop="20250807130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Model</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver sends his picture in to a modeling agency and they reply with a letter stating they will place his photo in a modeling directory. Soon after Beaver receives another letter this time asking for $30 and when Beaver ignores it, the company threatens legal action."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807130000 +0000" stop="20250807140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners, until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret, a young woman on the make, entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807140000 +0000" stop="20250807150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Psychic  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a psychic claiming to have had a premonition of a murder before it took place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807150000 +0000" stop="20250807160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hard Choices</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eugene tries to protect a friend who was an unwilling accomplice to a robbery and in doing so endangers his probation -- and his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807160000 +0000" stop="20250807170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Stray</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Waltons find a 12 year old runaway in their barn</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807170000 +0000" stop="20250807180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Reprisal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman plots her revenge on Matt for killing her husband in a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807180000 +0000" stop="20250807190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Long Way To Ogden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and a fellow cattleman set out to foil the scheme of a meat packer trying to make them sell their herds at rock bottom prices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807190000 +0000" stop="20250807193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Actress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A deathbed request from an old friend sends Lucas to a neighboring town in search of the man's long-lost sweetheart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807193000 +0000" stop="20250807200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas thinks he has seen a ghost when a young man, eerily similar to a man he killed in the Civil War, challenges him to a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807200000 +0000" stop="20250807210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sam Livingston Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Abigail has lost her driver to the better paying mines. Her new driver says he owns a bank and a pig. The ride west reveals another side of him, one that takes at least the pig to change both heart and mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807210000 +0000" stop="20250807220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>One Of Those Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly woman's stomach problems lead to a family brawl. Roy and John treat a drunk in a hotel with a broken elevator. Doctors treat a boy with meningitis. Paramedics respond to a two-car accident with no victims, treat a man who fell in the bathtub and rescue a child trapped in a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807220000 +0000" stop="20250807223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807223000 +0000" stop="20250807230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Kim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye operates on a five-year-old Korean boy, and Radar can't find his family. Henry plans to send him to the orphanage, and the camp enjoys his company while they can. Trapper decides to adopt him after consulting his wife, and has to rescue him after he wanders into the minefield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807230000 +0000" stop="20250807233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>L.i.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporal Walker is being sent home, and he wants to marry his Korean girl so she and their baby can return with him. CID sends Lt Willis to investigate, but when he refuses Hawkeye and Trapper frame him. Hawkeye is upset that a nurse he was pursuing does not approve of the marriage between "a gook" and "one of us."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250807233000 +0000" stop="20250808000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Of Henry Blake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Majors Houlihan and Burns press charges against Colonel Blake to get him arrested and put Frank in charge. They also put Hawkeye and Trapper under arrest so that they can't help Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808000000 +0000" stop="20250808003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Crime-free Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are honored for achieving the lowest crime-rate in the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808003000 +0000" stop="20250808010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy learns a great deal about Thelma Lou's cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808010000 +0000" stop="20250808013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Chickadee Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is still hoping to marry burlesque dancer Chickadee Laverne, and she is still hoping for a dance engagement from the Clampetts. Chickadee returns to the mansion, making Jethro very happy. However, her plan to show them her new act, Little Red Riding Hood, goes haywire thanks to a meddling raccoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808013000 +0000" stop="20250808020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Glove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is getting the apartment re-decorated for free but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808020000 +0000" stop="20250808023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes A Thief... Sometimes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of underground operatives that Hogan and his team begin working with is actually a group lead by a Gestapo captain who's set on capturing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808023000 +0000" stop="20250808030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808030000 +0000" stop="20250808033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Rip Van Winkle Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves put themselves into suspended animation for 100 years after hiding a million dollars worth of gold bars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808033000 +0000" stop="20250808043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shifty Shoebox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbery, embezzlement and a coverup at a trucking company end in the murder of one of the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808043500 +0000" stop="20250808050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808050500 +0000" stop="20250808053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Design For Loving</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plots to get away from his wife for a while without her knowing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808053500 +0000" stop="20250808060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man With A Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man stands on the ledge of a hotel while police try to talk to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808060500 +0000" stop="20250808070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Button For General D</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of Mannix's friends takes a hostage and is subsequently shot down, Mannix finds out that the man was involved in criminal activity that may also include a famous United States general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808070500 +0000" stop="20250808080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By The Numbers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After a model ends up dead, the man last seen with her hires Cannon. He insists the girl was alive when he left her, so Cannon starts to dig - and turns up quite a collection of motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808080500 +0000" stop="20250808090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Coronado Triangle, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The vanishing of boats and their crews may be caused by supernatural forces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808090000 +0000" stop="20250808093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808093000 +0000" stop="20250808100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808100000 +0000" stop="20250808103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Krash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's brand new car gets dinged up when he has to bail out to chase down a purse snatcher, but Sgt. MacDonald promises him his kid brother in Beverly Hills can fix it on the cheap. Out on patrol, he and Reed search for a drunk man accused of randomly shooting arrows, respond to a robbery at a deli that results in tragedy and search for a drug store robbery suspect who gets away after being shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808103000 +0000" stop="20250808110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Routine Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by responding to a call of a drunken woman threatening the patrons of a bar with a handgun. Afterwards, they search for a group of four carjackers who go on a robbery spree after targeting a man with a cache of guns in his trunk, and investigate the suspicious death of a mentally disabled man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808110000 +0000" stop="20250808120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toony Opens A Club</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony wants to run his own entertainment joint. But which kind? Bill takes some inspiration from famous hangouts of the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808120000 +0000" stop="20250808123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Businessman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally gets a job selling Igloo ice cream and quickly finds himself giving credit to everyone, including Eddie. However, as the day approaches that his money is to be collected, Wally scrambles to get those who owe him money, to pay up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808123000 +0000" stop="20250808130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Ivanhoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Assigned to read one more book before the end of the school year, Ward suggests Ivanhoe, and Beaver reads it and takes the ideas of knighthood and chivalry to heart. He begins defending girls and begins charging his friends to make them knights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808130000 +0000" stop="20250808140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Mourner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Carla Adrian is having trouble fending off amorous neighbor Mark Cushing. When another neighbor hears a shot and a woman's scream in Mark Cushing's cabin, it's not long before the police discover Cushing's dead body and arrest Mrs. Belle Adrian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808140000 +0000" stop="20250808150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thoroughbred  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the manager of a thoroughbred farm is murdered, her father begs Matlock to represent the mentally handicapped man accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808150000 +0000" stop="20250808160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Time's Long Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet tries to stop an arrogant developer from destroying an important archeological site.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808160000 +0000" stop="20250808170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Recluse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason helps a woman named Fern; she is withdrawn from the world because of a past relationship</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808170000 +0000" stop="20250808180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Coventry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man and his expectant wife are stranded on the prairie, their only hope—a man ostracized by the community—is unwilling to help them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808180000 +0000" stop="20250808190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Return Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Smitten with a beautiful actress, Hoss is the prime suspect when her jealous leading man is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808190000 +0000" stop="20250808193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas agrees to take a job as a federal undercover agent and goes to Wyoming to investigate rumors of sales of arms to renegade indians. His life is endangered by the town drunk, who stumbles onto his true identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808193000 +0000" stop="20250808200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wyoming Story: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark stays with Miss Milly, while Lucas is in Wyoming on the trail of a gang illegally selling weapons to the Indians. Mark suffers from loneliness and doubt while his father is away for two months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808200000 +0000" stop="20250808210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Shadrack Bennington Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Shadrack Bennington has been a cavalier of the open road, not wanting to be tied down until he joins the wagon train, heading for San Francisco and a future even he couldn't anticipate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808210000 +0000" stop="20250808220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Lighter-than-air Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>En route to a rescue, Roy and John supposedly sideswipe an elderly crossing guard. A couple on their way to a wedding hits a fire hydrant. A burning camper drives up to the station house. A truck carrying insecticide overturns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808220000 +0000" stop="20250808223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad... Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Once more Hawkeye writes home to his father: the doctors operate on a soldier with a grenade shot into his body; Hawkeye and Trapper color the skin of a racist patient, who demanded the right color blood, while he is asleep; Henry gets a movie of his daughter's birthday from home; the officers hold the monthly staff meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808223000 +0000" stop="20250808230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A lone sniper has the 4077th pinned down—including Radar and Henry in the shower. The poor boy thinks he's firing on McArthur's headquarters, and a chopper finally comes by and wounds him with gunfire from above, ending the siege. Hawkeye walks out to into the bush to tend to the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808230000 +0000" stop="20250808233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Carry On Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp succumbs to the Asian flu, except for Hawkeye and Margaret, who have to do everything themselves. As the others start to recover, Hawkeye falls ill but he still manages to operate when wounded arrive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250808233000 +0000" stop="20250809000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809000000 +0000" stop="20250809003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Brief Encounter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Aunt Bee falls for traveling handyman Henry Wheeler, Andy soon learns that Wheeler is not as nice as he appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809003000 +0000" stop="20250809010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Andy's big-city fishing buddies invites him to join the Esquire Club, an exclusive Raleigh men's organization. Barney also is asked to join but tries a little too hard to fit in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809010000 +0000" stop="20250809013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Present</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are preparing for Christmas, but are lacking in one thing: Christmas spirit. Jed thinks it is because they aren’t doing anything special for anyone this Christmas. He thinks they should do something special for Mrs. Drysdale, unaware she is still trying to get rid of them. They try to get jobs to raise money for her gift, so she doesn’t find out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809013000 +0000" stop="20250809020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to hit the high note on a civil service exam as well as his cornet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809020000 +0000" stop="20250809023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Fat Hermann, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get a trainload of stolen paintings back to London, but things get complicated when Marya uses Schultz to impersonate Reich Marshall Goehring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809023000 +0000" stop="20250809030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Softer They Fall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kinchloe fights a German boxing champ, creating a diversion for a heist Hogan is planning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809030000 +0000" stop="20250809033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A talkative man takes a $500,000 offer to keep silent for a year.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809033000 +0000" stop="20250809043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drowsy Mosquito</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason investigates when the sale of phony gold mines leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809043500 +0000" stop="20250809050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809050500 +0000" stop="20250809053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Safety For The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man witnesses a murder by two gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809053500 +0000" stop="20250809060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Me Twice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman commits murder while under hypnosis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809060500 +0000" stop="20250809070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to retrieve compromising negatives showing a retired U.S. general stolen by a spy ring. His mission is to buy the confidential documents—no matter the price.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809070500 +0000" stop="20250809080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of The Damned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a counterfeiting suspect escapes custody, rumors fly that Jim Farragut, the cop in charge of him, succumbed to either greed or cowardice. Jim's an old friend, so Cannon agrees to find a witness Jim claims can prove that he neither took a bribe nor experienced a failure of courage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809080500 +0000" stop="20250809090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Jeopardy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must find a key witness to a murder hiding in a remote area before hit men do.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250809090000 +0000" stop="20250809093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Curse Of Chester W. Farnsworth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe is convinced that the Shady Rest is haunted by a guest who visited 50 years ago, Chester W. Farnsworth.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
