<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122123000 +0000" stop="20251122130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tall In The Trap, The Mad Maestro, Kitty Foiled</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry is a cheese rustler in the old west and Tom gets deputized to bring him to justice., A maestro conducts an orchestra of various animals but some of them aren’t very good at following his directions., Tom catches Jerry but the house canary saves the mouse and then Tom chases both of them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122130000 +0000" stop="20251122140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tepee For Two, The Case Of The Elephant's Trunk, Swing Your Partner, Hassle In A Castle, Room And Wrath, Mousie Come Home, Slingshot Six-and-7/8ths</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody's neighbors evict him from the entire city, so Woody moves to the top of an indigineous man's teepee. He doesn't appreciate Woody's noise either., Inspector Willoughby tracks a rajah's kidnapped elephant., Homer drags his horse out of bed to drive his buggy to the barn dance. In anger, Hank breaks up the dance and forces Homer to pull the buggy home., A king looks for a goom for his daughter, who will be turned into an evil witch if not married by midnight. Woody is captured and presented as a potential suitor., Smedley tries to evict Chilly from his Snowtel when he can only pay the bill in fish., Andy Panda and Milo move to avoid a mouse., Tenderfoot Woody with a slingshot and indigienous tribesman Buzz with a bow and arrow face off in a target shooting contest for a $1,000 prize."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122140000 +0000" stop="20251122150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dumb Patrol, Street Cat Named Sylvester, A (1953), Cracked Quack, Little Red Riding Rabbit, Hairied And Hurried, Rabbit Stew And Rabbits Too (1969), Rabbit's Feat</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs Bunny and Porky Pig are World War I pilots that are trying to rid the skies of Yosemite Sam who is Baron Sam Von Schamm. , Tweety is freezing in the winter cold and seeks warmth in Granny's home where Sylvester and Hector are also. , Instead of flying south, Daffy chooses to stick around and breaks into Porky's house. He sees a stuffed duck over the fireplace, whom he throws out and replaces with himself. The house dog, Rover, gets wise to Daffy's presence, but Porky doesn't believe Rover. , Riding Hood takes Bugs over to Granny's house and finds a note to leave Bugs at the door, not knowing the Big Bad Wolf is inside. , Wile E. Coyote sends in a mail-order to ACME for a snow machine and then he sets up signs for "Chains Required" and then gives away chains at another stop. He intends to use a portable electro-magnet to catch the Road Runner but it fails. , A fox reads in a cookbook that the first thing he has to do before cooking is to catch a rabbit. , Wile E. Coyote decides to cook and eat Bugs, but Bugs is on to his plan. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122150000 +0000" stop="20251122160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Winged Terror (2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The plans of The Raven seem to be successful as they have hypnotized Jim West and had him assassinate the Mexican Ambassador. Unfortunately for the group, Frank Harper had been impersonating the ambassador to test whether Jim had been conditioned. West and Harper work together to infiltrate and undermine the group and capture everyone except for the huge-headed Tycho.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122160000 +0000" stop="20251122170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Orly French Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"A Bible-quoting marshal joins the wagon train with his prisoner, a young bank robber whom he claims to be trying to reform. He wants the prisoner to atone for his sins by telling the location of the money he hid from his last holdup."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122170000 +0000" stop="20251122180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Itinerant “preacher” Brother Love tries his charm on Audra; Heath sets out to prove the preacher is a con man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122180000 +0000" stop="20251122190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Kite</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt must stop a killer from realizing his victim's daughter was a witness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122190000 +0000" stop="20251122200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Sisters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam is seeing a young woman, Sue-Ellen Terry. He seems to be serious about her until after a sudden turn of events, he finds himself defending a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122200000 +0000" stop="20251122203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122203000 +0000" stop="20251122210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vaqueros</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While Lucas and Mark are traveling across the Mexican desert they encounter a trio of Mexican bandits. They demand payment from Lucas for crossing "their" desert. Lucas refuses. In retaliation, the three slam Lucas in the throat with his rifle, strip him of all his possessions (including Mark), tie him to a tree and leave him to die of thirst and exposure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122210000 +0000" stop="20251122220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Waiting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy had given testimony against his friend Capt. Ballinger, resulting in a death sentence. Now Ballinger has called on Rowdy to witness the possible execution unless a way can be found to escape that punishment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122220000 +0000" stop="20251122223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Dr. Thackeray</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dr. Phyllis Thackeray diagnoses the cook at the Barton Ranch with smallpox. All the cowhands may be infected and need to be vaccinated. Dr. Thackeray sends for the one man she thinks can help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122223000 +0000" stop="20251122230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Tolliver Bender</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>To net a $1,000 reward Josh saves Tolliver Bend from a hanging so he can testify in a nearby trial. Double-crosses are immediately hatched by those who want Bend dead and by those who want the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251122230000 +0000" stop="20251123010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Scotch, Back To The Woods, Yes We Have No Bonanza, Pardon My Clutch, Loose Loot, Whoops I'm An Indian</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are running the local drugstore and mix up a potion that a desperate businessman decides to sell as scotch.  , Set in colonial times, the Stooges are convicted criminals who are banished from England to the American colonies.  When they arrive, they find that the colonists are starving because the local Indians won't let them on their hunting grounds.  The Stooges go hunting any, and after a wild chase, are captured by the Indians.  They escape and another wild chase ensues. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are crooked gamblers gypping the resident of a frontier town. They are discovered and must escape into the woods. , Gold prospectors Larry, Moe and Curly. , The stooge's friend Claude sells them his old lemon of a car so they can take Shemp, who is sick with a toothache, camping.  The car won't work and the boys are apparently out a bundle, when a car collector happens on the scene and offers to buy it at a premium.  Claude backs out on the deal and gives the Stooges their money back, only to discover the "collector" is an escaped lunatic. , The Stooges are willed a lot of dough from a rich uncle, but the executor of the estate, Icabob Slipp, is a crook who absconds with the money.  The Stooges trail him to a theater where they engage in a wild chase and ultimately recover their inheritance.  [ the opening scenes are taken from "Hold that Lion".  ] "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123010000 +0000" stop="20251123033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Curse Of The Undead</sub-title>
    <desc>"B-grade western with a twist: mysterious gunslinger-for-hire Drake Robey is really a vampire, and it's up to Preacher Dan to save the town and girlfriend Dolores Carter.   "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123033000 +0000" stop="20251123040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Riddler's False Notion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddle continues his film debut, this time planning to capture the demise of Robin. When Batman comes to the rescue, the Riddler, disguised as a silent film villain, attacks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123040000 +0000" stop="20251123050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Squire Of Gothos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A being that controls matter and creates planets wants to play with the Enterprise crew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123050000 +0000" stop="20251123053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Tomb Of Zaharan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Near Eastern vistors mistake Lois for their lost queen. They induce her and Jimmy to come to Beldad, then seal the two inside the Tomb of Zaharan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123053000 +0000" stop="20251123060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Made Dreams Come True</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A mystertious villian called the Dreamer convinces a superstitious king to perform fatal acts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123060000 +0000" stop="20251123070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Space Croppers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of space hillbillies comes to Priplanis. The leader is an articulate female, whom Smith tries to court so he may have transportation back to Earth. Don falls for the sexy alien daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123070000 +0000" stop="20251123080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Plant Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview battles multiplying plant monsters and the pair of scientists who've created them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123080000 +0000" stop="20251123090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Pay The Piper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien Pied Piper, who claims to be the original from Earth, comes to the Land of the Giants and targets a politician's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123090000 +0000" stop="20251123100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Chase Through Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Planting a bomb in the time tunnel, a saboteur leads Tony and Doug on a chase through three epochs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123100000 +0000" stop="20251123110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is given an alien crystal, which is soon believed to be a miracle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123110000 +0000" stop="20251123120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Track Of The Cougar</sub-title>
    <desc>"Nakoma is seeking out a cougar who attacked his village and it's inhabitants. Adams realizes that it's Sekota, a cougar he raised from a cub. Adams then struggles with a loyalty to both his Indian and animal friend."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123120000 +0000" stop="20251123123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Killers Of The Rupununi</sub-title>
    <desc>"Deep in the interior of British Guiana roam the big cats of South America…the jaguar, cougar, margay, ocelot and the jaguarundi. Marlin and Jim journey by canoe and horseback to get a closer look at these killer cats in action."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123123000 +0000" stop="20251123130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Okavango</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Okavango, a vast area of swamp and sand is a haven for many animals of Africa.  Marlin and Jim explore this luxuriant oasis that’s alive with animal activity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123130000 +0000" stop="20251123133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Challenge To Survival</sub-title>
    <desc>"As civilization moves step by step into the wild kingdom, all forms of wildlife are forced to retreat until in many cases their survival is challenged.  Man must meet this challenge and help animals survive.  In this episode, man finds excitement and action as he captures, tags and relocated animals all over the world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123133000 +0000" stop="20251123140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Shadows</sub-title>
    <desc>"Deep in the forest of South America Marlin and Jim journey through this twilight world to observe the many strange and beautiful creatures that inhabit this primitive forest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123140000 +0000" stop="20251123143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Winter In The Wild Kingdom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bulldogging elk from helicopters in the snow-covered Colorado mountains highlights a trip to the wild kingdom in winter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123143000 +0000" stop="20251123150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lair Of The Tiger</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Sariska jungle in Rajasthan, northern India, a family of Bengal tigers have established their home.  Marlin journeys to this distant land to observe the cats in their natural environment."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123150000 +0000" stop="20251123153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Un-underground Movie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg's history project is a home movie about the pilgrims with the rest of the Brady clan as the cast. However, everyone's got their own idea about how the movie should go, and Greg soon loses control of his own project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123153000 +0000" stop="20251123160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's Smoke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg is spotted puffing on a cigarette with some members of a rock band. Mike and Carol get word, but refrain from punishing him. However, it's not long before a pack of cigarettes falls out of his letterman jacket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123160000 +0000" stop="20251123163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The First Thanksgiving</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Upset that the rest of the family is watching a football game instead of helping her prepare the Thanksgiving dinner, Marion reminds them of the meaning of the holiday with the story of the first Thanksgiving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123163000 +0000" stop="20251123170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley call in sick so they can have a day of fun, they meet a couple of fellows who may not be what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123170000 +0000" stop="20251123173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Virgil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to help out his visiting cousin, Virgil. When Virgil makes one too many mistakes, Barney rails against him and storms out. Leave it to Andy to put things right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123173000 +0000" stop="20251123180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Crooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy sneaks into the Mertzes' apartment to borrow one of Fred's suits so that she can order him a custom-made tweed suit for his birthday. This leads Ethel to think that Lucy is the notorious neighborhood burglar, "Madame X," and she goes spying on her friend to prove it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123180000 +0000" stop="20251123183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Pigeons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Larry and Whitey begin a pigeon club and they each purchase pigeons of their own. Beaver names his two Miss Canfield and Miss Landers, after his two teachers. However, when Beaver comes down with chicken pox, Wally is forced into caring for them, but soon finds Beaver isn't the only one ill, Miss Canfield and Miss Landers are also ailing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123183000 +0000" stop="20251123190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver learns he has to go to the dentist and that's when his friends tell him some horror stories about the drill the dentist is going to use. This prompts Beaver to become downright scared of going to the dentist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123190000 +0000" stop="20251123193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly's First Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May is set up with Sonny Drysdale. Their date, however, end very quickly: Sonny tries to kiss Elly’s hand, which she mistakes for him trying to bite her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123193000 +0000" stop="20251123200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Turkey Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May makes a pet out of the Thanksgiving turkey Drysdale gives the family, making it impossible for "Herman" to be killed. And to celebrate in her own way, Mrs. Drysdale organizes a picture to represent the first Thanksgiving, enlisting two actors portraying Native Americans. But when they head over to the Clampetts' mansion to get the turkey for the picture, Elly and Granny think they are being attacked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123200000 +0000" stop="20251123203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Little Island, Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A well known crook tries to evade police after a heist and is dropped off on the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123203000 +0000" stop="20251123210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch doctor makes voodoo dolls from the castaways' personal affects, which he has stolen from their huts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123210000 +0000" stop="20251123213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>An Ill Wind  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A tornado on Thanksgiving Day traps the Harper family, Iola and Effie in the basement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123213000 +0000" stop="20251123220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Fly Naomi  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Naomi wants to be a flight attendant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123220000 +0000" stop="20251123230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Best Of Friends / Too Many Dads / Love Will Find A Way</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>On this Thanksgiving cruise, a father and his adopted son try to evade the boys biological father by escaping to Mexico; an older couple plan to travel with their daughter and her fiance who, unknown to them, is crippled; the smooth operation of the ship suffers as one by one the entire crew, after trading a bevy of insults, ends up not speaking with one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251123230000 +0000" stop="20251124010000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>A Boy Named Charlie Brown</sub-title>
    <desc>"Charlie Brown competes in a spelling bee, and he'll need the help of Linus and Snoopy' to overcome his unlucky streak. This Academy Award nominated animated feature was the Peanuts film debut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124010000 +0000" stop="20251124013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After an accident on the loading dock brings Archie within inches of his life,he suddenly becomes a devout-if somewhat hypocritical- churchgoer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124013000 +0000" stop="20251124020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Atheist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving dinner becomes a family battleground when Archie discovers that Mike and Gloria don't want to impose the family's religious beliefs on their baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124020000 +0000" stop="20251124023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Stretch Cunningham, Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie reluctantly agrees to deliver Stretch Cunningham's eulogy, unaware that his departed friend was Jewish.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124023000 +0000" stop="20251124030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Joys Of Sex</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Gloria and Mike help Edith and Archie express their sexual interaction after catching Edith reading How to be your Husband's Mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124030000 +0000" stop="20251124033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Bird, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barones find that their differing traditions encourage lots of conversation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124033000 +0000" stop="20251124040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>No Fat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra, Ray and the kids make plans to spend the holiday at Frank and Marie's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124040000 +0000" stop="20251124043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Punch Thy Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Jerry constant teasing about "The Alan Brady Show" causes a rift with Rob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124043000 +0000" stop="20251124050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Who Owes Who What?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob tries to find a way to secretly remind Buddy of an unpaid debt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124050000 +0000" stop="20251124053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Ralph Kramden, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton invests in Ralph's stock when Ralph wants twenty dollars. When Ralph thinks he is named in a millionaire's will, arguments arise. It turns out Ralph was simply left a pet bird named Fortune, and much of the money was left to the butler and maid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124053000 +0000" stop="20251124060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Time Enough At Last</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank teller pestered by the demands of his job and wife longs for time alone to read books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124060000 +0000" stop="20251124070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Hangover  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A man wakes up with a hangover, an unknown woman in his room and his wife lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124070000 +0000" stop="20251124080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Encounter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate boss Frank Brady and his underling, Martin Stoner, are terrorizing Southwestern businessmen, forcing them to partner with the Syndicate. The weak spot is Stoner's wife, Lois, who has become an alcoholic under the pressures of her husband's work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124080000 +0000" stop="20251124090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>An Apple A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Running from the police, Kimble hides out at a farm owned by a local country doctor, named Josephus Adams, who treats his patients with little more than a dose of honey and a reassuring word. After one elderly woman under Adams' care dies from a protracte</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124090000 +0000" stop="20251124100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Guardian At The Gates</sub-title>
    <desc>"Business mixes with pleasure for Harry O whose search for a would-be killer draws him into a romance with the daughter of the intended victim."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124100000 +0000" stop="20251124103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124103000 +0000" stop="20251124110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124110000 +0000" stop="20251124113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>A Fool And His Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy wins $10,000 in a contest to name a new woman's shampoo, resulting in a lot of unwanted advice on how to use the money. On patrol, he and reed deal with a loud music complaint that has a romantic sub-context, encounter a sniper perched atop a parki</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124113000 +0000" stop="20251124120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of A 415</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed return a young runaway to his home while responding to a domestic disturbance call at the same address, discovering a dysfunctional situation that appears to be escalating toward a tragic conclusion. In the meantime, they search for a female drug pusher who mistakes a stranger for a fellow pusher, investigate a man attempting to force his way into a truck and encounter a wino riding a stolen bike at night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124120000 +0000" stop="20251124130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toonlandia</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124130000 +0000" stop="20251124133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets Adopted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally wins a trophy at school and Beaver accidentally breaks it. This leads Ward to accuse Beaver of being jealous of Wally and that he broke it on purpose. Upset, Beaver decides to get new parents and heads to an adoption agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124133000 +0000" stop="20251124140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus Ride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward allow Wally to escort Beaver on a bus headed to a friend's house in Crystal Falls. However, on one of the stops, Beaver inadvertently gets on the wrong bus, a bus that takes him back to Mayfield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124140000 +0000" stop="20251124150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prudent Proecutor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>DA Hamilton Burger asks Mason to defend an old friend who once saved his life in a boating accident 10 years before. The old friend of Burger's is now facing a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124150000 +0000" stop="20251124160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Network  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Network programming chief Paul J. Bartel is murdered, leaving Hollywood baffled as to the identity of the killer. Matlock comes to town to represent the television producer accused of the crime, and finds more than his fair share of suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124160000 +0000" stop="20251124170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Baby For Sale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Bubba's cousin adopts a baby her husband is blackmailed by the child's real parents - they want him to help them steal the payroll where he works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124170000 +0000" stop="20251124180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pursuit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman accuses Jim-Bob of fathering her unborn child</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124180000 +0000" stop="20251124190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Comanches Is Soft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After spending a wild night in Wichita, Quint and Festus deal with a saloon girl who claims they invited her to Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124190000 +0000" stop="20251124200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss and Joe are out on a hunting trip when they come across a pregnant indian woman. Hoss and Joe look after the woman and end up delivering her baby. After deciding to take her back to the ranch house, they soon discover that they are being followed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124200000 +0000" stop="20251124203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>First Wages</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to find out why Mark has taken a job as a stableboy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124203000 +0000" stop="20251124210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sheer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and Milly are held prisoner in her general store when two gunmen attempt a daring robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124210000 +0000" stop="20251124220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Donna Fuller Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>"A woman and three companions in a runaway wagon are rescued by a winemaker and Charlie. They are against the consumption of alcohol and join the wagon train. However, she begins to fall for the winemaker until she learns his trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124220000 +0000" stop="20251124230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Professor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man shows signs of schizophrenia for no apparent reason and the Secret Service won't give any clues. Roy has an admirer, yet John accuses him of having no charisma. The paramedics respond to a false alarm on a fireboat, and end up saving the victim of a plane crash; they also deliver a premature baby and rescue a man threatening to jump off a tall building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124230000 +0000" stop="20251124233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Unforgettable Characters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets accepted into the "Famous Las Vegas Writers School," and begins to write his impressions of the camp. It happens to be Frank's birthday, so Hawkeye and B.J. stage a fight with each other to make Frank happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251124233000 +0000" stop="20251125000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125000000 +0000" stop="20251125003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125003000 +0000" stop="20251125010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125010000 +0000" stop="20251125013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Deputy Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has been writing letters to his brother and sister-in-law for some time on courthouse stationary. Because of this, they have come to believe that he is a deputy, something they expect to see on their upcoming visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125013000 +0000" stop="20251125020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Mcbeevee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While walking through the woods, Opie meets Mr. McBeevee, a man who, Opie claims, "lives in the trees" and "jingles when he walks." Andy eventually learns that Opie's new friend works for the telephone company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125020000 +0000" stop="20251125023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Boob Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is upset when she sees Ray's reaction to her friend's "new and improved" breasts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125023000 +0000" stop="20251125030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Can Opener, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone in the family takes sides when Ray and Debra have an argument.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125030000 +0000" stop="20251125033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125033000 +0000" stop="20251125040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a Luftwaffe codebook, but must organize a special mission when Newkirk drops it down a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125040000 +0000" stop="20251125043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Talk Show, Steve fights for control of his talk show from his obnoxious guests. Then, in Cobumble, the gang parodies "Columbo" with Steve as Peter Falk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125043000 +0000" stop="20251125053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sausalito Sunrise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An art dealer and his girlfriend are arrested for two murders related to a series of hijacks. Paul goes undercover to ferret out the hijacking ring, and Mason finds himself staring down the barrel of a gun pointed by a killer even he never considered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125053500 +0000" stop="20251125060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is terrified of falling asleep for fear he might die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125060500 +0000" stop="20251125070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Bonfire  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Preacher Robert Evans will go to murderous lengths to obtain a woman's manor for his gospel sanctuary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125070500 +0000" stop="20251125080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Chance Meeting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Two buddies from Vietnam meet and one of them ends up dead. The murder might be connected to a third man, a deserter still evading the authorities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125080500 +0000" stop="20251125090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flight Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A political refugee gets a unwilling helping hand from Frank when he creates a change of identity to help flee the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125090500 +0000" stop="20251125100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Programmed For Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A genius and his partner use a computer to commit murder and larceny.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125100000 +0000" stop="20251125103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125103000 +0000" stop="20251125110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125110000 +0000" stop="20251125113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Keeping Tabs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are stunned to discover that the driver who led them on a high-speed chase is the son of Sgt. MacDonald, and Malloy takes it upon himself to help his boss figure out why the young man is acting out. In the meantime, they investigate a possible burglary in progress at an apartment building, mediate a dispute at a park over an elderly woman feeding ducks, respond to a call of two armed men fighting over a woman and deal with a wino who is attempting to direct traffic at a busy intersection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125113000 +0000" stop="20251125120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Rap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed naively thinks the system can help a young serial car thief who continually skirts responsibility for his actions with the help of his rich father's lawyer. In the meantime, he and Malloy help a woman track down the drug dealer responsible for her boyfriend's fatal overdose, and pull over a stubborn elderly woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125120000 +0000" stop="20251125130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Infamous Battles</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125130000 +0000" stop="20251125133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Gilbert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors in the Gates family and Beaver befriends their son, Gilbert Gates (changed to "Bates" in later episodes). However, Ward, June and Wally quickly realize the obvious when Beaver comes home with all kinds of wild stories that Gilbert has told and that Beaver is convinced are true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125133000 +0000" stop="20251125140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Fame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying after school cleaning the chalkboards, Larry convinces Beaver that Mrs. Rayburn keeps a spanking machine in her office closet. Later, a curious Beaver sneaks a peek but soon finds himself locked in the principal's office. Beaver's fame doesn't go over well with his family, but Beaver has another problem on his hands: he's just gotten his head stuck in an iron fence in the park.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125140000 +0000" stop="20251125150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gallant Grafter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporate intrigue is the backdrop of this episode when embezzling accountant Robert Doniger is murdered and Edward Nelson is charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125150000 +0000" stop="20251125160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Best Friend  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Vanessa Douglas when she's accused of murdering Stephen Cassidy, an author who destroyed a political family's ambitions with a tell-all book. When Matlock realizes his client is indeed guilty, he sets up an ingenious plan to draw out a confession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125160000 +0000" stop="20251125170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Obsession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A flirtatious schoolteacher is stalked by a madman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125170000 +0000" stop="20251125180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Thanksgiving Story - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving time on Walton's Mountain means a turkey shoot, a school play about early settlers, and the big meal. One year it also included a rekindled love affair and a life-threatening accident</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125180000 +0000" stop="20251125190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Father's Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman learns that the man who tried to have his way with her is her husband's uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125190000 +0000" stop="20251125200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>El Toro Grande</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben sends Hoss and Little Joe down to Mexico to purchase the bull known as El Toro Grande. While down there, Joe gets involved with the beautiful daughter of El Toro's owner and Hoss finds out that the son of one of the ranch hands has formed a very deep attachment to the bull.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125200000 +0000" stop="20251125203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stand-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two prison wagon drivers stop at the McCain ranch looking for whiskey. Lucas turns them down because they are escorting Rudy Croft, a murderer who is to be hanged in Yuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125203000 +0000" stop="20251125210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark goes to work for Will Temple, a badly scarred and very mysterious rancher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125210000 +0000" stop="20251125220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sam Darland Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon train finds Sam Darland with orphan boys in an old ghost town. Hale tries to convince Darland that it is not safe to stay in the town, as it in the midst of Indian territory and the leader of the tribe has been on the warpath."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125220000 +0000" stop="20251125230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>John tries to convince Roy he has tonsillitis. An old flame of Dixie's, who is now a famous actor, is admitted to Rampart. Two kids are trapped on top of a gas tank; a girl's college lacrosse game turns violent; Boot has surgery to remove a tick; Dr. Early deals with a hypochondriac. Chet is injured during a rescue and is roomed with Roy, who has had his tonsils removed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125230000 +0000" stop="20251125233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251125233000 +0000" stop="20251126000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126000000 +0000" stop="20251126003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126003000 +0000" stop="20251126010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126010000 +0000" stop="20251126013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Rich Girlfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy has begun seeing Peggy McMillan and he discovers she is from a wealthy family. The differences in their upbringings and education unsettle Andy, and he begins to doubt the ability of the relationship to endure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126013000 +0000" stop="20251126020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The New Mayor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and the new mayor are not on the same page in terms of Andy's style of managing Mayberry's sheriff's department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126020000 +0000" stop="20251126023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Turkey Or Fish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides it's her turn to prepare the holiday meal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126023000 +0000" stop="20251126030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>You Bet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone questions Frank's radical change in behavior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126030000 +0000" stop="20251126033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Klink Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer for a German suicide squad train bound for the Russian front in order to steal key documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126033000 +0000" stop="20251126040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gasoline War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men plan to destroy a gasoline station that has just been built in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126040000 +0000" stop="20251126043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ruth Buzzi And Jack Gilford</sub-title>
    <desc>In Censorship, Carol and Vicki cut lines from a sketch so they don't offend anyone. Then, in Carol and Sis, Carol suspects Harvey is having an affair after he gets into an automobile accident. Finally, in Snow White - Fifteen Years Later, Carol plays an aged Snow dissatisfied with her Prince Charming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126043000 +0000" stop="20251126053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crying Comedian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Comic Charlie Hatch learns that the woman he loved and lost, Anne Gilrain, has escaped from a sanitarium to which she was forced to commit herself by her husband, Tom. When Tom Gilrain is murdered, Charlie is afraid that Anne did the deed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126053500 +0000" stop="20251126060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126060500 +0000" stop="20251126070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Tender Poisoner  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Two business executives throw themselves into a battle of wits and trickery as they compete for a gorgeous lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126070500 +0000" stop="20251126080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Edge Of The Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An anthropology professor comes to believe one of his students had an affair with his wife, and denies the man a degree. Then someone murders the professor, and the police come knocking, leaving Mannix as the young man's only hope for freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126080500 +0000" stop="20251126090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A former motorcycle officer who was disabled when a thief tried to steal the payroll from an armored car, seeks Frank's help for the purpose of exacting his revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126090500 +0000" stop="20251126100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gold Record For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to preserve his reputation for genius, a rock star kills the ghost writer who always complained for never getting credit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126100000 +0000" stop="20251126103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126103000 +0000" stop="20251126110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126110000 +0000" stop="20251126113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harbor Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy needs to sell two tickets to the ballet after his date cancels, but he quickly regrets putting a notice on the station's bulletin board. While patrolling the harbor and surrounding area, he and Reed investigate a marine fuel dealer accused of forgery, pull over a driver with a suspicious box on the roof of his car, question a suspicious young couple, deal with an astrologer who is driving recklessly and encounter a drunken cook shooting a rifle from the crow's nest of a docked ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126113000 +0000" stop="20251126120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Rampart Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an elusive purse snatcher whose latest victim was visiting her husband's grave. In the meantime, they deal with an annoying former cop turned security guard, encounter a desperate old man attempting to break into a car, help a cantankerous elderly woman who is being evicted, mediate a near-violent dispute over five dollars, track down a runaway baby carriage and search for an armed suspect who just robbed a cocktail lounge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126120000 +0000" stop="20251126130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Paperboy Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126130000 +0000" stop="20251126133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Horse Named Nick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally get jobs at the circus cleaning the animals and a promise to each be paid $10 dollars at the end of the week. However, the end of the week comes and there is no money in sight; instead, Beaver and Wally become the proud owners of a horse named Nicholas, which they hide in the garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126133000 +0000" stop="20251126140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver discovers that Ward was in WWII and brags to his classmates that Ward was a war hero. As usual, his classmates don't believe him and Beaver promises to bring in some momentos to prove it. However, at home, Beaver discovers that Ward was an engineer in the war and didn't actually fight in combat, thus leaving Beaver to take drastic measures so as not to look like a fool in front of his classmates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126140000 +0000" stop="20251126150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wary Wildcatter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Houston cleverly gets away with killing his wife by making it look like she died in a car accident. Then a wildlife photographer shows up with the murder on film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126150000 +0000" stop="20251126160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Body  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a woman after she's accused of murdering an aerobics instructor who slept with her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126160000 +0000" stop="20251126170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Liar's Poker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A game of high stakes poker ends in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126170000 +0000" stop="20251126180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Thanksgiving Story - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving time on Walton's Mountain means a turkey shoot, a school play about early settlers, and the big meal. One year it also included a rekindled love affair and a life-threatening accident</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126180000 +0000" stop="20251126190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Now That April's Here</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The only ones who believe Festus' girlfriend witnessed a murder are the killers themselves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126190000 +0000" stop="20251126200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Outcast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman's life is ruined by her relation to criminals. Only the Cartwrights treat her differently. When she turns to Clay Renton, an ex-con, and Ben must help her out of a bad situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126200000 +0000" stop="20251126203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Corey Hazlett insists he's innocent of murder, despite Lucas's eyewitness testimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126203000 +0000" stop="20251126210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to dissuade a latter-day knight from rushing into battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126210000 +0000" stop="20251126220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Abel Weatherly Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"A sea captain traveling west haunted by nightmares from his past is found stranded, injured and drunk by Bill and Charlie. After hearing his story, they help him reach his destination to locate a ghost: a dead sailor that may be alive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126220000 +0000" stop="20251126230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Honest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A gas explosion results from a white lie, prompting Johnny to go on an honesty kick. At the hospital, doctors work to save a boy who is inexplicably choking to death. In the field, the paramedics rescue a teenage boy injured in a dive off a roof, and a baby and his blind grandfather trapped in a burning house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126230000 +0000" stop="20251126233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251126233000 +0000" stop="20251127000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127000000 +0000" stop="20251127003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127003000 +0000" stop="20251127010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127010000 +0000" stop="20251127013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Bachelors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie are left alone while Aunt Bee goes out of town. Peggy, Andy's new girlfriend, takes great delight in helping the boys handle things. Floyd warns Andy that Peggy is using her feminine wiles to "snare" him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127013000 +0000" stop="20251127020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Cow Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The mayor calls in an investigator from the state capital to help solve a string of cow thefts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127020000 +0000" stop="20251127023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>No Thanks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is intent on finding a way to improve her relationship with Marie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127023000 +0000" stop="20251127030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sex Talk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra are discouraged when they realize their sex life isn't what it used to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127030000 +0000" stop="20251127033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Unfair Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan kidnaps Burkhalter's sister in order to exchange her for a captured Allied agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127033000 +0000" stop="20251127040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127040000 +0000" stop="20251127043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Kay Ballard</sub-title>
    <desc>In Service Station Attendant, a bank robber stops for gas, only to be served by a slow attendant. Then, in The Luncheon, girlfriends fight over who should pay most of the bill. Finally, in The Dater's Game, a parody of "The Dating Game", a male stage manager assumes the position of one of the female contestants after he ruins her dress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127043000 +0000" stop="20251127053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Twice-told Twist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young car thief—who helped strip Mason's car down to the frame—is charged with murder, Mason decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127053500 +0000" stop="20251127060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>And When The Sky Was Opened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When three U.S. astronauts return to Earth after the first flight into space, they begin being erased from history one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127060500 +0000" stop="20251127070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Thirty-first Of February  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The passing away of Andrew Anderson's spouse sets off strange events calculated to drive the widower insane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127070500 +0000" stop="20251127080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Ransom For Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone demands a quarter-of-a-million-dollars ransom—for a boy missing six years!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127080500 +0000" stop="20251127090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Of San Ignacio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Stolen precious artifacts from a church in Mexico, has Cannon in search of three suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127090500 +0000" stop="20251127100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Friends Till Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Betty's is now smuggling heroin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127100000 +0000" stop="20251127103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127103000 +0000" stop="20251127110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127110000 +0000" stop="20251127113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Foothill Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy, Reed and Sgt. MacDonald go horseback as part of the search for suspects responsible for a break-in at a large ranch. Meanwhile, Sgt. MacDonald offers a reward for the return of his favorite boots, Officer Wells starts a collection for a couple who claims their baby needs brain surgery and the station is attacked by a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127113000 +0000" stop="20251127120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>West Valley Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy has his eye on an attractive woman he's seeing all over town walking a scotty dog, which eventually turns out to be bad news for her. Meanwhile, he and Reed assist a police helicopter track down a young man riding his dirt bike in the hills illegally during fire season, search for an armed suspect who held up a movie theater before escaping on a motorcycle and coordinate with the police helicopter in a futile search for two armed robbery suspects who fatally shot a night watchman inside a department store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127120000 +0000" stop="20251127130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>It's Turkey Day!</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127130000 +0000" stop="20251127133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Says Good-bye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward makes an offer on a house located in a neighboring town and Beaver believes moving is going to be a sure thing. This leads him to tell all his classmates that he's moving, but when the deal falls through Beaver must tell his class that he won't be moving after all—after they've just thrown him a goodbye party and shoved a handful of presents in his face!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127133000 +0000" stop="20251127140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>While cleaning in the garage, Beaver and Wally come across an old typewriter. Beaver decides to fix it up and begin his own newspaper with Larry. However, someone is standing in his way, Wally, who claims the typewriter is his property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127140000 +0000" stop="20251127150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mythical Monkeys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Author Mauvis Meade sends her secretary, Gladys Doyle, out to a mountain cabin to pick up a package. Gladys gets lost and her car gets stuck in the mud. She then walks to a cabin looking for help and encounters a mysterious man who appears to know her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127150000 +0000" stop="20251127160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Singer  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a producer accused of killing a singer, trying to prove that someone else at the recording studio is guilty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127160000 +0000" stop="20251127170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Ruda's Awakening</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's Aunt Ruda is the only witness to a struggle between Bubba and a young robbery suspect that ends in the young man’s death. But her prejudice against the police -- and Virgil clouds her memory of the incident. Bubba returns to Los Angeles to testify at a murder trial and is reunited with Pat Day as they try to protect Mike from killers sent to prevent him from testifying.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127170000 +0000" stop="20251127180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Waiting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy is no longer missing in war</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127180000 +0000" stop="20251127190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Caleb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Having grown tired of farming, Caleb Marr comes to Dodge in search of adventure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127190000 +0000" stop="20251127200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A House Divided</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Frederick Kyle arrives in Virginia City on a mission for the Confederacy. Kyle is also looking for Joe Cartwright. After they meet, Joe starts warming to the idea of helping Kyle out, much to the disappointment of his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127200000 +0000" stop="20251127203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Honest Abe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Able Lincoln's claim that he's the Great Emancipator himself amuses everyone except Matt Yorty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127203000 +0000" stop="20251127210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogarty is Lucas's main roadblock as he tries to get young Woody Fogarty to attend school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127210000 +0000" stop="20251127220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Davey Baxter Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>"When his wagon falls down a cliff, Davey Baxter's mother is killed, and his arm is crushed. The doctor is unavailable, so Chris is forced to make the decision to amputate. This changes everything for Davey and the girl he plans to marry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127220000 +0000" stop="20251127230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Seance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman keeps calling the squad because she's convinced the bad things that happen to her husband are the result of her recently deceased sister. A youth suffering side effects from tranquilizers is treated in the ER. The paramedics rescue a man pinned under a stack of heavy cartons, and a driver trapped underwater in his car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127230000 +0000" stop="20251127233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251127233000 +0000" stop="20251128000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128000000 +0000" stop="20251128003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128003000 +0000" stop="20251128010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128010000 +0000" stop="20251128013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Mends A Broken Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy shows up for a date with Peggy McMillan only to learn her old friend, Don, has arrived unexpectedly, leading to a string of misunderstandings and Barney's attempts at help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128013000 +0000" stop="20251128020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Lawman Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's ability to be a lawman is put to the test with some peddlers and he fails. His confidence is shattered until Andy steps in behind the scenes and warns the peddlers of "Fife the Fierce."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128020000 +0000" stop="20251128023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Fighting In-laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra discovers that her seemingly contented parents are not happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128023000 +0000" stop="20251128030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Older Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is thrilled that both her parents have agreed to have Thanksgiving dinner with the Barones.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128030000 +0000" stop="20251128033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128033000 +0000" stop="20251128040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128040000 +0000" stop="20251128043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests John Byner And Petula Clarke</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Old Folks, a couple reminisces over their keepsakes, singing "You're My Reason". Then, in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parodies TV commercials, including S-inchester Cigars, Second Cup of Coffee, MacDougal's Hamburger, Rational Airlines, and Tidey. Next, in Alice Portnoy, Carol as a Fireside girl scout is kidnapped, only she's more than the kidnappers bargained for. Finally, in The Firing of Donald Duck, the movie studio decides to can the famous bird.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128043000 +0000" stop="20251128053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Meddling Medium</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>On the case of a phony psychic who met with a grisly death, Mason devises a fantastic demonstration to prove his client innocent and expose the real culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128053500 +0000" stop="20251128060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What You Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A two-bit thug thinks he's found the key to a better life in an old sidewalk salesman who has the uncanny ability to tell people what they need the most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128060500 +0000" stop="20251128070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>What Really Happened  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a distressed housekeeper murders her boss, the deceased man's wife is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128070500 +0000" stop="20251128080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves plan to start a holiday weekend by looting every office in a high-rise. That leaves Mannix and a friend trapped in a vault, with limited air and no one likely to discover them for several days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128080500 +0000" stop="20251128090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Vine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor who is conducting a medical research project at the state prison is the victim of harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128090500 +0000" stop="20251128100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Rendezvous With Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to find the son of a South American ruler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128100000 +0000" stop="20251128103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128103000 +0000" stop="20251128110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A purse-snatching dog? This is the case Friday and Gannon must solve. Making things more difficult, victims give different descriptions of the four-legged thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128110000 +0000" stop="20251128113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Venice Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have to break the news to a young model that her press agent lied when he said there would be nothing wrong with having a nude photo shoot on a busy public beach. Later, they discover a man stealing from a phone booth, assist in the chase of a stolen dune buggy, try help an attractive woman whose safety is put in grave danger by an obscene phone caller, deal with a wino who dies while eating at a diner and pull over a woman towing a large jack-o-lantern.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128113000 +0000" stop="20251128120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Today's patrol begins with a traffic stop of a high-society cat burglar who's just finished serving a four-year prison term, and Malloy senses the guy is about to return to his old ways. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a standoff with a wounded robbery suspect who fatally shot a convenience store worker, examine an abandoned vehicle, investigate the theft of a book from a library and deal with a distraught unemployed man who takes his young daughter hostage in his home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128120000 +0000" stop="20251128130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Survival A La Mode</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony learn outdoor survival skills from a true bushcraft expert."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128130000 +0000" stop="20251128133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver sees an Eskimo sweater in a store window and becomes determined to get one. He finally convinces Ward and June to get him one, but the first day he wears it he sees Judy Hensler wearing the same sweater.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128133000 +0000" stop="20251128140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver spends the weekend at Larry's but the first night there they get into a terrible argument and Beaver goes home angry. After Ward tells Beaver a story about Damon and Pythias, Beaver and Larry swear to die for each other. Larry then promptly demands that Beaver give him his homework to prove himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128140000 +0000" stop="20251128150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Singing Skirt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Big Barn is a legal gambling casino run by George Anclitis. Things are going well until George's second banana, Slim Marcus, botches a crooked card game and is exposed for cheating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128150000 +0000" stop="20251128160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Reunion  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of Matlock's old law school pals is murdered, he faces the unpleasant task of proving that a former classmate is guilty of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128160000 +0000" stop="20251128170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Unfinished Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to L.A. to testify in an organized-crime trial and to safeguard the key witness---a young boy (Mike Chin) who saw a mobster commit a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128170000 +0000" stop="20251128180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Ten Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and another captured solider are led from camp on an unknown trip</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128180000 +0000" stop="20251128190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Owney Tupper Had A Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Owney Tupper decides to take action when he's forced to give up custody of his daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128190000 +0000" stop="20251128200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gunmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Hoss arrive in the town of Keowa Flats, Texas. They are immediately mistaken for two gunslinging brothers, the Slades. Joe and Hoss soon find themselves involved in a feud, realizing they are the only ones in a position to stop the fighting before it gets any worse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128200000 +0000" stop="20251128203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark meet Mark Twain and find out that he hides a sad secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128203000 +0000" stop="20251128210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun From Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to stop embittered John Holliver from venting his wrath on the people who expelled him from town years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128210000 +0000" stop="20251128220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Johnny Masters Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>"On his way to Fort David, wagon scout Duke Shannon rescues Sgt. Johnny Masters being sent to prison for twenty years; a man caught between two worlds. The world of his ancestors the Cherokee, and the world of his loyalty, the U.S. Army."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128220000 +0000" stop="20251128230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen are puzzled by Boot's strange behavior. Meanwhile, paramedics rescue a woman whose sports car is pinned under a gas truck and investigate a series of unusual incidents in the home of a woman attempting to cook a meal for her boyfriend and his mother. An unconscious man is brought in to the hospital suffering from internal bleeding. Dr. Early deals with the victim of a curse. An explosion in a hospital lab endangers a number of workers and important records.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128230000 +0000" stop="20251128233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251128233000 +0000" stop="20251129000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129000000 +0000" stop="20251129003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129003000 +0000" stop="20251129010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129010000 +0000" stop="20251129013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Mayberry Band</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Stoner declares the town's marching band a disgrace and refuses to allocate money for its annual trip to the state competition. Andy takes matters into his own hands, with help from Bobby Fleet and his Band with a Beat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129013000 +0000" stop="20251129020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Floyd The Gay Deceiver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Madeline Grayson, a rich widow that Floyd has been "pen-palling" with, announces in her next letter that she wants to meet him face-to-face. Of course, the whole time Floyd has been pretending in his letters to be a wealthy entrepreneur.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129020000 +0000" stop="20251129023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Will, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra must decide who would make the best guardians for their children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129023000 +0000" stop="20251129030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sister, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is upset when her sister decides to become...a sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129030000 +0000" stop="20251129033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must prevent the Germans from getting ahold of a secret device that was aboard a plane shot down near camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129033000 +0000" stop="20251129040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Defector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a defecting field marshal to England, whom Hochstetter has followed to Stalag 13.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129040000 +0000" stop="20251129043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Valerie Harper</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Ham Actor, an obnoxious actress fills in for the sick leading lady. Then, in The First Blind Date, Valerie helps Carol woo her date. Finally, in The Oldest Man, Harvey's house is on fire, and the Oldest Man comes to his rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129043000 +0000" stop="20251129053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tsarina's Tiara</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When a jeweler and gem expert is pulled over for speeding, the corpse of an international jewel thief is found in the trunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129053500 +0000" stop="20251129060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Four Of Us Are Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who can change his face to resemble others gets into hot water with gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129060500 +0000" stop="20251129070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Forecast: Low Clouds And Coastal Fog  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A lady is plunged into a nightmare after she refuses to help a man and his badly beaten girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129070500 +0000" stop="20251129080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Quartet For A Blunt Instrument</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix agrees to help a mechanic accused of beating an inventor to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129080500 +0000" stop="20251129090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Guinea Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon discovers that a man is posing as the son of a wine maker is likely the suspect of the three death attempts already tried against his "father."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129090500 +0000" stop="20251129100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple murders young men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251129100000 +0000" stop="20251129103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Last Chance Farm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe convinces two overweight women that the Shady Rest is actually a fat farm.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
