<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011070500 +0000" stop="20251011080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Melted Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates when an heiress finds an ax buried into the head of a snowman outside of her home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011080500 +0000" stop="20251011090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadline For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of men pretending to be Barnaby and J.R. murder a writer employed by a publishing empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011090000 +0000" stop="20251011093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Why Girls Leave Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobbie Jo decides to move to New York to take singing lessons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011093000 +0000" stop="20251011100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>There's No Stove Like An Old Stove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe has had enough of chopping wood for Kate, so he hits upon an idea to make her buy a new stove.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011100000 +0000" stop="20251011103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Servants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are doing repairs for their home, just as Elly is adapting to the look of a city girl, but not enjoying being called a “city girl.” Drysdale and Jane have figure out a way to improve the Clampetts by lending them servants. However, the Clampetts don’t want any servants, so Drysdale tells them that some of his staff is just going to be staying with them for a few days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011103000 +0000" stop="20251011110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Gorilla</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly and Jethro both want a gorilla to help out around the house, so Jed asks Drysdale to get them one. Drysdale hires a man dressed as a gorilla to scare the Clampetts, but it fails. They put their new gorilla, Herby, to work doing chores and dress him in old clothes. Mr. Kelly, the man in the gorilla suit, wants out of the deal and gives his suit to Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011110000 +0000" stop="20251011113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Morning, Noon And Night Club, Mess Production, The Spinach Overture</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye temporarily drops his nautical air to become a night club dancer, all for Olive's sake., Popeye and Bluto, two rival factory workers, fight each other for privilege of saving Olive Oyl., Popeye turns his talents to music and is seen conducting an orchestra."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011113000 +0000" stop="20251011120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Jekyll And Mr. Mouse, The Bookworm Turns, Jerry And The Goldfish</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry drinks a potion that makes him grow to the size of a giant and decides to go after Tom this time. Academy Award nominee for 1948 Best Short Subject., A crazed Dr. Jekyll switches out the brain of a crow for that of a bookworm., Tom tries to cook the house’s goldfish, Goldie, which has become Jerry’s new friend."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011120000 +0000" stop="20251011130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Smoked Hams, Hunger Strife, Rough And Tumbleweed, Pantry Panic, Yukon Have It, Apple Andy, Ration Bored</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally tries to get some sleep during the day, but Woody makes noise moving the lawn and burning leaves. Wally gets revenge when Woody goes to sleep., Ranger Willoughby insists Fatso go on a diet and not accept food from travelers during tourist season., Inspector Willoughby pursues a Wild West outlaw., Woody fails to go South for the winter, leaving him vulnerable to a starving cat., Chilly Willy enrolls as a mountie, but his enrollment photo gets pasted over the wanted poster for criminal Caribou Lou. Smedley chases Chilly, but Chilly ends up catching the real Caribou Lou and becoming an honorary mountie., Andy Panda is tempted to steal apples by the devil on his shoulder., Woody refuses to present his ration card to fill up his gas tank and tries to siphon some gas from a police car. The policeman pursues him, resulting in both their deaths, and Woody is issued bigger wings than the policeman in heaven."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011130000 +0000" stop="20251011140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Prince Violent, Tired And Feathered, A Tale Of Two Kitties, Bedevilled Rabbit, Walky Talky Hawky, Feline Frame-up, Hot Cross Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs tries to protect a castle by kicking Sam the Terrible out and not letting him back in. , The Coyote once again chases the Road Runner and tries to fly. , Babbit and Catstello try to capture Tweety. , Bugs gets dropped into Tasmania where he confronts the Tasmanian devil and tricks him into believing he's not a rabbit. , Henery goes out to fulfill his destiny: hunting chickens. Foghorn Leghorn is fighting with a dog and uses the naive Henery against his enemy. , Marc Anthony gets trouble when Claude Cat frames him trying to eat Pussyfoot. As soon as Marc Anthony gets kicked out, Claude Cat proceeds with images of kitten torture and it's up to Marc to save the kitten. , Bugs Bunny is a science research test subject for the switching of his brain with a chicken. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011140000 +0000" stop="20251011150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Avaricious Actuary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Agents West and Gordon have been investigating a series of explosions that have demolished several palatial homes. While they are guests of the wealthy Mr. Taney, they hear a high, whining sound. Suddenly the house begins to crumble and the agents escape in the nick of time to see a giant tuning fork radiating powerful sound waves. As they delve deeper into the case, they discover a letter to Mr. Taney from the Cyclops Insurance Company, urging him to take out a policy against further destruction of his property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011150000 +0000" stop="20251011160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Martin Onyx Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>"A man finds a corpse that looks remarkably like himself. On an impulse he takes on the persona of the dead man only to find he was a living legend of west and had made a lot of enemies along the way."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011160000 +0000" stop="20251011170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Boy Into Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Lud, the oldest of three children, refuses to cooperate with the Barkleys, who have taken him and his siblings in. He is determined to track down their mother, who has disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011170000 +0000" stop="20251011180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Man's Bluff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt must rely on his wits and instincts when he goes blind while on the prairie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011180000 +0000" stop="20251011190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Search In Limbo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is accused of murdering a corrupt real estate broker, and, due to a concussion, cannot remember where he was on the day of the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011190000 +0000" stop="20251011193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rancher dies after the bank forecloses the mortgage on his property, his son blames the banker for his father's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011193000 +0000" stop="20251011200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind Reader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E40</episode-num>
    <desc>When a wealthy rancher is killed, Mark suggests that they seek the aid of a mind reader to identify the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011200000 +0000" stop="20251011210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Night On The Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Akins tells Favor he has 750 head of Mrs. North's cattle. Lewis, Mrs. North's lawyer, says the cattle that Wesley Adams turned over to Favor were Mrs. North's and were to be delivered to the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011210000 +0000" stop="20251011213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Prize Fight Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Paladin goes to a mining town to promote a prizefight, his boxer is arrested and he ends up having to take the man's place in the ring -- against the Welsh champion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011213000 +0000" stop="20251011220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Angela</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A grieving daughter impatient with the slow-moving wheels of justice vows to bring vengeance upon the man who murdered her father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011220000 +0000" stop="20251012000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Boobs In Arms, From Nurse To Worse, Sock-bye-baby, Spooks, Muscle Up A Little Closer, Gents In A Jam</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are greeting card salesmen who are mistakenly inducted into the army after escaping from the jealous husband of one of their customers.  In boot camp their sergeant turns out to be the same man, whom they constantly vex and bewilder.  When the boys are sent to the front lines and the sergeant is captured they must rescue him, which they do after doping themselves with laughing gas.  At the end they get shot off into the sunset on a cannon shell. , The stooge's friend Jerry convinces them to take out on insurance on Curly and then have him act insane to collect.  Moe and Larry put Curly on a leash and take him to the insurance doctor and have him act like a dog.  Unfortunately, the insurance doctor wants to perform a brain operation (Cerebrum decapitation).  The boys try to escape by hiding in the dog catchers wagon, but are caught and taken to the hospital.  They escape again, this time by rigging a sheet to a gurney and sailing down the street, where they run into Jerry and knock him into wet cement. , Shemp's rich Uncle Phineas comes to visit the Stooges who are broke and about to be evicted.  The boys convince their landlady Mrs. McGruder not to toss them out as Shemp is set to inherit a fortune.  The boys also have trouble with a circus strongman after Shemp accidentally rips off his wife's dress.  Uncle Phineas gets in the middle of the fight, and Mrs. McGruder ends it by knocking out the strongman.  It turns out that Uncle Phineas and the landlady were childhood sweethearts and he marries her, leaving the Stooges out of the bucks once again. , The Stooges mistakenly kidnap a baby they find on their doorstep.  When the cops and the baby's mother come looking for the baby, the boys panic and flee into the country with the cops (one of them is the baby's father) pursuing them by motorcycle.  It all ends happily with the baby reunited with its parents and the Stooges running off disguised as bushes. , The stooges are private detectives hired to find a missing girl, which leads to a mad scientist. , Joe is engaged but can't get married until he recovers the engagement ring which has disappeared.  The Stooges suspect the ring was stolen by Elmo, a beefy bully, who works at the same factory they do.  They confront Elmo in the company gym, but he's too tough for them.  Fortunately Joe's girl is even tougher, and she gets Elmo to confess and return the ring. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012000000 +0000" stop="20251012023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Them!</sub-title>
    <desc>"The earliest atomic tests in New Mexico cause common ants to mutate into giant man-eating monsters that threaten civilization."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012023000 +0000" stop="20251012050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Arachnophobia</sub-title>
    <desc>"A new species of spider causes trouble in a small town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012050000 +0000" stop="20251012060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>War Of The Robots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Will and Dr. Smith stumble upon another robot. More capable than their own robot, the alien robot works to gain the confidence of the Robinsons. At a critical point he plans to transport them to his home planet as slaves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012060000 +0000" stop="20251012070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An extraterrestrial stranger tries to force Nelson to destroy the Pacific fleet with a nuclear missile.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012070000 +0000" stop="20251012080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Comeback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate actor captures the Earthlings, and forces them to act in his new movie so he can help the director save money on special effects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012080000 +0000" stop="20251012090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Visitors From Beyond The Stars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1885 Arizona, aliens force Tony and Doug to help them deplete the Earth's protein foodstuffs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012090000 +0000" stop="20251012100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Possessed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent meets a troubled man whose experiments have led to an unprecedented relationship with aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012100000 +0000" stop="20251012110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Survival</sub-title>
    <desc>"Robbie Cartman turns to Adams to save a deer named Ginger. Adams helps by going into the woods to create the proper medicine but gets injured,losing his memory. Will he find himself again,in time to cure Ginger?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012110000 +0000" stop="20251012113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Prairie Village</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the base of Devils Tower near Horse Heaven Pass in Wyoming, is a wilderness city populated by the ….prairie dog."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012113000 +0000" stop="20251012120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Shines</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim rate the I.Q.’s of the gorilla, chimpanzee, baboon, orangutan, gibbon and ring-tailed monkey."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012120000 +0000" stop="20251012123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Island Outposts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go island-hopping around the world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012123000 +0000" stop="20251012130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Puma Pass</sub-title>
    <desc>"A story of the community of wildlife living in a mountain valley, reigned over by a puma who lives at the head of the pass."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012130000 +0000" stop="20251012133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Fact Or Fallacy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim set out to separate fact from fallacy among many popularly held ideas about the animal kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012133000 +0000" stop="20251012140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Amazon Jungle (the Great)</sub-title>
    <desc>"The great tropical rain forest, supports life at all levels.  Fowler captures the largest mammal of the Amazon Jungle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012140000 +0000" stop="20251012143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Fright Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The boys trick Jan and Cindy into thinking they've seen a ghost. The girls plot their revenge, but it's Alice, Carol and Mike who mistakenly end up as their victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012143000 +0000" stop="20251012150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Earring Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter's new detective kit comes in handy when Cindy loses a pair of antique earrings that Marcia has borrowed from Carol. This leads Peter and Cindy on a search for the missing earrings, hoping to find them before an impending costume party, at which Carol plans to wear them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012150000 +0000" stop="20251012153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Haunted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After experiencing a few strange happenings, Richie begins to buy into the legend that the place where Ralph's Halloween party is to be held, the old Simpson house, is haunted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012153000 +0000" stop="20251012160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Two Of Our Weirdos Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley discover that Lenny and Squiggy have run off to join the circus. However, it falls to the girls to inform their friends that the ringmaster doesn't want to hire them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012160000 +0000" stop="20251012163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Opie and his friend, Arnold, hit a baseball into the window of an old, abandoned house, they hear noises and run for help. Barney and Gomer go to investigate—and hear noises, too!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012163000 +0000" stop="20251012170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Seance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy suddenly becomes interested in numerology and superstitions. After advising Ricky that it's a good day for him to make deals, she realizes that she read yesterday's horoscopes and that today is actually a bad day for Ricky.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012170000 +0000" stop="20251012173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Larry become convinced that the Cooper house is haunted by a witch and Beaver and Larry are scared to death. So when June gets Beaver a job walking Mrs. Cooper's dog, Beaver's fear gets the best of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012173000 +0000" stop="20251012180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Long Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has Gilbert over to spend the night but after they watch a gangster movie things get out of hand. A suspicious car has just pulled up to the front of the house with two strange characters sitting inside, and they just happen to be Lumpy and Bill, dressed for a masquerade party. Not knowing this, Beaver calls the police and Lumpy and Bill are arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012180000 +0000" stop="20251012183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Trick Or Treat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are feeling homesick. They are mostly all alone in Beverly Hills. And none of their neighbors are visiting them. So they decide to go visit their new neighbors. Little do they know, it is Halloween, a holiday they have never heard of. They visit many different houses, and in the end they get bagfuls of candy and treats.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012183000 +0000" stop="20251012190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>That Old Black Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny believes that Mrs. Drysdale has turned herself into a bird after she said a few zodiacal words, which Granny believes is black magic. Granny does what she can to change her back to normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012190000 +0000" stop="20251012193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Ghost A Go-go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A ghost appears on the island and tries to scare the castaways off, but they turn the tables by dressing in sheets to scare the visitor away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012193000 +0000" stop="20251012200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Up At Bat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan is bitten by a bat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012200000 +0000" stop="20251012203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Grave Mistake  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama discovers her husband's been buried in the wrong spot and that she's been visiting another man's grave. Anxious over the mistake, she refuses to visit again until she receives a sign that he forgives her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012203000 +0000" stop="20251012210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Farewell, Frannie  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Fran dies, Mama is set on giving her sister the perfect sendoff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012210000 +0000" stop="20251012220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Ship Of Ghouls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A magician keeps his engagement secret in order to dazzle female audiences, while his neglected fiancee turns to Captain Stubing for comfort; Doc and Gopher pursue a model who is afraid to face people after a recent accident; a boy with a habit of lying can't get anyone to help during a real time of need.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012220000 +0000" stop="20251012223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy's pretty young cousin, Gloria, comes for a visit after breaking up with her boyfriend. Aunt Bee asks Andy to be nice to her and his attention makes Helen jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012223000 +0000" stop="20251012230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Ashley Bevilacqua-berton &amp; Anne Olivares- Drew Barrymore Memorabilia</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ashley &amp; Anne are what you might call Drewbie's-fans and collector's of Drew Barrymore. Their friendship grew out of their love for all things Drew, and has culminated in an online museum which they call the Drewseum. Today, they'll show Lisa some of her most iconic items, including the prom dress she wore in Never Been Kissed and even some personal Christmas items Ashley received from Drew's own production company. Our expert today, Patrick Scott Patterson is also a Drew fan and collector who'll be tasked with appraising the ladies' collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012230000 +0000" stop="20251012233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sons And Bowlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing to the Marines once again, Colonel Potter wishes there was one sport the 4077th were any good at. When Klinger mentions he can bowl, the Colonel decides to have a bowling competition. Unfortunately, he and Klinger are the only two good bowlers in the camp, so BJ and Father Mulcahy are "recruited" to the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251012233000 +0000" stop="20251013000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Picture This</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter's attempts to assemble the crew for a family portrait are thwarted by a feud between bunkmates Pierce, Hunnicutt and Winchester. Things are not helped by the efforts of Margaret, Klinger and Mulcahy to bring the Swampmen back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013000000 +0000" stop="20251013003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Saga Of Cousin Oscar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is furious with his houseguest, Cousin Oscar. It seems when they were kids, Oscar bullied Archie and now Oscar is taking full advantage of his visit at the Bunkers. Archie wants to throw him out, but Oscar makes an exit of his own when he turns up dead. This leaves Archie left with the funeral arrangements which drives him up the wall after looking over the costs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013003000 +0000" stop="20251013010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Finds A Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It looks like Archie has turned over a new leaf when he befriends a Jewish man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013010000 +0000" stop="20251013013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike's integrity is put to the test when he loses a teaching position to an equally qualified black candidate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013013000 +0000" stop="20251013020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Weighty Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Energetic Justin Quigley inspires Archie to stick with the diet his doctor has recommended.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013020000 +0000" stop="20251013023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Lynde And Nanette Fabray (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Paul Lynde and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/29/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013023000 +0000" stop="20251013030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Lynde And Nanette Fabray (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Paul Lynde and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/29/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013030000 +0000" stop="20251013033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Unwelcome Houseguest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob agrees to take care of Buddy's dog and ends up in the dog house himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013033000 +0000" stop="20251013040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Meershatz Pipe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob gets a bad case of envy when Alan gives Buddy a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013040000 +0000" stop="20251013043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Something Fishy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton don't want to take their wives on a Raccoon fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013043000 +0000" stop="20251013050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Probe 7 - Over And Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The lone survivors of two annihilated worlds find themselves stranded together on a distant and uninhabited planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013050000 +0000" stop="20251013053000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Maria</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A carnival man buys a monkey to use in his act, but the "monkey" doesn't like being used.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013053000 +0000" stop="20251013060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cop For A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two crooks rob a bank messenger but don't manage to make a clean getaway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013060000 +0000" stop="20251013070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Blind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An undercover agent, Hays, assigned to gather evidence against Syndicate head John Lawton is blinded in an explosion. Lawton's lieutenant, Deetrich, and his business advisor, Matula, are rivals, with Matula actually an IMF undercover plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013070000 +0000" stop="20251013080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Middle Of A Heat Wave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>While dating a local woman named Laurel Harper, Kimble breaks off their romantic affair and she angrily storms out of the bar they are in and into the night. The next morning, Laurel is found on an abandoned road unconscious and badly beaten. While she is</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013080000 +0000" stop="20251013090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Victim</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a young girl is raped and the police refuse to prosecute her assailants, she hires private investigator Harry Orwell to help her prove their guilt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013090000 +0000" stop="20251013093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013093000 +0000" stop="20251013100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013100000 +0000" stop="20251013103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 135 -- Arson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In what would prove to be a very busy shift, Malloy and Reed search for a serial arsonist who spawns a copycat, settle a domestic dispute that results from a love triangle, rescue a man who wandered onto the ledge of a high rise and deal with a mentally ill man who is holding his wife at knife-point.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013103000 +0000" stop="20251013110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 46 -- Pilgrimage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Christmas Eve in Los Angeles, and Malloy and Reed track down a suspect who beat and mugged a rescue mission Santa, who later gets arrested himself. They also respond to an alcohol-related traffic accident that resulted in a fatality, help a penniless widow who has been detained for shoplifting and take part in the search for a young Native American child who wandered off into a mountainous area while her parents were asleep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013110000 +0000" stop="20251013120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Merman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony turns into a human to see what life with legs is all about. You know, just like the Little Mermaid."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013120000 +0000" stop="20251013123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prep School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward are excited when they learn that Aunt Martha has made arrangements to send Beaver to a prep school in New England. However, Beaver quickly realizes he will miss his friends as they are all entering Mayfield High School next year. This puts Beaver in a delicate position: how to tell Aunt Martha he doesn't want to go without hurting her feelings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013123000 +0000" stop="20251013130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And The Fraternity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has his mind pretty much made up about going to Ward's alma mater, State University, and he's even considering joining Ward's old fraternity. However, both Eddie and Wally think twice when they hear from a college student that that's the worst fraternity on campus, but Ward has already sent out his letter of recommendation for both of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013130000 +0000" stop="20251013140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Glittering Goldfish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An inventor of a cure for sick fish is charged with the murder of the purchaser of a pet fish store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013140000 +0000" stop="20251013150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Formula  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A young acquaintance of Matlock's asks for his expertise when accused of murder and the theft of a secret formula.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013150000 +0000" stop="20251013160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Loss Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Darnell plans on indicting a teenager for murder after her father is found in the basement and her mother turns up missing. But Gillespie and his men don't believe she is guilty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013160000 +0000" stop="20251013170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Founder's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The town prepares for a Founder's Day Celebration</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013170000 +0000" stop="20251013180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Quint's Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Quint is accused of horse theft and beaten by a group of vigilantes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013180000 +0000" stop="20251013190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>He Was Only Seven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young boy is killed during a bank robbery in Virginia City, Ben and Jamie are determined to hunt down his murderers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013190000 +0000" stop="20251013193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013193000 +0000" stop="20251013200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013200000 +0000" stop="20251013210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Pederson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>"Overwhelmed girl takes on her father's responsibility as man of the house after he passes. She cares for her pregnant mother and 5 sisters and is suspicious of a young drifter who joins the train and pays too much attention to the girls."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013210000 +0000" stop="20251013220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>What's A Nice Girl Like You Doing... (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto travel to San Francisco, where they observe some topnotch women paramedics in action during major rescue missions. An injured worker is stranded on the Golden Gate bridge. Ambulance squads treat a heart attack victim at a dance bar and an epileptic at a coffee shop. A bad driver causes a traffic accident involving an ambulance carrying the heart patient, resulting in his death and five other injuries. Johnny dates a nurse interested in a long-term relationship. Careless workers and deadly chemicals combine to spark an explosive fire at a pier on the Embarcadero."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013220000 +0000" stop="20251013223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That Darn Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger buys a goat, with the intention of getting rich by selling its milk. Then the goat eats the 4077th's $22,340 payroll, leaving paymaster Hawkeye holding the bag. Meanwhile, Charles also thinks he can make a killing when he sees an ancient vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013223000 +0000" stop="20251013230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and her nursing staff are about to be inspected by Col. Bucholz. Meanwhile, Kellye is offended that Hawkeye is attracted to nurses besides her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013230000 +0000" stop="20251013233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Affairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Army tries to get a North Korean pilot to defect, and Charles gets a rude shock when he falls for a French nurse with a Bohemian past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251013233000 +0000" stop="20251014000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Is Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of reminders about Trapper John's skill as a practical joker, B.J. bets Hawkeye he can prank everyone present.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014000000 +0000" stop="20251014003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Punch In The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>In going through some courthouse paperwork, Barney discovers an open case involving Floyd and Charlie Foley. He tries to close the books on the case, but ends up reopening the arguments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014003000 +0000" stop="20251014010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie and his friends decide to start a newspaper. The early issues don't sell well, so the boys begin eavesdropping and printing local gossip in the paper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014010000 +0000" stop="20251014013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra yearns for a peaceful and quiet birthday at home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014013000 +0000" stop="20251014020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>I Love You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra really gets mad when Ray talks about their problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014020000 +0000" stop="20251014023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan blackmails General Burkhalter to keep Klink from being transferred to the Russian front for failing to keep Hogan from blowing up a radio tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014023000 +0000" stop="20251014030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Colonel Klink's Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink suffers at the hands of a tough sergeant sent to discipline prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014030000 +0000" stop="20251014033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Karen Black And Paul Lynde</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Karen Black and Paul Lynde. Originally aired on 03/22/72."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014033000 +0000" stop="20251014043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lover's Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An art critic is found dead in his bedridden wife's bed, yet his wife is nowhere to be found. The woman's caretaker is charged with murder, and it's up to Mason to find the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014043500 +0000" stop="20251014050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The 7th Is Made Up Of Phantoms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Three National Guardsmen explore the site of Custer's Last Stand and begin hearing strange noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014050500 +0000" stop="20251014053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Keep Me Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's desire for company proves disastrous for her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014053500 +0000" stop="20251014060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Beta Delta Gamma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A fraternity beach party takes a grim turn when a practical joke gets out of hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014060500 +0000" stop="20251014070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Sing A Song Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix searches for clues when someone tries to kill a former opera star on the verge of coming out of retirement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014070500 +0000" stop="20251014080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding March</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is asked to find out if a judges fiancé is responsible for him being compromised."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014080500 +0000" stop="20251014090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killin' Cousin, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty is suspected of killing two members of her family by father and son detectives. This was intended to launch a spinoff called Tarkington (named after the father and son).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014090000 +0000" stop="20251014093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014093000 +0000" stop="20251014100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014100000 +0000" stop="20251014103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 85 -- Sign Of The Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed start the shift with a call to a liquor store robbery, where a fellow officer was shot but the owner of the store appears to be lying. Further investigation pushes the owner to admit one of the thieves was his brother and he was trying to protect him. In the meantime, they have a zoning issue with an elderly astrology reader followed by the report of a young boy asking a pharmacist questions about Seconal pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014103000 +0000" stop="20251014110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 175 -- Con Artists</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy respond to a car rollover where a good samaritan makes matters worse. Afterward, they respond to several victims of a well-known family of seasonal home improvement con artists before finally catching them in the act. In the meantime, they search for a disgruntled ex-employee who is trying to sabotage his former workplace, and take a drunk driver off the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014110000 +0000" stop="20251014120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Roughrider State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Teddy Roosevelt makes a man out of Bill in the state that meant the most to him, North Dakota."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014120000 +0000" stop="20251014123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie has been seeing one particular girl, Cindy Andrews, and she wants to give Eddie a birthday gift, so she decides to knit a sweater. She uses Wally as a model and he begins spending so much time at Cindy's he arrouses the suspicions of Julie, Eddie, Lumpy, Beaver and his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014123000 +0000" stop="20251014130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Book Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been assigned to write a book report on 'The Three Musketeers.' However he's waited right down to the wire to get reading and quickly realizes that he'll never get finished. So, he decides to watch the movie that's going to be on TV and write his book report based on the movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014130000 +0000" stop="20251014140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Foot-loose Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Millie Crest assumes another woman's identity after an embezzlement scheme, she ends up stabbing an intruder in self-defense—but, of course, things are not what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014140000 +0000" stop="20251014150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Trail: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Assistant District Attorney Howard Wright is murdered, the attorney general puts Matlock on the case. With Michelle and Conrad's help, Matlock begins to investigate Wright's past, realizing he was spending money he could not have earned legitimately.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014150000 +0000" stop="20251014160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Bubba's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone abandons a baby at Bubba's door.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014160000 +0000" stop="20251014170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Home Front - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John has been appointed to the local draft board</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014170000 +0000" stop="20251014180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Anybody Can Kill A Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of outlaws hire a drifter to do what they couldn't: kill Matt Dillon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014180000 +0000" stop="20251014190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Younger Brothers' Younger Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Joe are jailed as part of the Younger clan after arriving in town to free Hoss, who also was mistaken as a Younger brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014190000 +0000" stop="20251014193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014193000 +0000" stop="20251014200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014200000 +0000" stop="20251014210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hobie Redman Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"When three wagons are late in the desert, Chris sends Duke to find them and bring them to the wagon train as the train cannot wait for them. It may be a suicide mission due to water holes drying up and the missing people's personal issues."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014210000 +0000" stop="20251014220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>What's A Nice Girl Like You Doing... (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto travel to San Francisco, where they observe some topnotch women paramedics in action during major rescue missions. An injured worker is stranded on the Golden Gate bridge. Ambulance squads treat a heart attack victim at a dance bar and an epileptic at a coffee shop. A bad driver causes a traffic accident involving an ambulance carrying the heart patient, resulting in his death and five other injuries. Johnny dates a nurse interested in a long-term relationship. Careless workers and deadly chemicals combine to spark an explosive fire at a pier on the Embarcadero."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014220000 +0000" stop="20251014223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Who Knew?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye volunteers to deliver the eulogy for a dead nurse that he briefly dated, and belatedly discovers her deep feelings for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014223000 +0000" stop="20251014230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombshells</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing the theory that people will believe in anything, Charles and Hawkeye start a rumor that Marilyn Monroe plans to visit the 4077th, which gets everyone excited. Meanwhile, B.J. feels responsible when he's unable to rescue a wounded soldier, and is less than impressed when he is presented with a Bronze Star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014230000 +0000" stop="20251014233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Settling Debts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and the crew surprise Colonel Potter with a party to commemorate Mildred's final payment on the couple's mortgage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251014233000 +0000" stop="20251015000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moon Is Not Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the camp facing prohibition and a severe medical supply shortage during another heat wave, Hawkeye resolves to lift morale by importing a racy new movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015000000 +0000" stop="20251015003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Invisible Beau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee begins to feel that she is preventing Andy and Helen from pursuing their relationship. She then conjures up a beau for herself—trouble is it's the butter and egg man and he's already married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015003000 +0000" stop="20251015010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrest Of The Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney arrest the "fun girls" for speeding. It turns out to be a big mistake because Helen and Thelma Lou become jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015010000 +0000" stop="20251015013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>I Wish I Were Gus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Alda arrives at his favorite uncle's funeral to rekindle a family feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015013000 +0000" stop="20251015020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Standard Deviation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert gives Ray and Debra an IQ test as part of his assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015020000 +0000" stop="20251015023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Top Secret Top Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a top-secret document from Klink's coat to save him from being arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015023000 +0000" stop="20251015030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015030000 +0000" stop="20251015033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bernadette Peters And Cass Elliot</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bernadette Peters and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 11/10/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015033000 +0000" stop="20251015043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fetish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a pin-prick to a voodoo doll seemingly results in a stab wound through the chest, Mason is called to determine a more down-to-Earth cause of death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015043500 +0000" stop="20251015050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ninety Years Without Slumbering</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man fears that he will die if his grandfather clock stops running.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015050500 +0000" stop="20251015053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Can't Be Little Girl All Your Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a woman is attacked, she tries to hide from the incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015053500 +0000" stop="20251015060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Pro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A professional killer tries to retire from his job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015060500 +0000" stop="20251015070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A blind crook and Mannix are both on the trail of some valuable stolen jewels.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015070500 +0000" stop="20251015080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank investigates the death of a gang member, who seems to have been killed by the son of a General and war hero.."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015080500 +0000" stop="20251015090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of men pretending to be Barnaby and J.R. murder a writer employed by a publishing empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015090000 +0000" stop="20251015093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015093000 +0000" stop="20251015100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015100000 +0000" stop="20251015103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 115 -- Gang War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed loses a robbery suspect while in foot pursuit. Afterward, he and Malloy try to help a priest prevent bloodshed between rival hispanic gangs, and then respond to a battered wife whose husband is very familiar to the officers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015103000 +0000" stop="20251015110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 26 -- Lemras</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed drive up on a convenience store robbery in progress, which results in the suspects taking hostages. Later, they pull over a reckless driver who has just committed a heinous crime, learn about a new computer system designed to help them be more productive and finally thwart a group of serial burglars who use motorcycles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015110000 +0000" stop="20251015120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Hitting Pause On Adulting</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015120000 +0000" stop="20251015123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Poor Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward is given two tickets to a baseball game and is faced with an impossible decision. Should he take Wally or Beaver? Beaver lets him off the hook when he announces he has plans with Gilbert. However, when they fall through, Beaver changes his mind about the game and becomes convinced because he's the youngest he gets the short stick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015123000 +0000" stop="20251015130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Don Juan Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A school dance has Beaver with a major dilemma. He has two girls who ask him to go with them. However, he has a little problem, he accepted the first invitation but now wants out of it when he's asked by the second girl. This leads him to take some of Eddie's poor advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015130000 +0000" stop="20251015140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fraudulent Photo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating corruption in a Northport Hospital project, District Attorney Brander Harris is the victim of a setup, resulting in an incriminating photo. When one of the men who may be trying to besmirch Harris's name ends up dead, Harris is charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015140000 +0000" stop="20251015150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Trail: Part 2  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Assistant District Attorney Howard Wright is murdered, the attorney general puts Matlock on the case. With Michelle and Conrad's help, Matlock begins to investigate Wright's past, realizing he was spending money he could not have earned legitimately.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015150000 +0000" stop="20251015160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Home Is Where The Heart Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Maybelle the madam returns to Sparta with her " nieces ".And sets up shop just out of Gillespie's jurisdiction. Her return is not without controversy and soon one of her most vocal critics is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015160000 +0000" stop="20251015170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Home Front - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The family members all seem involved in the war effort</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015170000 +0000" stop="20251015180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Two Of A Kind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt gets caught in the middle of a feud between two immigrants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015180000 +0000" stop="20251015190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Place To Hide</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Donahue is in pursuit of Confederate officer Cody Ransom and his men despite Ben's attempt to arrange a surrender.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015190000 +0000" stop="20251015193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015193000 +0000" stop="20251015200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015200000 +0000" stop="20251015210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Malachi Hobart Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke comes across Malachi Hobart, a preacher who has dedicated his life to his fellow man. However, he soon begins to believe that the preacher is in fact a con artist using religion to swindle people out of their money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015210000 +0000" stop="20251015220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Convention, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gage and DeSoto work their medical magic at a convention in this 2-part feature-length episode of Emergency!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015220000 +0000" stop="20251015223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Run For The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Olympic runner assigned to the 4077th fails to materialize, Father Mulcahy must save the camp's honor in a high-stakes footrace against the 8063rd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015223000 +0000" stop="20251015230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>U.n., The Night And The Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A United Nations delegation tours the 4077th—a Swede, a Hindu and a British officer— and each leaves a lasting effect on the men and women of the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015230000 +0000" stop="20251015233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Bedfellows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th faces a sleepless night as Charles's snoring keeps B.J. and Hawkeye from counting sheep. Meanwhile, Colonel Potter discovers that his son-in-law, Bob Wilson, has had an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251015233000 +0000" stop="20251016000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Say No More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A military strategist refuses to accept responsibility for the war games that have mortally wounded his own son. And Margaret develops laryngitis, as she is about to meet her hero, Dr. Chesler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016000000 +0000" stop="20251016003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Luck Of Newton Monroe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant peddler comes to town (Don Rickles) and sells Barney, Floyd and Goober defective goods. After he disregards Andy's warning, he finds himself in the Mayberry jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016003000 +0000" stop="20251016010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016010000 +0000" stop="20251016013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Look, Don't Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a waitress, catches Ray's eye, he has a lot of explaining to do.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016013000 +0000" stop="20251016020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Frank The Writer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank submits his writing to Ray's editor hoping to get his own column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016020000 +0000" stop="20251016023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Crittendon Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon disrupts Hogan's plan to blow up a tunnel and stop a convoy of rocket fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016023000 +0000" stop="20251016030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Some Of Their Planes Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Germans plan to send their men into England via captured planes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016030000 +0000" stop="20251016033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/15/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016033000 +0000" stop="20251016043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sad Sicilian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After a dispute between Sicilian business partners leads to murder, Mason is enlisted to find the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016043500 +0000" stop="20251016050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ring-a-ding Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A movie star receives a ring from her home town fan club. In it she sees the faces of people she knows telling her she's needed there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016050500 +0000" stop="20251016053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Spy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires a detective to follow his estranged wife, who he believes is seeing another man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016053500 +0000" stop="20251016060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Services Rendered</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting hit on the head, a young man suffers from amnesia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016060500 +0000" stop="20251016070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Madonna</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When an actress is the target of a strange murder attempt, Mannix is called on the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016070500 +0000" stop="20251016080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>To Still The Voice</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is sent to investigate when a black community leader is murdered, just as he was to reveal a wrong doing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016080500 +0000" stop="20251016090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A sportsman's plans for a new life begin with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016090000 +0000" stop="20251016093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016093000 +0000" stop="20251016100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016100000 +0000" stop="20251016103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 155 -- I.a.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Tony Johnson finds out he has been accused of a shakedown just after saving Malloy's life during a shootout. Reed and Malloy set out to find a bar girl named Ginger who Johnson says will prove his innocence, but her story leaves Malloy with an uneasy feeling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016103000 +0000" stop="20251016110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 66 -- The Vandals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy have a gun pulled on them after stopping a car that turns out to be stolen, but the contents of the trunk link the two suspects to an even more sinister crime. Afterward, a recently widowed father and his teenage daughter report that their home has just been toilet papered, which ends up being a prelude for a much more serious incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016110000 +0000" stop="20251016120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Old October</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony reminicse on Octobers of the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016120000 +0000" stop="20251016123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Summer In Alaska</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie is happy to break the news that he plans to spend his summer on a fishing boat in Alaska and this prompts Wally and Lumpy to think about signing up to do the same thing. However, they all get a dose of reality when they discover just what kind of conditions they would be living in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016123000 +0000" stop="20251016130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>It's come down to the final week before junior high school graduation and Beaver is having a ball and even skips a class with Gilbert. However, Beaver becomes convinced he won't graduate after Gilbert and him take a peek at the diplomas on Mrs. Rayburn's desk and find Beaver's diploma to be missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016130000 +0000" stop="20251016140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Romantic Rogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After con man Stacey Chandler and Helen Harvey are married in Vegas, Chandler's former associate and scheming con woman, Irene Wallace, is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016140000 +0000" stop="20251016150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Accident  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of two partners at a law firm is murdered after he is unable to keep a promise to a client, the other attorney is suspected.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016150000 +0000" stop="20251016160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>An Angry Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>First the mother, then the father of two young children are murdered. Althea takes responsibility for the children. The killings appear to be related to a shady trucking firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016160000 +0000" stop="20251016170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Kinfolk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose arrives at the Waltons' home with her grandchildren</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016170000 +0000" stop="20251016180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>I Call Him Wonder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E28</episode-num>
    <desc>The citizens of Dodge refuse to hire a drifter because he's decided to look after an orphaned Indian boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016180000 +0000" stop="20251016190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit To Upright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Complications arise when the Cartwrights purchase a broken-down saloon in Upright, Nevada, which they believe contains a fortune in hidden gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016190000 +0000" stop="20251016193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Town character Brett Conway blackmails Lucas with the knowledge that a young couple Lucas rescued are suffering from yellow fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016193000 +0000" stop="20251016200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Ordeal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When their wagon breaks down, Mark and an injured Lucas are stranded in the desert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016200000 +0000" stop="20251016210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dr. Denker Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The wagon train takes in a terrified young boy who has just seen his father murdered by a bandit gang. While Bill and Flint try to help him recover, embittered Civil War vet Ed Beaufort tells the boy that taking vengeance is the best medicine. Soon a traveling musician, Dr. Denker, joins the wagon train and he and Billy hit it off, but it becomes evident that Billy and the doctor had a prior connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016210000 +0000" stop="20251016220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Convention, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"San Francisco firefighters and paramedics rescue a man. A paramedic convention brings Gage and DeSoto back to San Francisco. While attending a picnic, SF firefighters and paramedics are called back to work for a mutual aid response in Marin County. Gage and DeSoto tag along on a rescue."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016220000 +0000" stop="20251016223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Friends And Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter must deal with an old Army friend who is getting his own soldiers killed through his incompetency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016223000 +0000" stop="20251016230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give And Take</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded GI learns a painful lesson when he forms a recovery room friendship with the enemy soldier he's critically wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016230000 +0000" stop="20251016233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As Time Goes By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and Hawkeye work on a time capsule to commemorate their time in Korea; Rizzo and B.J. goof around with a fake hand grenade; Klinger becomes smitten with a young, pretty Korean war criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251016233000 +0000" stop="20251017000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot Episode</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital (M.A.S.H) unit in Korea, two army doctors by the names of Hawkeye Pierce and Trapper John McIntyre receive some exciting news in the mail. Their Korean house boy, Ho-John got accepted into Hawkeye's old college. Hawkeye and Trapper decide to hold a party filled with music, dancing, and alcohol to raise money for Ho-John's plane trip to the U.S. They achieve this by raffling off a weekend pass with a nurse, Lieutenant Dish for R&amp;R in Tokyo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017000000 +0000" stop="20251017003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie goes to the carnival and blows all his money on a game to win a birthday gift for Andy. The game, however, is rigged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017003000 +0000" stop="20251017010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banjo-playing Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When former carnival man Jerry Miller becomes deputy to Sheriff Taylor, he finds himself jeopardizing Mayberry, making him question his decision to become a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017010000 +0000" stop="20251017013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Your Place Or Mine?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ray's parents stop speaking, Marie moves in with Ray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017013000 +0000" stop="20251017020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>In-laws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ray's in-laws come for a visit, he begs his parents to be nice to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017020000 +0000" stop="20251017023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>D-day At Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan pulls a hoax to get a general to believe Klink is replacing him as chief of staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017023000 +0000" stop="20251017030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017030000 +0000" stop="20251017033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017033000 +0000" stop="20251017043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Murderous Mermaid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After a swimming stunt goes horribly wrong, a young woman is charged with orchestrating the mayhem, and Mason must set the record straight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017043500 +0000" stop="20251017050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>You Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving home one rainy evening, a man accidentally hits a boy on a bicycle. Determined to hide his guilt, the man flees the scene—but his car has other ideas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017050500 +0000" stop="20251017053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Right Kind Of Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A bank robber with a bullet wound receives the wrong medicine from an old pharmacist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017053500 +0000" stop="20251017060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Jury Of Her Peers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A sheriff suspects the wife of a murdered man to be his killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017060500 +0000" stop="20251017070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanks to an old gal-pal, Mannix gets trapped in the middle of a feud between rival smugglers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017070500 +0000" stop="20251017080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017080500 +0000" stop="20251017090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sunday: Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby engages in a game of cat-and-mouse with a murderer who blames him for his jail time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017090000 +0000" stop="20251017093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017093000 +0000" stop="20251017100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017100000 +0000" stop="20251017103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Man Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed, who is an optimist and still has faith in the human race, is subjected to ridicule from Officer Wells after he is swindled twice. On patrol, he and Malloy come to the aid of a woman whose baby has been kidnapped by a heavily armed man seeking a large ransom. Afterward, wells once again questions Reed's judgment during the search for an intoxicated sniper at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017103000 +0000" stop="20251017110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 165 -- Once A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The search for a stabbing suspect leads to a bitter ex-cop who has just moved into the area. Afterward, Malloy and Reed deal with a naive and frustrated starlet who shoots up a telephone booth and loses her suitcase containing a live rattle snake. The officers then become involved in shootout at a train station that leads to another unfortunate run-in with the ex-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017110000 +0000" stop="20251017120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Roller Coasting Along</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony learn about roller coaster design from a real-life roller coaster engineer!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017120000 +0000" stop="20251017123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Practical Joke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie fall prey to Lumpy's practical joking after he plants cherry bombs under the hoods of Eddie's car and Wally's car. Both Eddie and Wally want to get him back but their plan goes awry when they destroy Lumpy's car after chaining it to a tree. All fingers point to Wally after Fred finds that the chain has Ward's name printed on it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017123000 +0000" stop="20251017130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The All-night Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E36</episode-num>
    <desc>After graduation, an all-night party is set to begin, which has June and Ward very wary. They aren't sure if they should allow Wally to attend. Meanwhile, Wally's date for the party has the same problem. This leads her to invite Wally to meet her folks and put their worries to rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017130000 +0000" stop="20251017140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tragic Trophy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hollywood wheeler-dealer is in desperate need of cash and has gotten himself in some trouble with the ladies. But before things can get any worse, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017140000 +0000" stop="20251017150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Celebrity  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a cosmetics mogul accused of murdering an ex-lover in order to keep scandalous photos of herself under wraps.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017150000 +0000" stop="20251017160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Indiscretions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea does not realize that an old friend from Philly is hiding a dark secret, nor does Sweet who has fallen in love with the woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017160000 +0000" stop="20251017170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Diploma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>John has to prove he graduated from high school in order to continue getting contracts and security for government contracts</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017170000 +0000" stop="20251017180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>With A Smile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A powerful rancher's spoiled son gets violent when a pretty girl rebuffs his affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017180000 +0000" stop="20251017190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>One Ace Too Many</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben's evil twin, Bradley Meredith, begins to liquidate the Ponderosa assets while Ben is away on a vacation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017190000 +0000" stop="20251017193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spiked Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is kidnapped as he and Lucas try to protect Banker Hamilton's gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017193000 +0000" stop="20251017200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas makes a life-or-death decision when Micah is held hostage and the kidnappers demand the release of a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017200000 +0000" stop="20251017210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jeff Hartfield Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jeff Hartfield becomes concerned when his sister Jenny begins dating Dallas who threatens him with an orphanage at journey's end. Jeff takes off but Dallas follows with deadly intent, believing Jeff knows the location of $30,000."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017210000 +0000" stop="20251017220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Wedsworth-townsend Act, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Seeing a dire need in the community for on-the spot medical assistance, Roy and John attempt to convince their staunchest opponent, Dr. Brackett, to support paramedic legislation that means getting help to where it's needed most. Martin Miller and Kent McCord of Adam-12 guest star in this thrilling 2-hour pilot movie"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017220000 +0000" stop="20251017223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>To Market, To Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After black marketers hijack the 4077th's supply of hydrocortisone, Hawkeye and Trapper concoct a deal with local black marketer, Charlie Lee, to get some more. The catch: Henry's antique oak desk, which they must trade in order to get the medicine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017223000 +0000" stop="20251017230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Lightweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper and Hawkeye seek to keep a new nurse from being transferred by Hot Lips, and they vie for her affection. Henry Blake, challenged by another commander to a boxing tournament, makes Trapper fight a big, intimidating soldier in exchange for keeping the nurse at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017230000 +0000" stop="20251017233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Chief Surgeon Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Burns complains about Hawkeye Pierce's disrespect, and when Henry appoints Hawkeye chief surgeon, it's to Burns' shock. The rest of the 4077th "coronates" Hawk while Frank and Hot Lips complain to General Barker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251017233000 +0000" stop="20251018000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Baker arrives at the camp with his "moose." Hawkeye decides to find a way of getting her away from Baker. He tries ordering him to release her, tries buying her and then resorts to cheating at cards. He releases her but she won't go, so he tries to teach her how to be independent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018000000 +0000" stop="20251018003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Housekeeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose, the former housekeeper, gets married and Opie is unhappy at her departure. Aunt Bee comes to live with Andy and Opie, and Opie is not exactly thrilled with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018003000 +0000" stop="20251018010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The state police arrogantly ask Andy and Barney to step aside while they search for an escaped convict in Mayberry, believing that the Mayberry sheriff's department is not capable of doing "real" police work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018010000 +0000" stop="20251018013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Win, Lose, Or Draw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray gets tired of being treated like a kid at his father's poker game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018013000 +0000" stop="20251018020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Nemo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is reminded by Debra that their kids are growing up fast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018020000 +0000" stop="20251018023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Funny Thing Happened On The Way To London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winston Chuchill's right-hand man, Group Captain "Robbie" Roberts, is shot down, captured and brought to Stalag 13. The Luftwaffe scheme to assassinate Churchill by keeping Roberts in the cooler while an impostor escapes to England to carry out the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018023000 +0000" stop="20251018030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Casanova Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Burkhalter plans to get Klink to marry his sister, while a Gestapo plant has infiltrated the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018030000 +0000" stop="20251018033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Carol Channing And Steve Lawrence (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Carol Channing and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018033000 +0000" stop="20251018043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Careless Kitten</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman receives a phone call from a man claiming to be her wealthy uncle who disappeared 10 years prior, Mason is called in to investigate. A proposed encounter with the man leads to the discovery of a corpse and soon the niece of the phantom uncle is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018043500 +0000" stop="20251018050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Morrow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Before leaving on a 40-year mission, an astronaut meets a woman and they fall in love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018050500 +0000" stop="20251018053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Silk Petticoat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to remarry after the death of his first wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018053500 +0000" stop="20251018060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Actor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An actor is outraged when another man gets the part he wanted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018060500 +0000" stop="20251018070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>All The Dead Were Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates when a plane crash is followed by murder attempts on the survivors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018070500 +0000" stop="20251018080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stone Seahorse</sub-title>
    <desc>A smuggler is attacked by mobsters interested in learning where he has hidden his booty. He escapes in Raymond Durstin's gallery. He turns to Cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018080500 +0000" stop="20251018090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murdering Class, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a murder at a prep-school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018090000 +0000" stop="20251018093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Brontosaurus Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo has a new love interest, her science teacher. She even gives up baseball to have more time to dream of him.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
