<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307160000 +0000" stop="20260307170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Around The Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Planning to sail to Boston, the Major, Hawks and Charlie are instead shanghaied to New Orleans where they meet a Captain who has different ideas on raising his child and running a ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307170000 +0000" stop="20260307180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jarrod’s client, Jeff Bowden, was convicted of the murder of a priest. Jarrod is convinced of the man’s innocence and sure he can win on appeal. When Bowden escapes during his transfer to prison, Jarrod tries to intervene before he or anyone else gets killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307180000 +0000" stop="20260307190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hootie Kyle is a poor but honest farmer whose credit has run out. Matt Dillon and Festus lend him some money, only to be swindled out of it in a poker game. Later, Hootie gets circumstantially framed for the murder of the card shark who swindled him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307190000 +0000" stop="20260307200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Samuel Bellis is accused of desertion, murder and selling guns to the Indians. Bellis insists that he's innocent, and Candy believes him, but before he can clear Bellis' name, he must elude the Army patrol hot on the fugitive sergeant's heels.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307200000 +0000" stop="20260307203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The High Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes the target of a vengeful mountaineer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307203000 +0000" stop="20260307210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend In Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself the unwilling companion of gunman Carl Avery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307210000 +0000" stop="20260307220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>The Gray Rock Hotel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Stricken with a mysterious illness, the drovers stagger into a deserted town where they are met by a pretty yet strange woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307220000 +0000" stop="20260307223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A British woman, Diana Coulter, hires Paladin to guide her to her brother's ranch in Shiprock, Arizona, where the Comanches are on the warpath.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307223000 +0000" stop="20260307230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Twain Shall Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh allows a newspaper reporter from the east to follow him on a manhunt for a story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307230000 +0000" stop="20260308010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Little Pirates, Hugs And Mugs, Hold That Lion, Punchy Cowpunchers, Who Done It, Outer Space Jitters</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are castaways from a garbage scow who land on Dead Man's Island where everyone is living in olden times.  To escape from the governor, they disguise Curly as a Maharaja and win permission to journey to their own country to fetch presents.  The governor is fooled, but the boys run into more trouble in the den of Black Louie the pirate where Curly is forced into a knife-throwing contest with Larry as the target.  Things look bad until a mis-thrown knife cuts the rope that holds the chandelier and it crashes down on Black Louie's men.  With the pirates defeated, Moe decides to take over as ruler of the island. , The Stooges run a furniture store and come into possession of a stolen pearl necklace.  Three crooked dames convince the boys that the necklace is theirs, and when the real thieves arrive, the Stooges fight to defend the girl's property.  The Stooges defeat the bad guys and the girls decide to go honest and return the necklace to its rightful owner. , The Stooges accompany professor Jones on an expedition to Venus, where they discover that the Venusians are planning to conquer the earth with an army of zombies.  When the boys learn that they're going to be turned into zombies, they escape.  The scene changes to the Stooges apartment where we learn they are just telling a bedtime story to their kids (also played by the Stooges) while they wait for the baby sitter to arrive.  When the baby sitter shows up, she looks like one of the zombies and the boys exit in a hurry. , The Stooges are gypped out of their inheritance by Icabob Slipp, a crooked lawyer.  The boys follow Slipp onto a passenger train and corner him, but not before they accidentally let a lion loose on the train. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are three soldiers assigned to go undercover and spy on an outlaw gang that's terrorizing a nearby town.  The bad guys have the Arizona Kid locked up, so the boys set about rescuing him with the help of beautiful Nell, his girl.  They free the kid, and he rides to summon help.  The Stooges, with the help of Nell, manage to subdue the bad guys before the kid arrives with the cavalry. , The Stooges are private detectives looking for a missing millionaire.  They wander around the millionaire's spooky mansion confronting various crooks and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308010000 +0000" stop="20260308033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Son Of Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wolf Frankenstein, son of Henry Frankenstein, returns with his wife, to his fathers estate to claim his inheritance. When he arrives with his family he recieves a hostile reception from locals. While exploring his fathers laboratory he comes across crooked blacksmith - Ygor, who asks him to revive his father's creation - the MONSTER who is lying in a coma. Wolf tries to revive the monster and believes he fails but then some of the locals are found murdered soon after who just happened to be part of the jury that sent Ygor to the gallows. The villagers immediately connect the killings to Frankenstein and send the inspector to investigate. He discovers the monster is alive and is being used as tool by Ygor. Wolf then in fit of madness shoots Ygor. The then enraged monster losing his only friend kidnaps Wolf's son. In the end Wolf tracks the monster to the lab where he swings down on a chain knocking the monster into a sulpher pit and thus his demise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308033000 +0000" stop="20260308040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Cat's Meow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Using her Voice-Eraser, Catwoman plans to steal the voices of British rock singers staying at the Wayne Manor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308040000 +0000" stop="20260308050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Operation — Annihilate!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk and the Enterprise must combat parasitic aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308050000 +0000" stop="20260308053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted Lighthouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Jimmy Olsen visits his aunt and discovers a group of smugglers on her island home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308053000 +0000" stop="20260308060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Talkative Dummy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Armored cars are robbed and then disappear. A ventriloquist's dummy is used to transmit the armored cars' routes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308060000 +0000" stop="20260308080000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Curse Of Cousin Smith</sub-title>
    <desc>"A person known as ' the thief from outer space' appears in a puff of smoke, will agrees to help him rescue a princess who was lost more than 200 years ago by evil vizier."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308080000 +0000" stop="20260308080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Flight Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Spindrift party encounter an amnesiac Earthling who has been stranded on the planet for some time. However, it soon becomes clear that the newcomer isn't what he claims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308080000 +0000" stop="20260308090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The travelers materialize in 1895 on Devil's Island, where they try to help French captain Alfred Dreyfus escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308090000 +0000" stop="20260307110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Betrayed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>David's personal life threatens his mission when aliens resort to foul play to recover a computer tape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260307110000 +0000" stop="20260308100000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Cub (pilot)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Little Eliza and her parents are headed out west. During a stop, she wanders off and they (unknowingly) leave without her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308100000 +0000" stop="20260308110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Cub (pilot)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Little Eliza and her parents are headed out west. During a stop, she wanders off and they (unknowingly) leave without her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308110000 +0000" stop="20260308113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lair Of The Tiger</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Sariska jungle in Rajasthan, northern India, a family of Bengal tigers have established their home.  Marlin journeys to this distant land to observe the cats in their natural environment."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308113000 +0000" stop="20260308120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Adelie Of Antarctica</sub-title>
    <desc>"The life story of the Adelie penguin, the principal inhabitant of this barren continent at the end of the earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308120000 +0000" stop="20260308123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tigers Of Sariska</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin goes unarmed deep into the jungles of India to film the adventures of a full-grown Bengal tigress and her two young cubs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308123000 +0000" stop="20260308130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Voyage To Raza</sub-title>
    <desc>"Travel with Marlin and his band of adventurers as they explore the Golf of California, the last great unexplored marine paradise in the Western hemisphere, lying between the Mexican main land and Baja, California."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308130000 +0000" stop="20260308133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chincoteaque Roundup</sub-title>
    <desc>"There’s a legend that during the 16th century, Spanish ponies from a sinking galleon swam ashore to the island of Assateague, Virginia.  Today, once a year, men from neighboring Chincoteague Island gather for one of the most unusual roundups."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308133000 +0000" stop="20260308140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lions Of Gir Forest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin travels to Gir Forest in India in search of the king of beasts…the lion."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308140000 +0000" stop="20260308143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Big Little Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby becomes extremely self conscious about his height and tries different ways to make himself "big." When there's a dangerous situation at Sam's Butcher Shop, though, Bobby is exactly the right size to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308143000 +0000" stop="20260308150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Dough Re Mi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg, wanting to make a record, books a recording studio and plans on singing a song with his siblings. However, when Peter's voice begins to change, his hopes of recording are dashed. That is until Greg gets a new idea that just may accommodate Peter's changing voice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308150000 +0000" stop="20260308153000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale gets Jed to back the Beverly Hills Ballet Company, and Jed figures that ballet is the perfect way to keep Granny, who is tired of getting “butler sassed,” among other things, in Beverly Hills. Jed gets her interested in the dance just as Mrs. Drysdale gets the money she needs to save the ballet company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308153000 +0000" stop="20260308160000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny decides to start her own boarding house. The Clampetts put out signs welcoming any incoming boarders and advertising what they offer. When the Drysdale's new butler, Arthur Pinckney, arrives in town he thinks the signs are meant as a welcome for him so he goes to the Clampetts' mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308160000 +0000" stop="20260308163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308163000 +0000" stop="20260308170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy's Bicycle Trip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ricardos and Mertzes pedal their way from Italy to the French Riviera. It's a bumpy ride, thanks (of course) to Lucy, who left her passport in her purse, which she locked in a suitcase, which she sent ahead to their hotel in Nice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308170000 +0000" stop="20260308173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with a black eye and Ward is upset when he learns that Beaver didn't fight back. This leads Ward to teach Beaver how to defend himself. Little does Ward know, the person who punched Beaver is a girl, Violet Rutherford, the daughter of one of Ward's co-workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308173000 +0000" stop="20260308180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets "spelled"</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver's teacher, Miss Canfield, sends a note home with Beaver and the other kids convince him that it's news that he's getting kicked out of school. So Beaver and Wally take steps to hide the note from Ward and June."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308180000 +0000" stop="20260308190000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Bullseye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A recruit in the Women's Army Corps is shot to death on the firing range and Charlie's Angels are assigned to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308190000 +0000" stop="20260308200000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>A New Kind Of High</sub-title>
    <desc>"The mysterious death of a scientist at a Hart-owned chemical company risks exposing a pair of chemists who have created a powerful new hallucinogen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308200000 +0000" stop="20260308210000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Poof, You're A Movie Star / Over The Hill Caper</sub-title>
    <desc>"Attractive Miss Shirley Russell wants to become a movie star. Roarke has arrange everything including a press party to announce the signing of her contract with Arthur Gantman, the Studio Chief, for her new picture, "Wayward Wife." Her co-star is handsome Desmond Vaughn. After a very late date with Desmond, Shirley is awakened at 5 A.M. by Liz Perry, her press agent, and taken to the studio. By 6:00 she is working on her first scene, which requires a dozen takes. She is exhausted, but Liz gives her the day's itinerary -lunch, fan club meeting and another date with Desmond. Shirley is beginning to have her doubts about the movie business. The morning's work is finished and a demolished Shirley is changing for her lunch date with Gantman when Roarke appears with a surprise. Shirley's fiancée, Bill Windsor, has arrived from Omaha to share her fantasy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308210000 +0000" stop="20260308220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>A Dress To Remember</sub-title>
    <desc>"A model goes on a crash diet to fit into a dress, a husband tries to win back his wife, and a father and long-lost daughter end up on the same cruise."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308220000 +0000" stop="20260308223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308223000 +0000" stop="20260308230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Ashley Bevilacqua-berton &amp; Anne Olivares- Drew Barrymore Memorabilia</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ashley &amp; Anne are what you might call Drewbie's-fans and collector's of Drew Barrymore. Their friendship grew out of their love for all things Drew, and has culminated in an online museum which they call the Drewseum. Today, they'll show Lisa some of her most iconic items, including the prom dress she wore in Never Been Kissed and even some personal Christmas items Ashley received from Drew's own production company. Our expert today, Patrick Scott Patterson is also a Drew fan and collector who'll be tasked with appraising the ladies' collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308230000 +0000" stop="20260308233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260308233000 +0000" stop="20260309000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309000000 +0000" stop="20260309003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Archie's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When Archie's brother, Fred, visits Archie to open up a business, he also brings his 18 year old wife, Katherine. Both, Archie and Edith, and even Stephanie, are shocked as they find out. While the new bride and Edith cook supper, Archie and Fred argue about Katherine's age. Before dinner, Fred (and Katherine) leave the Bunker's home, canceling the business. In bed, Edith asks Archie if he were a single 55 year old man, would he go for a young girl. Archie answers no.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309003000 +0000" stop="20260309010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Stephanie's Conversion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Stephanie comes back from Sunday School, Rev. Chong visits Edith to tell her that even though she is welcome anytime at Sunday School, Stephanie is Jewish. Edith accepts it, unlike Archie. Selfishly, Archie decides to change Stephanie's religion but Edith interrupts that it's not his decision. So Edith brings Archie and herself to visit a Rabbi to get more information of the religion. 
Later that night, Stephanie awaits at the porch for the return of Edith and Archie. She and her uncle discuss and he approves that it's her decision and whatever religion she'll be, he'll love her the way he has.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309010000 +0000" stop="20260309013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Gets Fired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When an ill woman tells Edith to let her die with dignity at the SunShine Home, the woman's family are furious after her death. The manager fires Edith for her selfishness, even though Edith honoured the woman's wish. Later that night, the woman's daughter thanks Edith to be with her mother as she passed away since she (the daughter) never got to visit her own mother back then.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309013000 +0000" stop="20260309020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Next Door</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Louise Jefferson returns for a visit at the Bunker's place to ask Edith if she can sell her (Louise's) former house. Edith doubts but Archie makes her agree so that they (mostly he) can choose white people to move in. When Edith sells the house to a couple and she invites the lady to her house, Archie realises that the woman is black and so is her husband. But Archie isn't disturbed when he finds out that the man is a cop, which could be good for Archie's safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309020000 +0000" stop="20260309023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ride-along, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond gains a new respect for his brother, Robert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309023000 +0000" stop="20260309030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Family Bed, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ally, claiming that there are monsters in her room, insists on sleeping in her parent's bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309030000 +0000" stop="20260309033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Foul Weather Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura gets jealous when Rob spends too much time trying to help an old friend break into showbusiness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309033000 +0000" stop="20260309040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Will You Two Be My Wife?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Buddy and Sally discovers Rob's memoir and discover there was a woman before Laura.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309040000 +0000" stop="20260309043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309043000 +0000" stop="20260309050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare At 20,000 Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While aboard a commercial aircraft, a man believes he is seeing a gremlin on its wing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309050000 +0000" stop="20260309060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Look Behind You  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A number of women have been victims of ritualistic murders, and a medical undergraduate thinks she's next.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309060000 +0000" stop="20260309070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Trapped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An $8 million army payroll has been stolen from a base in Southeast Asia by the Stafford family, who are Syndicate drug smugglers. The IMF must recover the money. Jim and Barney steal a Stafford truck and then offer to sell it back to the family if they pay "protection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309070000 +0000" stop="20260309080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Chinese Sunset</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble is working as the "general factotum" in a swank Beverly Hills hotel on Sunset Blvd. An undercover policeman, named Fred Bragin, checks into the hotel to survey Eddie Slade, a notorious mob bookie. When Slade leaves town for a few days to sort out s</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309080000 +0000" stop="20260309090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Kill</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry O runs into a deadly conspiracy when he tries to clear a deaf man charged with arson and murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309090000 +0000" stop="20260309093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309093000 +0000" stop="20260309100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309100000 +0000" stop="20260309103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up One L-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While transporting a burglar to the station with Malloy's assistance, Sgt. MacDonald strikes and kills a jaywalker with his cruiser, but unfortunately all of the witnesses on the sidewalk inexplicably claim she was in the crosswalk. With the burglar unmotivated to testify on MacDonald's behalf, Malloy has to take it upon himself to clear his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309103000 +0000" stop="20260309110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Who Won?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed try to curb a chronic street racing problem by befriending the club leaders and working with a racing promoter to open a legitimate drag strip. Their efforts, along with a highly anticipated race between reed and officer wells, are put in</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309110000 +0000" stop="20260309120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Outhousing</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony sign up to compete in an outhouse race."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309120000 +0000" stop="20260309123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Water, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally and his friends are trying to earn enough money to buy baseball uniforms so they put a plan into action by doing their chores at a slow pace in order to maximize their hourly pay. Meanwhile, Beaver, also wanting to be on the team, begins selling water to his family and neighbors."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309123000 +0000" stop="20260309130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Girl Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver dread attending dance school, so when Wally suddenly takes a liking in it, June and Ward are dumbfounded. It seems Wally has developed a crush on a girl named Penny and Beaver soon feels neglected and left out when Wally begins spending all his time with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309130000 +0000" stop="20260309140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hateful Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Young cop Jimmy Anderson and his veteran partner come across a robbery at the Wilson Plastics Company while on patrol one night. His partner killed in the ensuing shootout, evidence then points to Jimmy as having been an accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309140000 +0000" stop="20260309150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 1  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired by a friend to defend his enlisted son. The boy's been charged with killing a sadistic lieutenant whose mistreatment led to the death of another soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309150000 +0000" stop="20260309160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An opposition leader for Greece is living in exile in Hawaii.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309160000 +0000" stop="20260309170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Conflict - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandpa's sister in law is being forced out of their home by a government project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309170000 +0000" stop="20260309180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Whispering Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After eight years in a prison for robbery, a farmer returns home and hopes to find the stolen fortune he had buried under a tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309180000 +0000" stop="20260309190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Hot Day For A Hanging</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On behalf of his father, Hoss sets out to deliver a large sum of money to the town of Dutchman Flats. Upon his arrival, however, Hoss is arrested by Sheriff Stedman on a charge of bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309190000 +0000" stop="20260309193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Skull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for escape after he's captured by outlaws while seeking help for an injured Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309193000 +0000" stop="20260309200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Queen-to-be of France hides out in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309200000 +0000" stop="20260309210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Juan Ortega Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Juan awakens to the sound of three men hanging his beloved father. Joining the wagon train, he comes across one of the three, tortured by Indians. He nurses him back to health but only under the guise of looking for the other two killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309210000 +0000" stop="20260309220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Unlikely Heirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After John and Roy rescue an elderly transient from a fire, Chet and Marco discover $80,000 in the man's mattress. A bride faints while walking down the aisle. Dixie administers a tetanus shot to a young boy. An elderly woman loses her cat. A plane crashes into a warehouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309220000 +0000" stop="20260309223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Stars And Stripes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friction arises between B.J. and Winchester when they are asked to write an article for a prestigious medical journal on how they saved a soldier's life with a daring operation. Meanwhile, Hot Lips receives an eventful visit from Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309223000 +0000" stop="20260309230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yessir, That's Our Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby born to a Korean woman and an American GI is abandoned at the 4077th. Knowing that Amer-Asian children are often mistreated in Korean society, the troop sets about the frustrating task of finding a new home for the infant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309230000 +0000" stop="20260309233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottle Fatigue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrified by the gigantic size of his monthly bar tab at the officer's club, Hawkeye vows to give up booze for a week. Meanwhile, Winchester desperately tries to halt his sister's impending marriage to a man he considers unworthy of the Winchester heritage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260309233000 +0000" stop="20260310000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heal Thyself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter turns crotchety when he catches the mumps, and his condition is worsened when Winchester gets the same disease and has to be quarantined with him. A temporary replacement surgeon, Newsome, is quickly brought into the 4077th and seems to be a gem in terms of both personality and ability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310000000 +0000" stop="20260310003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>High Noon In Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets hysterical when Andy receives a letter from a man he arrested and sent to prison. The convict is to be released soon and says in the letter that he is coming to settle the score with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310003000 +0000" stop="20260310010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310010000 +0000" stop="20260310013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Good Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra discovers that Marie, likes Robert's girlfriend, Amy, better.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310013000 +0000" stop="20260310020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>T-ball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra brings an "unapproved snack" to Ally's T-ball game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310020000 +0000" stop="20260310023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who Came To Dinner?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan learns his underground contact may be a double agent after he arranges for her to go to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310023000 +0000" stop="20260310030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>No Names Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after Hogan helps a journalist escape from the Germans, an American paper tells of Hogan's operations at his camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310030000 +0000" stop="20260310033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Rita Moreno</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Drum-Out, Sergeant Harvey is dishonorably discharged, but Officer Tim can't do it without fumbling around. Then, in The Pronie, an woman cured from her klutzy behavior meets head on with an accident-prone nurse. Finally, in Stick 'Em Up, Please, a bank robber and bank teller instruct their inexperienced protege, falling in love at the same time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310033000 +0000" stop="20260310043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Petulant Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret was a much younger woman on the make who entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310043500 +0000" stop="20260310050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Kind Of A Stopwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is given a stopwatch that allows him to halt time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310050500 +0000" stop="20260310053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When the husband of an unhappy marriage disappears, the neighbors suspect foul play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310053500 +0000" stop="20260310060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Claus And The Tenth Avenue Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal fresh out of prison takes a job as Santa Claus for the holiday season.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310060500 +0000" stop="20260310070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Winifred, private secretary and lover of the publisher George Diamond, becomes a runaway witness when a woman falls into the sea and drowns after a quarrel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310070500 +0000" stop="20260310080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Perfect Fit For A Frame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon gets hired to protect a girl but when her supposed pursuer is found dead he finds himself charged with murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310080500 +0000" stop="20260310090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On Campus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the supposed suicide of a college professor who had been the victim of his student's pranks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310090000 +0000" stop="20260310093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310093000 +0000" stop="20260310100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310100000 +0000" stop="20260310103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a six-year-old boy who was apparently abducted while walking home from school, and later fear that an elderly witness's wildly inaccurate account may actually pertain to a different crime. They also respond to a barking dog complaint and become suspicious of the dog's owner, mediate a domestic dispute caused by a husband's obsession with watching football, respond to a very creative college prank and pursue armed robbery suspects through a crowded train depot with the aid of a police helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310103000 +0000" stop="20260310110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Wednesday Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed becomes preoccupied with the well being of a friend, an electrical engineer by profession, who has just qualified as a reserve police officer and has the bad luck of drawing Officer Wells as his partner. On patrol, Reed and Malloy help out a group of distrusting young adults who are planning to illegally camp in a public park after a rock concert, pull over a young couple in a stolen car and aid wells and the reservist in the foot chase of a heavily armed man who has been coercing innocent strangers into committing bank robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310110000 +0000" stop="20260310120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Greener Posture</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310120000 +0000" stop="20260310123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Part Time Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After taking an IQ test, Beaver scores the highest in his class and Mrs. Rayburn suggests that it would be best if Beaver went to a special school, where his abilities can be challenged. However, little does anyone know, everything is not as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310123000 +0000" stop="20260310130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors, the Donaldsons, and June sends Beaver over to welcome them with a vase of flowers. However, when Mrs. Donaldson thanks Beaver by kissing him on the cheek, Beaver becomes convinced that Mr. Donaldson will kill him because he let a married woman kiss him, and it's all thanks to Eddie Haskell, who planted that idea in Beaver's mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310130000 +0000" stop="20260310140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dodging Domino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Phil Schuyler is a two-bit songwriter who comes to a bad end on Halloween night. Someone enters his bungalow while Phil is taking a bath and tosses an electric heater into his tub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310140000 +0000" stop="20260310150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 2  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>As the murder case involving the death of a sadistic Army lieutenant progresses, Matlock discovers that the lieutenant and four other officers may have been involved in smuggling drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310150000 +0000" stop="20260310160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Time And Memories</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a lawyer is murdered, his wife becomes the top suspect and McGarrett investigates. However, matters are complicated by the fact that the woman had a relationship with McGarrett, and he jeopardizes his job because of this.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310160000 +0000" stop="20260310170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The First Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Everything seems to go wrong on John-Boy's first day at Boatwright University</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310170000 +0000" stop="20260310180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E09</episode-num>
    <desc>All of Dodge City is suffering from a drought. A rainmaker (Guy Raymond) tries to put an end to it before the town's public well, their last source of water, runs dry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310180000 +0000" stop="20260310190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The First Born</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man comes to town claiming to be Marie's son, Joe is not sure what to think. Could this be his brother, or is it all just a big lie?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310190000 +0000" stop="20260310193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gunfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah has an infamous outlaw, Charlie Gordo, in his jail waiting for the U.S. marshal from Denver to take Gordo to the Yuma prison for hanging. With the arrival of the stage, Micah finds that the lawman has been killed, and he has to look to his friends to defend the jail from Gordo's gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310193000 +0000" stop="20260310200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Quiet Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas' old Army pal settles in North Fork with his deaf daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310200000 +0000" stop="20260310210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jennifer Churchill Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jennifer Churchill, pampered all her life, runs away from a smothering lifestyle and pending marriage to join the wagon train. With bounty hunters on her heels, she finds Flint, a man who she wants but doesn't want her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310210000 +0000" stop="20260310220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>That Time Of Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone gives Roy advice on where to go on vacation. Roy gets dizzy during a fire at a singles club. An instructor is injured during a self-defense class. A man with stomach pains is brought into Rampart. The firemen rescue two hang glider pilots from the face of a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310220000 +0000" stop="20260310223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Old Soldiers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is appointed temporary commander of the 4077th when Colonel Potter rushes off to Tokyo on a mysterious mission. While in command, Hawkeye's main problem is housing a large group of Korean refugees comprised mainly of rambunctious children who need medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310223000 +0000" stop="20260310230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Morale Victory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of their constant complaints about the quality of recreational activities at the 4077th, Colonel Potter appoints Hawkeye and B.J. as the new morale officers. Winchester's morale has already reached a new peak: He's ecstatic about his operation on a wounded soldier, Sheridan, which saved the boy's leg, leaving only "negligible" side effects—less use of his right hand. However, the soldier was a concert pianist before the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310230000 +0000" stop="20260310233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lend A Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Irritated that the 4077th is planning a "surprise" party for him, Hawkeye volunteers to go to the aid of a wounded surgeon at the front. An additional irritant to Hawkeye is the arrival of Dr. Borelli, a wisecracking medical advisor with whom he habitually disagrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260310233000 +0000" stop="20260311000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Cruel World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger redecorates his quarters, but the resultant ridicule he receives drives him to new heights in his efforts to get out of the Army. Meanwhile, the doctors are perplexed by the reaction of an Asian-American war hero who tries to kill himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311000000 +0000" stop="20260311003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311003000 +0000" stop="20260311010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311010000 +0000" stop="20260311013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Traffic School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's students complain that his class causes severe insomnia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311013000 +0000" stop="20260311020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Six Feet Under</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra tries to teach Raymond how to have a "normal" mid-life crisis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311020000 +0000" stop="20260311023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Day In Berlin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. undercover agent helps Hogan and his men get a defecting Nazi officer out of Berlin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311023000 +0000" stop="20260311030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Blue Baron Strike Again?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to throw a party for WW I flying ace Blue Baron in order to find his headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311030000 +0000" stop="20260311033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Career Couple, a career-obsessed couple tries to fit each other into their schedule. Then, in Riddles, Carol gets aggravated when Vicki won't tell her the answer to a riddle. Finally, in Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball tries to teach Mrs. Wiggins how to use an intercom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311033000 +0000" stop="20260311043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dangerous Dowager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Matilda Benson is a tough old broad who rules her children with an iron hand and the promises in her will. When Benson and her brood become involved in a gambling scandal and the death of a nightclub owner, Mason looks into the matriarch's matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311043500 +0000" stop="20260311050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Night Of A Jockey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A dejected jockey wants to be tall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311050500 +0000" stop="20260311053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cheney Vase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A dishonest ex-museum curator uses a forged letter to get close to an elderly woman and her priceless vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311053500 +0000" stop="20260311060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Bullet For Baldwin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Benjamin Stepp turns into a cold-blooded murderer after being fired from his job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311060500 +0000" stop="20260311070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harlequin's Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix searches for Australian sailor Paul Gantry, who is supposedly due to inherit a million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311070500 +0000" stop="20260311080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311080500 +0000" stop="20260311090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The two amateur singers that Barnaby put in jail escape and head for Nashville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311090000 +0000" stop="20260311093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311093000 +0000" stop="20260311100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311100000 +0000" stop="20260311103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Dirt Duel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of purse snatching leads Malloy and Reed to investigate a motorcycle gang. Determined to convince the gang he has not prejudged them, Malloy challenges their leader to a motocross duel at Indian Dunes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311103000 +0000" stop="20260311110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy finds himself attracted to the new girl in the steno pool, and decides to ask her on a date after learning she's Officer Wells' 25-year-old niece. Out on patrol, he and Reed investigate a report of a prowler in a heavily wooded neighborhood, make a deal with a flower vendor before booking him for unpaid tickets, engage in a high-speed pursuit with a green corvette and investigate a suspicious gardener.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311110000 +0000" stop="20260311120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Women's History - Media</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311120000 +0000" stop="20260311123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Haircut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing his lunch money three days in a row, Ward gives Beaver one last chance by letting him handle his haircut money. However, when he loses that too, Beaver decides to give himself a haircut just days before he's scheduled to be an angel in a play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311123000 +0000" stop="20260311130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>June has had it with Wally and Beaver's fighting and demands they make a pact to be nice to one another and do things together. However, when each boy gets an invitation for individual social outings, they each attempt to break the pact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311130000 +0000" stop="20260311140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unsuitable Uncle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An unscrupulous uncle, who is in reality the father of his niece, returns home from the sea seeking money from the sale of oil leases on his land. When the man is found murdered, his shipmate is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311140000 +0000" stop="20260311150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Therapist  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired to defend a popular actor accused of killing the owner of a sex-therapy clinic at which he was staying. Meanwhile, the lawyer also finds himself hounded by a law student looking for a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311150000 +0000" stop="20260311160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Guarnerius Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Shortly after giving a recital, the priceless Guarnerius violin of a visiting Russian virtuoso is stolen. McGarrett must retrieve it before the theft turns into an international incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311160000 +0000" stop="20260311170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Thoroughbred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy and his mule aim to get the Walton family name on a local race's trophy for the first time since Grandpa won the race years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311170000 +0000" stop="20260311180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Stage Stop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc Adams takes up arms to defend a gold shipment from bandits, first during a stagecoach ambush and then at a weigh station. He is aided by a blind man and a wounded man in the battle against the bandits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311180000 +0000" stop="20260311190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Jury</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss faces scorn and accusations of bribery when he refuses to vote with his fellow jurors to convict a man for murder based solely on the testimony of the victim's brother, who witnessed the act on a dark night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311190000 +0000" stop="20260311193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sporting Chance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An Englishman arrives with a custom-made rifle—and a plan to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311193000 +0000" stop="20260311200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Salinas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Banker Hamilton is closing up for the day when Rudy Gray persuades him to stay open for one more transaction—a withdrawal at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311200000 +0000" stop="20260311210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tobias Jones Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Adams allows two stowaways, Tobias Jones and his young friend, Midge, to stay with the train. But Tobias is in trouble because of his drinking, and things get worse when he's accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311210000 +0000" stop="20260311220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Fair Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The crew finds a droopy-eyed hound dog in the station; at an industrial fire, Gage and DeSoto check a secret room for victims; a "therapeutic" argument between a husband and wife keeps getting out of hand; while attempting to rescue two injured workers, Johnny is trapped in a tunnel cave-in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311220000 +0000" stop="20260311223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th can't escape the Korean War, even in its dreams. Exhausted after two days without sleep, members of the 4077th steal away for catnaps and experience dreams that reveal their fears, yearnings and frustrations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311223000 +0000" stop="20260311230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Co-respondent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. finds himself attracted to a famous war correspondent, Aggie O'Shea, who has fallen in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311230000 +0000" stop="20260311233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Back Pay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Angered by the way civilian doctors in the States are profiting from the war, Hawkeye presents the Army with a bill for his medical services. Meanwhile, Charles reluctantly demonstrates American medical practices to three Korean medics, and is on the receiving end of their medical expertise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260311233000 +0000" stop="20260312000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Of Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to some R&amp;R in Tokyo, a North Korean soldier forces Hawkeye to perform an emergency roadside operation on his buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312000000 +0000" stop="20260312003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Spoiled Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Arnold the spoiled kid moves to town, he thinks he can walk all over the townsfolk, including Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312003000 +0000" stop="20260312010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Filling Station Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is accused of being the mysterious crook who's been robbing Wally's filling station. Andy and Barney try to determine his guilt or innocence in a variety of methods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312010000 +0000" stop="20260312013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond and Debra take a walk back in time -- to the very beginning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312013000 +0000" stop="20260312020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray fears that Debra is more interested in the wedding than in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312020000 +0000" stop="20260312023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Colonel Klink Please Stand Up Against The Wall?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When Carter, in disguise as the camp kommandant, is seen near one of Hogan's operations, Klink is threatened with a treason charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312023000 +0000" stop="20260312030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to capture LeBeau, but not before he lets him complete his mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312030000 +0000" stop="20260312033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Swiped Life, A</sub-title>
    <desc>In A Swiped Life, the gang parodies "A Stolen Life" with Carol as Bette Davis' role of twin sisters with opposite personalities who get confused for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312033000 +0000" stop="20260312043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Toy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Selkirk is a major league rotter who wants Claire Allison in the worst way, even though she's dating Dirk Benedict. Selkirk has Dirk's jaw broken and begins sending Claire threatening mail. Then Selkirk is murdered in his beach house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312043500 +0000" stop="20260312050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Living Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is displeased when his wife buys an expensive doll for his step-daughter. He becomes even more displeased when the doll tells him it doesn't like him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312050500 +0000" stop="20260312053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Switch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man buys an alibi so he can murder his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312053500 +0000" stop="20260312060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Got To Have Luck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man holds a woman hostage in her farmhouse while he plans his escape from the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312060500 +0000" stop="20260312070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search For A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires Mannix to locate a dead body. The twist is that the client is the murderer, a contract killer who wants to clean up after himself, and Mannix somehow fits into his scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312070500 +0000" stop="20260312080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Missing At Fl307</sub-title>
    <desc>"An ex-convict boards an airplane in Atlanta for a reunion with his daughter but when the plane lands he's nowhere to be found."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312080500 +0000" stop="20260312090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Inside Man, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An aspiring robber is declared a hero for facing his double-crossing partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312090000 +0000" stop="20260312093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312093000 +0000" stop="20260312100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312100000 +0000" stop="20260312103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Airdrop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While on duty in a rural area, Reed and Malloy request the assistance of the DEA to build a case against the smug pilot of a light plane whom they suspect is involved in a drug smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312103000 +0000" stop="20260312110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lost And Found</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed transport an unconscious 8-year-old boy to Rampart General Hospital and help him and his parents cope with the ordeal. Afterwards, they assist a child welfare hotline operator locate a 15-year-old girl who has intentionally overdosed on pills, and then race to find the boy they brought in earlier after he escapes from the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312110000 +0000" stop="20260312120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Barnstorming Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312120000 +0000" stop="20260312123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfume Salesmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to win a fancy film projector and in order to get it they have to sell 24 bottles of perfume. However, the appalling aroma of the perfume quickly leads to zero sales and has Ward trying to think up a sales gimmick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312123000 +0000" stop="20260312130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubhouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and his friends build a clubhouse, and Beaver wants to join. Although the dues are $1 for 8th graders, Beaver has to come up with $3 in order to join their club. How can Beaver earn the money?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312130000 +0000" stop="20260312140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Stand-in Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Two brothers, one a businessman, one a mobster, at separate times have claimed the same young girl as their daughter. Trouble follows when it is revealed that $100,000 due to the girl via a trust fund has been mishandled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312140000 +0000" stop="20260312150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>People Vs. Matlock  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While defending a union boss (Dan Keaton) accused of murdering a rival, a juror (Harry Craven) comes forward with a bombshell: he claims Matlock paid him off to vote a certain way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312150000 +0000" stop="20260312160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Five-O's efforts to rescue a young boy from kidnappers go wrong when Kono is captured and beaten. An angry McGarrett must work out a way to rescue Kono without further endangering him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312160000 +0000" stop="20260312170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Runaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone in the Walton house is too busy to pay attention Jim Bob so he takes matters into his own hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312170000 +0000" stop="20260312180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Newcomers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lars Karlgren, a Scandinavian immigrant and his teenage son, Petter, find the west even wilder than they had imagined when they settle in Dodge City. Petter gets framed for the murder of a man who was picking a fight with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312180000 +0000" stop="20260312190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Ones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mexican freedom fighters loyal to Benito Juárez take over the Ponderosa, gravely wound Little Joe and force Ben to guide them to a wagon train loaded with gold being smuggled to California by Emperor Maximilian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312190000 +0000" stop="20260312193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Two Ounces Of Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sammy Davis Jr. stars as Tip Corey, son of a man allegedly murdered in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312193000 +0000" stop="20260312200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On the trail Len Richards and his brother, Ab, confront a Lucas McCain look-alike, Earl Bantry and his sidekick K.C. Peters, for slaughtering one of Richards' steers. Bantry kills Ab Richards, and Len wants Micah to arrest Lucas for the murder. More problems ensue because of this "evil twin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312200000 +0000" stop="20260312210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Liam Fitzmorgan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Liam Fitzmorgan has come from Ireland on a mission to kill an informer he believes is traveling with the train. However, his mission is complicated when he falls in love with his target's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312210000 +0000" stop="20260312220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Rules Of Order</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A driver crashes into a pole, injuring two workers. John and Roy are asked to be on a paramedic advisory committee, but they have to put up with everyone's favorite paramedic, Brice. The firemen rescue a stunt climber from the side of a building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312220000 +0000" stop="20260312223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Members of the 4077th share their impressions of war in response to letters from fourth graders in Hawkeye's hometown. Margaret writes about how there are some patients she will never forget, while the Colonel tells of his days as "Hoops."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312223000 +0000" stop="20260312230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cementing Relationships</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A jilted Italian soldier, Corpsman Ignazio De Simone, is smitten by Margaret; Klinger pours a cement floor in the operating room to fight the spread of germs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312230000 +0000" stop="20260312233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Father's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret has trouble pretending she's a chip off the old block when her dad, blood and guts "Howitzer" Al Houlihan, arrives for a visit. Also, Hawkeye fixes up a soldier who repays them with a large side of steak, but the general who it belongs to is really steamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260312233000 +0000" stop="20260313000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Death Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester fulfills a family Christmas tradition but has trouble maintaining the anonymity required to keep it a truly charitable act. Even Klinger lends a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313000000 +0000" stop="20260313003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Discovers America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie doesn't like his new teacher, "Old Lady Crump," because she gives too much homework. Andy comments on the teacher, words which Opie twists in his retelling to Ms. Crump, and she is furious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313003000 +0000" stop="20260313010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darlings Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry is visited by an unusual family from the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313010000 +0000" stop="20260313013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Garage Sale, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray gets upset that Debra doesn't want to have any more children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313013000 +0000" stop="20260313020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Invasion, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond moves his entire family into his parent's house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313020000 +0000" stop="20260313023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to kidnap Burkhalter to trade him for an underground agent but ends up with Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313023000 +0000" stop="20260313030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Who Stole My Copy Of Mein Kampf?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to eliminate a beautiful allied defector who is giving Klink an award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313030000 +0000" stop="20260313033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Strickly For The Birds / Fun In A Drugstore</sub-title>
    <desc>In Strictly for the Birds, Harvey tries to hurray a bird feeding Carol along. Then, in Fun in a Drugstore, Tim gives Harvey the run-around while filling a prescription. Finally, in The Cruise, a hum-drum secretary dreams of a shipboard romance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313033000 +0000" stop="20260313043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spanish Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Jimmy Morrow can't seem to catch a break. Already on probation for car theft, he's charged with stealing a valuable Spanish cross and killing its owner. Mason feels sorry for the kid and decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313043500 +0000" stop="20260313050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man In The Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious guardian helps a tiny community survive after nuclear war destroys much of the Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313050500 +0000" stop="20260313053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Older Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter discovers the truth about the infamous Lizzie Borden murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313053500 +0000" stop="20260313060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Shopping For Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Two retired sales clerks test their theory that people become killers at 92 degrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313060500 +0000" stop="20260313070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Only One Death To A Customer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping three consecutive attempts on his life, Mannix learns that someone has placed a $5,000 bounty on his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313070500 +0000" stop="20260313080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Set-up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is a victim of mistaken identity and later almost killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313080500 +0000" stop="20260313090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Run Away To Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway thinks she committed a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313090000 +0000" stop="20260313093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313093000 +0000" stop="20260313100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313100000 +0000" stop="20260313103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After completing a hazardous driving refresher course, Sgt. MacDonald assigns Malloy and Reed to a nighttime undercover bicycle patrol to test Officer Wells' idea on how to deal with a rash of residential car break-ins. The next day, they pull over a hippie with an obnoxious passenger, and then put their refreshed driving skills to the test when called to a burglary in progress at a new car showroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313103000 +0000" stop="20260313110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Badge Heavy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed puts his reputation on the line when he decides to file a formal complaint against a fellow officer after witnessing him use excessive force. On patrol, he and Malloy search for suspects in two separate robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313110000 +0000" stop="20260313120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Pie Day</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313120000 +0000" stop="20260313123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Short Pants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When June goes on a trip to visit her sister, Peggy, June's Aunt Martha steps in and stays with Ward and the boys. They do their best not to hurt Martha's feelings, but Beaver has the hardest time, when she buys him a suit, knee socks, a cap and short pants and makes him wear the outfit to school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313123000 +0000" stop="20260313130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Crush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has a crush on his teacher, Miss Canfield. When Judy, Whitey and Larry tease him for being a "teacher's pet," Beaver tries to prove them wrong and places a spring snake in her desk. However, Beaver has second thoughts and becomes determined to remove the snake before she finds it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313130000 +0000" stop="20260313140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Weary Watchdog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Della asks Mason for $25,000 to help her friend, Janet Brent, who is being blackmailed by an employee of her husband, who has staged compromising photos of her in a motel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313140000 +0000" stop="20260313150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock goes pro bono to help a troubled young woman accused of murdering her photographer boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313150000 +0000" stop="20260313160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Force Of Waves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A ruthless businessman is blown up in a boat explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313160000 +0000" stop="20260313170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In this episode, John Boy encourages his mother, Olivia's, talent in painting</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313170000 +0000" stop="20260313180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Quaker Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The identity of a criminal is confused with that of Deputy Marshal Thad when a Quaker party rescues the pair from a do-or-die fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313180000 +0000" stop="20260313190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss picks up a mail order bride for a friend, but problems arise when the bride decides she has fallen in love with Hoss and has no interest in her husband to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313190000 +0000" stop="20260313193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark stop on the way to the county fair to deliver a message to Micah, who is on the trail escorting a prisoner scheduled to be hanged. Mark and Lucas recognize the prisoner, Mr. Renolds, as someone who saved Mark's life from a snake bite a few years back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313193000 +0000" stop="20260313200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Tinhorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A professional card player, John Keeler, has set up business in North Fork, but local Jesse Phillips claims that this tinhorn is a cheat. Lucas starts playing poker with Keeler to draw him out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313200000 +0000" stop="20260313210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctor Willoughby Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Concerned by one of the passengers on the wagon train, a woman doctor tries to help even though she's hampered by the fact that everyone shuns her. Later, an indian chief needs doctoring, but he and his tribe don't believe in female medicine men either.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313210000 +0000" stop="20260313220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Exam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy worry about their recertification exams. A fireman's widow keeps calling the station for assistance in minor matters. A TV sports fan experiences shortness of breath. The daughter of the fireman’s widow suffers a serious fall. An accident on a movie set turns deadly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313220000 +0000" stop="20260313223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A War For All Seasons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>On New Year's Eve, the staff looks back on the highlights of 1951: The doctors invent an artificial kidney machine; Mulcahy plants a garden; Margaret takes up knitting; and Klinger and Winchester bet on which baseball team will win the pennant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313223000 +0000" stop="20260313230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Retention Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger is so depressed by news that his ex-wife plans to remarry, he reenlists for an additional six-year stretch. Meanwhile, a male nurse has a gripe against the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313230000 +0000" stop="20260313233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester takes command during Potter's absence; and B.J. and Hawkeye try to convince the Marines to grant a hardship discharge to an immigrant soldier, Private Jost Van Liter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260313233000 +0000" stop="20260314000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Taking The Fifth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye uses a bottle of vintage wine to lure unsuspecting nurses into his den; and Potter tries to secure a different sort of anesthetic when the army threatens to ban a painkiller.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314000000 +0000" stop="20260314003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's English Valet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A tourist from England has to do chores to pay off a fine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314003000 +0000" stop="20260314010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's First Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney uses his life savings of $300 to buy a car, which almost immediately begins to break down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314010000 +0000" stop="20260314013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Driving Frank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides that the kids can't ride with Frank anymore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314013000 +0000" stop="20260314020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sitter, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides to get a babysitter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314020000 +0000" stop="20260314023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Hannibal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and the daughter of a German general try to photograph her father's plans designed to prolong the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314023000 +0000" stop="20260314030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>My Favorite Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A baroness is asked by Klink to get secrets out of Hogan, and he complies by giving her a British agent with phony invasion plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314030000 +0000" stop="20260314033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Oldest Man, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice and Mama go to an elegant restaurant and feel the pressure to put on airs. Then, in The Oldest Man, a bank robber is chased by the Oldest Man in the Wild West.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314033000 +0000" stop="20260314043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dubious Bridegroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason returns to his office late one night and finds an attractive woman climbing into his balcony window. She claims to be Virginia Colfax, the secretary of Ed Garvin, who has an office next door to Mason's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314043500 +0000" stop="20260314050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Simon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After her mean-spirited uncle dies, an old maid inherits the crotchety inventor's estate, with the stipulation that she cares for his latest invention, a robot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314050500 +0000" stop="20260314053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Derelicts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is having monetary problems and his wife has just bought a mink coat. To make matters worse, two bums are blackmailing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314053500 +0000" stop="20260314060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>And So Died Riabouchinska</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist with a very lifelike puppet is accused of a murder at a vaudeville theater.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314060500 +0000" stop="20260314070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Fly, Little One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is asked to clear a psychotherapist charged with murder and robbery, the main witness being an autistic girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314070500 +0000" stop="20260314080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is called in to investigate police corruption by the mayor of a Midwestern town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314080500 +0000" stop="20260314090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Beat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a TV reporter who fakes stories just to get big ratings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260314090000 +0000" stop="20260314093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>He Loves Us, He Loves Us Not</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bradley girls all think handsome crop-duster Steve Elliott is in love with them.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
