<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816023000 +0000" stop="20250816030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Experts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan saves a German radio expert whom the Nazis want to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816030000 +0000" stop="20250816033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and a woman, on opposite sides of a future war, encounter each other in a deserted town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816033000 +0000" stop="20250816043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Festive Felon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy but dying Bebe Brent gives the bulk of her estate to her loyal nurse. Needless to say, this act angers the remainder of the Brent clan and leads to a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816043500 +0000" stop="20250816050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816050500 +0000" stop="20250816053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Morning Of The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman is apprehensive about meeting her future mother-in-law for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816053500 +0000" stop="20250816060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Diamond Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is told he has to retire from his job at the jewelry store where he has worked most of his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816060500 +0000" stop="20250816070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Babe In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After an engineer is shot, Mannix is hired to retrieve important construction plans, which may have been taken by the shooter. This leads Mannix to the discovery that the man led a double life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816070500 +0000" stop="20250816080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Where's Jennifer?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxer Ron Johnson's manager convinces him that he killed a man in a barroom brawl, and uses that control to get the fighter to throw a bout so he can collect a fortune in unfair wages. Johnson's fiancee hires Cannon to dig him out from under.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816080500 +0000" stop="20250816090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A millionaire hires Barnaby to rescue his son from kidnappers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816090000 +0000" stop="20250816093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Billie Jo's First Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate is unhappy when Billie Jo lands a job as secretary to novelist Oliver Fenton, who has written books that are banned in Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816093000 +0000" stop="20250816100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Communication</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The girls want a telephone added to the Shady Rest, but Kate insists that they cannot afford such a luxury.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816100000 +0000" stop="20250816103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Annul That Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Gloria get married, everyone but the two of them want the marriage annulled. Gloria decides she’d like to experience what her new life will be like, and Jed tells her that he’ll show her. When he calls the mansion to tell them to put up the cabin, Granny thinks he got married as well. But when both “couples” come home, Granny, Jethro, and Elly learn that Shorty got married, but Elverna didn’t, and Gloria got married, but Jed didn’t, making Jethro and Granny believe both couples are in a Hollywood marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816103000 +0000" stop="20250816110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Pollution Solution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale is trying to get his money back, while Jed is trying to prevent him from doing so. And Jethro is trying to come up with a way to beat the smog problem. Drysdale sends Jane over to get the money, posing as a guard. When Jed doesn't give it to him, Drysdale tells him what he's got is a drop in the bucket, and only the President could really do anything. Jed returns the money and says he plans to give all his money to the President.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816110000 +0000" stop="20250816113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Service With A Guile, Pitchin’ Woo At The Zoo, Cartoons Ain’t Human</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Bluto stop by Olive's service station., Popeye's four nephews unwillingly sample a plate of spinach and then give their uncle a hard time., Popeye creates his own cartoon idea and casts himself as the hero and Olive as the heroine in a spoof of an old-fashioned melodrama."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816113000 +0000" stop="20250816120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Shutter-bugged Cat, The Shooting Of Dan Mcgoo, Unshrinkable Jerry Mouse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tired of his old experiments failing to catch Jerry, Tom gets an idea to revise one of them., Droopy is Dangerous Dan McGoo who has to win the love of his life from a wolf who wants her for himself., A kitten shows up and Tom wants to get rid of it but Jerry stops him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816120000 +0000" stop="20250816130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hook, Line And Stinker, The Painter And The Pointer, Plumber Of Seville, Termites From Mars, Operation Cold Feet, Jungle Medics, Nautical Nut</sub-title>
    <desc>"A fisherman can't catch anything for hours. He is irate when Woody sits down right next to him and immediately catches fish and attempts to kick Woody off the pier., Andy tries to paint a portrait of his dog, Butch, but it's difficult for Butch to stand still., Hercules noisly fixes the pipes at Carnegie Hall during a performance, falling in love with a female harp player in the process., Woody must fend off termites from Mars who have invaded and are eating his treehouse., At the South Pole, where the Armed Forces are camped for the winter, Chilly tries to steal cans of sardines form the food stores under the watchful eye of dog sentry Smedley., Monkey medics help a lion with a tooth ache., Woody is mistakenly captured and brought aboard a ship, where he pranks the captain and first mate."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816130000 +0000" stop="20250816140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Grey Hare, Mouse Menace, Dog Pounded, Hare Force, Ready Woolen And Able, Bugs Bonnets, Touché And Go</sub-title>
    <desc>"Elmer Fudd asks God when he will finally be able to catch Bugs. , Porky goes to any length to get rid of the mouse living in his house., Tweety stays comfy up inside his nest which is actually right in the middle of a dog yard. Sylvester must try to figure out a way of successfully getting past all the dogs to get to Tweety. , On a cold snowy night, a frozen Bugs gets taken in by a kind old lady and set by the fireplace. , Sam the Sheepdog and Ralph Wolf work together but don't like each other. , Bugs and Elmer Fudd exchange blows when wearing different hats give them different personalities., Pepe LePew believes he has found a female skunk, but she is really a black cat who accidentally got a white stripe painted across her back."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816140000 +0000" stop="20250816150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Juggernaut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone is trying to run settlers off their land, buying some of them out, scaring other away,and even murdering those who refuse to leave. The government sends Jim and Artie in to investigate the situation and to stop whoever is behind this.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816150000 +0000" stop="20250816160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cathy Eckhart Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>One murder begets a second murder while a treacherous journey awaits the wagon train. An unknown scout and Kiowa indians threaten the pass. Now there may be a renegade and murderer in their midst, a situation Adams must resolve before continuing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816160000 +0000" stop="20250816170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Wagonload Of Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barkleys help a Greek immigrant deliver his fruit to San Francisco via wagon after the railroad manager jacks up the freight price to make a windfall profit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816170000 +0000" stop="20250816180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chester's Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E32</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a fishing trip, Chester shoots an Indian who was courting a white teenage girl, whom Matt then tries to save from her ruthless father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816180000 +0000" stop="20250816190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Virginia City Died</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy Coffey and Clem search for an arsonist torching ranches around Virginia City. Clem is devastated to discover that his fiancée, Janie, is a prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816190000 +0000" stop="20250816193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816193000 +0000" stop="20250816200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vaqueros</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While Lucas and Mark are traveling across the Mexican desert they encounter a trio of Mexican bandits. They demand payment from Lucas for crossing "their" desert. Lucas refuses. In retaliation, the three slam Lucas in the throat with his rifle, strip him of all his possessions (including Mark), tie him to a tree and leave him to die of thirst and exposure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816200000 +0000" stop="20250816210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Piney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A cattle baron has lost everything and has filed bankruptcy. He decides to get the money he needs to rebuild his ranch by stealing money from the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816210000 +0000" stop="20250816213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Singer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A cowboy seeks help for his former girlfriend, a dancehall singer, who he says was forced into marriage and is now being held prisoner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816213000 +0000" stop="20250816220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Reckless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Well-known businessman Tate Bradley hires Josh and other bounty hunters to find Tony Egan, who he says killed his son, although the death was ruled an accident. When Randall finds the supposed killer and returns him. Bradley refuses to pay the bounty because Egan is still alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250816220000 +0000" stop="20250817000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Sitter Downers, Cactus Makes Perfect, Gem Of A Jam, Hold That Lion, Squareheads Of The Round Table, All Gummed Up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marriage isn't all bliss as Larry, Moe and Curly find out when they set up house with Corabell, Florabell, and Dorabell. You could call them the Dumbbells. , The Stooges are living with their mother who persuades them its time to leave home and seek their fortune.  After a con man sells them a phony deed to a lost gold mine, the boys head west to find the treasure.  After some mishaps with Curly's gold finding invention, they locate the mine and strike it rich.  When two crooked miners try to take their gold they hole up in an abandoned hotel and, although they get bombarded by dynamite, triumph over the crooks. , The Stooges run a drug store and are about to have their lease taken away by the Flint, the mean old man who owns the place.  When Flint kicks his wife out for being old, the Stooges try to help her by inventing a formula that makes old people young.  Their concoction turns the wife into a beautiful young woman, and Flint offers the boys the store for free if they'll transform him as well.  They agree, but after he swallows the stuff he turns into an infant, and the boys leave on the run. , The Stooges are janitors working in the offices of Doctors Harts, Burns and Belcher.  Some crooks arrive seeking medical attention after their boss has been wounded in a shoot out with the cops.  Mistaken for doctors, the boys are forced to operate on the wounded crook, but instead they accidentally dump him out the window into a passing police car.  The rest of the gang chases them into a storeroom filled with dummies where the cops finally catch the bad guys. , The Stooges are gypped out of their inheritance by Icabob Slipp, a crooked lawyer.  The boys follow Slipp onto a passenger train and corner him, but not before they accidentally let a lion loose on the train. , Set in Elizabethan times, the Stooges decide to help their friend Cedric the Blacksmith win the hand of the fair princess Elaine.  At night the group sneaks into the castle to serenade Elaine, but pick the wrong window and are caught by the King.  Tossed in the dungeon, the boys escape with Cedric's help and manage to foil the plans of the Black Prince who was plotting against the King.  All turns out well when the grateful King allows Cedric to marry Elaine. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817000000 +0000" stop="20250817023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Horror Of Dracula</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jonathan Harker begets the ire of Count Dracula after he accepts a job at the vampire's castle under false pretenses, forcing his colleague Dr. Van Helsing to destroy the predatory villain when he targets Harker's loved ones."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817023000 +0000" stop="20250817030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Ring Around The Riddler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler attempts to control prize fighting by brainwashing the current champ into throwing the next fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817030000 +0000" stop="20250817040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Dagger Of The Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk investigates an experimental facility for holding prisoners and finds a sinister scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817040000 +0000" stop="20250817043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>King For A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jimmy is mistaken for a young king, and the country's ruthless dictator tries to execute him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817043000 +0000" stop="20250817050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Joey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Daily Planet buys a racehorse from Perry White's old friend. But the horse can't race without Alice, the little girl who used to take care of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817050000 +0000" stop="20250817060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Sky Is Falling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting family of aliens, called Taurons, have decided to use the Robinson's planet as a new colony. Although the Robinsons cannot understand the language of the visiting family, they welcome them to live in peace and harmony. However, as usual, Dr. Smith causes problems when he panics and draws a gun on the alien family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817060000 +0000" stop="20250817070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Monster's Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview battles a giant spider monster while retrieving explosive fuel cylinders from a wrecked nuclear sub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817070000 +0000" stop="20250817080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Inside Rail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitzhugh comes up with a foolproof betting system to win at the tracks. However, when he convinces a giant hobo to help him place his bets, the local criminals become suspicious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817080000 +0000" stop="20250817090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Long Knives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>In 19th-century India, Tony and Doug join forces with Rudyard Kipling to forestall an uprising by mountain tribesmen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817090000 +0000" stop="20250817100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Summit Meeting: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rising levels of radiation threaten Earth, but the aliens may have the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817100000 +0000" stop="20250817110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Redemption Of Ben</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams may be buried alive by a rock avalanche and Ben the Grizzly may never see home or be the same,after a traveling circus owner catches him and treats him with cruelty. Will these 2 friends survive to see each other again?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817110000 +0000" stop="20250817113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bobcat Kingdom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim observe a family of bobcats in the Zion Canyon area in the Utah wilderness."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817113000 +0000" stop="20250817120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Mysteries Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"Many mysteries of the wild present a challenge to seek the answer. In this episode Jim Fowler brings to the viewer some of the most memorable scenes ever captured on film."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817120000 +0000" stop="20250817123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit South Africa to study and photograph the chacma baboons in their natural environment and to conduct some fascinating experiments."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817123000 +0000" stop="20250817130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"The chacma baboon has many homes.  Marlin and Jim explore all of ‘chacma country’ from the lush coastal areas to the semi-desert interiors of South Africa."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817130000 +0000" stop="20250817133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Whale</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim spend weeks traversing the Southern California Coast in search of a whale."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817133000 +0000" stop="20250817140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Killers Of The Rupununi</sub-title>
    <desc>"Deep in the interior of British Guiana roam the big cats of South America…the jaguar, cougar, margay, ocelot and the jaguarundi. Marlin and Jim journey by canoe and horseback to get a closer look at these killer cats in action."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817140000 +0000" stop="20250817143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Greg's Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After he and his teammates swipe a rival school's mascot in retaliation for theirs being stolen first, Greg is tasked with watching Raquel, a goat. Things get out of control when Raquel proves to be hard to handle, easy to feed and not easy to catch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817143000 +0000" stop="20250817150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Today, I Am A Freshman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>It's the beginning of another school year, and Marcia panics about becoming a freshman, going as far as pretending to be sick. However, after Mike and Carol see through her act, they insist she'd enjoy school if she were involved in extracurricular activities. Marcia then proceeds to join every group or club available. Meanwhile, Peter tries to build a model volcano on the patio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817150000 +0000" stop="20250817153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>R.o.t.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie is named R.O.T.C. squad leader but has trouble controlling his squad. After several warnings to obey his commands, he puts them all on report.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817153000 +0000" stop="20250817160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Laverne And Shirley Go To Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>In hopes of becoming a medical assistant, Shirley enrolls in night school and drags Laverne with her. There, they get mixed up with a nutty professor and accidentally destroy a skeleton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817160000 +0000" stop="20250817163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817163000 +0000" stop="20250817170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Charm School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>It's time for charm school for Lucy and Ethel when their men eye a pretty woman at a party. But Ricky and Fred are anything but charmed by the results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817170000 +0000" stop="20250817173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Plays Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver find themselves tardy for the third time this week and decide to skip altogether. However, they quickly find themselves caught when they accidentally walk on the set of a live TV show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817173000 +0000" stop="20250817180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A new school year has the bus service being extended to those students living in town. However, after not even a week, Beaver gets suspended from riding the bus after getting into a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817180000 +0000" stop="20250817183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Starts To School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May enrolls at a finishing school and her clothes start a fashion trend among the rich girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817183000 +0000" stop="20250817190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro's Graduation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is very excited about graduating from the sixth grade. But in order to prevent embarrassment, Mrs. Potts gets help from Drysdale and Diana to get Jethro to miss his sixth grade graduation. She schemes to turn Jed and Jethro’s watches back 45 minutes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817190000 +0000" stop="20250817193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Meet The Meteor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A huge meteor lands on the island, causing everything nearby to age very rapidly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817193000 +0000" stop="20250817200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Man With A Net</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lord Beasley Waterford, a famous butterfly collector, lands on the island searching for the world's rarest butterfly, the pussycat swallowtail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817200000 +0000" stop="20250817203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Educating Mama  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Bubba enrolls in night school, the family convinces Mama to join him and earn her high school equivalency diploma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817203000 +0000" stop="20250817210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Pomp And Circumstance  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A disappointed Bubba refuses to go to his graduation when he learns his parents will not be there. And Mama, the valedictorian and speaker for the commencement, refuses to go without him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817210000 +0000" stop="20250817220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Isaac's Teacher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Isaac hides from his high-school teacher; a man tries to please his seal; a wife who thinks she's dying wants to choose her successor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817220000 +0000" stop="20250817223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817223000 +0000" stop="20250817230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Ozzie Cicchetti- He-man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ozzie Cichetti is the master of the collecting universe, and he has an incredible He-Man collection to prove it, featuring rare gift sets, prototypes, a ginormous and still working Eternia playset, and more. Lisa Whelchel and expert John Ragusa explore Ozzie’s collection, and John presents a trade to Ozzie with a tempting MOTU rarity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817230000 +0000" stop="20250817233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Adam's Ribs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sick and tired of having liver and fish for an 11-day stretch, Hawkeye, driven near to insanity, starts a riot in the mess tent. He and Trapper then orders spare ribs and sauce from his favorite barbecue joint—in Chicago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250817233000 +0000" stop="20250818000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Full Rich Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye records a letter to his dad, detailing the exploits of a mad Turkish soldier who calls Hawkeye a "damn good Joe," the unfortunate loss of the corpse of a Luxembourg soldier (who turns out not to be dead), Lt. Henri-Batiste LeClerc and a gun-happy officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818000000 +0000" stop="20250818003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Longest Kiss (part 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie returns from his sorry adventure -he got sidetracked to a podiatrists' convention in Rochester- to find his friends and family celebrating his return with kissing contests,Hula Hoops, and ballroom dancing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818003000 +0000" stop="20250818010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After an accident on the loading dock brings Archie within inches of his life,he suddenly becomes a devout-if somewhat hypocritical- churchgoer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818010000 +0000" stop="20250818013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>George And Archie Make A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>George Jefferson seeks Archie's help when he runs for local political office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818013000 +0000" stop="20250818020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Contract</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Irene and the Jeffersons bail the Bunkers out after Archie buys two thousand dollars worth of aluminum siding from a fast-talking saleman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818020000 +0000" stop="20250818023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Debbie Reynolds And John Davidson</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Debbie Reynolds and John Davidson. Originally aired on 11/30/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818023000 +0000" stop="20250818030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Edward Villella And Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Edward Villella and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 10/06/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818030000 +0000" stop="20250818033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Talk To The Snail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The gang quits when they think Alan is going to let one of them go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818033000 +0000" stop="20250818040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Day In The Life Of Alan Brady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>For a documentary, Alan Brady stages an event with Rob to make himself look good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818040000 +0000" stop="20250818043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818043000 +0000" stop="20250818053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The New Exhibit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The curator of a murderers' row in a soon-to-be-defunct wax museum persuades the owner to let him keep the figures at his home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818053000 +0000" stop="20250818060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Relative Value</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man schemes to become the sole heir to his rich uncle's estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818060000 +0000" stop="20250818070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Kitara (aka The Bigot)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When government forces in a racist African country capture the leader of its resistance movement, the IMF devise a plan to manipulate the security official task with interrogating the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818070000 +0000" stop="20250818080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Gets Hit In The Mouth Sometime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a truck driver for a small freight company, Kimble discovers that his angry and bitter boss, Gus Hendrick, is being blackmailed by Lucia Mayfield, the wife of his late business partner, into paying her bills and for child support since Mr</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818080000 +0000" stop="20250818090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Reflections</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell plots a dangerous course to rescue his ex-wife from a storm of blackmail and murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818090000 +0000" stop="20250818093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818093000 +0000" stop="20250818100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818100000 +0000" stop="20250818103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. MacDonald is suffering a marital crisis and turns to Malloy for advice. On today's patrol, a female cashier is taken hostage inside a grocery store by a couple of trigger-happy robbers who attempt to escape on the roof, and an elderly woman turns up missing from her retirement home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818103000 +0000" stop="20250818110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Beware  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed join forces with Sgt. Gloria Tyler to search for a rapist who attacks teen girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818110000 +0000" stop="20250818120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Fools Of The Road</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill teaches Toony the rules of the road so he can get his driver's license."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818120000 +0000" stop="20250818123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Glamour Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is shocked to learn that the glamorous Kitty Bannerman is visiting Mayfield and he's afraid that she will find out that he's not the rich hot shot that he told her he was in the letters that he had sent her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818123000 +0000" stop="20250818130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Chuckie's New Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor gives Wally the responsibility of taking her son, Chuckie, down to the shoe store to pick out a pair of shoes. However, when Wally gives the job to Beaver, Beaver finds himself searching for Chuckie, who has gotten himself lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818130000 +0000" stop="20250818140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Moth-eaten Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Restaurateur Morey Allen, a friend of Mason and Della's, contacts Mason after his waitress, Dixie Dayton, is struck by a car while fleeing the restaurant after spotting a man stalking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818140000 +0000" stop="20250818150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Priest  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends when a mobster is accused of murdering a priest. It doesn't take long before Matlock suspects that the Church is covering something up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818150000 +0000" stop="20250818160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Racial tensions run high when a married white woman has an affair with a black businessman from New York. Meanwhile Virgil is not happy when the Chief enlists his aid in tracking down Bubba's cousin, a suspected moonshiner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818160000 +0000" stop="20250818170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The First Casualty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>GW Haines is in the army</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818170000 +0000" stop="20250818180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A military prison escapee shows up in Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818180000 +0000" stop="20250818190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights discover that their friend, Dusty Rhoades, has taken in a young boy whose father was a slain rainmaker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818190000 +0000" stop="20250818193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>First Wages</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to find out why Mark has taken a job as a stableboy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818193000 +0000" stop="20250818200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sheer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and Milly are held prisoner in her general store when two gunmen attempt a daring robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818200000 +0000" stop="20250818210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bleymier Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Heed the signs! Or so says Samuel Bleymier. When the rain won't stop, a splintered group of the wagon train has to travel through a Sioux indian burial ground. That may have consequences all its own but what of the signs?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818210000 +0000" stop="20250818220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Right At Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Brackett rides along with a fire department helicopter crew. A boy causes trouble for the paramedics when he and his father are rescued after their camper has overturned in a canyon. Dr. Early treats a boy with spinal meningitis. The firemen rescue a man from a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818220000 +0000" stop="20250818223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Dogs And Servicemen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A local dog bites Radar, and the camp conducts a search to find the pooch so that Radar doesn't have to undergo a series of painful rabies vaccinations. Hawkeye defies Frank, to take care of a GI who's suffering from a case of hysterical paralysis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818223000 +0000" stop="20250818230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Charles Lamb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A Greek Colonel thanks the 4077th by giving them food and drink for an Easter celebration. But the feast is foiled when softhearted Radar saves the main course from the spit—a lamb, which Radar tricks Henry into giving a medical discharge and sends home to Ottumwa, Iowa. Thus, Hawkeye and Trapper invent the famed Spam Lamb!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818230000 +0000" stop="20250818233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp is under fire and is swamped with wounded. They are being attacked by their own artillery in a frightening "friendly fire" incident. After Trapper and Margaret get trapped in the supply tent together, Frank's jealousy of Trapper drives him to propose to Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250818233000 +0000" stop="20250819000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bulletin Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Camp activities include Henry's nervous delivery of a sex lecture, with Hawkeye and Trapper heckling, a Shirley Temple movie and a cookout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819000000 +0000" stop="20250819003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Warden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Mayberry jail is filled to capacity with a group of moonshiners who blame Otis for their capture, Andy takes Otis home to serve his term.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819003000 +0000" stop="20250819010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The County Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Simpson, the county nurse, wants to get all of the farmers in the county to take their innoculations. Figuring everyone will follow suit if she can just get Rafe Hollister to do it, she enlists the help of Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819010000 +0000" stop="20250819013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Opal Clampett are continuing to stay at the Clampett mansion, and Elly and Jethro are more than happy to serve them. But Granny isn’t impressed by Jake at all, and isn’t even sure if Jake is related to Jed. Jethro and Elly both decide they want to get into the movie business, and the two get help from Jake and Opal. Jethro turns into a Marlon Brando-type and Elly fancies herself a glamorous movie star, taking the name Venus Adore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819013000 +0000" stop="20250819020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Safety Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph has an accident on his way to receiving his Safest Bus Driver Award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819020000 +0000" stop="20250819023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An English traitor, who could pass for Colonel Crittendon's twin brother, parachutes into camp with information for Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819023000 +0000" stop="20250819030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan becomes convinced that Crittendon can't fool Hitler, things get complicated when Chitterly escapes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819030000 +0000" stop="20250819033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A plane lands safely, but all its passengers, pilot and crew are missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819033000 +0000" stop="20250819043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Devious Delinquent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a crook double-crosses his partner and ends up dead, Mason must maintain the man's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819043500 +0000" stop="20250819050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819050500 +0000" stop="20250819053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Right Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A burglar bargains with his victim when he discovers robbery will not be very profitable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819053500 +0000" stop="20250819060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Take Care Of You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A used car salesman is driven to murder by his big-spending wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819060500 +0000" stop="20250819070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is in search of a businessman who disappeared without a trace. Then a second disappearance happens, and this time the culprit leaves a tape recorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819070500 +0000" stop="20250819080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819080500 +0000" stop="20250819090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Frame For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. attempts to save his reputation when he's framed for rape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819090000 +0000" stop="20250819093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819093000 +0000" stop="20250819100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819100000 +0000" stop="20250819103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>X-force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed lead a house-to-house search for a missing six-year-old girl, and what Malloy does after discovering the horrible things that have happened to her could short-circuit his career ambitions. Meanwhile, they come to the aid of a man who's gotten stuck in a storm sewer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819103000 +0000" stop="20250819110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol</sub-title>
    <desc>"A drunk's antics appear harmless at first; a stakeout uncovers a cash stash."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819110000 +0000" stop="20250819120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>This Old Car</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill fixes up an antique automobile and takes Toony to a classic car show."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819120000 +0000" stop="20250819123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Kenneth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While at a parent's meeting, June leans from Miss Landers that someone has been stealing in Beaver's class. So far a baseball glove, a lunch box and a baseball cap were heisted. Later, June makes a shocking discovery; she finds the stolen items under Beaver's bed. This leaves June and Ward wondering if they're raising a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819123000 +0000" stop="20250819130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Accordian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An advertisement in the mail for a free tryout of an accordion has Beaver sneaking around behind Ward's back. After rescuing the flyer from the trash, Beaver sends it in and indeed gets an accordion that he quickly finds hard to hide from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819130000 +0000" stop="20250819140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baited Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert Dawson confronts Albert Tydings, his partner, about $80,000 missing from Carol Stanley's trust account. Tydings admits he embezzled the money and blackmails Dawson into keeping quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819140000 +0000" stop="20250819150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Judge  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock accepts the pro bono case of Kevin Meredith, a young man accused of murdering his lover, who, as Matlock discovers, had a shocking secret. In order to capture the real killer, Matlock must end a long-time friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819150000 +0000" stop="20250819160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Spot: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil refuses to let go of a grudge against a wealthy former classmate who cheated him out of a scholarship. The man has promised city leaders that he will move his business to Sparta, but not all of his business interests are legal. The nephew of an old friend of Gillespie's finds his life in danger after he steals drugs stored in the businessman's mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819160000 +0000" stop="20250819170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Drucilla's Pond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Soldiers practice war at Drusilla's pond</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819170000 +0000" stop="20250819180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A snake-oil pitchman hatches a scheme to swindle the citizens of Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819180000 +0000" stop="20250819190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Weary Willies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cartwrights discover the trouble Civil War veterans are having trying to resume their former lives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819190000 +0000" stop="20250819193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stand-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two prison wagon drivers stop at the McCain ranch looking for whiskey. Lucas turns them down because they are escorting Rudy Croft, a murderer who is to be hanged in Yuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819193000 +0000" stop="20250819200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark goes to work for Will Temple, a badly scarred and very mysterious rancher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819200000 +0000" stop="20250819210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Colter Craven Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Craven feels he can't perform surgery any longer. When he joins the wagon train and his services are desperately needed, he realizes he may be wrong after Major Adams gives him a history lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819210000 +0000" stop="20250819220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl On The Balance Beam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl is in a rush to go to the Olympics. The firemen rescue an actress trapped on a high wire at a studio, extricate a drunk driver from his car and attend to a burning train carrying ammonium nitrate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819220000 +0000" stop="20250819223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Consultant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Borelli visits the 4077th to demonstrate his artery transplant technique. Unfortunately, being so close to the front at the 4077th causes Borelli's drinking problem to interfere at the worst time—when a patient needs the transplant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819223000 +0000" stop="20250819230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>House Arrest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye hits Major Burns and Houlihan is a witness. Despite Hawkeye and Trapper's claims that it wasn't intentional, Frank makes allegations against Hawkeye, and he is put in house arrest facing court martial. A female colonel is sent to inspect the nurses. When she cries "Rape!" when Burns visits her tent, Houlihan recants her story, and Burns, not Hawkeye, ends up under house arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819230000 +0000" stop="20250819233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Aid Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye, Houlihan and Klinger go to an aid station at the front. Working closely together under heavy fire and unsanitary medical conditions, the three return to camp with new found respect for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250819233000 +0000" stop="20250820000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love And Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper prevent a GI from marrying a call girl who has TB, while trying to help a Korean soldier join his pregnant wife. Radar, of course, provides his usual invaluable help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820000000 +0000" stop="20250820003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Barney In The Big City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying in Raleigh, Barney believes he is witnessing a man casing the hotel clientelle. Barney is right in believing a crime about to be committed, but he is tailing the house detective and has hooked up with the real crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820003000 +0000" stop="20250820010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Bells For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Clara convinces Aunt Bee that Andy won't be able to find a wife as long as she's around, Aunt Bee begins searching for a man whom she can marry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820010000 +0000" stop="20250820013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Comes Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly shows Granny an article about an old school mate getting engaged after having a coming out party. Granny tells Jed about this, and the clan decides to give Elly May a coming out party. Drysdale isn’t happy about hearing this, especially the spare-no-expense part and seeing the Clampetts’ country decorations. Drysdale decides to get someone to help with the task so the Clampetts don’t embarrass themselves, getting his wife to tend to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820013000 +0000" stop="20250820020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820020000 +0000" stop="20250820023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Masterpiece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that the kommandant is a great painter so the prisoners can meet an underground contact at an art gallery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820023000 +0000" stop="20250820030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gestapo Takeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo takes over Stalag 13, planning to send Klink and Schultz to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820030000 +0000" stop="20250820033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Shelter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nuclear attack appears imminent, several suburban friends and neighbors fight over control of a single bomb shelter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820033000 +0000" stop="20250820043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bouncing Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An insurance policy, an untimely death and a plot of land surround a murder and a suspect who may be innocent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820043500 +0000" stop="20250820050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820050500 +0000" stop="20250820053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Avon Emeralds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A Scotland Yard detective is assigned to tail a woman and prevent her from smuggling jewels out of England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820053500 +0000" stop="20250820060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kind Waitress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A waitress and her boyfriend plan the death of an elderly rich guest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820060500 +0000" stop="20250820070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is convinced that the man who is intending to kill Ken Mitchell is his own partner, Paul Anders. Yet the whole thing becomes muddled when Ken confesses that Anders is a fictitious character he came up with only for tax purposes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820070500 +0000" stop="20250820080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>General O'Hara, now a mercenary, hires Cannon to find his brother's killer. But the mercenary knows more than he's admitting, and Cannon finds himself in someone's cross hairs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820080500 +0000" stop="20250820090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Stages Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's former drama coach asks her to look into a series of unexplained events that are scaring a young actress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820090000 +0000" stop="20250820093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820093000 +0000" stop="20250820100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820100000 +0000" stop="20250820103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Credit Risk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After his wife's credit card is turned down attempting to buy a washing machine, an irate Reed begins a long and painful process with his bank to get his credit rating corrected. Out on patrol, he and Malloy investigate a parking lot hit-and-run accident based on the victim's recollection of the perpetrator's license plate number, search for two runaways who steal camping gear from a store's basement and make a rare mistake after responding to a liquor store robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820103000 +0000" stop="20250820110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>During their Christmas Eve Patrol, Malloy and Reed contemplate using their patrol car to deliver a Christmas tree to the residents of a soon-to-be-closed retirement home. Meanwhile, an elderly man's bagpipe playing is considered a public nuisance, a couple of teenagers steal a delivery truck containing radioactive material, a nervous man is desperate to cover up the smell of perfume on his clothing and an armed robbery suspect becomes intent on committing suicide-by-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820110000 +0000" stop="20250820120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Free State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit Maryland on the next stop of Toon in With Me's "Trekkin' All 50" tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820120000 +0000" stop="20250820123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward's Uncle Billy arrives in Mayfield for a visit and begins telling Wally and Beaver exaggerated stories. Not realizing this, Beaver expects Billy to come through after promising Beaver a fishing reel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820123000 +0000" stop="20250820130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's latest girlfriend is Julie Foster, who just happens to be the daughter of a Mr. Foster, who teaches English. Meanwhile, at school, a new semester lands Wally in Mr. Foster's class and he quickly finds himself feeling uncomfortable—especially after Eddie tells him that his relationship with Julie will determine his grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820130000 +0000" stop="20250820140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fan-dancer's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After witnessing an automobile accident, Mason comes to represent the driver of the vehicle, an exotic dancer charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820140000 +0000" stop="20250820150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Affair (aka The Maid)  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents a maid accused of killing her employer at the request of the man's widow. The request is a little odd, but it seems the widow wants everyone to know exactly what kind of man her husband was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820150000 +0000" stop="20250820160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Spot: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An angry Gillespie seeks answers when an old friend is shot. And Virgil narrowly escapes death after trying to ascertain the real reason behind an old adversary's return to Sparta. Nan finds herself in danger after she finds out the truth about her new love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820160000 +0000" stop="20250820170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob meets a boy who is on his way to join the Air Corps, but the boy never actually leaves</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820170000 +0000" stop="20250820180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A suspected horse thief tries to survive in the wilderness when he gets hurt fleeing from his pursuers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820180000 +0000" stop="20250820190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Wagon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After he is arrested by a sheriff for no reason, Hoss escapes from a prison wagon along with a woman whom he believes to be innocent, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820190000 +0000" stop="20250820193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Corey Hazlett insists he's innocent of murder, despite Lucas's eyewitness testimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820193000 +0000" stop="20250820200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to dissuade a latter-day knight from rushing into battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820200000 +0000" stop="20250820210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jane Hawkins Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"We're out of beef!" says Charlie to Flint. Heading to the nearest town to buy some, he finds a girl who's been shot. He brings her into town with him for medical attention, but the local doctor there says he should have left her out on the range to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820210000 +0000" stop="20250820220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Involvement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Rampart's former Emergency! department head nurse tries to commit suicide; she is brought to Rampart, where she befriends a paraplegic child who almost drowned in a swimming pool. Also: a woman wrapped in plastic, a family suffering from carbon monoxide poisoning and a man pinned under a tank truck containing volatile fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820220000 +0000" stop="20250820223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820223000 +0000" stop="20250820230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820230000 +0000" stop="20250820233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250820233000 +0000" stop="20250821000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Abyssinia, Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry finally gets his discharge. While he is tying things up, Burns prepares for his new command. Henry bids a tearful adieu, but not before Klinger turns up in an outrageous tropical outfit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821000000 +0000" stop="20250821003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Every time Andy tries to be alone with Mary, Barney shows up. After Andy explains that he wants to be alone with her, Barney believes that Andy is planning to propose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821003000 +0000" stop="20250821010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bookie Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A bookie from Raleigh sets himself up in Floyd's barbershop as an extra barber, trying to avoid the heat. Andy gets suspicious when the new barber has the same three clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821010000 +0000" stop="20250821013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Garden Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale is having a garden party and tells the Clampetts not to attend. However, they misunderstand and think she wants them to come. Jane and Drysdale try to stop them, but when they say how they still want to go, Jane arranges for them to have society clothes. When they arrive at the party, Mrs. Drysdale sends them back next door to handle the overflow crowd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821013000 +0000" stop="20250821020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Alice And The Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and Nortons visit the Wedemeyers and the wives believe their husbands are neglecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821020000 +0000" stop="20250821023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Schultz lets his new power as camp kommandant go to his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821023000 +0000" stop="20250821030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Eight O'clock And All Is Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan finds that a new prisoner is a German spy right after he tells the man all about their secret operations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821030000 +0000" stop="20250821033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Passersby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A Confederate soldier and a widower meet during the end of the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821033000 +0000" stop="20250821043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Badgered Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When two brothers inherit their father's chain of department stores, disagreement abounds and leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821043500 +0000" stop="20250821050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821050500 +0000" stop="20250821053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Cheap Is Cheap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A miserly man is appalled to discover his wife is planning to spend his life's savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821053500 +0000" stop="20250821060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Waxwork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter decides to stay overnight in the Murderers' Den of a wax museum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821060500 +0000" stop="20250821070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A power struggle between two crime lords may erupt into war with Mannix standing in the middle. After arranging a secret reunion between the lords, the son of one of them is shot to death and Mannix is blamed for the ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821070500 +0000" stop="20250821080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stone Seahorse</sub-title>
    <desc>A smuggler is attacked by mobsters interested in learning where he has hidden his booty. He escapes in Raymond Durstin's gallery. He turns to Cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821080500 +0000" stop="20250821090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R.'s old flame asks him to protect her from her desperate ex-husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821090000 +0000" stop="20250821093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821093000 +0000" stop="20250821100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Parolee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon retrace a 14-year-old investigation to determine whether charges can be brought against a man up for parole.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821100000 +0000" stop="20250821103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While paying a visit to the laundromat before going into work, Malloy encounters a man using the facilities to dry something much different from clothing. On patrol, he and Reed deal with a minister-in-training who uses a very unorthodox method to get his message across, try to reunite a Finnish-speaking child with her family, mediate a strange dispute between feuding neighbors and engage in a high-speed chase with a well known drug dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821103000 +0000" stop="20250821110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>G.t.a.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate a large car theft operation that targets older cars, then stages them around the city as abandoned vehicles so they can be towed and scrapped. Meanwhile, they try to figure out why the son of Malloy's girlfriend is getting bad grades, search for a suspect who robbed an elderly woman and attempt to rescue two foolish teenagers who enter a house that is being fumigated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821110000 +0000" stop="20250821120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Forever Young</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill discovers the wonders of anti-aging!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821120000 +0000" stop="20250821123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting Ward to become a millionaire, Beaver buys him a book called "I Became a Millionaire in Twelve Months." Ward thanks him for it but Beaver quickly learns that Ward is just being polite as to spare his feelings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821123000 +0000" stop="20250821130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After revealing that he wants to be a writer when he grows up, Ward buys Beaver a diary to practice writing and Beaver begins keeping a record of his daily activities. However, June and Ward pick the lock and sneak a peek at his diary after Beaver neglects to come home on time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821130000 +0000" stop="20250821140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Demure Defendant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Nadine Marshall lives with her Uncle Martin and Captain Hugo. She comes home excited one day with the news of her engagement to John Locke. When she tells her uncle, he shows her disquieting papers about her family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821140000 +0000" stop="20250821150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Boy  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Hating his mother's new boyfriend, Tony Morgen kills the man and frames his mother. Matlock takes the case to prove the woman's innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821150000 +0000" stop="20250821160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Necessary Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In this humorous episode Virgil and the Chief arrest a man for bigamy. It soon becomes a polygamy case after an endless parade of wives come to visit their husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821160000 +0000" stop="20250821170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Children's Carol - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas approaches, Mary Ellen and the baby leave to be near Curt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821170000 +0000" stop="20250821180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Call Me Dodie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt meets a girl who ran away from an orphanage that functions like a prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821180000 +0000" stop="20250821190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Power Of Life And Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and Joe play a game of cat and mouse when they chase a man who shot a colonel through the desert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821190000 +0000" stop="20250821193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Honest Abe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Able Lincoln's claim that he's the Great Emancipator himself amuses everyone except Matt Yorty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821193000 +0000" stop="20250821200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogarty is Lucas's main roadblock as he tries to get young Woody Fogarty to attend school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821200000 +0000" stop="20250821210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy O'hara Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Gabe Henry and his son have been sorely missing the female touch for more than five years now. Finding a wife during a stopover is his top priority, but his choice is known to Major Adams, who does not approve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821210000 +0000" stop="20250821220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Above And Beyond... Nearly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John receive commendations for bravery, but they can't remember the incident. A 94-year-old man breaks his ankle while dancing. Dr. Brackett treats a man who passed out in a dentist's chair. An injured mountaineer is stranded on a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821220000 +0000" stop="20250821223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp. On the way back, BJ is introduced to the Korean War.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821223000 +0000" stop="20250821230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821230000 +0000" stop="20250821233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Command</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank settles in as commanding officer, only to have a new one appointed over his head, one that, to his chagrin, fits in very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250821233000 +0000" stop="20250822000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>It Happened One Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It happened one night: freezing cold, an artillery barrage that's coming too close, a patient going downhill and Frank's searching Hot Lips' tent for his letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822000000 +0000" stop="20250822003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy On Trial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A news mogul swears revenge on Andy after he is arrested for what he deems a minor infraction. In retaliation, he sends a reporter to Mayberry to dig up whatever dirt she can on Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822003000 +0000" stop="20250822010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Virgil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to help out his visiting cousin, Virgil. When Virgil makes one too many mistakes, Barney rails against him and storms out. Leave it to Andy to put things right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822010000 +0000" stop="20250822013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Gypsy's Warning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale hires two gypsies, Narda and Yerko, to scare the Clampetts away. Granny is afraid that the gypsies will try to steal Jethro away. But the gypsies have another plan, after they hear how much the Clampetts have. They try to trick the Clampetts to get some of their fortune, as well as get money out of the Drysdales.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822013000 +0000" stop="20250822020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Bensonhurst Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph gets into an argument at the pool hall and has to fight a big guy at the gym. He arranges it so that he can pretend to knock out a bigger man and make the other one scared. Instead he knocks out a stranger, regaining his confidence to go ahead with the fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822020000 +0000" stop="20250822023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cook A German Goose By Radar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A new prisoner in a corporal's uniform turns out to be a general with a mission for Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822023000 +0000" stop="20250822030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It's Dynamite</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A dynamite truck, which Hogan plans on hi-jacking, deviates from its planned route.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822030000 +0000" stop="20250822033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Game Of Pool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Championship pool player Fats Brown returns from the grave for one last game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822033000 +0000" stop="20250822043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wednesday Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Released from prison after serving a sentence for the murder of his employer, Phillip maintains his innocence and may do something reckless to prove it. But it isn't long before Phillip is again arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822043500 +0000" stop="20250822050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822050500 +0000" stop="20250822053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Impossible Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's dream comes true when she witnesses a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822053500 +0000" stop="20250822060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Banquo's Chair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A suspected murderer is put through a little hoax by Scotland Yard to make him confess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822060500 +0000" stop="20250822070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Walk In The Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tom Farnon is in a tight spot: When he wants to catch his wife, Linda, with her lover on his yacht, a shot rings out and Linda falls dead overboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822070500 +0000" stop="20250822080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bobby Loved Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon delivers a ransom, but the deal goes bad and Cannon winds up with no memory of the event, kidnappers on his trail, and people willing to exploit his lack of memory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822080500 +0000" stop="20250822090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Memory Of A Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's escort is killed in a car crash, leaving her with partial amnesia and on suspicion of drunken driving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250822090000 +0000" stop="20250822093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
