<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920170000 +0000" stop="20250920180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Crooked Mile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's whip-wielding father does not approve of her romance with Quint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920180000 +0000" stop="20250920190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Bushwhacked!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe is found shot in the back and delirious by a pair of cowboys roaming the prairie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920190000 +0000" stop="20250920193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of A Young Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is forced to give refuge to Will Fulton, a young bank robber who was injured while saving Mark's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920193000 +0000" stop="20250920200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920200000 +0000" stop="20250920210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Damon's Road: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After escaping from the railroad builder, Favor attempts to get his drovers back, but they are set on being railroaders. Favor must hatch a scheme to get his men back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920210000 +0000" stop="20250920213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Teacher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin defends a schoolmistress who's being theatened for teaching about war crimes that took place during the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920213000 +0000" stop="20250920220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Gang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After being arrested for a minor offense, Josh is put on the chain gang and put to work on the local mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250920220000 +0000" stop="20250921000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Mummy's Dummies, Dopey Dicks, Don't Throw That Knife, Cuckoo On A Choo Choo, Blunder Boys, Studio Stoops</sub-title>
    <desc>"Set in ancient Egypt, the Stooges run a used chariot lot where they unload defective chariots on unsuspecting customers.  When they gyp the head of the palace guard, they're brought to the palace to be executed, but instead become royal chamberlains after curing the King's toothache.  When they recover some tax money stolen by a corrupt official, the King rewards them with marriage to his daughter.  After getting a look at the ugly crone, Moe and Larry select Shemp to be the groom. , It's mindless fun at its best when the Stooges meet a mad scientist in search of a human brain for his headless mechanical man.  , The Stooges are hired by a movie studio as publicity men.  Their first assignment is to get publicity for Dolly Devore, a pretty starlet.  They fake a kidnapping, but the cops won't believe their story.  Then the girl is really kidnapped and the Stooges must come to the rescue.  Shemp winds up hanging out a tenth story window on an extending telephone. , The Stooges become census takers and wind up in the apartment of a lady whose husband is both jealous and a knife thrower.  When the husband arrives home, the boys try to hide, but are discovered, and after dodging some knives, leave on the run. , Larry and Shemp are living in a stolen railroad car.  Larry wants to marry his girlfriend, but she won't consent until Shemp marries her sister.  Shemp however, is constantly drunk and in love with "Carry", an imaginary giant canary.  Moe is an investigator from the railroad, sent to discover how the car was stolen from a moving train.  Moe is also in love with Shemp's girl.  Shemp winds up with both women, but still prefers his imaginary canary. , A parody of the television series Dragnet. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921000000 +0000" stop="20250921023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Tarantula</sub-title>
    <desc>"This classic science fiction film featuring Academy Award winning screen legend Clint Eastwood tells the story of a scientist who, while researching the effects of a new synthetic nutrient, releases a giant spider in the American Southwest.  A quintessential exercise in pulp horror, "Tarantula" is the drive-in, monster flick that still thrills and chills. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921023000 +0000" stop="20250921030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em The Axe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An explosion renders Batman and Robin unconscious and believed dead by the Riddler. When the Dynamic Duo comes to, it's up to Robin to sneak into the museum and stop the plot to raid an ancient sarcophagus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921030000 +0000" stop="20250921040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Conscience Of The King</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk is one of the last survivors who can identify a mass killer lurking among a Shakespearean troupe aboard the Enterprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921040000 +0000" stop="20250921043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Dagger Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Clark and Lois are umpires in a treasure hunt on Dagger Island. One of the heirs is ruthless in his quest and endangers the rest of the party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921043000 +0000" stop="20250921050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Blackmail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Inspector Henderson pretends to take a bribe so he can catch a crime boss. Superman intervenes to clear the cop's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921050000 +0000" stop="20250921060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Keeper: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Keeper, played by Michael Rennie, is a zookeeper of sorts. He wants to take the children and add them to his collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921060000 +0000" stop="20250921070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Werewolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Volcanic radioactivity turns a scientist into a werewolf who threatens the Seaview. Meanwhile, Nelson and Crane attempt to snuff out the volcanic island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921070000 +0000" stop="20250921080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Every Dog Needs A Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clipper is injured by a giant dog, the Earthlings must take him to a pet store owner, but his employee isn't so sympathetic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921080000 +0000" stop="20250921090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Idol Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1519, Tony and Doug vow to slow down Cortez's conquest of Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921090000 +0000" stop="20250921100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Believers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The aliens plot to eliminate Vincent once and for all, attacking a group of "believers".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921100000 +0000" stop="20250921110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Home Of The Hawk</sub-title>
    <desc>"A wagon falls on the leg of a settler,"Metcalf". He and his daughter are assisted by Adams,who lets them stay with him. She likes all the animals, mainly a hawk and the next day,despite her dad's warning,goes out exploring on her own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921110000 +0000" stop="20250921113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Roundup On The Rupununi</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin travels to Guyana to join Stan Brock in a cattle drive.  Soon they are aware of a jaguar marauding the herd.  There is only one thing to do if the drive is to continue … catch the jaguar."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921113000 +0000" stop="20250921120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cougar Mountain</sub-title>
    <desc>"High in the Rocky Mountains a puma and here three cubs end their first summer together.  Soon snow falls and the animals begin their annual trek down to a lower valley."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921120000 +0000" stop="20250921123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Beneath Kilimanjaro</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beneath Kilimanjaro lies the Amboseli Game Reserve, last refuge for the remnants of the great cattle and wild animal herds that once roamed east Africa.  Marlin and Jim seek a way for coexistence of the animals in the Amboseli."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921123000 +0000" stop="20250921130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Leopards Of Sawai Madipur</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rajastan India lies in an ancient, deserted castle.  This is the story of a family of leopards who now occupy this castle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921130000 +0000" stop="20250921133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Arctic Adventure</sub-title>
    <desc>"A trip to the top of the world … above the Arctic Circle, north of Hudson Bay for a polar bear hunt and a walrus capture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921133000 +0000" stop="20250921140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Lightning</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mother cheetah leads her playful cubs over the vast Rhodesian veldt teaching them the ways of defense and hunting."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921140000 +0000" stop="20250921143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Career Fever</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg writes a class paper about wanting to become an architect like his dad. Mike reads the paper and is ecstatic and encouraging, but is Greg's heart really in it?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921143000 +0000" stop="20250921150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>To Move Or Not To Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>With constant complaints about the size of the house bombarding Mike and Carol, Mike puts the house up for sale and looks into buying a new one. It isn't long after that that the house appears to be haunted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921150000 +0000" stop="20250921153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Kiss Me Sickly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie asks Richie to watch after his girl, Denise, while he's out of town at a demolition derby. Denise, upon hearing what Fonzie's asked Richie to do, decides to test Richie's trustworthiness. Richie succumbs to temptation and makes out with Denise at Inspiriation Point, later finding out that she has mononucleosis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921153000 +0000" stop="20250921160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Hi, Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Just when Laverne and Shirley thought they'd have some peace and quiet, look who moves into the building—Lenny and Squiggy are their new second-floor neighbors!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921160000 +0000" stop="20250921163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Song Festers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's singing voice surprises everyone, especially Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921163000 +0000" stop="20250921170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ricky And Fred Are Tv Fans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>With Ricky and Fred glued to a TV fight, their wives go to the local cafe, where service is so slow that Lucy makes change for herself at the cash register and the girls are arrested. They finally prove their innocence and get home to husbands who didn't know they were gone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921170000 +0000" stop="20250921173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Marine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward comes down hard on Wally after he comes home two hours late, this fuels June and Ward's suspicions that Wally is contemplating joining the Merchant Marines. June had discovered some pamphlets hidden in his dresser drawer. However, little does anyone know, Wally has been getting the information for Lumpy who's seriously thinking of joining.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921173000 +0000" stop="20250921180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Versus Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a new girl in his class and is instantly smitten. He begins walking her home from school but he soon realizes that the girl has an agenda on her mind. Her sole purpose is to get close to Beaver in order to get close to Wally. This leads Beaver to accuse Wally of stealing his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921180000 +0000" stop="20250921183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girls From Grun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finish dining with their Grunion, a surfer boy and a girl, and tell the captives they will let them go. Jethro wants to keep his captured girl, but Jed let’s the two go. At the bank, Drysdale, who tells Helen she must take the blame for his stupid mistakes, decides to get his former secretary back. Helen goes to the beach to try to get Jane back, and finds out the Clampetts still believe Grunion are people, a poor excuse, but people nonetheless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921183000 +0000" stop="20250921190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly, The Secretary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts receive a telegram that says Louellen Aden is coming out to California. When Jed tells Jethro about this, they figure out that she wants to marry Jethro. He gets scared and runs away. Meanwhile, Elly is learning to be a secretary, but is not very good at it. She and Miss Jane go to bring Louellen to the Clampett mansion, and the family learns that she has changed into a lovely young lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921190000 +0000" stop="20250921193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Seer Gilligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan discovers an island bush that produces seeds that when eaten give a person the ability to read the minds of others.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921193000 +0000" stop="20250921200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Love Me, Love My Skipper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Howell's plan a party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921200000 +0000" stop="20250921203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Now Hear This  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Vint installs baby-monitoring intercoms in the house, the Harpers begin eavesdropping on each other—and it isn't long before everyone is upset!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921203000 +0000" stop="20250921210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Tri-state's Most Wanted  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama believes she's fallen for a wanted criminal, she decides to capture him herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921210000 +0000" stop="20250921220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>I Don't Play Anymore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gopher thinks he recognizes a woman; a pianist debates ending his retirement; a man tries to claim workers' compensation for insanity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921220000 +0000" stop="20250921223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921223000 +0000" stop="20250921230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Jeremy Beaver- Hip Hop Memorabilia</sub-title>
    <desc>"Music producer and collector, Jeremy Beaver, started the National Hip Hop Museum to share the culture and history of hip-hop with America, and now he’s sharing it with Collector’s Call, including the turntables that started it all, DJ Kool Herc’s equipment used to invent the genre in 1973, and a collection from the legendary Sugarhill Gang, introduced by member, Master Gee himself. Expert and music historian, JayQuan, attempts a trade with a record-breaking record of his own."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921230000 +0000" stop="20250921233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250921233000 +0000" stop="20250922000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922000000 +0000" stop="20250922003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Pains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike must decide if he wants to be in the delivery room during the birth of the baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922003000 +0000" stop="20250922010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Chain Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's refusal to particpate in a chain letter triggers a string of unlikely events.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922010000 +0000" stop="20250922013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Faces Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike becomes the sole support of a growing family when Gloria loses her job because of her pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922013000 +0000" stop="20250922020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Breaks Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie feels abandoned after Edith begins to volunteer part-time at the Sunshine Home for the Elderly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922020000 +0000" stop="20250922023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Cass Elliot And Pat Paulsen</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Cass Elliot and Pat Paulsen. Originally aired on 09/21/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922023000 +0000" stop="20250922030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 10/12/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922030000 +0000" stop="20250922033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sally And The Lab Technician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura sets Sally up with a shy cousin and a disastrous dinner date ensues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922033000 +0000" stop="20250922040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Washington Vs. The Bunny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob has the worst dilemma: choose to travel on business or see his son's school play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922040000 +0000" stop="20250922043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Ralph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, after making a suggestion at work, is laid off. Alice decides to take a job as a secretary, but tells her boss that Ralph is her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922043000 +0000" stop="20250922053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Bard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An untalented would-be writer's career takes off when the ghost of William Sharespeare writes his script.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922053000 +0000" stop="20250922060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Moral Theft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate man tries to save his company from bankruptcy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922060000 +0000" stop="20250922070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>A Ghost Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Howard Bainbridge, a chemical warfare expert who defected to the East, was contaminated by his own experiments and then returned back to the U.S. and his family manor, where his father (a paranoid arch-conservative) had him killed and the body buried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922070000 +0000" stop="20250922080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man Picked A Lemon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a ranch hand on a California citrus farm, the owner, Leland Hagerman, suddenly dies in an accident and the man's racist and sadistic son, Blaine, arrives to stake his claim to the place and sees everyone as expendable, including Kimble wh</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922080000 +0000" stop="20250922090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Past Imperfect</sub-title>
    <desc>"Private investigator Harry Orwell helps a young woman save the life she has made for herself from a ruthless man out of her past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922090000 +0000" stop="20250922093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922093000 +0000" stop="20250922100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A purse-snatching dog? This is the case Friday and Gannon must solve. Making things more difficult, victims give different descriptions of the four-legged thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922100000 +0000" stop="20250922103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922103000 +0000" stop="20250922110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 63 -- Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's wife is in the hospital expecting their first child, and Reed soon regrets his decision to report for work as usual. Out on patrol, they encounter a drunken man directing traffic, chase down a robbery suspect, investigate the theft of money from washing machines and become involved in a minor traffic accident that results in a major delay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922110000 +0000" stop="20250922120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Fall Equinox</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922120000 +0000" stop="20250922123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Yard Birds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward doesn't take any excuses when he puts his foot down and demands that Wally and Beaver clean the yard. They each reluctantly cancel their plans with Richard and Eddie and get to work but soon find themselves with distractions. This causes them to miss the deadline to call the hauler who is suppose to take all the yard waste away and this leads them to pay Eddie and Lumpy to take care of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922123000 +0000" stop="20250922130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tennis, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally finds himself smack dab in the middle of a lover's quarrel when a woman tries to make her estranged boyfriend jealous by continually making tennis dates with Wally. Wally finds himself in an awkward position when the boyfriend threatens him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922130000 +0000" stop="20250922140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Terrified Typist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>While a woman is searching the office of the South African Diamond Company, George Baxter enters to meet Walter Lumis and Duane Jefferson. He notices things in disarray and tries to question the woman, but she makes her escape and seeks out Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922140000 +0000" stop="20250922150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Nowhere To Turn: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends himself against a murder charge after a judge who issued him a contempt citation is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922150000 +0000" stop="20250922160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie is kidnapped and Virgil believes that Tom Dugan is involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922160000 +0000" stop="20250922170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Illusion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Verdie Foster's daughter Esther returns to the mountain. After graduating with honors from college, she cannot find a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922170000 +0000" stop="20250922180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Six years after her husband's hanging, Ma Stone plots her revenge against Matt Dillon by first kidnapping Kitty to use as a lure and then jailing Matt with the intention to hang him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922180000 +0000" stop="20250922190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Rock-a-bye Hoss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is reluctantly made to judge a contest for the most beautiful baby in Virginia City.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922190000 +0000" stop="20250922193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922193000 +0000" stop="20250922200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922200000 +0000" stop="20250922210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Chalice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>"An Italian immigrant couple needs help in transporting water for their grapevines to California. Unfortunately, the two men who offer the use of their wagon plan to steal the treasure they've heard the immigrants are carrying in return for their services."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922210000 +0000" stop="20250922220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Firehouse Quintet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Station 51 basketball team qualifies for the semi-finals. The paramedics rescue victims at a gas explosion. While at basketball practice, the firemen treat an injured gymnast. The night before the big game the firemen get very little sleep: they respond to a number of emergencies, including a workman trapped at a studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922220000 +0000" stop="20250922223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922223000 +0000" stop="20250922230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922230000 +0000" stop="20250922233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250922233000 +0000" stop="20250923000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923000000 +0000" stop="20250923003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923003000 +0000" stop="20250923010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923010000 +0000" stop="20250923013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Corn Pone Picassos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mrs. Drysdale buys a statue named "Ecstasy," which is nothing but a huge pile of metal scraps, the Clampetts decide to get involved in art to help their neighbor in the contest she is entering. Jed and Jethro buy an authentic Rembrandt, a Sam Rembrandt, and Granny uses her artist cousin as influence to paint Mrs. Drysdale a for-sure winner, thinking the statue she bought has no chance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923013000 +0000" stop="20250923020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, Civilian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sgt. Carter orders him to take a furlough, Gomer becomes a civilian employee at the base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923020000 +0000" stop="20250923023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Assassin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon interferes as Hogan tries to help a defecting scientist, whom they were ordered to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923023000 +0000" stop="20250923030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cupid Comes To Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps Klink fall in love with General Burkhalter's sister to get his mind off not being promoted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923030000 +0000" stop="20250923033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll And Art Carney</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll and Art Carney. Originally aired on 01/04/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923033000 +0000" stop="20250923043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Betrayed Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A recently widowed women becomes tangled in a web of suspicion when she hastily remarries a fortune-hunting Frenchman. When the Frenchman's ex-wife comes looking for him, he turns up shot dead in a swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923043500 +0000" stop="20250923050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Person Or Persons Unknown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man wakes up one morning to discover that no one knows who he is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923050500 +0000" stop="20250923053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Contest For Aaron Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man devotes his entire stay at a summer camp to modeling a one-armed clay knight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923053500 +0000" stop="20250923060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Five-forty-eight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A philandering senior manager finds himself being stalked by a previous secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923060500 +0000" stop="20250923070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to help break up a narcotics ring, Peggy is recruited to pose as a prostitute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923070500 +0000" stop="20250923080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is called in to investigate police corruption by the mayor of a Midwestern town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923080500 +0000" stop="20250923090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Indoctrination Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>While on the search for a missing girl, Betty uncovers a center for white slavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923090000 +0000" stop="20250923093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Pyramid Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A female con-artist uses an evangelistic approach to lure buyers into her pyramid scheme. The Bunco division can't charge her with false advertising, so they prosecute her for operating a lottery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923093000 +0000" stop="20250923100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Police Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate a scam involving a phony LAPD newsletter, which comes with a card for subscribers entitling the bearer to preferential treatment from the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923100000 +0000" stop="20250923103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 93 -- Once A Junkie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former convict and informant who Malloy helped give a second chance is accused of assaulting a priest, dealing drugs and stealing a gun after being fired from his dish-washing job at Duke's Longhorn Café. Malloy and Reed set out to determine if his story, which is full of suspicious coincidences, is actually true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923103000 +0000" stop="20250923110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 123 -- Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed feels a strong sense of accomplishment when he stumbles upon a large stash of narcotics as he secures a residence after executing a traffic warrant with Malloy and Officer Ed Wells. He's in for a rude awakening at the trial, however, when he's cross examined by the defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923110000 +0000" stop="20250923120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Believe Your Brain!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Prepare to have your mind blown, as Bill reveals common shared false memories involving cartoons."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923120000 +0000" stop="20250923123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>One Of The Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie and Wally finally get a chance to join the most exclusive social club in school, the Barons. However, after hanging out with the Barons on a Friday night, Eddie and Wally realize they don't want to be in this club because the guys really aren't who everybody thinks they are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923123000 +0000" stop="20250923130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Sweatshirt Monsters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Richard, Whitey and Alan each buy sweatshirts that have monster faces on the front of them. They like them so much they each decide to wear them to school the next day. However, each one finds that their parents forbid them from wearing such hideous sweatshirts to school. However, Beaver manages to sneak out of the house with his on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923130000 +0000" stop="20250923140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Rolling Bones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When Daniel Reed finds himself being blackmailed by an old business partner from his time in Alaska, Mason must first save him from the insane asylum and then the gas chamber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923140000 +0000" stop="20250923150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Nowhere To Turn: Part 2  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends himself against a murder charge after a judge who issued him a contempt citation is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923150000 +0000" stop="20250923160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After being released by his captors, the chief discovers that his abduction is part of a plot to assassinate a visiting civil rights leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923160000 +0000" stop="20250923170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Beau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A former boyfriend of Grandma's comes to visit</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923170000 +0000" stop="20250923180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Charlie Noon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt, his hardened prisoner Charlie Noon, an indian woman and her white stepson are tracked by the Comanches as they try to cross the desert. The indians are going to kill all of them unless Matt hands over the woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923180000 +0000" stop="20250923190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While helping to escort an old outlaw to jail, things take a turn for the worse when the prisoner murders the lawman and puts a bullet in Joe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923190000 +0000" stop="20250923193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Italian count arrives in North Fork, his strange attire attracts the attention of Groder, a town bully. Groder, trying to have fun with this stranger, destroys some of the count's currency, mocks him and tries to humiliate him. Eventually the count challenges Groder to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923193000 +0000" stop="20250923200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Floyd Doniger comes to North Fork, looking to start a new life. He's got a steady job as the guard at the new bank and he's entertaining ideas of settling down on a spread of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923200000 +0000" stop="20250923210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Janet Hale Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>"After losing one of her children in an accident, a woman is bitter with the wagon train and plans to turn back east, while her husband wishes to continue west. Hale, trying to persuade her to continue on, tells her the story of his own trip west with his family and the ensuing tragedy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923210000 +0000" stop="20250923220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Charlie, the station mechanic, stores the boat he wants to sell at the station house, where the firemen decide that they want to chip in and buy it. The paramedics rescue two boaters from Catalina Island. A bookie has a heart attack. An explosion in a lab starts a fire at the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923220000 +0000" stop="20250923223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Are You Now, Margaret?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Congressional aide, Williamson, visits the 4077th on a supposedly routine fact-finding tour, but it's discovered that his motives are far deeper—too uncover Margaret as a communist sympathizer. His case is full of innuendo, so the gang set out to help Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923223000 +0000" stop="20250923230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923230000 +0000" stop="20250923233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250923233000 +0000" stop="20250924000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924000000 +0000" stop="20250924003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924003000 +0000" stop="20250924010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924010000 +0000" stop="20250924013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Play Cupid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is hoping that Elly May and Dash Riprock will settle down and get married, since the two have been out on a lot of dates. Dash is hoping to get a more serious relationship with Elly as well, but her family keeps getting in the way. But Elly is not looking for a future with the Hollywood movie star; she’d rather have a farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924013000 +0000" stop="20250924020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries cheering up a depressed waitress, only to discover that she is the girlfriend of a tough Marine sergeant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924020000 +0000" stop="20250924023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flame Grows Higher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a POW is caught at the processing location after Stalag 13, Hogan suspects there is a traitor in the underground. Newkirk and LeBeau help him find out who it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924023000 +0000" stop="20250924030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Request Permission To Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving a "Dear John" letter, Carter asks Hogan if he can escape and get back to his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924030000 +0000" stop="20250924033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Steve Lawrence. Originally aired on 09/28/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924033000 +0000" stop="20250924043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nautical Knot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is summoned when Harvey Scott's efforts to retain temporary control of the family mining company lead to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924043500 +0000" stop="20250924050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Little People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>An astronaut declares himself a god when his ship lands on a planet populated by people smaller than ants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924050500 +0000" stop="20250924053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Pen Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With the law one step ahead of him, runaway prisoner Rod Collins searches for the pen pal he plans to wed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924053500 +0000" stop="20250924060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>O, Youth And Beauty!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Cash Bentley frantically clings to his youth, even if it means proving he can do exhausting corporal calisthenics.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924060500 +0000" stop="20250924070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Carol Lockwood, Past Tense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix seeks to prove that the death of one of his former gal-pals was not an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924070500 +0000" stop="20250924080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady On The Run</sub-title>
    <desc>"After witnessing a murder, a woman flees to a sanitarium where she was once a patient. It's up to Cannon to find her and keep her safe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924080500 +0000" stop="20250924090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Homecoming For A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby finds a man who vanished ten years ago - along with a fortune in stolen gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924090000 +0000" stop="20250924093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An officer accused of taking a bribe has chosen Sgt. Friday to represent him at his trial board hearing. Witnesses saw the officer accept the money, but he insists it was for the payback of a loan made years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924093000 +0000" stop="20250924100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A statue of the child Jesus was stolen from a church. Joe and Bill have to get it back by Christmas. They have less than 48 hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924100000 +0000" stop="20250924103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 143 -- Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin their shift responding to a disgruntled tenant who is holding his landlord at knife point. Later, they investigate a rash of property theft from multiple homes in a quiet neighborhood, stake out an apparent bag of laundry left on the side of the road and search for a runaway boy who gets himself into a life-threatening situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924103000 +0000" stop="20250924110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 142 -- As High As You Are</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy and Reed's patrol begins, an uneventful traffic stop becomes more interesting when something catches Malloy's eye. Later, they discover an unusual situation responding to a break-in at a hospital supply warehouse, which becomes even more odd when the warehouse owner and a group of revenge-seeking thugs show up at the scene. The shift ends in a fitting way when they are called to an apartment where a baby has been left unattended with a pet lion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924110000 +0000" stop="20250924120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Horsin' Around</sub-title>
    <desc>"Stick around! Because Bill has joined the latest craze, hobby horses."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924120000 +0000" stop="20250924123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Night In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends are all psyched to go on a camping trip with Gilbert's father as an escort. However, when Gilbert's father suddenly has to work, Wally agrees to take them. Meanwhile, Eddie and Lumpy decide to secretly tag along and scare the boys with animal noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924123000 +0000" stop="20250924130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Long Distance Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends decide to make a call to California to talk to Don Drysdale and they agree to chip in on the cost of the call, assuming that it's only going to be a couple dollars. However, when they're put on hold, the cost quickly jumps up to $9.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924130000 +0000" stop="20250924140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Corresponding Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason receives a telephone call from George Beaumont, a man who supposedly died in a plane crash nearly three years earlier. In reality, Beaumont missed the plane and after hearing about the accident decided to disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924140000 +0000" stop="20250924150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Personal Trainer  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When personal trainer Harry Slade is murdered, Matlock agrees to defend his roofer, George Wilton, in a complicated case involving quite a few sexual indiscretions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924150000 +0000" stop="20250924160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Rape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil struggles to help Althea after she is raped by a fellow teacher. Darnell does not think they can get a conviction because the man's wife has given him an alibi. Virgil tries to control his anger - until the man returns to intimidate Althea. And Gillespie tries to convince the wife to tell the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924160000 +0000" stop="20250924170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Infamy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen packs to go to Hawaii to join Curtis at Pearl Harbor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924170000 +0000" stop="20250924180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>A Man A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaws threaten to kill one person every day until Matt gets out of town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924180000 +0000" stop="20250924190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Cassie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss creates a "fixed" horse race in order to help a lazy dreamer and his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924190000 +0000" stop="20250924193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924193000 +0000" stop="20250924200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiffauges, a wealthy and sadistic Frenchman who is used to getting whatever he wants, decides he wishes to purchase the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges' lead man, Xavier, proclaims Lucas to be muy macho, and does not believe Lucas will give in so easily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924200000 +0000" stop="20250924210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Wagon To Fort Anderson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>"Flint comes across four survivors of an Indian massacre, the two Ellison sisters and two Carder brothers. One of the sisters is deaf and mute. The brothers are the only survivors of their Army unit. The older brother, Joe, wants to desert and take advantage of the situation in order to break away and look for gold. The younger brother, George, is simple-minded and good-hearted but loyal to the older one who raised him. Flint tries to lead the four to safety, but Joe Carder tries to mislead the Ellison sisters into believing that Flint is leading them into danger."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924210000 +0000" stop="20250924220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Isolation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John are trapped at Station 86 when a rain storm washes out the bridge, and they become the only medical treatment in the area. They assist two victims of an auto accident and a child with bronchitis. Doctors at the hospital treat a policeman hit by lightning. Copter 15 transports the victims to the hospital, where a power failure complicates matters. Dr. Morton accompanies the paramedics back to Station 86, where they respond to an auto accident with multiple injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924220000 +0000" stop="20250924223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924223000 +0000" stop="20250924230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924230000 +0000" stop="20250924233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250924233000 +0000" stop="20250925000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925000000 +0000" stop="20250925003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925003000 +0000" stop="20250925010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925010000 +0000" stop="20250925013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Housekeeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Jane is worried about Granny, who cleans the entire mansion by herself. Jane tells Jed and Elly that she thinks they need a housekeeper. Drysdale tells Jane that his wife is looking, and Mrs. Drysdale comes through with one. They decide to have Granny accept her by telling her this housekeeper is a little lady just like her who needs the money, and Granny decides to allow the help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925013000 +0000" stop="20250925020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma Pyle, Fortune Teller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer's fortune-telling grandma pays a visit. When she predicts trouble for someone close to him, Gomer worries that the someone is Sgt. Carter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925020000 +0000" stop="20250925023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Gives A Birthday Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hijacks a German bomber, and plans to use it to destroy an oil refinery and foil a German general who knows about the his operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925023000 +0000" stop="20250925030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Schultz Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink and two other prison camp kommandants are arrested for conspiring against General Burkhalter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925030000 +0000" stop="20250925033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eydie Gorme And Joan Rivers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eydie Gorme and Joan Rivers. Originally aired on 10/05/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925033000 +0000" stop="20250925043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bullied Bowler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a struggling bowling alley is shut down at the insistence of a domineering townswoman, a doctor involved in the closure is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925043500 +0000" stop="20250925050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Four O'clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A bitter, self-righteous man believes that he can will every evil person in the world to shrink to two-feet tall at four o'clock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925050500 +0000" stop="20250925053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Pushed by his girlfriend, Larry Chetnick plans to rob his company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925053500 +0000" stop="20250925060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Diplomatic Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple tries to smuggle a corpse out of Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925060500 +0000" stop="20250925070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Last Rites For Miss Emma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix suspects Floyd Brown of stealing 45 cases of morphine. That's bad news for Peggy because Floyd is her boyfriend. This case almost costs Joe his secretary, and Peggy her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925070500 +0000" stop="20250925080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former convict gets Cannon to help him find the man who sent him to jail for no reason."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925080500 +0000" stop="20250925090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>False Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty probes the rape of a friend who was in shock when she identified her attacker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925090000 +0000" stop="20250925093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925093000 +0000" stop="20250925100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925100000 +0000" stop="20250925103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 43 -- Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and several civilians are taken hostage after he is shot and seriously injured by robbers while stopping for lunch at Duke's Longhorn Café.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925103000 +0000" stop="20250925110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 34 -- Astro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed become envious of officer wells, who has been given a coveted assignment in the newly established astro helicopter division. Out on patrol, they require assistance saving a wealthy elderly couple who get locked in their heavily fortified basement safe, and then use air support to track down robbery suspects who escape on a motorcycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925110000 +0000" stop="20250925120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The First State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit the state of Delaware on their "Trekkin' All 50" tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925120000 +0000" stop="20250925123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Stocks And Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally become interested in the stock market and Ward decides that they should try their hand at it. However, Wally and Beaver have different ideas about what to invest in compared to Ward who wants them to play it safe and invest in Mayfield Power and Electric, while they want to invest in a more risky venture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925123000 +0000" stop="20250925130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Untogetherness</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Cleavers are all excited about their annual summer vacation up to the cabin, that is except Wally. Wanting to be close to his latest girl, Wally wants to stay behind and gets permission to stay at Eddie's house during the two weeks the Cleavers are on vacation, but June and Ward are a bit unsure of Wally's plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925130000 +0000" stop="20250925140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lucky Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason has all kinds of trouble when a murder brings him into the tangled financial and personal affairs of the wealthy Balfour family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925140000 +0000" stop="20250925150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Narc  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a police officer is murdered after exposing a group of dirty cops to top brass, Matlock agrees to take the case in defense of suspected killer Officer Johnny Bauer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925150000 +0000" stop="20250925160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Fairest Of Them All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A beauty contest is marred by blackmail and the ambitious mother of a contestant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925160000 +0000" stop="20250925170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Yearning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A new minister joins the community at Walton's Mountain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925170000 +0000" stop="20250925180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>A Quiet Day In Dodge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After 36 hours in the saddle, Matt rides into Dodge exhausted and, rather than finding some rest, is bombarded with constant yet trivial annoyances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925180000 +0000" stop="20250925190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Cry, My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the infant son of a Virginia City doctor dies in childbirth, his wife leaves him and the grieving doctor abducts another baby to have for his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925190000 +0000" stop="20250925193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Apprentice Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Willard is filling in as temporary marshal while Micah is away. Some Texas cowhands are in North Fork looking for some fun and relaxation, but Dan keeps coming down hard on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925193000 +0000" stop="20250925200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark, returning from selling their herd, share the stagecoach trip with a Marshal and his prisoner, Johnny Cotton. Johnny's gang arrives to free their partner and steal the contents of the stage's strongbox, as well as Lucas' money and rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925200000 +0000" stop="20250925210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Don Alvarado Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E38</episode-num>
    <desc>"A dying Spanish nobleman asks Flint to impersonate Don Alvarado to claim the inheritance for the rest of his family. This brings Flint into contact with the men who murdered the nobleman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925210000 +0000" stop="20250925220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Upward And Onward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley worries that the chief will sabotage his attempt to pass the chief's exam. A soap opera doctor with mono causes havoc on set and in the hospital. John, Roy and a retired doctor with a self-diagnosed heart aneurysm get stuck in an elevator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925220000 +0000" stop="20250925223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925223000 +0000" stop="20250925230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. race against the clock to save a soldier from paralysis. B.J.'s harvesting an aorta from a dead soldier doesn't sit well with the soldier's friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925230000 +0000" stop="20250925233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250925233000 +0000" stop="20250926000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926000000 +0000" stop="20250926003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926003000 +0000" stop="20250926010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926010000 +0000" stop="20250926013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Diner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed thinks that it is time for Jethro to start in the business world, and Jethro decides to become a fry cook and open his own restaurant. Jed is okay with this, but when he tells Drysdale, he is unsure because he is afraid of losing some of the Clampett money. The banker does end up buying Jethro a place on Restaurant Row, but the building is a wreck, with rent only thirty-five a month. Jethro is just glad to have a place of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926013000 +0000" stop="20250926020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The County Clerk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen try to play matchmaker for Howard Sprague, the county clerk, but his mother wants to keep him close to home (and to her).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926020000 +0000" stop="20250926023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds In The Rough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A German officer threatens to expose Hogan unless he is paid a million dollars in diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926023000 +0000" stop="20250926030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926030000 +0000" stop="20250926033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 10/19/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926033000 +0000" stop="20250926043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Prudent Proecutor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>DA Hamilton Burger asks Mason to defend an old friend who once saved his life in a boating accident 10 years before. The old friend of Burger's is now facing a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926043500 +0000" stop="20250926050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Hocus-pocus And Frisby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A loud-mouthed braggart's boasts attract the attention of aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926050500 +0000" stop="20250926053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Man With Two Faces</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A widow sees her son-in-law's photograph among law enforcement mug shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926053500 +0000" stop="20250926060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Blue Expression</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Philip Weaver concocts a scheme to murder his employer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926060500 +0000" stop="20250926070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search For A Whisper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A political candidate hires Mannix to dig up dirt, but not on an opponent. He wants the gumshoe to dig up dirt on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926070500 +0000" stop="20250926080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Ends At Noon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a Cuban exile to investigate the death of the man's brother at the hands of law enforcement officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926080500 +0000" stop="20250926090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>School Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Drug dealers infiltrate a treatment center and murder J.R.'s counselor friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926090000 +0000" stop="20250926093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are convinced that "Brother" William Bentley's Temple of the Expanded Mind is just a sham—a front for Bentley to sell LSD to the students of a nearby elementary school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926093000 +0000" stop="20250926100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926100000 +0000" stop="20250926103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 14 -- S.w.a.t.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are the first to respond to a downtown rooftop sniper who has been indiscriminately shooting at anyone he can find with his scoped rifle. After risking their lives to get civilians out of his line of sight, they become lead participants in the S.W.A.T. team's attempt to neutralize the suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926103000 +0000" stop="20250926110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 64 -- Bottom Of The Bottle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see the same drunk twice in one night, respond to a bar fight and engage in a high-speed pursuit with good samaritans who make a bad decision. They also search for a biker who tries to coerce a woman to repay a debt by riddling her apartment with buckshot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926110000 +0000" stop="20250926120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Buys The Farm</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill discovers the joys of rural living when he purchases a farm."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926120000 +0000" stop="20250926123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Dinner Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has been constantly spending his time at Julie Foster's house and June suggests that he's old enough to take her out on a dinner date. Julie suggests a new expensive restaurant called The White Fox. However, during the meal Wally discovers that he forgot his wallet at home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926123000 +0000" stop="20250926130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Football Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is scheduled to receive a football award at a father-son dinner being held in the school gym. While talking with his friends, Beaver learns that none of them are planning on wearing a jacket and a tie so when June and Ward insist that he wear one, he adamantly refuses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926130000 +0000" stop="20250926140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Pint-sized Client</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbers lift a bundle from the Hargrove Finance Company and Frank Anderson is murdered in the aftermath. Anthony "Pop" Renzi is identified as one of the robbers and charged with both the robbery and the murder. Mason sets out to clear him of both charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926140000 +0000" stop="20250926150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a plastic surgeon is found dead after an argument with his partner about dissolving the business, the business partner is the immediate suspect, until Matlock meets the man's twin brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926150000 +0000" stop="20250926160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Most Ancient</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An unhappy wife asks her lover to place a bomb in her abusive husband's truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926160000 +0000" stop="20250926170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Boosters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben starts an autocourt venture with Corabeth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926170000 +0000" stop="20250926180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Ash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The friendship between business partners is jeopardized when one of them sustains a head injury, changing his personality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926180000 +0000" stop="20250926190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A classmate of Jamie witnesses a brutal murder, but is too terrified to recount what has happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926190000 +0000" stop="20250926193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926193000 +0000" stop="20250926200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926200000 +0000" stop="20250926210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Captain Dan Brady Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>"Dan Brady, a colorful, boisterous and veteran frontier scout famous in the East, demands to be taken on as trail scout. Hale faces a dilemma as he will lose a freight contract necessary to finance the wagon train if he doesn't hire Brady."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926210000 +0000" stop="20250926220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Hypochondri-cap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Stanley convinces himself he has arthritis. A man gets his hand caught in his garage door opener. A woman passes out and has an auto accident. The doctors treat a woman infected from plastic surgery gone awry. The station responds to a two-alarm fire at an oil refinery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926220000 +0000" stop="20250926223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Stars And Stripes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friction arises between B.J. and Winchester when they are asked to write an article for a prestigious medical journal on how they saved a soldier's life with a daring operation. Meanwhile, Hot Lips receives an eventful visit from Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926223000 +0000" stop="20250926230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yessir, That's Our Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby born to a Korean woman and an American GI is abandoned at the 4077th. Knowing that Amer-Asian children are often mistreated in Korean society, the troop sets about the frustrating task of finding a new home for the infant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926230000 +0000" stop="20250926233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottle Fatigue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrified by the gigantic size of his monthly bar tab at the officer's club, Hawkeye vows to give up booze for a week. Meanwhile, Winchester desperately tries to halt his sister's impending marriage to a man he considers unworthy of the Winchester heritage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250926233000 +0000" stop="20250927000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heal Thyself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter turns crotchety when he catches the mumps, and his condition is worsened when Winchester gets the same disease and has to be quarantined with him. A temporary replacement surgeon, Newsome, is quickly brought into the 4077th and seems to be a gem in terms of both personality and ability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927000000 +0000" stop="20250927003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927003000 +0000" stop="20250927010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927010000 +0000" stop="20250927013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Topless Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Happy Gizzard isn’t doing well, and Jethro wants to improve his business. He thinks he has an idea to make his restaurant a huge success. After seeing signs outside other restaurants, he believes his restaurant should have topless waitresses. But he thinks this means the waitresses don’t wear hats. Jethro tells Drysdale just as he is working on landing a $20 million dollar account, scaring the millionaire Vanderponts away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927013000 +0000" stop="20250927020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Segeant Carter Dates A Pyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter agrees to go on a date with Gomer's visiting cousin after seeing a photo that he believes to be of her. But after learning that the girl is Gomer's date, he attempts to gracefully back out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927020000 +0000" stop="20250927023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Two German officers interfere with Hogan's operations when one tries to turn Stalag 13 into an officer's retirement home the other wants to use the facilities to interrogate the citizens of the local town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927023000 +0000" stop="20250927030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Rise And Fall Of Sergeant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is stymied in the rescue of a captured member of the underground until a potential diversion appears in the form of an old WWI buddy of Sgt. Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927030000 +0000" stop="20250927033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bernadette Peters And Donald O'connor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bernadette Peters and Donald O'Connor. Originally aired on 10/26/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927033000 +0000" stop="20250927043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tragic Trophy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hollywood wheeler-dealer is in desperate need of cash and has gotten himself in some trouble with the ladies. But before things can get any worse, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927043500 +0000" stop="20250927050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade-ins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple visits the New Life Corporation, hoping to transport their personalities into youthful artificial bodies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927050500 +0000" stop="20250927053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Man Who Found Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveler William Benson learns the hard way that integrity may not always be the best strategy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927053500 +0000" stop="20250927060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Changing Heart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Dane Ross falls in love with a gorgeous lady who has an eccentric reliance on her watchmaker grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927060500 +0000" stop="20250927070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Quote A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A vagrant becomes the target of killers whenever he wears a patchwork coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927070500 +0000" stop="20250927080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Search And Destroy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon tries to find a girl who went missing after witnessing a murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927080500 +0000" stop="20250927090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Cry For Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-policeman, whose son was killed as a warning not to interfere with the local protection racket, leads a vigilante group in a barrio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927090000 +0000" stop="20250927093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bedloe's Most Fiendish Scheme: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe and the girls are forced to find employment after Homer arranges for the bank to foreclose on Kate's mortgage.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
