<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328220000 +0000" stop="20250328223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328223000 +0000" stop="20250328230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328230000 +0000" stop="20250328233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250328233000 +0000" stop="20250329000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329000000 +0000" stop="20250329003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329003000 +0000" stop="20250329010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329010000 +0000" stop="20250329013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Son Of Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May and her new beau, Fred Penron, are getting rather serious. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns, this time with his son, Dub. He plans to set Dub up with Elly, to once again try to get some of Jed's money. Jed and Jethro try to hide this from Granny because the Cricks really rile her up. She sees the Cricks, but Jed tries to convince her that she is having visions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329013000 +0000" stop="20250329020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Girl-shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Warren is truly shy around women except when he is sleepwalking. When he sleepwalks he turns into a lothario of the first order—and his new conquest is Helen!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329020000 +0000" stop="20250329023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Klink's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets himself sent to the hospital so he can get information from a wounded agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329023000 +0000" stop="20250329030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Purchasing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and crew are ordered to deliver airdropped ammo to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329030000 +0000" stop="20250329033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Wrong Number / Saturday Night / Recital, The / Vacuum Salesman</sub-title>
    <desc>In Wrong Number, Carol questions a strange phone call for her husband. Then, in Saturday Night, Carol tries to get invited to a party next door. Next, in The Recital, four talentless musicians perform a showcase. Finally, in Vacuum Salesman, Tim has an emotional breakdown while trying to sell a vacuum.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329033000 +0000" stop="20250329043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Madcap Modiste</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After one of the biggest names in fashion is poisoned after embarrassing her husband on TV.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329043500 +0000" stop="20250329050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329050500 +0000" stop="20250329053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hooked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A man schemes with a young woman to get rid of his wealthy wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329053500 +0000" stop="20250329060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Greatly Beloved</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A newcomer refuses to allow his garden to be used for a church activity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329060500 +0000" stop="20250329070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Then The Drink Takes The Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates why a man who is against the evils of drink is spending a load of cash and time at an alcoholic retreat in Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329070500 +0000" stop="20250329080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On The Hill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A military general hires Cannon to find the daughter he put up for adoption years ago but it appears as though someone doesn't want the girl to be found.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329080500 +0000" stop="20250329090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Image In A Cracked Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune hunter marries rich women and makes off with their valuables.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329090000 +0000" stop="20250329093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Cannonball Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe's latest plan for decommissioning the Hooterville Cannonball falls on the holidays, as the gang are decorating the train for the annual Christmas Eve caroling run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329093000 +0000" stop="20250329100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Herbie Gets Drafted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Jo's boyfriend, Herbie Bates, has just been drafted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329100000 +0000" stop="20250329103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampett Look</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are getting ready for Mrs. Fenwick and Cynthia to come to share a meal with them, hoping to give them a better life than what the Clampetts believe they are leading. Jed and Jethro head to visit the Fenwick house, still thinking the gardener’s place is their house, and after seeing the little building decide to get the Fenwicks to move into the Clampett mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329103000 +0000" stop="20250329110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro has an idea of starting a new business, a five-second car wash. But Jed and Granny don’t care for the idea and think that Jethro and Elly need jobs to fill their time. At the bank, Milburn is taking care of his nephew, little Milby. Jane doesn’t want to take care of the sneaky child and Drysdale doesn’t have the time. When Jed visits asking for jobs for Elly and Jethro, he says that Elly May can take care of Milby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329110000 +0000" stop="20250329113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Spinach Packin' Popeye, Nix On Hypnotricks, Fowl Play</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Popeye loses a boxing match, Olive thinks he's not strong enough anymore., Popeye's nemesis is a leering hypnotist who attempts to lure Olive Oyl to his home., Bluto tries to steal a parrot which Popeye has given Olive Oyl as a gift."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329113000 +0000" stop="20250329120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hatch Up Your Troubles, Chips Off The Old Block, Cat Fishin'</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry is forced to take care of a baby woodpecker and try to avoid Tom while doing it, A tomcat named Butch has a delivery of kittens left on his doorstep and he spends his time trying to hide the mischief making kittens from his owner., Spike is guarding a "No Fishing" area but Tom, using Jerry as bait, doesn't let that bother him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329120000 +0000" stop="20250329130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gold Diggin' Woodpecker, Mouse Trapped, South Pole Pals, Paste Makes Waste, The Mad Hatter, Three Ring Fling, Woody The Giant Killer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody and his horse Sugarfoot discover gold in an abandoned mine and have to fight off another miner trying to claim jump., Doc must evade the police (with the help or rather hindrance of Hickory and Dickory) when the police try to capture all black cats on Friday the 13th., Smedley is sent to capture an emperor penguin and tries to capture Chilly. But an actual Emperor Penguin helps Chilly avoid him., Bessie pretends it is raining outside to get Charlie to help her wallpaper the house instead of playing golf., Woody encounters difficulties acquiring a new top hat for his Hollywood screen test., Windy tries to get into the circus for free., Woody is looking for an apartment, and Buck Beaver sells him magic beans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329130000 +0000" stop="20250329140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Long-haired Hare, Plane Dippy, Ain't We Got Fun, Hillbilly Hare, Daffy Dilly, Compressed Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs distracts Giovanni Jones from practicing for his concert. , Air Corpsman Porky is caught in a voice-controlled airplane responding to commands given to a dog by children near the microphone. , A cat defend's his master's home from a group of mischievous mice., Bugs makes a wrong turn and ends up in the Ozarks where he meets the end-barrels of two hillbillies., When Daffy gets word of a sick millionaire willing to pay a million dollars to whoever makes him laugh, Daffy is quick to respond – but the butler keeps him out of the house. , Wile E. Coyote becomes Bugs' new neighbor. While the Coyote pretends to be his friend, his real interests are in cooking the rabbit. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329140000 +0000" stop="20250329150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Hangman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>During a stopover in a small Kansas town, the agents become involved in a murder investigation. After a man is found guilty and sentenced to hang, the agents uncover valuable information that points in an entirely different direction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329150000 +0000" stop="20250329160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Willy Moran Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Willy Moran, Adams' old Civil War commanding officer, is now a drunkard. Adams offers him a job on the wagon train, provided that he can stay sober.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329160000 +0000" stop="20250329170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>By Force And Violence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When Heath is trapped under a broken-down wagon, the only person who can help Victoria save him is an escaped convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329170000 +0000" stop="20250329173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Alarm At Pleasant Valley</sub-title>
    <desc>"While on the way back to Dodge, Matt and Chester discover a homesteading family fleeing Pleasant Valley, which is besieged by Indians."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329173000 +0000" stop="20250329180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cow Doctor</sub-title>
    <desc>"After he is summoned unknowingly by Ben Pitcher to treat one of his cows, a human patient of Doc's dies. During a fight with Pitcher, Doc is knifed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329180000 +0000" stop="20250329190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Credit For A Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe takes credit for a killing when he learns that the dead man's brother is out for revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329190000 +0000" stop="20250329193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329193000 +0000" stop="20250329200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329200000 +0000" stop="20250329210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Ten Trees</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The drovers find a young white woman dressed as an indian, babbling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329210000 +0000" stop="20250329213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Misguided Father</sub-title>
    <desc>"Charlie Blackburn, an old friend of Paladin, is shot and found dead in Paladin's hotel room. Paladin takes his body back home for burial but no one wants the body. While trying to find Blackburn's killer, he comes up against Win Loring and his psychopathic son."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329213000 +0000" stop="20250329220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Eager Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh is approached by the wife of a wanted man eager to turn himself in peacefully, provided Josh split the bounty with his wife. To ensure the deal goes as planned, Josh enlists the aid of an old friend: Sheriff Pat Garrett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250329220000 +0000" stop="20250330000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Restless Knights, Uncivil Warriors, For Crimin' Out Loud, Rumpus In The Harem, Sappy Bull Fighters, Dutiful But Dumb</sub-title>
    <desc>"Set in Medieval times, the Stooges learn they are of royal blood and vow to save the kingdom.   , Set in the civil war, the Stooges are spies for the north.   , The Stooges are photographers for Whack magazine ("If it's a good picture it's out of Whack") who, after messing up an assignment, are sent to the country of Vulgaria to get a picture of a death ray gun.  In Vulgaria the penalty for taking pictures in is death, and the boys soon wind up in front of a firing squad.  Curly's last request is a giant cigar and by the time he's done smoking it all the soldiers are asleep and the Stooges make their escape. , The Stooges are private detectives hired to protect a rich politician.  After the man disappears, the boys wander around his spooky mansion confronting various villains and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man. , Set in a desert land where the Stooges run a restaurant, the boys need money to pay their fiancee's taxes, or the girls will be sold as slaves.  Some crooks come into their restaurant and convince the boys to recover the stolen Rootin Tootin diamond.  The Stooges decide to return the diamond to the government and get the reward money.  They learn that the Emir of Shmo has absconded with the contraband jewel.  They journey to the stronghold of Shmo where they disguise as Santa Clauses and scare the ruler into giving them the diamond. , Stranded in Mexico, the Stooges need a job and a pretty actress friend gets them an engagement at the Plaza de Toros.  When they accidentally switch suitcases with that of their friend, they must sneak into her house to retrieve their own and are confronted by her jealous husband who vows to kill them if he sees them again.  At the arena where they perform a comedy bullfight (Joe is the matador, Moe and Larry are in a bull costume) the husband bribes the attendants to let a real bull into the ring.  Joe knocks the bull out with a head butt and becomes a hero. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330000000 +0000" stop="20250330023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Godzilla Vs. Monster Zero</sub-title>
    <desc>"Aliens from Planet X request the use of Godzilla and Rodan to fight off King Ghidorah, but have a better use for the three monsters."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330023000 +0000" stop="20250330030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>A Horse Of Another Color</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of money for his parasol plan, the Penguin steals from the parasol collection at the library. Librarian Barbara Gordon alerts Batman, who uses Alfred as a ruse to trap the Penguin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330030000 +0000" stop="20250330040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Mark Of Gideon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk beams down on a diplomatic mission and finds himself on an Enterprise where all the crew have vanished and only a mysterious woman resides.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330040000 +0000" stop="20250330050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Trevi Collection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch desires to control the world of high fashion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330050000 +0000" stop="20250330060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Castles In Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinsons take in a princess who is fleeing from a bounty hunter. However, when Will is captured by the bounty hunter, he asks them to make a trade of Will for the princess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330060000 +0000" stop="20250330070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>...and Five Of Us Are Left</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral nelson heads an expedition to find the survivors of a sunken submarine trapped for 28 years in an undersea cave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330070000 +0000" stop="20250330080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Creed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barry is struck by appendicitis, the Earthlings have no choice but to seek out a Giant doctor for assistance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330080000 +0000" stop="20250330090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Chase Through Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Planting a bomb in the time tunnel, a saboteur leads Tony and Doug on a chase through three epochs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330090000 +0000" stop="20250330100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Vikor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>David goes undercover to infiltrate a manufacturing plant and find proof of alien activity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330100000 +0000" stop="20250330110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>36 Hours</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt race to find the landing device before astronauts perish in the re-entry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330110000 +0000" stop="20250330113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Date Auction   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The school holds a dance-date auction to pay for new cheerleading uniforms, with Zach, Slater and Screech up for auction. Jessie is appalled at the whole idea; meanwhile, Lisa becomes an intellectual to impress a smart boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330113000 +0000" stop="20250330120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Hold Me Tight   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a girl is rejected from wrestling tryouts because she is female, Zack, who has a crush on her, will do whatever it takes to see that she makes the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330120000 +0000" stop="20250330123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Zack   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack sprains his knee and learns that he will be going into surgery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330123000 +0000" stop="20250330130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Check Your Mate   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the annual chess competition between Valley and Bayside. Screech is Bayside's champion so Valley decides to dig up some dirt on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330130000 +0000" stop="20250330133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Pipe Dreams   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While putting up a new field goal post, oil is discovered. Soon the entire school is interested in the lucrative prospect of oil drilling, but Jessie doesn't like the idea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330133000 +0000" stop="20250330140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>All In The Mall   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack finds $5,000 in the mall, he plans to use the money to buy and then scalp tickets for a U2 concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330140000 +0000" stop="20250330143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Bobby's Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The principal calls to alert Mike and Carol that Bobby's been playing Jesse James at school. They have a hard time convincing Bobby to stop, until Mike tracks down a man whose father was killed by Jesse James.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330143000 +0000" stop="20250330150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Subject Was Noses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia inadvertently makes two dates for the same night; Charlie the nerd and Doug, the big man on campus. But Doug is only interested in having a pretty girl on his arm, something Marcia learns after suffering a swollen nose when she's hit in the face with a football.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330150000 +0000" stop="20250330153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Haunted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After experiencing a few strange happenings, Richie begins to buy into the legend that the place where Ralph's Halloween party is to be held, the old Simpson house, is haunted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330153000 +0000" stop="20250330160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Dating Slump</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Shirley becomes reclusive and refuses to date after learning that Carmine has a new girlfriend. Eager to help her friend, Laverne plans an evening out—only to have the two girls wind up in a barroom scuffle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330160000 +0000" stop="20250330163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330163000 +0000" stop="20250330170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Misses The Mertzes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>As the Ricardos get settled in their new country home, they immediately wind up in a mix-up with their old friends, Fred and Ethel Mertz. Missing their old friends already, Lucy and Ricky decide to visit the Mertzes. At the same time, the Mertzes decide to trek to the country to visit the Ricardos, and what began simply becomes complicated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330170000 +0000" stop="20250330173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend Beaver made at summer camp, Chopper, stays with the Cleavers for the weekend. Beaver is quickly introduced to Chopper's unusual life; he is the son of parents who have been married and divorced many times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330173000 +0000" stop="20250330180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Becomes A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver and Wally are fishing an abandoned canoe floats up and they responsibly return it to the owner, whose name had been carved in the paddle. However, after telling his friends the story, they adjust it to make it sound as if Beaver had saved a girl from drowning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330180000 +0000" stop="20250330183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly, The Secretary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts receive a telegram that says Louellen Aden is coming out to California. When Jed tells Jethro about this, they figure out that she wants to marry Jethro. He gets scared and runs away. Meanwhile, Elly is learning to be a secretary, but is not very good at it. She and Miss Jane go to bring Louellen to the Clampett mansion, and the family learns that she has changed into a lovely young lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330183000 +0000" stop="20250330190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Inherits A Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro tells Jed that he has inherited a castle in England, after hearing the word from Drysdale. He gets costumes from Tudor times, thinking that Queen Elizabeth I is still reigning. Jethro even makes Granny wear an oaf costume, since she doesn’t have Clampett blood. Drysdale and Jane visit, and Jane tells the Clampetts that what Jethro is telling them is wrong. But after Drysdale paints a picture for Jane, the two convince the Clampetts to go, even providing an oaf for Jethro, Miss Jane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330190000 +0000" stop="20250330193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Waiting For Watubi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Skipper discovers a carved statue of a tiki god.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330193000 +0000" stop="20250330200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Angel On The Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Howell decides to put on a play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330200000 +0000" stop="20250330203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Workman's Holiday  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint is so embarrassed when Mama brings his childhood lunchbox to work that he accidentally injures himself on the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330203000 +0000" stop="20250330210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Sees Red  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The Harpers are chosen as the "typical American family" to be visited by Olga, a "typical Russian homemaker," who not only cleans their house inside and out, but also decides to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330210000 +0000" stop="20250330220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Hometown Doc</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Isaac's criminal uncle arrives; Doc worries about a doctor's career decision; a proper woman meets her daughter's beau.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330220000 +0000" stop="20250330223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330223000 +0000" stop="20250330230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Collector's Recall</sub-title>
    <desc>"Join our host Lisa Whelchel as she gets updates from some of our past collectors to learn how their collections have changed since our first visit.  And see a sneak preview of some of the amazing collectors from our new upcoming Season 6. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330230000 +0000" stop="20250330233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250330233000 +0000" stop="20250331000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331000000 +0000" stop="20250331003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie In The Lock-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Lionel are planning on attending a demonstration at the United Nations. However, the rally gets out of hand and news of it appears on TV. This worries Gloria who begs Archie to go down there and get Mike. Later, Mike and Lionel return with reports that protesters were arrested. Pretty soon, the family figures out that Archie has been mistakenly arrested and is trapped in jail with a group of radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331003000 +0000" stop="20250331010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Writes A Song</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The family manages to collect $30 in the family pot and an argument ensues when Edith wants to use the money to set her lyrics for a song to music. Meanwhile, Archie is disturbed by robberies in the neighborhood and wants to use the money to buy a gun. They ultimately decide to go with Edith, but before Archie can return the pistol to the store, two robbers break into the house and hold the Bunkers at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331010000 +0000" stop="20250331013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Flashback: Mike Meets Archie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Gloria are all excited about their first wedding anniversary and order take-out as a special dinner. Sitting around the dinner table, an argument ensues which leads to Edith recalling the day Archie met Mike. It seems that things even then weren't smooth sailing, however, the real bombshell came when Mike and Gloria also announced that same day that they were planning to be married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331013000 +0000" stop="20250331020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Election Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A local election has the Bunker family in turmoil as Mike and Gloria are all for Claire Packer, a woman, which is exactly why Archie is dead set against her. However, once down at the voting booths, Archie soon realizes that he can't vote because he isn't registered, leaving it up to him to try to convince Edith to vote for his candidate of choice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331020000 +0000" stop="20250331023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Barry And Jack Weston</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Operation, Carol asks Harvey for a divorce, moments before he operates on an ailing patient. Then, in Ethel Herman, Jack Weston flirts with Carol, who replies to him only in song. Finally, in The Old Folks, Carol teases Harvey that he's too old to play golf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331023000 +0000" stop="20250331030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Rock Hudson</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary debating if she should leave her husband for a head-over-heels suitor. Then, in The Newscasters, Carol and Rock have a marital spat live on the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331030000 +0000" stop="20250331033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Impractical Joke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Buddy grows paranoid when Rob threatens to pull a prank on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331033000 +0000" stop="20250331040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Boy #1, Boy #2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura and Millie become stage mothers when their sons are cast in a TV commercial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331040000 +0000" stop="20250331043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Bensonhurst Bomber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph gets into an argument at the pool hall and has to fight a big guy at the gym. He arranges it so that he can pretend to knock out a bigger man and make the other one scared. Instead he knocks out a stranger, regaining his confidence to go ahead with the fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331043000 +0000" stop="20250331050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>And When The Sky Was Opened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When three U.S. astronauts return to Earth after the first flight into space, they begin being erased from history one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331050000 +0000" stop="20250331060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Paragon  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>John Pemberton comes up with an everlasting answer for dealing with his cruel, intrusive wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331060000 +0000" stop="20250331070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Crane</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Constantine, the guerrilla head of the People's Liberation Army of Logosia, has been captured by the corrupt government and the IMF must free him and help smash the military junta.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331070000 +0000" stop="20250331080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>When The Bough Breaks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>While hopping freight trains, Kimble meets a young woman, named Carol Hollister, who is traveling with her baby to meet her husband. But Kimble doesn't know that Carol is a mentally disturbed young woman whose newborn baby died a year earlier and she has</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331080000 +0000" stop="20250331090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Accounts Balanced</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell probes the mystery of an accountant leading a double life--as a paid killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331090000 +0000" stop="20250331093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331093000 +0000" stop="20250331100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331100000 +0000" stop="20250331103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Foothill Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy, Reed and Sgt. MacDonald go horseback as part of the search for suspects responsible for a break-in at a large ranch. Meanwhile, Sgt. MacDonald offers a reward for the return of his favorite boots, Officer Wells starts a collection for a couple who claims their baby needs brain surgery and the station is attacked by a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331103000 +0000" stop="20250331110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>West Valley Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy has his eye on an attractive woman he's seeing all over town walking a scotty dog, which eventually turns out to be bad news for her. Meanwhile, he and Reed assist a police helicopter track down a young man riding his dirt bike in the hills illegally during fire season, search for an armed suspect who held up a movie theater before escaping on a motorcycle and coordinate with the police helicopter in a futile search for two armed robbery suspects who fatally shot a night watchman inside a department store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331110000 +0000" stop="20250331120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day...march 31st</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331120000 +0000" stop="20250331123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Lifeguard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally is all set to begin his job as a lifeguard but is let down when he learns that had been a mistake and he's not old enough to fill the position, so instead he is hired to sell candy and hot dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331123000 +0000" stop="20250331130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Freckles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clarence gets fed up with Beaver calling him Lumpy, he gives Beaver a new nickname, Freckles. This leads Beaver to become self-conscious about his freckles and takes steps to try to remove them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331130000 +0000" stop="20250331140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shifty Shoebox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Robbery, embezzlement and a coverup at a trucking company end in the murder of one of the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331140000 +0000" stop="20250331150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Seller  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the friend of a famous novelist is found dead, suspicion falls on the husband of the author. While trying to clear the man's name, Julie discovers that not everything is as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331150000 +0000" stop="20250331160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>December Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Sparta police investigate a suspicious death in a nursing home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331160000 +0000" stop="20250331170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Erin adopts a wild animal while John Boy gets a life lesson with a new job</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331170000 +0000" stop="20250331173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Brush At Eklader</sub-title>
    <desc>"After his friend Ben Williams is shot down by Lou Shippen, Matt travels to Elkader to bring him him. The only problem, he doesn't know what he looks like and the town is protecting Shippen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331173000 +0000" stop="20250331180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Custer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt refuses to turn Joe Trimble a rustler over to Major Banker for court-martial."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331180000 +0000" stop="20250331190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Four Sisters From Boston</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When the four Lowell sisters come to claim an estate left by a late relative, everything seems to start  going wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331190000 +0000" stop="20250331193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rancher dies after the bank forecloses the mortgage on his property, his son blames the banker for his father's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331193000 +0000" stop="20250331200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind Reader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E40</episode-num>
    <desc>When a wealthy rancher is killed, Mark suggests that they seek the aid of a mind reader to identify the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331200000 +0000" stop="20250331210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jean Lebec Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A New Orleans aristocrat escorting a young lass to San Francisco arouses the fury of a tyrannical town boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331210000 +0000" stop="20250331220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Survival On Charter #220 (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Squad 51 C-shift paramedics rescue a stuntman from a tower. Gage and Desoto respond to treat the injured child of a fireman’s widow. A small plane and a chartered jetliner collide in midair, landing in a residential neighborhood, trapping Johnny and Roy. Station 18 leads a massive response from Battalion 14 and the Compton city fire department. Dr. Morton heads up a triage team from Rampart. Multiple rescues include passengers from both planes and people in the subdivision. Dr. Early performs brain surgery on the injured child. An elderly man’s dog leads Chief McConnike to its owner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331220000 +0000" stop="20250331223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331223000 +0000" stop="20250331230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331230000 +0000" stop="20250331233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250331233000 +0000" stop="20250401000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401000000 +0000" stop="20250401003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rehabilitation Of Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to use psychology to reform Otis of his drinking habit but this eventually leads Otis to "take his business" elsewhere—the jail in Mt. Pilot!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401003000 +0000" stop="20250401010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney receives a chain letter, but Andy goads him into throwing it away. Suddenly things begin going wrong for Barney and he's convinced he'll soon be out of a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401010000 +0000" stop="20250401013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Fishing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale and Jane try to get the Clampetts interested in deep-sea fishing, but face an obstacle: Granny. She has a fear of water and refuses to go on a boat. So, Jane comes up with the idea of letting them visit Marineland. They decide to go right away and are impressed by the giant fishing holes. And Granny sees the fish of fishes, a giant whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401013000 +0000" stop="20250401020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>How To Succeed In Farming Without Really Trying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter tries to teach Gomer a lesson about using all his free time to build a garden on the base. But the lesson backfires when the sergeant puts vodka in a watermelon—which is then sent to a visiting general's home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401020000 +0000" stop="20250401023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan faces a startling development: His captors are sending him to America to demand surrender—with a super weapon supposedly supplied by the Russians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401023000 +0000" stop="20250401030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must destroy an anti-aircraft defense system designed by a beautiful English woman who may have defected to Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401030000 +0000" stop="20250401033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Ham Actor, The / Oldest Man, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Ham Actor, Carol and Harvey try to survive an outdoor performance despite a coming storm. Then, in The Oldest Man, the Oldest Man captains a ship headed toward an iceberg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401033000 +0000" stop="20250401043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Slandered Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Navy Commander Jerome Burke is assisting the police in the investigation of the murder of a cafe singer. The police believe that a sailor assigned to a Navy submarine committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401043500 +0000" stop="20250401050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What You Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A two-bit thug thinks he's found the key to a better life in an old sidewalk salesman who has the uncanny ability to tell people what they need the most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401050500 +0000" stop="20250401053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Doubtful Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A man relates an unusual situation to his doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401053500 +0000" stop="20250401060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Moral Theft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperate man tries to save his company from bankruptcy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401060500 +0000" stop="20250401070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Falling Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>As movie starlet Anne Marion is scheduled to release her tell-all memoirs, an attempt is made on her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401070500 +0000" stop="20250401080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Missing At Fl307</sub-title>
    <desc>"An ex-convict boards an airplane in Atlanta for a reunion with his daughter but when the plane lands he's nowhere to be found."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401080500 +0000" stop="20250401090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Foul Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The owner of a basketball team accidentally kills a man who intended to blackmail the team's star player.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401090000 +0000" stop="20250401093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401093000 +0000" stop="20250401100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401100000 +0000" stop="20250401103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Venice Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have to break the news to a young model that her press agent lied when he said there would be nothing wrong with having a nude photo shoot on a busy public beach. Later, they discover a man stealing from a phone booth, assist in the chase of a stolen dune buggy, try help an attractive woman whose safety is put in grave danger by an obscene phone caller, deal with a wino who dies while eating at a diner and pull over a woman towing a large jack-o-lantern.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401103000 +0000" stop="20250401110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Today's patrol begins with a traffic stop of a high-society cat burglar who's just finished serving a four-year prison term, and Malloy senses the guy is about to return to his old ways. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a standoff with a wounded robbery suspect who fatally shot a convenience store worker, examine an abandoned vehicle, investigate the theft of a book from a library and deal with a distraught unemployed man who takes his young daughter hostage in his home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401110000 +0000" stop="20250401120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Day Of Foolery</sub-title>
    <desc>"On this April Fool's Day, Bill's on a mission to prank his closest friends."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401120000 +0000" stop="20250401123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Big Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Constantly entering contests, Beaver's latest one has him selling raffle tickets in hopes of winning a prize. Surprisingly, he does indeed win third prize and the prize is a $3,500 sports car. However, his dreams are dashed when Eddie's premonition comes true, Ward breaks the news that Beaver can't keep the car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401123000 +0000" stop="20250401130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Lander's Fiancee</sub-title>
    <desc>"While doing some yard work for Miss Landers, Beaver and Whitey witness their favorite teacher in the midst of a gentleman caller, which makes Beaver a bit jealous. However, Beaver gets sick to his stomach when he discovers Miss Landers is engaged to be married and the man he saw was her fiance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401130000 +0000" stop="20250401140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drowsy Mosquito</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason investigates when the sale of phony gold mines leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401140000 +0000" stop="20250401150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ex  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Julie's in Baltimore defending a man accused of killing a newspaper editor who besmirched his name. Complicating matters is the prosecutor, who just happens to be Julie's ex-husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401150000 +0000" stop="20250401160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Loss Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Darnell plans on indicting a teenager for murder after her father is found in the basement and her mother turns up missing. But Gillespie and his men don't believe she is guilty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401160000 +0000" stop="20250401170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Thanksgiving Story - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving time on Walton's Mountain means a turkey shoot, a school play about early settlers, and the big meal. One year it also included a rekindled love affair and a life-threatening accident</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401170000 +0000" stop="20250401173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Roundup</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt closes up shops to a group of drunken cowboys, which causes trouble."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401173000 +0000" stop="20250401180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Gun</sub-title>
    <desc>"After gunman, Sam Kercher is killed by Matt, his 16-year old brother arrives to fight Matt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401180000 +0000" stop="20250401190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Old Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A boastful teller of tall tales falls prey to the revenge-seeking brothers of a dead outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401190000 +0000" stop="20250401193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401193000 +0000" stop="20250401200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401200000 +0000" stop="20250401210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Cameron Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The husband of a much younger woman grows jealous of her flirtatious ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401210000 +0000" stop="20250401220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Survival On Charter #220 (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Squad 51 C-shift paramedics rescue a stuntman from a tower. Gage and Desoto respond to treat the injured child of a fireman’s widow. A small plane and a chartered jetliner collide in midair, landing in a residential neighborhood, trapping Johnny and Roy. Station 18 leads a massive response from Battalion 14 and the Compton city fire department. Dr. Morton heads up a triage team from Rampart. Multiple rescues include passengers from both planes and people in the subdivision. Dr. Early performs brain surgery on the injured child. An elderly man’s dog leads Chief McConnike to its owner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401220000 +0000" stop="20250401223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401223000 +0000" stop="20250401230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401230000 +0000" stop="20250401233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250401233000 +0000" stop="20250402000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402000000 +0000" stop="20250402003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402003000 +0000" stop="20250402010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Runs For Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers taking an out-of-town job, and with the election nearing, no one has yet filed to run for Sheriff. Barney throws his hat in the ring, and then Andy's job prospect takes a turn.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402010000 +0000" stop="20250402013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Critter Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke is sick, and Elly calls the "critter doctor" from the zoo. When Jed finds out he is a "college boy," he thinks it is a possible beau for Elly May, not knowing he is a graduate and an older man. Granny is against this doctor coming, and she mistakes a young salesman who is selling bug repellents for the doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402013000 +0000" stop="20250402020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Little Men From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter sends Gomer to a psychiatrist when he claims to have seen men from outer space. They're really actors in a sci-fi movie being filmed near the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402020000 +0000" stop="20250402023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Major Bonacelli</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Italian officer who studied under Klink helps Hogan photograph an air base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402023000 +0000" stop="20250402030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Dear Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's men plan to surprise him for his birthday by blowing up an ammunition dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402030000 +0000" stop="20250402033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Kidnapping / Family, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Kidnapping, Carol gets her fifteen minutes of fame when her husband is kidnapped. Then, in The Family, Eunice is determined to win "The Gong Show" by singing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402033000 +0000" stop="20250402043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ominous Outcast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a notorious bank robber's son returns to his hometown it seems as though everyone is interested in missing loot supposedly hidden by the man's father. This leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402043500 +0000" stop="20250402050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Four Of Us Are Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who can change his face to resemble others gets into hot water with gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402050500 +0000" stop="20250402053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Contest For Aaron Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man devotes his entire stay at a summer camp to modeling a one-armed clay knight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402053500 +0000" stop="20250402060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Five-forty-eight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A philandering senior manager finds himself being stalked by a previous secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402060500 +0000" stop="20250402070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>License To Kill—limit Three People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired when a sniper begins killing citizens, the prime suspect being an escaped mental patient.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402070500 +0000" stop="20250402080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Set-up</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is a victim of mistaken identity and later almost killed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402080500 +0000" stop="20250402090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gathering Of Thieves, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A real-estate scam leads to four murders, including that of a professor who was not pleased with his new property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402090000 +0000" stop="20250402093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402093000 +0000" stop="20250402100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402100000 +0000" stop="20250402103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Van Nuys Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy returns from vacation sporting a mustache, but finds it difficult getting his colleagues to accept his new look. On patrol, he and Reed respond to a small plane crash by a drunkard that critically injures his young son, investigate the theft of valuable stamps from a mansion, search for a jewelry store armed robber with the aid of a talented witness, deal with a very unlucky purse snatcher and interrogate an evasive department store shoplifter with a big surprise in her purse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402103000 +0000" stop="20250402110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Training Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While assisting in a tactics training course, Malloy and Reed meet Officer Wells' new partner, an overconfident probationary officer who seems destined to put himself and his colleagues in danger. On patrol, they deal with an unconventional bank robber, come to the aid of a motor officer who is injured during a traffic stop and investigate a credible bomb threat at a grocery store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402110000 +0000" stop="20250402120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Toy Voyage</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore the magical world of traveling toys!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402120000 +0000" stop="20250402123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Double Cross</sub-title>
    <desc>"Eddie crawls through the Cleaver house spreading the news that he's going steady with Caroline Schuster, something that worries June who doesn't want Wally to get any ideas about going steady. However, Wally has other worries when he overhears Caroline saying that she's only using Eddie while her boyfriend is grounded. Leaving Wally with the decision to tell Eddie or not."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402123000 +0000" stop="20250402130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's I.q.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning that he's going to be taking an I.Q. test, Beaver hits the books, scared after his friends tell him that if he doesn't pass he will be sent to "dumb school."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402130000 +0000" stop="20250402140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Decadent Dean</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends the dean of a prep school on charges of murdering a teacher who had been embezzling and blackmailing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402140000 +0000" stop="20250402150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Temptation  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A thug tries to make Leanne fall in love with him by using her journal that he stole from her house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402150000 +0000" stop="20250402160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Bubba's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone abandons a baby at Bubba's door.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402160000 +0000" stop="20250402170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Thanksgiving Story - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanksgiving time on Walton's Mountain means a turkey shoot, a school play about early settlers, and the big meal. One year it also included a rekindled love affair and a life-threatening accident</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402170000 +0000" stop="20250402173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Indian White</sub-title>
    <desc>"At Fort Dodge, home of the third cavalry, Mrs. Mary Cullen tells the colonel, that the twelve year old they got from the Cheyenne is her son Dennis. The Indians took him when he was two years old."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402173000 +0000" stop="20250402180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>How To Cure A Friend</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt's getting his haircut. The barber tells about a couple of Texans he shaved, who talked about a crooked gambler they played in San Antonio, named Nick Search. Matt saved Nick's life. Nick arrives on the stage and goes to see Bill Pence, who runs the Long Branch, about setting up a poker game."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402180000 +0000" stop="20250402190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Ballad Of The Ponderosa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A young singer returns to Virginia City where he claims that Ben Cartwright is responsible for the death of his father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402190000 +0000" stop="20250402193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402193000 +0000" stop="20250402200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402200000 +0000" stop="20250402210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ruth Owens Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's brother kills a man who made a derogatory remark about her, only to discover later that the remark was true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402210000 +0000" stop="20250402220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Most Deadly Passage (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Roy and Johnny are sent to Seattle to study the techniques used there. A skydiver jumps off the Space Needle, a worker is trapped at the top of the Kingdome, and a fuel pumper loads a ferry with gasoline instead of diesel fuel, which sets the ferry on fire in the middle of the Elliot Bay."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402220000 +0000" stop="20250402223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402223000 +0000" stop="20250402230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402230000 +0000" stop="20250402233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250402233000 +0000" stop="20250403000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403000000 +0000" stop="20250403003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>If I Had A Quarter-million</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney finds $250,000 stolen in a bank heist, he goes undercover to find the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403003000 +0000" stop="20250403010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy's pretty young cousin, Gloria, comes for a visit after breaking up with her boyfriend. Aunt Bee asks Andy to be nice to her and his attention makes Helen jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403010000 +0000" stop="20250403013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Shorty, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Jethro stay out all night, not to Granny's approval, Shorty is forced to chop wood in the early morning and do other chores the rest of the day so he will want to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403013000 +0000" stop="20250403020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Borrowed Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer borrows Sgt. Carter's car, and is followed by thieves who steal it. When Gomer searches for the missing car, he is spotted taking it back and is arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403020000 +0000" stop="20250403023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403023000 +0000" stop="20250403030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a Luftwaffe codebook, but must organize a special mission when Newkirk drops it down a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403030000 +0000" stop="20250403033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye Charlie / As The Stomach Turns</sub-title>
    <desc>In Goodbye Charlie, Tim writes a eulogy for his best friend, only to discover he was wooing his wife. Then, in As the Stomach Turns, Carol's daughter comes back to life as a Bionic Woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403033000 +0000" stop="20250403043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Irate Inventor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>James Frazer wants a divorce and his cheating wife refuses to give him one. She's also stealing the plans to his invention in order to bait her engineer lover into staying around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403043500 +0000" stop="20250403050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Third From The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>With all-out nuclear war about to ignite, a scientist and his pilot friend plot to escape on an experimental spaceship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403050500 +0000" stop="20250403053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Pen Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With the law one step ahead of him, runaway prisoner Rod Collins searches for the pen pal he plans to wed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403053500 +0000" stop="20250403060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>O, Youth And Beauty!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Cash Bentley frantically clings to his youth, even if it means proving he can do exhausting corporal calisthenics.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403060500 +0000" stop="20250403070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Deadfall: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Intertect is accused of stealing plans and a formula to create a laser ray, forcing Mannix and Lew Wickersham into a deadly feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403070500 +0000" stop="20250403080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is called in to investigate police corruption by the mayor of a Midwestern town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403080500 +0000" stop="20250403090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A comptroller fakes his death to avoid getting arrested for embezzling from an investment firm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403090000 +0000" stop="20250403093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403093000 +0000" stop="20250403100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403100000 +0000" stop="20250403103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Capture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The captain has ordered top priority be given to ending a rash of burglaries in the area, and all signs point to career criminal Reno West. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed use their creativity to neutralize a vicious guard dog at the home of an unresponsive diabetic man, investigate the theft of a jade figurine from a mansion and respond to a domestic dispute.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403103000 +0000" stop="20250403110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hollywood Division</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>There's a new dispatcher on today's day watch, and while Reed can't stand her voice, Malloy sees the situation much differently. On patrol, they search for a hit and run driver who left a small girl in serious condition, investigate a break-in at a synagogue, deal with a drunk woman who is searching for her daughter and become part of a SWAT team attempting to neutralize a sniper terrorizing the movie studio from which he was just fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403110000 +0000" stop="20250403120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill &amp; Toony Open A Video Store</sub-title>
    <desc>""Toony Video" is going to bring back the VHS rental business! Maybe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403120000 +0000" stop="20250403123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Glamour Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is shocked to learn that the glamorous Kitty Bannerman is visiting Mayfield and he's afraid that she will find out that he's not the rich hot shot that he told her he was in the letters that he had sent her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403123000 +0000" stop="20250403130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Chuckie's New Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor gives Wally the responsibility of taking her son, Chuckie, down to the shoe store to pick out a pair of shoes. However, when Wally gives the job to Beaver, Beaver finds himself searching for Chuckie, who has gotten himself lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403130000 +0000" stop="20250403140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Petulant Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret was a much younger woman on the make who entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403140000 +0000" stop="20250403150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Crook  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Wally McDaniels, a fellow choir member, after he is arrested for killing the man who had turned him in to the police for stealing rare books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403150000 +0000" stop="20250403160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Home Is Where The Heart Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Maybelle the madam returns to Sparta with her " nieces ".And sets up shop just out of Gillespie's jurisdiction. Her return is not without controversy and soon one of her most vocal critics is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403160000 +0000" stop="20250403170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Substitute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Miss Hunter is called away unexpectedly, a substitute teacher with ways of her own takes over</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403170000 +0000" stop="20250403173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Legal Revenge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc rides up to the Tibbs house to say his services are available. Florie won't invite him in, but her husband yells to let him in. He cut his leg chopping wood. Doc wants to take him to Dodge. Forie says no. Doc does what he can. Doc tells Matt Mr. Tibbs was holding a gun under his blanket. It was no wood cutting accident. She cut him with a knife."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403173000 +0000" stop="20250403180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Mistake</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kitty is in her cowgirl outfit. She's just return from a morning ride. Earl Haney, who runs the faro table, has had somebody bust his head open. Earl says he had a red shirt, black hair and mustache."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403180000 +0000" stop="20250403190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Oath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When his father is hung, Charlie vows to kill the man he thinks is responsible—Ben. It eventually falls on Joe to dissuade Charlie from his plan of revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403190000 +0000" stop="20250403193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403193000 +0000" stop="20250403200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403200000 +0000" stop="20250403210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Les Rand Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A paroled convict blames his physician father when Native American wife dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403210000 +0000" stop="20250403220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Most Deadly Passage (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Roy and Johnny are sent to Seattle to study the techniques used there. A skydiver jumps off the Space Needle, a worker is trapped at the top of the Kingdome, and a fuel pumper loads a ferry with gasoline instead of diesel fuel, which sets the ferry on fire in the middle of the Elliot Bay."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403220000 +0000" stop="20250403223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403223000 +0000" stop="20250403230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403230000 +0000" stop="20250403233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250403233000 +0000" stop="20250404000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404000000 +0000" stop="20250404003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Punch In The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>In going through some courthouse paperwork, Barney discovers an open case involving Floyd and Charlie Foley. He tries to close the books on the case, but ends up reopening the arguments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404003000 +0000" stop="20250404010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie and his friends decide to start a newspaper. The early issues don't sell well, so the boys begin eavesdropping and printing local gossip in the paper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404010000 +0000" stop="20250404013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Our Hero, The Banker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Lance Bradford has started working as vice president at the Commerce Bank, though he really isn’t doing anything helpful. Everyone at the bank, except Drysdale, is excited to get Jet Stream working at the bank. Jethro sees how the girls at the bank react to Lance’s Air Force uniform, so he goes out to get a four-star general uniform. When Lance visits, needing a new account, Jethro tells him he’ll put his whole allowance in the bank if he sets him up with the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404013000 +0000" stop="20250404020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, Super Chef</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter and Sgt. Hacker make a bet that Gomer cannot learn to cook in 24 hours. Hacker works with him but Gomer just can't seem to get it right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404020000 +0000" stop="20250404023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Klink Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer for a German suicide squad train bound for the Russian front in order to steal key documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404023000 +0000" stop="20250404030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gasoline War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men plan to destroy a gasoline station that has just been built in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404030000 +0000" stop="20250404033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Harry's Mirage And Grill</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Wiggins, just before Christmas, Mr. Tudball conducts a fire drill to keep the insurance company appeased. Then, in Harry's Mirage and Grill, Harvey and Tim find a desert oasis with a beautiful woman -- or is it just a mirage?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404033000 +0000" stop="20250404043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Flighty Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>When eighteen-year-old Trudy Holbrook's mother dies leaving her $10 million, two men blow into town claiming to be her long-lost father. Then the only person who could identify the real father, a blind uncle, is killed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404043500 +0000" stop="20250404050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Shot An Arrow Into The Air</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts crash-land on what they believe to be an asteroid and have limited water supplies to sustain them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404050500 +0000" stop="20250404053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Pushed by his girlfriend, Larry Chetnick plans to rob his company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404053500 +0000" stop="20250404060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Martha Mason, Movie Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>After years of being teased by her husband, a woman discovers that she looks very similar to movie star and decided to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404060500 +0000" stop="20250404070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Deadfall: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is fired from Intertect while his boss suffers from a medically induced psychosis, causing Joe to use desperate measures to crack the case and save Wickersham's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404070500 +0000" stop="20250404080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady On The Run</sub-title>
    <desc>"After witnessing a murder, a woman flees to a sanitarium where she was once a patient. It's up to Cannon to find her and keep her safe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404080500 +0000" stop="20250404090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Challenge, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As Barnaby attempts to uncover the motives for a man's alleged suicide, another detective tries to cover up the facts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250404090000 +0000" stop="20250404093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
