<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927193000 +0000" stop="20250927200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheridan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Blandon, a man with only one good arm, wanders onto the ranch. Lucas gives Blandon a job to "hire him and Mark a clear conscience." General Sheridan and his patrol wander by and Lucas offers to let them stay the night at the ranch. Blandon once pulled a gun on General Sheridan; as it turns out, Blandon was a Confederate soldier who once had General Sheridan in his gun sight during the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927200000 +0000" stop="20250927210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Backshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Jefferson aids Rowdy after his horse takes a spill. Sam is a wanted man and asks Rowdy to turn him in but give the $5,000 reward to his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927210000 +0000" stop="20250927213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Killer's Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After having killed a bank robber, Paladin is accused of having taken the stolen money. He visits the dead man's widow and tries to make amends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927213000 +0000" stop="20250927220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Vanishing Act</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Randall tracks down a bank-robbing magician and his henchmen, but while in custody of the sheriff, the man and his gang escape. Shot while tracking them down for a second time, Randall must keep the magician and his men at bay to save his own skin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250927220000 +0000" stop="20250928000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Vagabond Loafers, Self Made Maids, Hugs And Mugs, He Cooked His Goose, Tricky Dicks, For Crimin' Out Loud</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are plumbers who are called out to a fancy mansion where a high society party is being thrown., The Stooges are artists who want to marry their models; "Moella", "Larraine", and "Shempetta".  The girls' father doesn't approve, so the Stooges tickle him into submission. , The Stooges are private detectives hired to protect a rich politician.  After the man disappears, the boys wander around his spooky mansion confronting various villains and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man. , The Stooges run a furniture store and come into possession of a stolen pearl necklace.  Three crooked dames convince the boys that the necklace is theirs, and when the real thieves arrive, the Stooges fight to defend the girl's property.  The Stooges defeat the bad guys and the girls decide to go honest and return the necklace to its rightful owner. , Larry is a pet dealer who's seeing Moe's wife while at the same time trying to steal Shemp's fiancee.  When Moe's become suspicious, Larry attempts to frame Shemp as the boyfriend.  He gets Shemp a job as a door-to-door pajama salesman and sends him to Moe's apartment, and then tells both Moe and Shemp's fiancee to go there and catch him in the act.  Larry's plan backfires when Shemp catches him and lets Moe deliver some punishment. , The Stooges are policemen on the trail of a murderer.  They unsuccessfully interrogate an Italian organ grinder, among other suspects, and then catch the bad guy after a gunfight that nearly destroys the police station. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928000000 +0000" stop="20250928023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Strangler</sub-title>
    <desc>"A reporter hunts down a 144-year old alchemist who is killing women for their blood."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928023000 +0000" stop="20250928050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Amityville 3-d</sub-title>
    <desc>"A journalist purchases an infamous house to prove its supernatural horrors are fake but discovers the evil may be real."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928050000 +0000" stop="20250928060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Keeper: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Keeper, played by Michael Rennie, is a zookeeper of sorts. He wants to take the children and add them to his collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928060000 +0000" stop="20250928070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The World Ended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview loses contact with the world after a fanatic senator hypnotizes the entire crew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928070000 +0000" stop="20250928080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Chamber Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Diamond thieves take refuge in a wax museum, and Fitzhugh and Barry are caught in the middle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928080000 +0000" stop="20250928090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Billy The Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers find themselves being hunted by Billy the Kid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928090000 +0000" stop="20250928100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent is summoned when an alien outpost is discovered at a ski lodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928100000 +0000" stop="20250928110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Storm</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams (and Ben) await the arrival of Mad Jack and Nakuma for a great feast. Before they come,an Indian woman shows up, seeking her missing daughter. With a violent storm coming, it's a race against time to find her and have the feast as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928110000 +0000" stop="20250928113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Grizzly Disappears</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bears read signs! They read the signs signaling the beginning of winter – within twenty-four hours of first warning, all bears have disappeared into their caves.  We spend this last day with a young grizzly as he prepares for his long nap."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928113000 +0000" stop="20250928120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Porpoise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and his crew sail the waters of the California coast in search of the porpoise of the Pacific."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928120000 +0000" stop="20250928123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lost World Of Angel Falls</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan fly into the remote interior of Venezuela to a jutting plateau whose sheer cliff echoes the perpetual thunder of Angel Falls.  It is a region so remote that it has often been called the Lost World."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928123000 +0000" stop="20250928130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Exploring The Llanos</sub-title>
    <desc>"In South America there are fresh water porpoises living inland in the rivers and streams.  During the dry season, as the rivers recede, these porpoises may perish as the water level drops.  Marlin and Jim go on an expedition to rescue the trapped llanos porpoises."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928130000 +0000" stop="20250928133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Sea Lion Number Seven</sub-title>
    <desc>"Far out in the Pacific Ocean lies a tiny island.  Once every year, these barren rocks explode with life as Steller sea lions come ashore by the thousands to breed and give birth to their young. Marlin sails to the island to join a team of scientists to observe and take part in a tagging project."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928133000 +0000" stop="20250928140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Return Of The Salmon</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the chill, glacier-fed streams of Alaska sockeye salmon are born, and follow the current to the sea.  After two or three great annual circuits of the North Pacific, the call comes to return."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928140000 +0000" stop="20250928143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Grass Is Always Greener</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Each thinking their spouse has a much easier time of it, Mike and Carol switch roles for a day. Carol must help the boys with baseball practice and Mike must help Marcia with a cooking badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928143000 +0000" stop="20250928150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Locket, Found Locket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan receives a mysterious locket in the mail. Pretty soon a manhunt begins to find the sender, the only clue being the typewriter used to address the envelope drops its ‘y.’ When the locket mysteriously vanishes, Peter suggests they re-enact exactly what they were doing the night it disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928150000 +0000" stop="20250928153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Goin' To Chicago</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie, Potsie and Ralph go on a trip to Chicago with the school choir. Not wanting to stay in their hotel room all night, they decide to sneak out and see a show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928153000 +0000" stop="20250928160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Tenants Are Revolting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley believe they are doing a good deed by calling in a building inspector, until Mrs. Babish is given a deadline by which repairs are to be made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928160000 +0000" stop="20250928163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928163000 +0000" stop="20250928170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>No Children Allowed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a cranky tenant (Elizabeth Patterson in her first appearance as Mrs. Trumble) threatens to move because of Little Ricky's loud crying, Ethel makes it clear that her friendship with Lucy is more important than a rental agreement. But Ethel doesn't let the Ricardos forget her loyalty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928170000 +0000" stop="20250928173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's License</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Now that Wally is 17, he feels it's about time that he get his drivers license. However, June and Ward are a bit apprehensive about the idea of Wally driving, but Wally is persistant and finally gets his parents to agree to let him take a drivers class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928173000 +0000" stop="20250928180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his heart set on taking a swing at being a paper boy again but another kid beats him to it. This leads Beaver to think about using sabatoge to get the new paper boy fired. However, the boy may just do that himself when the service becomes terrible leading Beaver to confront him only to discover he is a she.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928180000 +0000" stop="20250928183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Strike Oil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed Clampett's swamp is loaded with oil. When a wildcatter discovers the huge pool, Jed sells his land to the O.K. Oil Company and, at the urging of cousin Pearl, moves his family to a 35-room mansion in Beverly Hills, California. But when they get to their new home, which they think is a prison and the gardeners are inmates, they are mistaken for vandals and get arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928183000 +0000" stop="20250928190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Settled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at their new home, but find there aren't any of the conveniences of their old home. Jethro makes a few new discoveries, things they have never seen before, like pink chickens (flamingoes) and a cement pond. When Miss Jane Hathaway arrives, the executive secretary for Mr. Drysdale, she mistakes the clan for a staff of bumbling, insubordinate backwoods servants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928190000 +0000" stop="20250928193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan's Living Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An experimental robot launched by the Air Force parachutes onto the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928193000 +0000" stop="20250928200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Forward March</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways are frightened as the sounds of battle, including hand grenades and machine guns, rock the island. The culprit turns out to be a gorilla who has found in an old WWII arsenal cave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928200000 +0000" stop="20250928203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Blast From The Past  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Thelma's high school reputation comes back to haunt her 50 years later.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928203000 +0000" stop="20250928210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Fights Back  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After calling in to give advice, Mama gets her own radio show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928210000 +0000" stop="20250928220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Green, But Not Jolly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A man insists a woman is his reincarnated wife; Julie's hair causes her headaches; a man discovers a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928220000 +0000" stop="20250928223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928223000 +0000" stop="20250928230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Lucky Meisenheimer- Yo-yo's</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucky Meisenheimer has assembled the world's largest, and most dazzling, yo-yo collection, including a laser yo-yo, an ice-cream-making yo-yo, and a 1950s Mickey Mouse Club yo-yo. Lisa's invited "America's Toy Scout" Joel Mageeto to appraise the collection, and Lucky offers both Lisa and Joel some basic lessons in yo-yo technique."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928230000 +0000" stop="20250928233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Old Soldiers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is appointed temporary commander of the 4077th when Colonel Potter rushes off to Tokyo on a mysterious mission. While in command, Hawkeye's main problem is housing a large group of Korean refugees comprised mainly of rambunctious children who need medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250928233000 +0000" stop="20250929000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Morale Victory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of their constant complaints about the quality of recreational activities at the 4077th, Colonel Potter appoints Hawkeye and B.J. as the new morale officers. Winchester's morale has already reached a new peak: He's ecstatic about his operation on a wounded soldier, Sheridan, which saved the boy's leg, leaving only "negligible" side effects—less use of his right hand. However, the soldier was a concert pianist before the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929000000 +0000" stop="20250929003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Grandpa Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie has difficuly keeping his blood pressure down for a company physical after the family launches into a heavy debate over the baby's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929003000 +0000" stop="20250929010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Suspects Mike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria suspects hanky-panky when she meets the beautiful blonde Mike's been tutoring after school hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929010000 +0000" stop="20250929013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Civil Rights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie gets a lesson in civil liberties when he's arrested using outlawed tear gas to protect himself against a mugger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929013000 +0000" stop="20250929020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Is Nervous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria takes out her frustrations about being pregnant on Mike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929020000 +0000" stop="20250929023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Don Rickles And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Don Rickles and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 12/07/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929023000 +0000" stop="20250929030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Ross Martin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Ross Martin. Originally aired on 11/16/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929030000 +0000" stop="20250929033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, How We Met On The Night That We Danced</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of Army boots remind Rob and Laura about the first time they met.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929033000 +0000" stop="20250929040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Harrison B. Harding Of Camp Crowder, Mo.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob thinks that a stranger claiming to be an old Army pal is actually a con-man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929040000 +0000" stop="20250929043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929043000 +0000" stop="20250929050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien crash-lands in a remote mountain village, stirring up fear and animosity among the villagers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929050000 +0000" stop="20250929053000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Summer Shade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple moves to a new town and discovers that their child seems to be the only one around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929053000 +0000" stop="20250929060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Crime For Mothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic woman threatens to take her daughter from the guardianship of her foster parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929060000 +0000" stop="20250929070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Alexander Vanin, arrested and convicted for espionage, hid a list of agents operating in the U.S. His control, Mishenko of the EEPR, has been ordered to get the list but Vanin refuses to give in because then Mishenko would cut him loose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929070000 +0000" stop="20250929080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Last Second Of A Big Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barry Craft figures he'll get some publicity by arranging to have Kimble captured at his wild-animal show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929080000 +0000" stop="20250929090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage</sub-title>
    <desc>"Private investigator Harry Orwell helps the police in their effort to disarm a dangerous bandit barricaded in a liquor store."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929090000 +0000" stop="20250929093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929093000 +0000" stop="20250929100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929100000 +0000" stop="20250929103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 54 -- Impersonation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed hope to find an impostor as they investigate a boxing promoter's accusation that a police detective stole $350 from him. In the meantime, they deal with a disgruntled wife who is in the process of destroying her own car in the middle of a downtown street, investigate a gun theft from a pawn shop, drive up on a home burglary in progress and obtain critical information while interrogating a suspected car thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929103000 +0000" stop="20250929110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 24 -- A Rare Occasion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy spends a weekend afternoon attending a barbecue at Reed's home, where Reed lets him hold his newborn son for the first time and tries to set him up with his wife's friend. However, their relaxation is interrupted when they have to deal with a young neighbor who overdoses on drugs and becomes the target of his dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929110000 +0000" stop="20250929120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Forgotten Fads</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill gives Toony a lesson in forgotten fads."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929120000 +0000" stop="20250929123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Double Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's new girlfriend, Carolyn, can't go out to the movies on Saturday night because she has to watch her little sister, Susan. Carolyn suggests that Beaver take Susan out to the movies and that they all double date. Not wanting to let Wally down, Beaver decides to go along, despite being nervous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929123000 +0000" stop="20250929130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie, The Businessman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie get jobs at the Mayfield Dairy thanks to Ward pulling some strings. They soon unknowingly find themselves involved in a plot started by the foreman and his assistant, who are secretly stealing the merchandise. When Ward learns of the plot, he warns Wally who in turn tries to warn Eddie, but Eddie doesn't buy it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929130000 +0000" stop="20250929140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sardonic Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Frank Lessing, a payroll officer on an Army base, is found murdered and Sergeant Joseph Dexter is charged with the crime. The case hinges on a payroll robbery committed in the Philippines years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929140000 +0000" stop="20250929150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929150000 +0000" stop="20250929160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>First Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Sparta P.D. gets its first black policewoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929160000 +0000" stop="20250929170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Conscience</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason expresses doubt to the army recruiters that he could ever kill a person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929170000 +0000" stop="20250929180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Abe Blocker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt pursues a frontiersman who's using force to take homesteaders' land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929180000 +0000" stop="20250929190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Iron Butterfly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a former actress kills her former boyfriend, Hoss takes the blame and the dead man's senator father vows to have his revenge by taking down the Cartwrights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929190000 +0000" stop="20250929193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929193000 +0000" stop="20250929200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929200000 +0000" stop="20250929210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kitty Albright Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>"Kitty Albright is a registered nurse who's stagecoach is attacked and destroyed. Flint agrees to let her use her new skill on the wagon train. She quickly becomes disturbed at the lack of hygiene and health in general around the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929210000 +0000" stop="20250929220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Limelight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man with a history of heart trouble becomes agitated when his daughter is trapped under a backhoe. A boy shoots himself with a pellet gun. Another paramedic appears on the news and in the paper, making John jealous. A babysitter has an anxiety attack. Gage and DeSoto rescue Brice from a fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929220000 +0000" stop="20250929223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lend A Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Irritated that the 4077th is planning a "surprise" party for him, Hawkeye volunteers to go to the aid of a wounded surgeon at the front. An additional irritant to Hawkeye is the arrival of Dr. Borelli, a wisecracking medical advisor with whom he habitually disagrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929223000 +0000" stop="20250929230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Cruel World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger redecorates his quarters, but the resultant ridicule he receives drives him to new heights in his efforts to get out of the Army. Meanwhile, the doctors are perplexed by the reaction of an Asian-American war hero who tries to kill himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929230000 +0000" stop="20250929233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th can't escape the Korean War, even in its dreams. Exhausted after two days without sleep, members of the 4077th steal away for catnaps and experience dreams that reveal their fears, yearnings and frustrations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250929233000 +0000" stop="20250930000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Co-respondent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. finds himself attracted to a famous war correspondent, Aggie O'Shea, who has fallen in love with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930000000 +0000" stop="20250930003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930003000 +0000" stop="20250930010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taylors quickly realize why they haven't invited Bee's sister and her husband, Ollie, for a visit in more than a decade. When Uncle Ollie borrows Andy's squad car to go fishing, it's the final straw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930010000 +0000" stop="20250930013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Snow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny misses the seasons, especially the snowy winter. She wants to go home to the hills and see some snow. Jed decides to let Granny win and calls Drysdale to tell him that Granny wants to head back home to the hills. He learns that she wants the snow back. Drysdale comes up with a plan to keep the hillbillies in Beverly Hills, telling them that a big blizzard is going to strike Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930013000 +0000" stop="20250930020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is pleased when asked to be one of three busboys for a visiting colonel. But his attention is turned to the officer's sad little daughter, who is lonely and needs a playmate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930020000 +0000" stop="20250930023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses a broken water main under the camp to aid the escape of captured resistance fighters by creating a health spa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930023000 +0000" stop="20250930030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Klink, A Bomb And A Short Fuse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>General Burkhalter wants Hogan to defuse a bomb that has landed in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930030000 +0000" stop="20250930033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Debbie Reynolds And John Davidson</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Debbie Reynolds and John Davidson. Originally aired on 11/30/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930033000 +0000" stop="20250930043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Reckless Rockhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a businessman responsible for decimating a local mining business returns to town, it is not long before he is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930043500 +0000" stop="20250930050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Dummy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist is convinced that his dummy is not only alive but also evil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930050500 +0000" stop="20250930053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A practical joke has a devastating effect on an adulterous spouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930053500 +0000" stop="20250930060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Housewives being blackmailed by a plumber exact their revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930060500 +0000" stop="20250930070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Problem Of Innocence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The daughter of an ex-convict is the leading suspect in murders involving unrecovered loot from one of her father's robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930070500 +0000" stop="20250930080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930080500 +0000" stop="20250930090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Run To Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's friend dies of an alleged heart attack during his constitutional.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930090000 +0000" stop="20250930093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930093000 +0000" stop="20250930100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930100000 +0000" stop="20250930103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 124 -- Airport</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are rendered powerless when a drunken man with no flight experience decides to take a solo flight in a stolen airplane at a busy airport. Later, they try to locate a 17-year-old runaway living in a condemned home with a much older man, engage in a shootout with a convenience store robber and search for a booby-trapped bank safe that has been stolen with a tow truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930103000 +0000" stop="20250930110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 94 -- Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy fears that a boxer who has just been paroled after serving a murder sentence is going to seek revenge against him. Out on patrol, they try to save a man who has been crushed while working under a stolen car, apprehend a liquor store robber who swears revenge against reed, change a flat tire on their patrol car, locate a four-year-old child who locked himself in a refrigerator and become the targets of an ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930110000 +0000" stop="20250930120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Catch The Connection</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony solve a cartoon mystery as part of Mr. Quizzer's newest game show "Catch the Connection!""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930120000 +0000" stop="20250930123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To Ella</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After coming home late on a school night, Ward and June punish Beaver by not allowing him to go anywhere on school nights. Beaver feels the punishment is unfair, so Eddie suggests Beaver write to an advice column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930123000 +0000" stop="20250930130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Bachelor-at-large</sub-title>
    <desc>"The news that Eddie has moved out of his parent's house and into an apartment of his own has June worried that Wally may be contemplating something similar. However, Wally gets a picture of just how "happy" Eddie is being on his own and it makes him think twice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930130000 +0000" stop="20250930140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Curious Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Rhoda Reynolds is charged with murdering her blackmailing ex-husband, Arthur Kane. At the trial, Mason moves the proceedings to the room in which Kane was murdered in order to re-enact the fatal night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930140000 +0000" stop="20250930150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 2  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930150000 +0000" stop="20250930160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Crackdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Someone is selling crack to teenagers and Sweet tries desperately to save a young addict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930160000 +0000" stop="20250930170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Obstacle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy asks his family to help Mike Paxton, a friend who was recently handicapped</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930170000 +0000" stop="20250930180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt comes to the rescue when a father and son abuse the mother and daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930180000 +0000" stop="20250930190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Rattlesnake Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Doyle gang escapes while being transferred to a prison in Virginia City, they take Jamie and three others hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930190000 +0000" stop="20250930193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930193000 +0000" stop="20250930200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930200000 +0000" stop="20250930210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Maud Frazer Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>"Maud Frazer takes command of her wagon train after all the men are killed. Flint tries to dissuade Maud from going through hostile Indian country where there is gold.. She proceeds anyway but is forced to change plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930210000 +0000" stop="20250930220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Steel Inferno, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A careless worker sparks an explosive fire in a high-rise building. Station 110 leads a full alarm response, assisted by Squad 51. A triage team from Rampart Hospital, led by Dr. Brackett, sets up in a nearby garage. Several workmen and two women including the fiancee of a paramedic remain trapped on the 16th floor. A Coast Guard helicopter assists in rooftop evacuation; Dixie and Dr. Early take charge of the many patients at Rampart. A paramedic is injured attempting a rescue, while Gage and DeSoto extricate themselves from a broken elevator. An explosion on the 21st floor injures a fire captain, necessitating a dangerous rescue down an elevator shaft."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930220000 +0000" stop="20250930223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Back Pay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Angered by the way civilian doctors in the States are profiting from the war, Hawkeye presents the Army with a bill for his medical services. Meanwhile, Charles reluctantly demonstrates American medical practices to three Korean medics, and is on the receiving end of their medical expertise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930223000 +0000" stop="20250930230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>April Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A no-nonsense Colonel, who is notorious as a hard-nosed disciplinarian, visits the 4077th during an outbreak of April Fools' Day pranksterism. Colonel Potter tries in vain to halt the mayhem before Colonel Tucker arrives in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930230000 +0000" stop="20250930233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Best Of Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to some R&amp;R in Tokyo, a North Korean soldier forces Hawkeye to perform an emergency roadside operation on his buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250930233000 +0000" stop="20251001000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Members of the 4077th share their impressions of war in response to letters from fourth graders in Hawkeye's hometown. Margaret writes about how there are some patients she will never forget, while the Colonel tells of his days as "Hoops."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001000000 +0000" stop="20251001003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Education Of Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. is back in Mayberry to get his diploma. He is so determined that Andy convinces Helen to allow him to attend class, but Ernest T. isn't exactly classroom material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001003000 +0000" stop="20251001010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An old beau of Aunt Bee comes to town to court her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001010000 +0000" stop="20251001013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Double Naught Jethro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro decides to give up his dream of becoming a brain surgeon to try his luck at the spy business. Meanwhile, The Banker’s Convention is going on, including the beauty contest for Most Beautiful Bank Employee, and Drysdale could lose because of Mr. Cushing’s contestant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001013000 +0000" stop="20251001020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Star Is Born</sub-title>
    <desc>"Carter becomes the star of a documentary about the Marine Corps."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001020000 +0000" stop="20251001023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Tanks For The Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to photograph and destroy a model for a radio-controlled tank that is being tested at camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001023000 +0000" stop="20251001030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Adolf Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>With camp security raised, Hogan and his men are desperate to smuggle top-secret German fortifications information to the Allies. The solution? Make liberal use of Carter's remarkable impersonation of Adolf Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001030000 +0000" stop="20251001033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence, Durward Kirby, And Julie Bond</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Steve Lawrence, Durward Kirby, and Julie Bond. Originally aired on 12/14/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001033000 +0000" stop="20251001043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Latent Lover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A man left unhinged by his wife's affair has been acting out in very strange ways, even attempting to rob a bank in his despair. And when his wife ends up murdered, he is the natural suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001043500 +0000" stop="20251001050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man's Fancy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>When a newlywed couple visit the groom's childhood home, the ties of the past prove too strong to resist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001050500 +0000" stop="20251001053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Throwback</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Immature Elliott Gray challenges a much older gentleman for the hand of Enid Patterson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001053500 +0000" stop="20251001060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kiss-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After spending six years in prison for a robbery he didn't commit, a man decides to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001060500 +0000" stop="20251001070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Danford File</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix is hired to investigate a case of blackmail, the blackmailer turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001070500 +0000" stop="20251001080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Conspiracy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank Cannon and Barnaby Jones team up for an investigation of a murder at a big corporation in which a deliveryman was charged with the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001080500 +0000" stop="20251001090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Anger, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A black cab driver runs from a murder scene on the grounds that circumstantial evidence - and racism - would make him the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001090000 +0000" stop="20251001093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001093000 +0000" stop="20251001100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001100000 +0000" stop="20251001103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 104 -- The Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspect who frames an employee of a manufacturing plant for theft and then plants a powerful bomb on the premises. They also apprehend two criminals after questioning a suspicious man who is carrying heavy bags down the street, and protect an innocent motorist from a street race that still ends in tragedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001103000 +0000" stop="20251001110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 74 -- Light Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed spend a night shift on desk duty after Malloy breaks his wrist and another office worker calls in sick. With the assistance of a new female recruit, they deal with a homesick elderly woman who refuses to identify herself, help a lenient father bail out his son and become suspicious of a man who walks in looking for a wanted fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001110000 +0000" stop="20251001120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Weird Fall Fests</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit true American festivals dedicated to fire ants, werewolves, wooly worms and more!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001120000 +0000" stop="20251001123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Joins Record Club</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver wants to join a record club and asks Ward for the money to join. Fed up with Beaver constantly asking for money, Ward decides to put him on an allowance. However, Beaver is so thrilled with his records he disreguards the bills for them and quickly finds himself swamped with records, a rising bill and not enough allowance to pay for everything."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001123000 +0000" stop="20251001130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Car Accident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for the weekend and Wally asks to borrow Ward's new car to go to a dance. Although hesitant, Ward finally gives in and lets him take it. However, after the dance, Lumpy runs into some car trouble which results in Wally smashing the headlight on the car. Wally is now faced with having it repaired and paying for it himself and trying to find a way to break it gently to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001130000 +0000" stop="20251001140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Buried Clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Slimy Jack Hardisty embezzles $100,000 from his father-in-law, Dr. Blane. The greedy Hardisty then tries to blackmail the doctor for more. Mason is hired by Dr. Blane to put an end to Hardisty's machinations but before he can swing into action Hardisty is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001140000 +0000" stop="20251001150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cover Girl  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock meets Conrad's new girlfriend, Carla Royce. When Carla's boss is murdered and she is suspected, Matlock defends her against the charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001150000 +0000" stop="20251001160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Time Of The Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a private investigator searching for a missing child is found dead, the evidence points to a local dance teacher - a neighbor that Parker has become very fond of.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001160000 +0000" stop="20251001170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Parting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia is always tired these days. When a rest does not help, she sees a doctor and learns what is wrong</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001170000 +0000" stop="20251001180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Sunday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When his uncle comes to visit, Chester's plan to shorten his stay doesn't exactly work out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001180000 +0000" stop="20251001190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Come, Easy Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The peace of the Ponderosa is disrupted when a gambler arrives for a stay after losing all his money in a stock scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001190000 +0000" stop="20251001193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart arrives in North Fork in search of renegade indians suspected of the brutal killing of a Texas Ranger and his family. The townspeople are suspicious of him, however, when they discover that he, too, is an indian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001193000 +0000" stop="20251001200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarding House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Reformed card shark Julia Massini now runs a respectable boarding house in North Fork, but Sid Fallon is threatening to reveal her sordid past unless she lets him turn the establishment into a saloon and gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001200000 +0000" stop="20251001210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Selena Hartnell Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>"Selena Hartnell joins the train after bandits attack her wagon. Later, she reveals she is a bounty hunter looking for William Barrett, a murderer on the run. It turns out that Barrett is Will Cottrell, the leader of pacifists on the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001210000 +0000" stop="20251001220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Steel Inferno, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A careless worker sparks an explosive fire in a high-rise building. Station 110 leads a full alarm response, assisted by Squad 51. A triage team from Rampart Hospital, led by Dr. Brackett, sets up in a nearby garage. Several workmen and two women including the fiancee of a paramedic remain trapped on the 16th floor. A Coast Guard helicopter assists in rooftop evacuation; Dixie and Dr. Early take charge of the many patients at Rampart. A paramedic is injured attempting a rescue, while Gage and DeSoto extricate themselves from a broken elevator. An explosion on the 21st floor injures a fire captain, necessitating a dangerous rescue down an elevator shaft."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001220000 +0000" stop="20251001223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cementing Relationships</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A jilted Italian soldier, Corpsman Ignazio De Simone, is smitten by Margaret; Klinger pours a cement floor in the operating room to fight the spread of germs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001223000 +0000" stop="20251001230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Father's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret has trouble pretending she's a chip off the old block when her dad, blood and guts "Howitzer" Al Houlihan, arrives for a visit. Also, Hawkeye fixes up a soldier who repays them with a large side of steak, but the general who it belongs to is really steamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001230000 +0000" stop="20251001233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Retention Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger is so depressed by news that his ex-wife plans to remarry, he reenlists for an additional six-year stretch. Meanwhile, a male nurse has a gripe against the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251001233000 +0000" stop="20251002000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester takes command during Potter's absence; and B.J. and Hawkeye try to convince the Marines to grant a hardship discharge to an immigrant soldier, Private Jost Van Liter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002000000 +0000" stop="20251002003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Bloodhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's attempts to train an old mutt named Blue as a police dog coincide with a manhunt for an escaped criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002003000 +0000" stop="20251002010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In The Middle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Thelma Lou have an argument. They reconcile quickly, but it leads to other arguments between Andy and Barney, Thelma Lou and Helen, Andy and Helen, and another between Barney and Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002010000 +0000" stop="20251002013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Tag-team Match</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the day after Granny beat up the Boston Strong Girl, making her the new champ, and the Clampetts are celebrating Granny’s great victory. But not all is well. The woman who plays the Boston Strong Girl is in trouble for getting beat up. The woman who plays Rebecca of Donnybrook Farm, a former topless waitress, has learned the truth, getting an invitation from Granny to visit. Their manager, Gene Booth, sees this as an opportunity to get Granny to fight, after hearing the huge ratings the fight got.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002013000 +0000" stop="20251002020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Phone Company</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries to repay the $40 he received at a pay phone to the phone company, but gets arrested instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002020000 +0000" stop="20251002023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One Army At A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter convinces the German he is one of them when he is captured in German uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002023000 +0000" stop="20251002030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Standing Room Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to save Klink from an officer who plans on turning him in for not having balanced books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002030000 +0000" stop="20251002033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Jerry Lewis And Leslie Uggams</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Jerry Lewis and Leslie Uggams. Originally aired on 01/11/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002033000 +0000" stop="20251002043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wooden Nickels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason becomes embroiled in a case involving coin collectors, counterfeit coins, fraud—and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002043500 +0000" stop="20251002050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Sing The Body Electric</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A widower buys a robotic grandmother for his three children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002050500 +0000" stop="20251002053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a man turns to prayer, he starts to win at the races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002053500 +0000" stop="20251002060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Incident In A Small Jail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>In prison for jaywalking, a salesman finds himself locked in a cell with an accused murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002060500 +0000" stop="20251002070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Polka Dot Dress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix scoffs at a psychic's tale about a woman in danger. Then the prophecy comes true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002070500 +0000" stop="20251002080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Medicine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates a doctors claim that he is innocent of a death he was charged with concerning a patient he was treating that had slipped into a diabetic coma. Cannon becomes involved in a medical malpractice suit when a young resident physician is charged with making the wrong diagnosis on a woman in an apparent diabetic coma who dies after his treatment. Hired by the hospital facing a two million dollar suit, Cannon hears testimony of the accused Dr. Jeff Reston, played by guest star David Birney, that the woman he treated wore a diabetic's bracelet. She was, in fact, suffering from hypoglycemia. But the bracelet disappeared and none of the nurses attending with Reston can back up his story. Reston then gives Cannon a motive for a possible conspiracy against him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002080500 +0000" stop="20251002090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Point, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks for a millionaire's mistress, unaware that she's stolen a priceless objet d'art.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002090000 +0000" stop="20251002093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002093000 +0000" stop="20251002100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002100000 +0000" stop="20251002103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 114 -- The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed witness a young hispanic man save a trapped watchman from a burning warehouse, but become suspicious when he resists numerous attempts of private and public commendation. They also try to prevent a drunken man from falling out a window, and resuscitate a man with a heart condition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002103000 +0000" stop="20251002110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 134 -- Child Stealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has to deal with the consequences of forgetting to roll up the window on the patrol car before he left it. Back on patrol, Malloy and Reed search for an estranged husband who kidnaps his own child, deal with an elderly man who tries to pay for a meal with trading stamps, engage in a shootout with an escaped prisoner caught napping on a city bus and pull over a hijacked delivery van full of booze.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002110000 +0000" stop="20251002120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1982</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony reminisce on the year 1982."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002120000 +0000" stop="20251002123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Sheep Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>At school, Beaver gets into an argument with a girl who retaliates by making fun of Beaver's hair, calling him a sheepdog. Incredibly self-concious, Beaver goes out to the store and buys different hairsprays and gels to try to improve his hairdo. He doesn't get the reaction he was expecting when he tries his new hairdo out on his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002123000 +0000" stop="20251002130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>During one of his football team's games, Beaver is sent in and scores the winning touchdown, which results in a picture in the paper. Soon, Beaver finds himself swamped with attention and quickly lets it goes to his head. He begins acting like he's better than everyone and begins to alienate Gilbert, Whitey and Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002130000 +0000" stop="20251002140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Married Moonlighter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A moonlighting school teacher is charged with the murder of an acquaintance he had taken home after the man had earlier raised a disturbance at his night job at a cafe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002140000 +0000" stop="20251002150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Biker  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a well-known actor with a bad reputation is murdered, Matlock is asked by a judge friend to defend his son, who had recently lost his job as bodyguard for the deceased.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002150000 +0000" stop="20251002160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An outlaw family seeks revenge against Bubba after he is forced to shoot one of them during a holdup. The chief wants him to stay out of sight until they are arrested - a suggestion that does not set well with Bubba.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002160000 +0000" stop="20251002170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Burden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>While Jim-Bob is working underneath a car, it falls and Jim-Bob has a close call with death</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002170000 +0000" stop="20251002180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>False Front</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A gambler makes a bet that a man who's never used a gun can pass as a gunslinger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002180000 +0000" stop="20251002190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Home For Jamie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamie's grandfather comes to claim him just as Ben is arranging for his adoption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002190000 +0000" stop="20251002193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas puts his life in jeopardy when he agrees to testify in a murder case involving a witness killed before he could testify and a killer still at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002193000 +0000" stop="20251002200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw Sam Morley falls in love with a young woman who has a serious illness. He asks Lucas to turn him in for the reward and then use the money to pay for her medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002200000 +0000" stop="20251002210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clementine Jones Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>"Clementine Jones is in the process of being thrown out of a town when a bank robbery occurs. She ends up joining the Hale wagon train on a wagon with one of the bank robbers using it to escape who she was in love with in the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002210000 +0000" stop="20251002220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Survival On Charter #220 (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Squad 51 C-shift paramedics rescue a stuntman from a tower. Gage and Desoto respond to treat the injured child of a fireman’s widow. A small plane and a chartered jetliner collide in midair, landing in a residential neighborhood, trapping Johnny and Roy. Station 18 leads a massive response from Battalion 14 and the Compton city fire department. Dr. Morton heads up a triage team from Rampart. Multiple rescues include passengers from both planes and people in the subdivision. Dr. Early performs brain surgery on the injured child. An elderly man’s dog leads Chief McConnike to its owner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002220000 +0000" stop="20251002223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Taking The Fifth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye uses a bottle of vintage wine to lure unsuspecting nurses into his den; and Potter tries to secure a different sort of anesthetic when the army threatens to ban a painkiller.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002223000 +0000" stop="20251002230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger saves Winchester's life when an explosion rocks the operating room; and B.J. is reluctant to reveal the extent of his injuries after the blast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002230000 +0000" stop="20251002233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Sweat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret develops a case of prickly heat, Charles does his tax returns and Klinger takes the P.A. apart—just some of the events that occur during another unendurably hot night at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251002233000 +0000" stop="20251003000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Depressing News</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger's army newspaper reports on Hawkeye's monument to military stupidity; a giant tower made from a half million erroneously shipped tongue depressors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003000000 +0000" stop="20251003003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Uniform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred the grocery store clerk repeatedly sweeps trash into the street, even after Barney writes him a citation. Fred threatens that if he ever sees Barney out of uniform, he'll pound him, causing Barney to leave his uniform on at all times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003003000 +0000" stop="20251003010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie finds a lost wallet containing $50, and just as he's waited the seven-day period to claim the money as his own, the owner steps forward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003010000 +0000" stop="20251003013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro Proposes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has heard that Miss Jane has never been proposed to and wants to help out. She tries to get Jed to propose, but has no luck with that plan. Granny then settles to have Jethro propose to her. Jethro asks Miss Jane out, and she accepts. While at the bank, Jethro also meets the gorgeous new night guard, Ilse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003013000 +0000" stop="20251003020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Foster Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>In search of a "real person" for his Foster Furniture Polish ad campaign, Mr. Foster thinks Aunt Bee has what it takes to make his television commercials memorable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003020000 +0000" stop="20251003023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003023000 +0000" stop="20251003030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Rocket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to detour the German bombers that normally attack London to a nearby Allied airbase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003030000 +0000" stop="20251003033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Mel Torme And Michele Lee</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Mel Torme and Michele Lee. Originally aired on 01/18/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003033000 +0000" stop="20251003043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blonde Bonanza</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady promoter is killed after a crooked modeling deal, his intended victim is suspected of his murder—but the truth in this case is more than skin deep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003043500 +0000" stop="20251003050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Cavender Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E36</episode-num>
    <desc>An angel trying to earn his wings comes to the aide of a down-on-her-luck woman who has just been fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003050500 +0000" stop="20251003053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman's Help</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After falling in love with his invalid wife's nurse, a man schemes to get rid of his wife altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003053500 +0000" stop="20251003060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Museum Piece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A museum piece causes problems for a curious visitor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003060500 +0000" stop="20251003070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Way To Dusty Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix ruffles some feathers in a small town when he arrives in search of a missing youth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003070500 +0000" stop="20251003080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Iceman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon reopens an investigation when he discovers a convicted man may be innocent, but then refuses parole. Robert Foxworth is the villain. He plays a murderer, an ex-Green Beret who served in Vietnam with overtones of CIA activity. The murdered man was Cannon's friend, and that brings him into the case. When the convicted murderer turns down a parole, Cannon becomes very curious."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003080500 +0000" stop="20251003090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Focus On Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Thugs steal a photographer's negatives and blind her after she does an assignment at an air-freight terminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003090000 +0000" stop="20251003093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003093000 +0000" stop="20251003100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-07</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon appear on a TV panel. The topic: "The Police—Who Needs Them?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003100000 +0000" stop="20251003103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 144 -- Bank Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are in for a rude awakening when they report to the home of a former professional wrestler on a domestic abuse call. Later, they become suspicious of an apartment burglary victim after they find one of the suspects dead, deal with a man who discovers car parts that were stolen from him installed on another car and become involved in a shootout responding to a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003103000 +0000" stop="20251003110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 44 -- Attempted Bribery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy businessman openly offers malloy and reed security jobs at three times their current salaries if reed agrees to withhold damaging testimony against his troubled son. In the meantime, they have to deal with an elderly man who has strangled his ch</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003110000 +0000" stop="20251003120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Hawkeye State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore the hawkeye state!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003120000 +0000" stop="20251003123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Autobiography</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been given an assignment in which he must write a autobiography for class but isn't sure about his abilities at writing. So, he convinces a girl, who likes him, to write it for him. When she discovers that he is merely using her, she writes an outrageous life story and hands it in, causing embarrassment for Beaver when the teacher reads it in class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003123000 +0000" stop="20251003130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Party Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks June and Ward if he could have a party and with some prodding, Wally finally gets their permission. June quickly begins the plans and Beaver gets a look at the guest list and quickly finds that he's not invited. For revenge, Beaver decides to sabotage Wally's party with a variety of gags that he bought at a magic shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003130000 +0000" stop="20251003140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Jilted Jockey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Jockey Tic Barton is in a mess of trouble. First, he's fired when his horse loses a fixed race and then he's charged with murder after confronting Johnny Starr, the man actually responsible for the fix. And, oh yes, Tic's wife was having an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003140000 +0000" stop="20251003150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Broker  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When stockbroker Richard Wagner is murdered, his former partner, Avery Campbell, needs Julie's help to prove his innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003150000 +0000" stop="20251003160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>My Name Is Hank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A young refugee claims to be the son of a Sparta cop who died in the war. But quickly becomes a suspect in a murder/robbery after he accepts a ride with the criminals who actually committed the crime. Gillespie looks into his story, while Virgil and the boys track down the shooter. Meanwhile, the young man’s presence triggers a surprisingly bitter reaction from Parker, who views him as a painful reminder of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003160000 +0000" stop="20251003170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Pin-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben has a new camera and takes pictures of Erin that becomes a pin-up</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003170000 +0000" stop="20251003180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A fall guy learns that his father, a general, is dying.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003180000 +0000" stop="20251003190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Warbonnet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After his horse breaks a leg, Joe is left stranded and exhausted in the desert—finding himself at the mercy of a tribe of Indians who discover him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003190000 +0000" stop="20251003193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>One Went To Denver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas welcomes his old friend, Tom Birch, who once saved his life, unaware that the man is now a bank robber who is on the run with his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003193000 +0000" stop="20251003200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Wait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Maury, released from Yuma prison, arrives in North Fork intent on getting even with Marshal Torrance, who helped send him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003200000 +0000" stop="20251003210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jenna Douglas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jenna Douglas is found by scouts for the wagon train. She appears to have been a victim of a scavenger attack and is adopted by the train. As time goes on people on the train begin to have doubts about her story and her mental state."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003210000 +0000" stop="20251003220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Survival On Charter #220 (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Squad 51 C-shift paramedics rescue a stuntman from a tower. Gage and Desoto respond to treat the injured child of a fireman’s widow. A small plane and a chartered jetliner collide in midair, landing in a residential neighborhood, trapping Johnny and Roy. Station 18 leads a massive response from Battalion 14 and the Compton city fire department. Dr. Morton heads up a triage team from Rampart. Multiple rescues include passengers from both planes and people in the subdivision. Dr. Early performs brain surgery on the injured child. An elderly man’s dog leads Chief McConnike to its owner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003220000 +0000" stop="20251003223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Laughing Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye wagers that he can go a full day without a wisecrack, and Winchester finally confronts the major who exiled him to the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003223000 +0000" stop="20251003230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, How We Danced</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester is sent to inspect sanitary conditions on the frontlines, while the rest of the camp plans a surprise anniversary party for B.J.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003230000 +0000" stop="20251003233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottoms Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Margaret's nurses tries to hide her severe drinking problem, and Hawkeye is scorned after a practical joke he plays on Winchester backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251003233000 +0000" stop="20251004000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Red/white Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter nearly blows his stack when his well-intentioned colleagues mollycoddle him in order to lower his blood pressure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004000000 +0000" stop="20251004003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Sheriff Taylor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers moving to Raleigh for another job. An upset Barney tries to demonstrate to Andy just how bad Mayberry would be without him, creating more harm than good in his effort to get Andy to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004003000 +0000" stop="20251004010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pageant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets the lead role in the Centennial Pageant as Lady Mayberry. She is, however, not up to the challenge, and Andy must find a way to tell her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004010000 +0000" stop="20251004013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro is still working on being a 007 spy, though it is annoying Granny. And Elly has been crowned Queen of the Bankers Ball. Mr. Cushing is not happy about this though, as he wanted his contestant to win. Because Jethro is having more fun at Cushing’s bank, he tries to get Jed to transfer his money to the Merchant’s Bank. And Cushing sees this opportunity and tries to get that gorgeous Clampett account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004013000 +0000" stop="20251004020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Vacation In Vegas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer wins a vacation for two to Las Vegas and Sgt. Carter joins him. Gomer doesn't want to gamble as much as he wants to see the sights, but the sergeant is committed to gaming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004020000 +0000" stop="20251004023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Information Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After detecting an information leak in the area of Stalag 13, the Germans replace Klink with a more efficient officer, who Hogan sets up to take the fall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004023000 +0000" stop="20251004030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Art For Hogan's Sake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a French painting from ending up in Goering's art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004030000 +0000" stop="20251004033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Rita Haryworth And Jim Bailey</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Rita Haryworth and Jim Bailey. Originally aired on 02/01/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004033000 +0000" stop="20251004043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ruinous Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a land development deal goes sour, Mason defends engineer Adam Conrad, accused of a murder committed in an old house that has something sinister hidden underneath it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004043500 +0000" stop="20251004050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Changing Of The Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly private school teacher wonders if his life has meant anything as he contemplates suicide on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004050500 +0000" stop="20251004053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Deathmate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>An older woman tries to convince her young lover to end her husband's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004053500 +0000" stop="20251004060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Gratitude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>When the syndicate turns against the owner of a casino, he fears for his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004060500 +0000" stop="20251004070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Climb A Deadly Mountain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Forced to crash land a plane, Mannix gets rescued by an escaped convict who's being pursued by corrupt law enforcement officers out to silence him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004070500 +0000" stop="20251004080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hear No Evil</sub-title>
    <desc>Reporter Molly Stoner needs the help of her friend Frank Cannon. The police wants to take her in coercive detention. Molly affirms that infamous gangster Benje Canto has been murdered. Yet her source cannot be revealed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004080500 +0000" stop="20251004090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murder In The Key Of C</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to find a composer's fiancé who disappeared running away from unscrupulous music publishers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004090000 +0000" stop="20251004093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Afraid Of The Big Bad Jinx?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lately it seems Uncle Joe can't do anything right, so everyone avoids him.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
