<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018140000 +0000" stop="20251018150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Man-eating House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim, Artie, and a sheriff are accompanying a prisoner through the swamps when they take refuge in an abandoned house... haunted by the spirit of a dead woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018150000 +0000" stop="20251018160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>"A little girl, crying each night, appears to be a ghost from The Donner Party. Many people hear her, but she appears each night to Charlie, who questions his own sanity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018160000 +0000" stop="20251018170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>A Noose Is Waiting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Two men are found hung, and a note left by each of them claims a third person will die: Victoria Barkley.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018170000 +0000" stop="20251018180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Far Places</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt tries to ease the tension between a rancher and her son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018180000 +0000" stop="20251018190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe is about to shoot what he thinks is a wolf but discovers it is a woman. She turns out to be a gypsy banished by her people because they believe she is possessed by the devil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018190000 +0000" stop="20251018193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas thinks he has seen a ghost when a young man, eerily similar to a man he killed in the Civil War, challenges him to a gunfight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018193000 +0000" stop="20251018200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Hostages To Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>At Halloween, rustlers take advantage of the seasonal disguises to raid a cattle ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018200000 +0000" stop="20251018210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Prairie Elephant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Favor finds a circus that is lost. Pascal, the owner and clown, beats his wife, Jenny, who wants to run away with Dario, the other half of her high wire act.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018210000 +0000" stop="20251018213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>No Visitors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Paladin finds a woman and her apparently typhoid-afflicted child abandoned by a wagonmaster, he enlists the aid of a female doctor from a nearby town, but a religious fanatic then tries to bar them from entry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018213000 +0000" stop="20251018220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Witch Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>In Mexico, Josh protects a sensible man and his pregnant wife. The villagers are angered because the man threw the town "witch" off his property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251018220000 +0000" stop="20251019000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Dutiful But Dumb, Busy Buddies, Booby Dupes, Tooth Will Out, Booty And The Beast, Pardon My Backfire</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are photographers for Whack magazine ("If it's a good picture it's out of Whack") who, after messing up an assignment, are sent to the country of Vulgaria to get a picture of a death ray gun.  In Vulgaria the penalty for taking pictures in is death, and the boys soon wind up in front of a firing squad.  Curly's last request is a giant cigar and by the time he's done smoking it all the soldiers are asleep and the Stooges make their escape. , The Stooges run a small restaurant, and must come up with some quick money to pay off a pie dealer whose wares they ruined.  They enter Curly in a milking contest at the county fair, but his technique leaves something to be desired, and he quickly falls behind the champ.  Moe and try to help by putting on a cow suit and pouring milk from a concealed bottle, but when their cheating is exposed, they must leave on the run. , The Stooges are auto mechanics who need money so they can marry their girls.  When some escaped convicts pull into their garage, the boys manage to capture them and use the reward money to marry their sweethearts. , The Stooges are three fish peddlers who decide to cut out the middleman by catching their own fish.  They trade their car and $300 for a "new" boat, which turns out to be a piece of junk that soon falls apart and sinks in the middle of the ocean.  Luckily the boys also have a rowboat, which they climb into and then try to signal some passing planes for help.  Unfortunately, their paint-spattered rag is mistaken for a Japanese flag and they are bombed from the sky. , The Stooges graduate from dental school and go out west to open a practice.  Everything goes well until Shemp "cures" an outlaw's toothache from the instructions in a carpentry book, and the boys must leave on the run. , The Stooges do a good turn and help a stranger open a safe in what they think is the man's house.  Actually the man is a crook and the boys were unwitting accomplices to a robbery.  Once they realize what's happened, the Stooges go after the bad guy and who's left on the train to Los Vegas.  The boys trap the villain and recover the booty. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019000000 +0000" stop="20251019030000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Young Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"After inheriting the Frankenstein Castle, a doctor who has tried all his life to distance himself from his notorious relative finds himself drawn to the unfinished work."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019030000 +0000" stop="20251019050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dr. Henry Frankenstein (Colin Clive) wants to build a man in his own image, using the body of a dead man. He and his assistent Fritz (Dwight Frye) dig up a freshly burried coffin and steal the body. When they realize the head and the brains of the body are severely damaged, they decide to steal a brain from Dr. Frankensteins former teacher Dr. Waldman (Edward van Sloan). When Fritz accidentely drops the glass jar with the label "good brain" on it on the floor, he decides to take the glass jar with the label "bad brain". Using some kind of mysterious ray that Dr. Frankenstein discovered, the body is brought to life during a thunderstorm, and the monster of Frankenstein (Boris Karloff) is born. Later, when Dr. Frankenstein realizes that he has created an agressive monster, he and Fritz lock the monster up in a cell. When the monster is repeatedly bullied and provoked by Fritz, the monster eventually manages to kill him. When the monster escapes, he meets a little girl playing near the water. The monster and the girl throw flowers in the water. Enjoying the playing, the clumsy monster proceeds to pick up the girl and throw her in the water, too. Later we learn that the little girl drowned in the incident, when her father carries her through the streets. The city's population propel into an uproar, demanding the death of Frankensteins monster. The monster is driven into an old mill, after which the people of the city set the mill on fire."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019050000 +0000" stop="20251019060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Penny and Judy stumble upon a mirror. Before they know it they are transported to the mirror universe which is occupied by only one person, a boy who is lonesome for companionship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019060000 +0000" stop="20251019070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Waters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Kowalski's brother, injured and unreasonable, nevertheless saves the Seaview crew from a deep-sea death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019070000 +0000" stop="20251019080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Place Called Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of time travelers from Earth's distant future are sent back to the past by their superiors on a mission of observation. However, the pair use the trip to plot for the eventual takeover of Earth, using the castaways as unwitting accomplices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019080000 +0000" stop="20251019090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Walls Of Jericho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Warrior-prophet Joshua sends Tony and Doug into Jericho as spies before he attacks the Biblical city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019090000 +0000" stop="20251019100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Counter-attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent recovers important information regarding the aliens just as a conspiracy targets his future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019100000 +0000" stop="20251019110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Bear's Life</sub-title>
    <desc>"A torrential rainstorm traps Adams and friends in his cabin overnight. The next day comes and it's time to repair it, but Ben the Grizzly has wandered off for the day."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019110000 +0000" stop="20251019113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Queen Of The Everglades</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim take us into one of the wildest areas of the natural wild kingdom in the U.S., the vast Everglades."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019113000 +0000" stop="20251019120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Survival In The Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Even under searing temperatures of 120 degrees or more, life tenaciously takes hold in the Sonora Desert.  This American Southwestern region is an arena of daily competition…between animals, plants and insects, struggling to survive the extremes and severities of the desert’s environment.  It’s truly a “survival of the fittest,” and a ruggedly beautiful adventure.  Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler are there observing as predator hunts its prey, be it the grey fox, badger or sidewinder snake.  Then you’ll be part of the intense excitement as a peccary…the only true wild pig in the United States…becomes the target of Marlin’s capture gun, which shoots a harmless, sleep-inducing drug into the animal.  The peccary is then tagged, so that its habits may be more carefully studied, and that life, under the difficult circumstances of the Sonora, may be more clearly understood by man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019120000 +0000" stop="20251019123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Poles Apart</sub-title>
    <desc>"Many animals dwell in the wild kingdom that literally are ‘poles apart’ in structure, habits and adaptations.  In the laboratory and in the wild, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore and explain such extreme contrasts such as: the slow heartbeat of the elephant and the rapid beat of a mouse; the alligators’ jaws built to crush and a tropical bird’s beak built to pry; birds that migrate and birds that ‘stay put’; a bird that flies a mile a minute and a sloth that travels a food a day."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019123000 +0000" stop="20251019130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>King Of Beasts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Comparisons and contrasts are drawn as Marlin and Jim analyze the behavior of the lion in his natural habitat in Africa and in the zoo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019130000 +0000" stop="20251019133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Crater Of Gold</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rivers of fire and erupting volcanoes in British East Africa have created a crater called Ngora Ngora, which shields the great herds of African wildlife from the advances of man.  By plane to the top of the crater and by jeep into the crater, we study one of the truly last strongholds of the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019133000 +0000" stop="20251019140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Vanishing With The Wilderness</sub-title>
    <desc>"What happens to the creatures living in the wilderness when their natural habitat is destroyed? Some die out…others move to a new home, and some like the coyote and opossum have journeyed far beyond their original range.  Others move in, attracted by food or by the elimination of their natural enemies.  Camped in a wilderness area on the fringe of civilization, Marlin Perkins explores the why and hows of this cross-migration."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019140000 +0000" stop="20251019143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Slumber Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Carol agree to allow Marcia to have a slumber party and the boys plot a series of tricks. But after Marcia is accused of insulting her teacher with a sketch at school, the party is in danger of being cancelled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019143000 +0000" stop="20251019150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Going, Going... Steady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia comes home from school in a daydream and the rest of the family can't figure out her problem. It seems Marcia has a crush on a boy who doesn't even know she's alive, at least not until she studies up on his favorite hobby, insect collecting. The next time she comes home from school, she has exciting news, he asked her to "go steady."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019150000 +0000" stop="20251019153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Fonsillectomy</sub-title>
    <desc>Fonzie has to have his tonsils removed and will miss a big Halloween party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019153000 +0000" stop="20251019160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Shirley And The Older Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Shirley's friendship with a rich older man is resented by Carmine, who is jealous, and the man's daughter, Adelle, is suspicious of Shirley's intentions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019160000 +0000" stop="20251019163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Lindsey is a young guitarist that lives in Mayberry. When the famous musician Bobby Fleet and his band arrive in Mayberry, Andy and Barney scheme to arrest Bobby and his band so that Jim can get an audition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019163000 +0000" stop="20251019170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Breaking The Lease</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The show opens with the Ricardos and the Mertzes sitting around the Ricardos' piano, singing songs together. After the Mertzes leave, Lucy and Ricky wind up in an argument. The Mertzes, who are trying to get some sleep, are most irritated by the noise. They angrily phone the Ricardos and demand that they cut down on the racket. This, as you can imagine, leads to a big quarrel between the Ricardos and the Mertzes. Lucy and Ricky decide that they can't take it anymore, and they want to move out. However, there is a slight problem—they've signed a lease. The Ricardos thus decide to become the most undesirable tenants ever so that they can break that lease.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019170000 +0000" stop="20251019173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Sees America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has the chance to travel around the country for six weeks during the summer and he's all excited about it. However, he quickly realizes when he's gone Gilbert will go after the girl Beaver has a crush on, Mary Margaret. But he quickly realizes, there's more to life than Mary Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019173000 +0000" stop="20251019180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clothing Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's school is having a clothing drive and whoever brings in the most clothes will be awarded 1,000 school points. June, Ward and Wally round up all the old clothes they can find and put them in a box. However, next to the box are three good suits of Ward's that are to be cleaned, and, of course, Beaver mistakes them as items for the clothing drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019180000 +0000" stop="20251019183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Rescues Pearl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Pearl's efforts to snag Mr. Brewster seem doomed until he makes a ridiculous public proposal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019183000 +0000" stop="20251019190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Californy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is confronted with too many cooks and not enough vittles when he invites Pearl and Jethrine to Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019190000 +0000" stop="20251019193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Operation: Steam Heat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot water spurting from beneath the island pleases the castaways as they can now have hot water piped into their huts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019193000 +0000" stop="20251019200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Mr. Howell Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>The radio reports that Mr. Howell has been rescued and is spending all of his money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019200000 +0000" stop="20251019203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's A Will  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama has to keep her temper under control for two weeks if she wants to collect on Fran's will.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019203000 +0000" stop="20251019210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Best Medicine  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A feud between Mama and Ellen rages—until she learns Ellen is in the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019210000 +0000" stop="20251019220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Eyes Of Love / Masquerade / Hollywood Royalty (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 1. Thieves eye a honeymooning actress's gems; a man encounters his blind childhood love; a wife meets her spouse's mistress."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019220000 +0000" stop="20251019223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie Walker, the local pharmacist's niece, comes to Mayberry to replace him on a temporary basis. Her "new" approach to dispensing medicine shakes things up in Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019223000 +0000" stop="20251019230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Phil Meenan- Frankenstein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frankenstein collector Phil Meenan's collection starts with the range of tattoos covering his head, and extends to nearly every inch of his home. Horror expert Phil Munis is on hand to appraise the Franken-treasures, from its monstrously oversized Mardi Gras mascot head to a prop wire from the actual lab used in the original 1931 movie."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019230000 +0000" stop="20251019233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Trick Or Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Halloween at the 4077th, and the staff dons costumes and trades ghost stories. Father Mulcahy discovers a soldier alive that had been pronounced dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251019233000 +0000" stop="20251020000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yankee Doodle Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is designated as the setting for the making of an army film on Mobile Army Surgical Hospital units. Hawkeye is chosen as the star while Margaret and Frank compose a screenplay. Hawkeye objects to the piece of propaganda that filmmaker Lt. Bricker is producing and, having exposed the original film, reshoots a new one his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020000000 +0000" stop="20251020003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Love By Appointment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Gloria's sex life suffers after they have to begin planning their encounters around the baby's feeding schedule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020003000 +0000" stop="20251020010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Joey's Baptism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie baptizes Baby Joey without Mike and Gloria's permission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020010000 +0000" stop="20251020013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria And Mike's House Guests</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A broken furnace forces Archie and Edith to spend a few nights under the Stivic's roof during a power blackout.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020013000 +0000" stop="20251020020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith The Judge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>One Sunday afternoon, Archie comes home from the laundromat in fury. It seems that he overloaded one of the machines causing the machine to eat his clothes and cause a flood. The irate proprietor of the laundromat, soon stops by the Bunker home to get Archie to pay for the damages but Archie refuses. Soon Edith is called in to act as judge to decide who is at fault in the matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020020000 +0000" stop="20251020023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ball, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray begins to doubt if anyone actually tells the truth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020023000 +0000" stop="20251020030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Debra's Sick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray tries to juggle the responsibilities of home and work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020030000 +0000" stop="20251020033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>It May Look Like A Walnut!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob falls asleep with a sci-fi movie on and gets visited by an alien from another planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020033000 +0000" stop="20251020040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of A Chantz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob, Laura, Buddy and Sally spend the night in a seemingly haunted cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020040000 +0000" stop="20251020043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Kramdens and Nortons enter a Raccoon costume contest a feud arises between Ralph and Ed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020043000 +0000" stop="20251020050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Self-improvement Of Salvadore Ross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds that he can trade anything he has, including youth and personality, with anybody else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020050000 +0000" stop="20251020053000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of M.j.h.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A small-time crook cooks up a scheme for getting rich quick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020053000 +0000" stop="20251020060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Faith Of Aaron Menefee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's belief in a faith healer leads to an interesting situation for both of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020060000 +0000" stop="20251020070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Encore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kroll and Stevens run the Northeast Syndicate and the IMF must bring them down. In '37 the two of them killed a rival mobster, hid the body and killed the witnesses, so the IMF needs to get Kroll to lead them to the remains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020070000 +0000" stop="20251020080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Crack In A Crystal Ball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A scam artist posing as a psychic goes on TV to prove that he knows where Kimble will appear next-with a little help from an accomplice who is traveling with Kimble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020080000 +0000" stop="20251020090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Ruby</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell goes undercover to expose a powerful auto theft organization and quickly becomes involved in murder, blackmail and illicit narcotics."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020090000 +0000" stop="20251020093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020093000 +0000" stop="20251020100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - Dr-33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gary Crosby plays a hippie whose wife has been persuaded—by other hippies—to pass bad checks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020100000 +0000" stop="20251020103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 76 -- The Militants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed participate in the search for two black militants who ambush and critically wound two officers in their patrol car. When one of the suspects subsequently dies in custody, a bitter public relations battle begins with the militant group as the search for the other suspect continues.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020103000 +0000" stop="20251020110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 164 -- The Poachers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young employee at the city garage steals a patrol car and engages in a high speed pursuit. Afterward, Malloy and Reed arrest a young woman trying to cash an old-age benefits check she found on the ground, report to an apartment complex garage that had its security camera stolen, investigate a break-in at a mortuary and arrest a couple of pill pushers at a warehouse in Officer Ed Well's territory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020110000 +0000" stop="20251020120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Chilling Traditions</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toon In With Me's Boo-Bash begins with a look back on some seriously spooky traditions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020120000 +0000" stop="20251020123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Family Scrapbook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While cleaning, June runs across an old family scrapbook and gathers the family together to reminisce about the past six years. The Cleavers recall scenes from previous episodes including: 'Beaver Gets 'Spelled,'' 'New Neighbors,' 'My Brother's Girl,' 'The Shave,' 'Beaver Runs Away,' 'Larry Hides Out,' 'Teacher Comes to Dinner,' and 'Wally's Election.'</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020123000 +0000" stop="20251020130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets "spelled"</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver's teacher, Miss Canfield, sends a note home with Beaver and the other kids convince him that it's news that he's getting kicked out of school. So Beaver and Wally take steps to hide the note from Ward and June."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020130000 +0000" stop="20251020140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Caretaker's Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Peter Baxter decides to test the loyalty of his heirs. He pretends to change his will cutting them all out and leaving his entire estate to groundskeeper James Hing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020140000 +0000" stop="20251020150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness Killings: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock goes back to his hometown for a family reunion, but things turn sticky when a good friend of his nephew's son dies, and his rival is charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020150000 +0000" stop="20251020160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Racial tensions run high when a white cabbie is murdered in the bottoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020160000 +0000" stop="20251020170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Innocents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The parents who work at Picket's defense plant leave their children in the parking lot while the parents work</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020170000 +0000" stop="20251020180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Panacea Sykes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Elderly Panacea Sykes is a conniving thief bent on robbing Kitty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020180000 +0000" stop="20251020190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Forever: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After Joe marries Alice Harper, trouble follows when a couple of men show up looking for money owed to them by Alice's brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020190000 +0000" stop="20251020193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to do a good deed for the old town drunk but it backfires when the drunk's son believes he inherited Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020193000 +0000" stop="20251020200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance hall singer asks Lucas to care for her daughter in an effort to hide the baby from her self-righteous, bigoted father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020200000 +0000" stop="20251020210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Daniel Clay Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"Judge Clay and his family join the wagon train. He has a reputation for cleaning up frontier towns, but his fanatical attention to the law sees him ostracized as often as he is praised. He must face this when his son must be tried by him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020210000 +0000" stop="20251020220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Wedsworth-townsend Act, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Seeing a dire need in the community for on-the spot medical assistance, Roy and John attempt to convince their staunchest opponent, Dr. Brackett, to support paramedic legislation that means getting help to where it's needed most. Martin Miller and Kent McCord of Adam-12 guest star in this thrilling 2-hour pilot movie"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020220000 +0000" stop="20251020223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020223000 +0000" stop="20251020230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020230000 +0000" stop="20251020233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251020233000 +0000" stop="20251021000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021000000 +0000" stop="20251021003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Irresistible Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy comes to believe that Ellie is a "deadly female hunter" out to marry him so he tries to put her onto other quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021003000 +0000" stop="20251021010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Runaway Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie becomes friends with an eight-year-old runaway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021010000 +0000" stop="20251021013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Handsome?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is reluctant to go on a date because he's insecure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021013000 +0000" stop="20251021020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Car, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gets upset when she discovers that she's driving Ray's old "make out mobile."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021020000 +0000" stop="20251021023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Dropouts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps three German scientists escape to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021023000 +0000" stop="20251021030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Nights In Shining Armor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan schemes to get a French courier and some Allied bulletproof vests out of Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021030000 +0000" stop="20251021033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021033000 +0000" stop="20251021043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A man suspects his father was killed by a gangster to whom he owed $10,000. When the gangster turns up dead, the timing couldn't be worse for the bereaving son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021043500 +0000" stop="20251021050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Number Twelve Looks Just Like You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In a future where everyone must undergo an operation at the age of 19 to make them identical to everyone else, one woman desperately tries to hang on to her own identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021050500 +0000" stop="20251021053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Who Wanted To Live</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>On the run from the law, an escaped convict kidnaps a young woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021053500 +0000" stop="20251021060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to cheat an insurance company out of a large amount of money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021060500 +0000" stop="20251021070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Race Against Time: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix travels to a Latin American country and gets himself involved with a revolution against its dictatorship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021070500 +0000" stop="20251021080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Game Children Play</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired when the only witness to a robbery is a young child who blames an Arabian heir for the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021080500 +0000" stop="20251021090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Perchance To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An affair leads to an accidental murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021090000 +0000" stop="20251021093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021093000 +0000" stop="20251021100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021100000 +0000" stop="20251021103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 16 -- Child In Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a tavern robbery in progress, and then are jolted by a severe domestic abuse situation they are powerless to stop. In the meantime, they lose track of a naive college girl who has just been carjacked by a convicted rapist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021103000 +0000" stop="20251021110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 56 -- Vice Versa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Malloy has allowed his driver's license to expire, Reed has to do the driving on today's busy patrol. They search for an ice cream truck driver who's been trying to sell marijuana to children, get an unexpected reaction from a bank robber, help a man who's had his house completely emptied by his neighbors, deal with a woman who shoots her husband dead and find a live baby in a trashcan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021110000 +0000" stop="20251021120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Tales Of Poe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill retell classic horror tales of Edgar Allan Poe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021120000 +0000" stop="20251021123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally send away for an alligator and they secretly keep it in the bathroom. When the alligator falls ill, the boys get some advice from Captain Jack, an owner of an alligator farm. However, keeping him a secret is going to be hard; the alligator is growing and they need a new place to keep him without June and Ward finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021123000 +0000" stop="20251021130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with a black eye and Ward is upset when he learns that Beaver didn't fight back. This leads Ward to teach Beaver how to defend himself. Little does Ward know, the person who punched Beaver is a girl, Violet Rutherford, the daughter of one of Ward's co-workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021130000 +0000" stop="20251021140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Stuttering Bishop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bishop Arthur Mallory is met in his hotel room by Wallace Lang, an associate of a wealthy man named Charles Burroughs. He is warned through physical violence to stop looking for Burroughs' granddaughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021140000 +0000" stop="20251021150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness Killings: Part 2  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock goes back to his hometown for a family reunion, but things turn sticky when a good friend of his nephew's son dies, and his rival is charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021150000 +0000" stop="20251021160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen Trundel: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet's sister is murdered on the orders of the wealthy white man who fathered her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021160000 +0000" stop="20251021170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Film makers film a documentary at Picket's Plant and make Erin the "star"". "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021170000 +0000" stop="20251021180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tell Chester</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl Chester likes has no idea that the man she has her eye on is already married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021180000 +0000" stop="20251021190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Forever: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Joe marries Alice Harper, trouble follows when a couple of men show up looking for money owed to them by Alice's brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021190000 +0000" stop="20251021193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Coward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas becomes involved in a battle between an aspiring writer and a cocky, bragging trail boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021193000 +0000" stop="20251021200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Surveyors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark runs away from home after his father questions his story about overhearing a plot to rob the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021200000 +0000" stop="20251021210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lieutenant Burton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>"A young lieutenant on his first assignment must face an overbearing, murderous sergeant who is determined to kill two deserters in cold blood. The sergeant wounds Chris thinking he is one of them and into a feud with Flint at the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021210000 +0000" stop="20251021220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Botulism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John plots his revenge after being the repeated target of practical jokes. A man breaks his back falling off a tower. A woman fakes an illness. Dr. Early's stethoscope becomes lodged in his ear. A man brought into the hospital from a movie set is the first indication of an outbreak of botulism. A boy is trapped in a condemned building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021220000 +0000" stop="20251021223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021223000 +0000" stop="20251021230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021230000 +0000" stop="20251021233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251021233000 +0000" stop="20251022000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022000000 +0000" stop="20251022003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy The Matchmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, trying to lift Barney's spirits, stages a minor robbery and tries to match his deputy with a shy seamstress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022003000 +0000" stop="20251022010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes upset when Opie contributes a measly three cents to the Underprivileged Children's drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022010000 +0000" stop="20251022013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray discovers the diamond in Debra's wedding ring is fake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022013000 +0000" stop="20251022020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Game, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and his family find themselves arguing about honesty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022020000 +0000" stop="20251022023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a counterfeiting operation that has been set up in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022023000 +0000" stop="20251022030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One In Every Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A prisoner offers the Nazis information on Hogan's operation in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022030000 +0000" stop="20251022033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022033000 +0000" stop="20251022043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gambling Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Counterfeit casino chips and chronic gambling lead to murder, and Mason suspects one of his clients may be culpable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022043500 +0000" stop="20251022050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Black Leather Jackets</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Three tough-looking, motorcycle-riding men disrupt a peaceful suburb when they move in. Yet, their neighbors could never imagine just how dangerous these men really are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022050500 +0000" stop="20251022053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An attorney seeks the truth more for his own satisfaction than the pursuit of justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022053500 +0000" stop="20251022060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Burglar Proof</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An advertising executive is on the verge of being fired when he can't sell a new product.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022060500 +0000" stop="20251022070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Race Against Time: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix travels to a Latin American country and gets himself involved with a revolution against its dictatorship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022070500 +0000" stop="20251022080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Reformer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired when a crusading newspaper editor is found near a dead body, while drunk and unconscious in a hotel room."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022080500 +0000" stop="20251022090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Connection, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is used to smuggle narcotics.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022090000 +0000" stop="20251022093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022093000 +0000" stop="20251022100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022100000 +0000" stop="20251022103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 106 -- Post Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After beginning the search for a well known suspect who just stole a 600-pound offset printing press, Reed and Malloy try to convince an 85-year-old man to leave the soon-to-be demolished apartment building where he's resided alone for 27 years. Afterward, they pull over a very unusual vehicle, and chase a delivery truck to the end of an unfinished bridge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022103000 +0000" stop="20251022110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 88 -- Reason To Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are called to a riding stable run by retired actor Slim Berkeley. The owner is careless about trusting people and has $100 and a gold belt buckle stolen. Because of a criminal record in New York his young assistant runs, but when searched nothing is found. A call to a phone booth where the man inside is being attacked leads to a drug arrest and sore jaw for Reed. Reed spots a robbery at a drive-in resulting in a shoot-out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022110000 +0000" stop="20251022120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Tiwm's Horror Show</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022120000 +0000" stop="20251022123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>New Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors, the Donaldsons, and June sends Beaver over to welcome them with a vase of flowers. However, when Mrs. Donaldson thanks Beaver by kissing him on the cheek, Beaver becomes convinced that Mr. Donaldson will kill him because he let a married woman kiss him, and it's all thanks to Eddie Haskell, who planted that idea in Beaver's mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022123000 +0000" stop="20251022130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>June has had it with Wally and Beaver's fighting and demands they make a pact to be nice to one another and do things together. However, when each boy gets an invitation for individual social outings, they each attempt to break the pact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022130000 +0000" stop="20251022140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lost Last Act</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Playwright Ernest Royce is found shot to death in the same manner as a character in one of his un-produced plays. The play deals with characters very close to real people and the real-life murder of a New York underworld figure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022140000 +0000" stop="20251022150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Strangler  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock goes after serial killer Jeffrey Speidel, the maniac plans to first ruin Matlock publicly and then murder the famed attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022150000 +0000" stop="20251022160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen Trundel: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Willins reveals Trundel's motive; and Sweet finds---and Trundel's wife sees---the missing photo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022160000 +0000" stop="20251022170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Journal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy is still missing, but a publisher has his journal and wants to publish it</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022170000 +0000" stop="20251022180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Quint-cident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Quint incurs the wrath of a widow he turned down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022180000 +0000" stop="20251022190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Heritage Of Anger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ben helps out ex-con John Dundee readjust to the world, the matter becomes complicated by broken promises of the man who framed him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022190000 +0000" stop="20251022193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of The Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous buffalo hunter tries to goad Lucas into a shooting match.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022193000 +0000" stop="20251022200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Order Groom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger arrives to marry the town spinster, two brothers who want her land try to discourage him with threats and a beating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022200000 +0000" stop="20251022210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charley Shutup Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon master encounters opposition when he calls a halt to the train due to weather. One group needs to push on due to an inheritance in California. Chris and Duke take them but Duke injures his foot forcing him to stay in a cabin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022210000 +0000" stop="20251022220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Cook's Tour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>John delivers a cyanotic baby. The firemen give Roy a bad time about his cooking. A boy gets his hand stuck in a vase; John rescues a kid in handcuffs. A man repairing a washer gets an electric shock. The paramedics rescue a man trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022220000 +0000" stop="20251022223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022223000 +0000" stop="20251022230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sometimes You Hear The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank throws his back out while spending the evening with Margaret, and ends up in traction. He promptly applies for the Purple Heart, having been 'technically' wounded at a frontline unit. Tommy Gillis, an old friend of Hawkeye's, is writing a book about the war, and pays him a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022230000 +0000" stop="20251022233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251022233000 +0000" stop="20251023000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023000000 +0000" stop="20251023003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Feud Is A Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy strives to end a long-running feud between two neighboring families.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023003000 +0000" stop="20251023010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie For Council</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie's decision to run for town council sparks a battle of the sexes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023010000 +0000" stop="20251023013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Recovering Pessimist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray agrees to become more upbeat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023013000 +0000" stop="20251023020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Dog, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray brings home a stray bulldog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023020000 +0000" stop="20251023023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Easy Come, Easy Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and Klink go to England to steal an allied airplane as part of Hogan's plan to expose Nazi spies in London.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023023000 +0000" stop="20251023030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Russian Is Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to get a Russian pilot, who refuses to escape to London, back to Russia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023030000 +0000" stop="20251023033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Dom Deluise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Dom Deluise. Originally aired on 10/20/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023033000 +0000" stop="20251023043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Duplicate Case</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After his cheating wife's body is recovered from the burned-out department store where she worked, a man finds $72,000 in his briefcase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023043500 +0000" stop="20251023050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Night Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mysterious phone calls haunt a disabled woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023050500 +0000" stop="20251023053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Score</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage gang of robbers hits one household too many.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023053500 +0000" stop="20251023060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Profit-sharing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to run away with his company's funds encounters a small hitch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023060500 +0000" stop="20251023070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix struggles to recall events that led to him being shot with his own gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023070500 +0000" stop="20251023080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>House Of Cards</sub-title>
    <desc>"The accountant of Eden Corporation has disappeared and along with him three million dollars. Does unscrupulous branch manager Sheffield have to do with the plot? Cannon comes across a discovery and suddenly local reporter Julie Foster also plays an important role."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023080500 +0000" stop="20251023090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murder In The Doll's House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby matches wits with a debonair killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023090000 +0000" stop="20251023093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023093000 +0000" stop="20251023100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023100000 +0000" stop="20251023103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023103000 +0000" stop="20251023110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023110000 +0000" stop="20251023120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Halloween Monsters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill turn into classic monsters."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023120000 +0000" stop="20251023123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Water, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally and his friends are trying to earn enough money to buy baseball uniforms so they put a plan into action by doing their chores at a slow pace in order to maximize their hourly pay. Meanwhile, Beaver, also wanting to be on the team, begins selling water to his family and neighbors."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023123000 +0000" stop="20251023130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Crush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has a crush on his teacher, Miss Canfield. When Judy, Whitey and Larry tease him for being a "teacher's pet," Beaver tries to prove them wrong and places a spring snake in her desk. However, Beaver has second thoughts and becomes determined to remove the snake before she finds it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023130000 +0000" stop="20251023140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bedeviled Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. David Craig discovers that tapes of conversations with his psychiatric patients are missing and being used for blackmail purposes. When the suspected thief and blackmailer, Mark Douglas, turns up murdered, Craig is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023140000 +0000" stop="20251023150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Nightmare  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a bump on the head, Matlock dreams he's in the Old West—and Conrad is about to be lynched by an angry mob!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023150000 +0000" stop="20251023160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs travels to Philadelphia to uncover the truth behind the apparent suicide of a friend who had knowledge of a police cover-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023160000 +0000" stop="20251023170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Sheep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ashley Longworth Jr returns to the mountain. He proposes to Erin and she accepts</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023170000 +0000" stop="20251023180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old York</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt comes face to face with the outlaw who saved his life long ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023180000 +0000" stop="20251023190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Initiation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy is accidentally killed while performing the initiation for a secret club, and one of Jamie's friends is blamed for the death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023190000 +0000" stop="20251023193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Case Of Identity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark finds himself in grave danger when two unscrupulous detectives searching for a man's long-lost son claim that it is Mark.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023193000 +0000" stop="20251023200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Visitor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucas is drawn to a young widow passing through town on her way to claim an inheritance, but others who covet it are trying to kill her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023200000 +0000" stop="20251023210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Amos Billings Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon train encounters Amos Billings who tells of a new road that might shorten their trip and avoid Indian trouble. Chris and Flint are very suspicious of the situation since the location has been a dead end."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023210000 +0000" stop="20251023220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Brushfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Station 51 is called to fight a wildfire. John and Roy rescue an elderly woman and her sister, treat an injured fireman, deliver a baby, catch a looter and find a boy's lost dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023220000 +0000" stop="20251023223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023223000 +0000" stop="20251023230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023230000 +0000" stop="20251023233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251023233000 +0000" stop="20251024000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024000000 +0000" stop="20251024003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger comes to town, Barney and the people of Mayberry grow suspicious when he seems to know too much about them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024003000 +0000" stop="20251024010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Hollywood film crew decides to use Mayberry as a backdrop for a movie, everyone in town begins to put on airs, risking the small-town charm that attracted the crew in the first place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024010000 +0000" stop="20251024013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's sawing and Marie's meddling bother the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024013000 +0000" stop="20251024020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Fascinatin' Debra</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is being interviewed by a psychotherapist for a book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024020000 +0000" stop="20251024023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>An Evening Of Generals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as waiters, Hogan and the gang scheme to get rid of a room full of German generals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024023000 +0000" stop="20251024030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Loves A Snowman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys must smuggle a U.S. bomber crew out of camp while under surveillance by Hochstetter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024030000 +0000" stop="20251024033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Diahann Carroll (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Diahann Carroll. Originally aired on 10/27/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024033000 +0000" stop="20251024043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Grinning Gorilla</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A scientist involved in a lawsuit with his former housekeeper is found stabbed to death, and the housekeeper—though cornered by a loose gorilla—is present when the corpse is discovered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024043500 +0000" stop="20251024050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>From Agnes - With Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A computer technician begins getting advice on his love life from Agnes, the computer he works with.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024050500 +0000" stop="20251024053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Apex</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and his lover decide to get rid of his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024053500 +0000" stop="20251024060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Remains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to hide the murder of his business partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024060500 +0000" stop="20251024070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Night Full Of Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's police department pal, Lieutenant Malcolm, is a victim of a setup. The private eye tries to get to the bottom of things in order to clear his friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024070500 +0000" stop="20251024080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is haunted by the memories of his time in the Korean War."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024080500 +0000" stop="20251024090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sing A Song Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The managers of a rock music star, whom they think drowned in his pool, cash in on his "tragedy""."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024090000 +0000" stop="20251024093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024093000 +0000" stop="20251024100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024100000 +0000" stop="20251024103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Million Dollar Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a run-in with a suspected professional jewel thief and fear she will walk due to lack of evidence. They also find themselves in competition with a millionaire vigilante, who provides assistance with apprehending a drunk driver and ending a shootout, but seems destined to soon overstep the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024103000 +0000" stop="20251024110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandmothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a hype who robbed a hand-made craft store run by elderly women, only to later return the money after robbing an antique store. In the meantime, they engage in a high-speed pursuit, and pull over a priest in possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024110000 +0000" stop="20251024120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Do You Want  To Play With Me?</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony discuss clowns and dolls."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024120000 +0000" stop="20251024123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubhouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and his friends build a clubhouse, and Beaver wants to join. Although the dues are $1 for 8th graders, Beaver has to come up with $3 in order to join their club. How can Beaver earn the money?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024123000 +0000" stop="20251024130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Girl Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver dread attending dance school, so when Wally suddenly takes a liking in it, June and Ward are dumbfounded. It seems Wally has developed a crush on a girl named Penny and Beaver soon feels neglected and left out when Wally begins spending all his time with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024130000 +0000" stop="20251024140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Howling Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Evelyn Forbes escapes from a mental institution only to be charged with murder. The key to the case is a dog that continues to howl no matter what.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024140000 +0000" stop="20251024150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Marriage Counselor  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a marriage counselor is murdered, Matlock must sort through a list of suspects including the man's coworkers and patients, as he was known to seduce the female half of the couples he treated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024150000 +0000" stop="20251024160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs goes home to Philadelphia, where he's implicated in a cop's murder while probing his own cop friend's apparent suicide---all with Althea about to give birth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024160000 +0000" stop="20251024170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Violated</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier is sending his wife mail, but getting no replies</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024170000 +0000" stop="20251024180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Daddy Went Away</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A widow returns Chester's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024180000 +0000" stop="20251024190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Riot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S14E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is taken as a hostage while inspecting conditions at a Nevada State Prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024190000 +0000" stop="20251024193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young stablehand kills a notorious gunslinger, he is baffled by the hostility of the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024193000 +0000" stop="20251024200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a horse dealer transporting a prize stallion stops in North Fork, two saddle tramps try to use trickery to obtain it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024200000 +0000" stop="20251024210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Baylor Crofoot Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"A teacher traveling with the wagon train encounters conflict when he become attracted to the daughter of a medicine man who has just joined the train. The man despises cowards and sees the teacher as one."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024210000 +0000" stop="20251024220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dealer's Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy talks down a boy in a plane after the pilot (his father) has a heart attack. The paramedics respond to an attempted suicide, an overturned truck and a teenage overdose victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024220000 +0000" stop="20251024223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Showtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kaplan is to be shipped home, but becomes paranoid that something will happen to him before he leaves. He takes the wheel of the jeep to drive to Kimpo himself, but crashes and ends up in plaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024223000 +0000" stop="20251024230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Divided We Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brought on by Frank and Margaret's negative reports, General Clayton assigns a psychiatrist, Captain Hildebrand, to examine the 4077th M*A*S*H unit to see if it should be disbanded. Henry tells them to be on their best behavior, or else they will be split up. But the 4077th soon begins to act in their traditional, insane way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024230000 +0000" stop="20251024233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251024233000 +0000" stop="20251025000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025000000 +0000" stop="20251025003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Trader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ignoring his own advice to Opie, Andy plays fast and loose with the facts when trying to sell the old town cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025003000 +0000" stop="20251025010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Those Gossipin' Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Andy teases the fairer sex about gossiping, Aunt Bee pulls a prank to prove that men are gossips, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025010000 +0000" stop="20251025013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Why Are We Here?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gets fed up with Ray's family intruding in her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025013000 +0000" stop="20251025020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ray's On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is devastated when he discovers his family lied to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025020000 +0000" stop="20251025023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plays a waiting game with a German general. The scheming general has planted a rocket-fuel depot right outside Stalag 13 in hopes of trapping the area's resident saboteur, whom he suspects is Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025023000 +0000" stop="20251025030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Carter Turns Traitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter pretends to be a traitor so he can learn the location of a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025030000 +0000" stop="20251025033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Diahann Carroll (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Diahann Carroll. Originally aired on 10/27/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025033000 +0000" stop="20251025043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wrongful Writ</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young lawyer is framed for the murder of a man claiming to be a government agent, Mason must cull through witnesses to identify the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025043500 +0000" stop="20251025050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Spur Of The Moment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After encountering a terrifying figure in black, a woman faces the biggest decision of her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025050500 +0000" stop="20251025053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Ten O'clock Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A seedy character comes up with an amazing formula and then puts it to good use.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025053500 +0000" stop="20251025060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kerry Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's love for his pet dog leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025060500 +0000" stop="20251025070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Walk A Double Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix wonders why a seemingly open-and-shut case got dropped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025070500 +0000" stop="20251025080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Wolf</sub-title>
    <desc>"A kidnapping with shady overtones compels a millionaire to hire Cannon for the investigation."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025080500 +0000" stop="20251025090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>See Some Evil, Do Some Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A blackmailer and murderer pretends to be blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251025090000 +0000" stop="20251025093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Curse Of Chester W. Farnsworth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe is convinced that the Shady Rest is haunted by a guest who visited 50 years ago, Chester W. Farnsworth.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
