<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411070500 +0000" stop="20250411080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Conspiracy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Frank Cannon and Barnaby Jones team up for an investigation of a murder at a big corporation in which a deliveryman was charged with the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411080500 +0000" stop="20250411090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Clycle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An insurance settlement hangs on the result of an investigation of a motorcycle manufacturer's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411090000 +0000" stop="20250411093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411093000 +0000" stop="20250411100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411100000 +0000" stop="20250411103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program to help ground based officers better understand the abilities and limitations of helicopter assistance, malloy and reed are selected to be observers on several air support division missions. This morning's missions include a sea</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411103000 +0000" stop="20250411110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed take flight in separate helicopters to provide assistance in the search of a light plane stolen from the los angeles airport by a distraught man. Afterwards, they search for a group of robbery suspects who flee in separate cars, then reed</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411110000 +0000" stop="20250411120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Minor Misunderstanding</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony step into the courtroom!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411120000 +0000" stop="20250411123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Dramatic Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After joining the dramatic club at school, Beaver is given the lead role in a play. However, after reading the script, he discovers he must kiss a girl and wants out of the production.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411123000 +0000" stop="20250411130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Dudley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A close friend of June's moves into the neighborhood and June arranges to have Wally show the new kid, Dudley, around school. However, everyone thinks Dudley is a creep and Eddie and Lumpy plan to make a fool of Dudley at a party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411130000 +0000" stop="20250411140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Badgered Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When two brothers inherit their father's chain of department stores, disagreement abounds and leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411140000 +0000" stop="20250411150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Con Man  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a victim of a group of con men is charged with murdering one of them, Matlock takes the case while Michelle attempts to get close to the remaining con artists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411150000 +0000" stop="20250411160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs travels to Philadelphia to uncover the truth behind the apparent suicide of a friend who had knowledge of a police cover-up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411160000 +0000" stop="20250411170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An offer to buy their land makes the Waltons think about what it would be like to have more money than they need</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411170000 +0000" stop="20250411173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Skid Row</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hank Groat bothers Kitty. Chester comes to her rescue. Ann Cabot arrives from Connecticut to marry Jack Shomer. Matt, Chester and Doc go to see Jack. He's drunk in his shack as usual. They sober him up. Jack says he can't face Ann."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411173000 +0000" stop="20250411180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sweet And Sour</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rena Decker, a new dance hall girl, purposely gets her admirers into fighting over her. Despite Kitty's negative opinion of her, Matt befreinds Rena and gets her a job at the Long Branch. Soon afterward, 4 men are dead and Rena is the cause."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411180000 +0000" stop="20250411190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Bride For Buford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman shows interest in a young prospector, Hoss tries to prove that she is really only interested in the man's fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411190000 +0000" stop="20250411193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young stablehand kills a notorious gunslinger, he is baffled by the hostility of the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411193000 +0000" stop="20250411200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a horse dealer transporting a prize stallion stops in North Fork, two saddle tramps try to use trickery to obtain it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411200000 +0000" stop="20250411210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Riley Gratton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Adams sets out to recover passengers' money that was taken by con man Riley Gratton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411210000 +0000" stop="20250411220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Convention, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"San Francisco firefighters and paramedics rescue a man. A paramedic convention brings Gage and DeSoto back to San Francisco. While attending a picnic, SF firefighters and paramedics are called back to work for a mutual aid response in Marin County. Gage and DeSoto tag along on a rescue."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411220000 +0000" stop="20250411223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411223000 +0000" stop="20250411230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411230000 +0000" stop="20250411233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250411233000 +0000" stop="20250412000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412000000 +0000" stop="20250412003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412003000 +0000" stop="20250412010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger comes to town, Barney and the people of Mayberry grow suspicious when he seems to know too much about them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412010000 +0000" stop="20250412013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Continental Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Having been given a stylish makeover by a famous French couturier, Elly May is mistaken for a visiting foreign princess by Mrs. Drysdale. Hoping to get in good with "royalty," Mrs. Drysdale throws a fancy party for Elly. This time around, the old dear is certain that her soiree won't be invaded by "those dreadful hillbillies."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412013000 +0000" stop="20250412020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Barney Fife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney returns home to Mayberry for a brief visit and discovers that his former girlfriend, Thelma Lou, has married. Fortunately, Nettie Albright, a secret admirer from days gone by, shows up at Barney's high school reunion dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412020000 +0000" stop="20250412023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412023000 +0000" stop="20250412030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Get Fit Or Go Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink to get back in shape so he won't be sent to the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412030000 +0000" stop="20250412033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Petula Clarke And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Moving Day, a young elevator operator has a crush on Carol, who plays it up to make Harvey jealous. Then, in As the Stomach Turns, Carol's soap opera alter ego inherits money from her late, great uncle, but problems arise when her family stops by for a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412033000 +0000" stop="20250412043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wandering Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man accused of a murder is freed from prison upon newly discovered eyewitness testimony, it starts a chain reaction of blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412043500 +0000" stop="20250412050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Monsters Are Due On Maple Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paranoia strikes the residents of Maple Street when they believe human-looking aliens have invaded the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412050500 +0000" stop="20250412053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kiss-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After spending six years in prison for a robbery he didn't commit, a man decides to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412053500 +0000" stop="20250412060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a man turns to prayer, he starts to win at the races.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412060500 +0000" stop="20250412070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Frame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate a possible forgery of a Renoir when the collector sees the model who posed for the painting in person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412070500 +0000" stop="20250412080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Medicine</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates a doctors claim that he is innocent of a death he was charged with concerning a patient he was treating that had slipped into a diabetic coma. Cannon becomes involved in a medical malpractice suit when a young resident physician is charged with making the wrong diagnosis on a woman in an apparent diabetic coma who dies after his treatment. Hired by the hospital facing a two million dollar suit, Cannon hears testimony of the accused Dr. Jeff Reston, played by guest star David Birney, that the woman he treated wore a diabetic's bracelet. She was, in fact, suffering from hypoglycemia. But the bracelet disappeared and none of the nurses attending with Reston can back up his story. Reston then gives Cannon a motive for a possible conspiracy against him. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412080500 +0000" stop="20250412090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must find out what happened to a woman who disappeared after dating a country singer's ex.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412090000 +0000" stop="20250412093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bobbie Jo And The Beatnik</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beatnik poet, Alan Landman, makes his way through Hooterville and Bobby Jo is entranced by him. It's up to Kate to show Bobby Jo the young man's true colors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412093000 +0000" stop="20250412100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Visit From A Big Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Shady Rest gets a visit from a Hollywood star, who wishes to lie low in Hooterville for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412100000 +0000" stop="20250412103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Greetings From The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Just as the Clampetts are preparing to go home to the hills, Jethro receives a draft notice from the President. The women go ahead without them, and Jethro gets a few uniforms from the movie studio, one of a Prussian Field Marshall and one for General Patton. Jethro buys a tank and hopes for a crew, employing Drysdale and outfitting him with a Prussian Field Marshall uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412103000 +0000" stop="20250412110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Army Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Elly arrive back home just as Jethro is going to head to the Army. Granny decides to give Jethro his physical examination so the Army doctors don’t touch him. Though, Granny’s medical tools consist of a hammer to test reflexes and a burning candle to examine his throat. She splints his busted knee and puts corks in his ear to keep the draft out of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412110000 +0000" stop="20250412113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Ration Fer The Duration, Axe Me Another, Alona On The Sarong Seas</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye's nephews would rather go fishing than work in his victory garden, so he tells them the story of Jack and the Beanstalk., Popeye challenges Bluto for throwing Olive Oyl into the river., Popeye and Bluto are on a battleship anchored off a tropic isle. The big-muscled gob is dreaming about Princess Alona who is really Olive Oyl in a sarong."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412113000 +0000" stop="20250412120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Professor Tom, Caballero Droopy, Buddies Thicker Than Water</sub-title>
    <desc>"A younger cat looks to Tom to teach him how to properly catch mice., Droopy is ambushed by Slick the Wolf who intends to steal his girlfriend., Jerry helps Tom out by getting him into the penthouse he is staying in and out of the cold night."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412120000 +0000" stop="20250412130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Coo Coo Bird, Crazy House, Pixie Picnic, Little Skeeter, Doc's Last Stand, Pig In A Pickle, Short In The Saddle</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody tries unsuccessfully to get a good night's sleep., Andy and his father take shelter from a storm in a fun house., A group of forest pixies have a picnic., Woody hires exterminator Happy Harry to get rid of the mosquito in his house., Doc sets up a traveling store with the help of Champ trying to sell to settlers in the Old West. When a wealthy indigenous cliet wants female companionship, Doc dresses Champ up as a woman., The neighboring family kidnaps Milford from his birthday party to have him for dinner, but Maw and Paw rescue him., Woody Woodpeckers goes out West."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412130000 +0000" stop="20250412140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Elmer's Pet Rabbit, Little Red Walking Hood, Little Red Riding Rabbit, Of Fox And Hounds, Bowery Bugs, Banty Raids</sub-title>
    <desc>"Elmer buys a rabbit that he pitied seeing in the pet store. The rabbit turns out to be Bugs, and makes Elmer's life a living nightmare. , The Big Bad Wolf breaks into Granny’s house, and Red Riding stops by not knowing he’s there. , Riding Hood takes Bugs over to Granny's house and finds a note to leave Bugs at the door, not knowing the Big Bad Wolf is inside. , A fox plays games with a dumb hunting dog., Bugs recounts a story of how he tricked a man so much so that he jumped off a bridge. , Foghorn finds himself an unexpected father, when a girl-crazy rooster pretends to be Foghorn's son so he can get with the "chicks". "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412140000 +0000" stop="20250412150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Circus Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Counterfeit money is appearing throughout the west in sufficient quantities to undermine the U.S. economy. West and Gordon attempt to track down the source of the fake currency before it's too late.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412150000 +0000" stop="20250412160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clara Beauchamp Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A cavalry colonel's wife tries to foment a war with Native Americans as part of a convoluted scheme to get her husband promoted and transferred back east.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412160000 +0000" stop="20250412170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Midas Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Scott Breckinridge offers to loan money to ranchers during a serious drought. When he will not give an extension to the loans, the ranchers believe the Barkleys are part of a plot to buy up foreclosed land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412170000 +0000" stop="20250412173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cain</sub-title>
    <desc>"A rancher comes to terms with his past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412173000 +0000" stop="20250412180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bureaucrat</sub-title>
    <desc>"A Washington Bureaucrat comes to Dodge to change the way Matt runs the town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412180000 +0000" stop="20250412190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Black Friday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John Saxon makes the first of three Bonanza appearances as Steve Friday, a former Ponderosa ranchhand turned gunfighter. Putting his own life on the line, Joe Cartwright tries to save an ailing Friday from a paid assassin, hired by the powerful and revenge-driven Judge Wyllit (Ford Rainey).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412190000 +0000" stop="20250412193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple moves to North Fork under an assumed name to hide the fact that they are the parents of a vicious killer. The plan backfires when the son shows up at their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412193000 +0000" stop="20250412200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After foiling a girl's attempt to rob the general store, Lucas finds that she and her brother are plotting the murder of their abusive stepfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412200000 +0000" stop="20250412210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Midnight Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in a fall, Wishbone faces a physical and emotional crisis.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412210000 +0000" stop="20250412213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Fight At Adobe Wells</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jonathan Guilder hires Paladin to escort him through Indian country. They end up trapped at an old adobe stage stop by Quanah Parker, a half-indian, half-white Indian warrior with a personal grudge against Guilder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412213000 +0000" stop="20250412220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Railroaded</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When a young runaway is framed for killing a Pinkerton agent, Randall turns detective to uncover the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250412220000 +0000" stop="20250413000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Smart Saps, Back From The Front, Monkey Businessmen, Tricky Dicks, Quiz Whizz, Ghost Talks</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are engaged to the three daughters of a prison warden.  When they learn that some crooks have taken over the prison and their prospective father-in-law has been locked up, they decide to go undercover to rescue him.  The Stooges sneak into the prison where they find a casino with a fancy party in progress.  After swiping some formal attire, they crash the party and get candid camera evidence to expose the crooked goings-on.  With the crooks behind bars once again, the Stooges are able to get married and all ends well. , Moe, Larry and Curly become sailors and go to sea.  And the Three Stooges as sailors are really something to see  - and laugh about.  When their ship is sunk by a nazi cruiser the boys are taken aboard by the enemy and in their own wild and zany way they end up  - after some pretty funny and weird happenings, in capturing the entire ship. , The Stooges are movers for an express company and on a rainy night are sent to move some junk, including a suit of armor, from a spooky old house.  The armor is haunted by the ghost of Peeping Tom, who has no intention of leaving.  The ghost foils the Stooges attempts to take the armor, until Lady Godiva shows up and the two ride off together. , The Stooges are bumbling electricians who decide to go away for a rest after they are fired for their incompetence.  The rest home they choose is run by Dr. Mallard, a quack who gyps the patients for everything they've got.  When the boys discover the crooked goings on they escape, but not before Curly accidentally cures another patient who rewards him with a thousand dollars. , The Stooges are policemen on the trail of a murderer.  They unsuccessfully interrogate an Italian organ grinder, among other suspects, and then catch the bad guy after a gunfight that nearly destroys the police station. , Joe wins a contest and is promptly fleeced out of his winnings by some con men.  When the Stooges go to recover his money, the bad guys convince them that they can get rich by posing as children and becoming the wards of a millionaire.  The boys go along with the plan, not realizing that the "millionaire" and his pretty niece are in on the scam and are planning to knock them off.  The Stooges foil the plan and recover Joe's money. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413000000 +0000" stop="20250413023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Mantis</sub-title>
    <desc>"The calving of an Arctic iceberg releases a giant praying mantis, trapped in suspended animation since prehistoric times. It first attacks military outposts to eat their occupants, then makes its way to the warmer latitudes of Washington and New York. A paleontologist works together with military units to try to kill it.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413023000 +0000" stop="20250413030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker's Flying Saucer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker uses an alien distraction in order to build his own flying saucer. Before Batman and Robin can stop him, the Joker's bomb destroys the Batcave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413030000 +0000" stop="20250413040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Lights Of Zetar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise must deal with discorporeal cloud-like aliens who have already destroyed the inhabitants of a library planet and plan to eliminate the Enterprise crew if they cannot acquire a human host.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413040000 +0000" stop="20250413050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Demon In Lace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>An evil succubus from ancient Mesopotamia murders young men to maintain her immortality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413050000 +0000" stop="20250413060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Target Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Space Pod lands on a planet that is inhabited by creatures who all look alike, yet aspire to be different. They capture the Robinsons and make duplicates of them with the objective of using the duplicates to fly the Jupiter II back to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413060000 +0000" stop="20250413070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Escape From Venice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Admiral Nelson engineers a daring rescue of Captain Crane from a group of enemy agents in Venice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413070000 +0000" stop="20250413080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Weird World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings find a fellow Earthling, Major Kagan, but the man has become paranoid from years of living on his own. His actions soon endanger the entire group.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413080000 +0000" stop="20250413090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Attack Of The Barbarians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In 13th-century Asia, Tony and Doug aid Marco Polo in defending a fort against Mongols led by Genghis Khan's grandson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413090000 +0000" stop="20250413100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Doomsday Minus One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A teacher stumbles upon a device that threatens mankind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413100000 +0000" stop="20250413110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Endurance (aka Survival)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Asylum escapees endanger Matt's classmates as they travel to an outdoor survival course."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413110000 +0000" stop="20250413113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Fight   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zach and Slater might turn back into rivals when they fall for a new girl from Idaho. Who'll be the one to have a date with her?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413113000 +0000" stop="20250413120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Rockumentary   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Casey Kasem hosts a biography of Zack's rock group,The Zack Attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413120000 +0000" stop="20250413123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Sats   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie's self-esteem takes a dive when she gets a lower score on her SAT than Zack, hurting her chances at getting into Stansbury College.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413123000 +0000" stop="20250413130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Bayside Triangle   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Screech realizes that Zack and Lisa have fallen for each other while Zack helps her put on a fashion show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413130000 +0000" stop="20250413133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Student-teacher Week   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's student-teacher week. Belding and Zack switch places while Kelly becomes Slater's teacher. When Kelly gives a test and everyone in her class fails, Zack faces a hard decision: to either be their friend or their leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413133000 +0000" stop="20250413140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Teacher's Strike   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>To go on a ski trip, the gang conjures up a teacher's strike only to learn that it could affect the academic bowl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413140000 +0000" stop="20250413143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>You're Never Too Old</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Robert Reed puts in double duty as Great-Grandpa Brady as does Florence Henderson when she portrays Great-Grandma Hutchins in an episode where the Brady kids play matchmakers and try to get the two together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413143000 +0000" stop="20250413150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>You Can't Win 'em All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby and Cindy have an opportunity to try out for a televised children's quiz show if they pass a written test. However, an overconfident Bobby doesn't study at all and fails. Cindy is chosen, but her ego gets the best of her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413150000 +0000" stop="20250413153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Not With My Sister, You Don't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When 12-year-old Joanie Cunningham is invited by Fonzie's leather-clad nephew, Spike, to go to a movie on her first real date, her parents and big brother, Richie, do what they do best...worry!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413153000 +0000" stop="20250413160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Drive! She Said</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne has an embarrassing secret: she never learned how to drive! Shirley is ready and willing to give her driving lessons, and Shirley assures her its a cinch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413160000 +0000" stop="20250413163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Hollywood film crew decides to use Mayberry as a backdrop for a movie, everyone in town begins to put on airs, risking the small-town charm that attracted the crew in the first place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413163000 +0000" stop="20250413170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Wants New Furniture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy tries to hide some new furniture she bought without Ricky's permission in the kitchen. Discovering his wife's extravagant purchase, Ricky insists that Lucy pays for it from her allowance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413170000 +0000" stop="20250413173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Spends The Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally invites Eddie to spend the night. However, during a game of chess, Eddie accuses Wally of cheating and they get into a big argument ending with Wally ordering Eddie to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413173000 +0000" stop="20250413180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Report Card</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets out of school early to go to the dentist, which prompts Gilbert to drop off his report card. However, Eddie and Lumpy get a hold of it and Eddie decides to alter Beaver's arithmetic grade from a D- to a B+.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413180000 +0000" stop="20250413183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Meanwhile, Back At The Cabin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts find that the comforts of the mansion do not always compare to the comforts of their former mountain shack. Elly gets gifts and tips from Miss Jane on how to be a Beverly Hills girl, and Jethro believes Jane likes him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413183000 +0000" stop="20250413190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Plot For Granny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>For Granny’s birthday, the Clampetts plan to surprise her with some land in the country. Jed calls a number Jethro saw an ad for. However, the Clampetts do not know they are calling a cemetery. After a misunderstanding, the men from the cemetery begin believing the Clampetts are cold-blooded killers, having killed an entire family named Green, Granny and Mrs. Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413190000 +0000" stop="20250413193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Water, Water Everywhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways discover that their supply of fresh drinking water is running out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413193000 +0000" stop="20250413200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>So Sorry, My Island Now</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways are captured by a Japanese sailor who thinks that WWII never ended, and it is up to Gilligan to save them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413200000 +0000" stop="20250413203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Friend Indeed  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama is jealous that Iola is spending a lot of time with her new friend, Arlene, but soon learns that Arlene can hardly wait to rid herself of the clinging Iola.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413203000 +0000" stop="20250413210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Gets The Bird  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama's crazy old Uncle Oscar passes on, he leaves her his talking parrot, Captain Petey, who convinces the family that treasure is hidden somewhere in the house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413210000 +0000" stop="20250413220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Two For Julie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubing's aunt wants to take Vicki; a jealous lover targets Doc; two passengers compete for Julie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413220000 +0000" stop="20250413223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Trader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ignoring his own advice to Opie, Andy plays fast and loose with the facts when trying to sell the old town cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413223000 +0000" stop="20250413230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Shawn Peterson- Pez</sub-title>
    <desc>"They say to do what you love, and Shawn Peterson loves PEZ.  After years of collecting rare dispensers, candies, and other company artifacts, Shawn successfully pitched a PEZ Visitor Center at the company’s historic and still-functioning factory, where he now manages and shares his collection with 80,000 visitors a year.  He also shares his collection with Collector’s Call, taking Lisa, and PEZ Price Guide expert and appraiser, John LaSpina, on a ride through PEZ history, including: a 1940s PEZ Girl uniform, a rare Colonel Sanders prototype, and a giant edible candy tablet that you can only acquire if you’re invited to the headquarters factory in Germany.  John appraises Shawn’s collection and attempts a trade, offering an ultra rare set and display featured in a Montgomery Ward catalogue in exchange for a dispenser from the 1984 Winter Olympics.  Also, Shawn shows Lisa around the PEZ factory and takes her behind-the-scenes of the candy-making process."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413230000 +0000" stop="20250413233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250413233000 +0000" stop="20250414000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Are You Now, Margaret?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Congressional aide, Williamson, visits the 4077th on a supposedly routine fact-finding tour, but it's discovered that his motives are far deeper—too uncover Margaret as a communist sympathizer. His case is full of innuendo, so the gang set out to help Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414000000 +0000" stop="20250414003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Man In The Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home from work in a great mood and orders Edith to have dinner ready and waiting, because he has an important date to watch the CBS Evening News to see himself on it. Apparently, Archie was interviewed as a man-on-the-street voicing his opinions on Nixon's presidency. However, getting to see himself proves to be difficult for him, when the TV breaks down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414003000 +0000" stop="20250414010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Maude's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith has been running herself ragged caring for Archie, Mike and Gloria, who have all come down with a terrible flu. This prompts her to call on her extremely liberal Cousin Maude to come and stay with the Bunkers and help out. Maude proves to be salt in an already open wound for Archie, who has never liked Maude and vice versa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414010000 +0000" stop="20250414013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Day At The Bunker's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Christmas Day and Archie is the only one not in the Christmas spirit. Mike and Gloria question him, but he refuses to reveal what's bugging him. The Jeffersons come over to wish the Bunkers a "Merry Christmas", but this does anything but cheer Archie up especially since Henry is dressed as Santa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414013000 +0000" stop="20250414020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Elevator Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers are celebrating Edith's birthday at an Italian restaurant in the city when Archie discovers that Edith failed to mail out a payment to the insurance company. This leads him to run across the street to drop it off. However, on his way he gets stuck in an elevator along with a pregnant Puerto Rican and her husband, an aging hippie, and an erudite black businessman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414020000 +0000" stop="20250414023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Swiped Life, A</sub-title>
    <desc>In A Swiped Life, the gang parodies "A Stolen Life" with Carol as Bette Davis' role of twin sisters with opposite personalities who get confused for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414023000 +0000" stop="20250414030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Paul Sand</sub-title>
    <desc>In Honeymoon Sweet, newlyweds Carol and Paul have honeymoon jitters. Then, Carol and the gang perform classic TV Commercial parodies, including Diaper Dampers, E.F. Mutton, the Innersplotch Water Mattress, Matador, Scoop Mouthwash, and Cross-My-Body-Bra. Finally, in Astronauts Going to Mars, Paul finds out that he wasn't invited to a barbecue back on Earth and rubs it in Harvey's face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414030000 +0000" stop="20250414033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Shoehorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob invests his bonus paycheck in Buddy's uncle's discount shoe store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414033000 +0000" stop="20250414040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Girls Will Be Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie says a girl's been beating him up in school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414040000 +0000" stop="20250414043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Ralph Kramden, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton invests in Ralph's stock when Ralph wants twenty dollars. When Ralph thinks he is named in a millionaire's will, arguments arise. It turns out Ralph was simply left a pet bird named Fortune, and much of the money was left to the butler and maid.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414043000 +0000" stop="20250414050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A World Of Difference</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman discovers that life as he knows it doesn't really exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414050000 +0000" stop="20250414060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Diagnosis: Danger  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Health department officials try to stop an anthrax outbreak spreading through Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414060000 +0000" stop="20250414070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Martyr</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Premier Rojek and his advisor, Czerny, put together a special congress of their youth organization to deter youth from following the memory of the deceased President Malik, a freedom fighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414070000 +0000" stop="20250414080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Tiger Left, Tiger Right</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a gardener on the estate of the wealthy Mike and Laura Pryor, Kimble is mistakenly abducted by Harold and Irene Cheyney. Harold is a Korean War veteran and former factory worker who lost the use of his legs after a truck owned by the Pryo</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414080000 +0000" stop="20250414090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>For The Love Of Money</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell tries to unravel the mystery of a mentally disturbed young man who's convinced that he's murdered his own brother twice!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414090000 +0000" stop="20250414093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Dognappers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon set out to muzzle thieves who steal dogs and then collect hefty rewards from the owners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414093000 +0000" stop="20250414100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Persons - The Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Working with the slimmest of leads, police attempt to identify a woman's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414100000 +0000" stop="20250414103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>L.a. International</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed barely get acquainted with their fill-in assignment at LAX when a security camera spots a car being stolen from a parking structure. While on foot-beat as Zebra-12 inside the airport, they find a surprise inside of a stolen suitcase, deal with a man who picks the pocket of a returning soldier, chase down a man buying airline tickets with stolen credit cards, escort a runaway boy back to his mother and track down a suspect who robbed a parking structure attendant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414103000 +0000" stop="20250414110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clinic On 18th St</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Abe Strayhorn and his assistants from the major fraud and consumer protection division of the Los Angeles District Attorney's Office launch an investigation into a local doctor following the death of one of his patients, who was found wearing a strange belt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414110000 +0000" stop="20250414120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Wacky World Of Oddball Sports</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony compete in some of the world's most interesting sports."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414120000 +0000" stop="20250414123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Mistaken Identity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer catches Richard throwing rocks at the windows of an old abandoned house. When asked for his name, he tells the officer it is Theodore Cleaver. Meanwhile, Ward has joined a committee to organize a youth center.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414123000 +0000" stop="20250414130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Dream Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally falls head over heels for a popular girl in school, Ginny Townsend. To get them together, June slyly invites Ginny on a picnic and the Cleaver's quickly discover that Ginny is not exactly a barrel of laughs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414130000 +0000" stop="20250414140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wednesday Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Released from prison after serving a sentence for the murder of his employer, Phillip maintains his innocence and may do something reckless to prove it. But it isn't long before Phillip is again arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414140000 +0000" stop="20250414150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner: Part 1  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a prison guard is accused of murder, Matlock goes into the prison to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414150000 +0000" stop="20250414160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Tibbs goes home to Philadelphia, where he's implicated in a cop's murder while probing his own cop friend's apparent suicide---all with Althea about to give birth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414160000 +0000" stop="20250414170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason and John Boy's friend Seth is diagnosed with leukemia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414170000 +0000" stop="20250414173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Last Fling</sub-title>
    <desc>"John Peevy and Milligan Rives go out for one "Last Fling" and Peevy makes a pass at Kitty. Kitty threatens to shoot him if he comes back. When Peevy gets shot he tells the marshall that Kitty did it. Someone takes a shot at Kitty and Matt thinks Peevy did it and goes looking for him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414173000 +0000" stop="20250414180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chester's Murder</sub-title>
    <desc>"Chester is drinking at the Long Branch and gets into an argument with a gambler over a girl. When the marshall breaks it up he tells Chester to bring the man to jail. On the way there the man is killed and everyone thinks Chester did it. Matt has to prove Chester is innocent."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414180000 +0000" stop="20250414190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Unseen Wound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran sheriff driven to insanity by years of senseless killings turns his gun on the people of his town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414190000 +0000" stop="20250414193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A condemned killer being transported by train murders a marshal and takes Mark hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414193000 +0000" stop="20250414200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark discovers that the new preacher and his wife are impostors planning a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414200000 +0000" stop="20250414210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Julia Gage Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Julia Gage is an independent woman who refuses to admit that she needs a man's help to drive her wagon. Major Adams persuades the shy Tobe Cannon to give her a hand anyway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414210000 +0000" stop="20250414220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Wedsworth-townsend Act, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Seeing a dire need in the community for on-the spot medical assistance, Roy and John attempt to convince their staunchest opponent, Dr. Brackett, to support paramedic legislation that means getting help to where it's needed most. Martin Miller and Kent McCord of Adam-12 guest star in this thrilling 2-hour pilot movie"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414220000 +0000" stop="20250414223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414223000 +0000" stop="20250414230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414230000 +0000" stop="20250414233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250414233000 +0000" stop="20250415000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415000000 +0000" stop="20250415003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy is chosen to be the sole judge of a local beauty pageant. The entrants include Floyd's niece, the mayor's daughter and Ellie Walker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415003000 +0000" stop="20250415010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy, The Marriage Counselor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy counsels a Mayberry couple who are constantly bickering with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415010000 +0000" stop="20250415013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed, Incorporated</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed becomes head of a corporation, which Drysdale organized for him as a tax write-off. The Clampetts decide they want to help out at their corporation, and get the penthouse suite in the bank building. They get all dressed up, Elly in one of her ball gowns, and go to the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415013000 +0000" stop="20250415020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Legend Of Barney Fife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Warren gets to meet his idol, Barney Fife. Barney is thrilled to have someone worship him, but has to sneak out of town when a case comes up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415020000 +0000" stop="20250415023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Fat Hermann, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get a trainload of stolen paintings back to London, but things get complicated when Marya uses Schultz to impersonate Reich Marshall Goehring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415023000 +0000" stop="20250415030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Softer They Fall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kinchloe fights a German boxing champ, creating a diversion for a heist Hogan is planning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415030000 +0000" stop="20250415033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Sand And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In An American Housewife, Carol finds the world falling apart around her with natural disasters and emergencies. Then, in Pregnant Pause, Paul is jealous of Carol's soon-to-be-born baby. Finally, in Gangster Movie, Tim tries to off the notorious "Mr. Big", but nothing works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415033000 +0000" stop="20250415043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Clumsy Clown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Two owners of a circus are trying to buy out each other. Both also are after a clown in the circus for the funds. The second owner is blackmailing him regarding his wife's second marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415043500 +0000" stop="20250415050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Long Live Walter Jameson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A history teacher talks about the past as if he had lived it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415050500 +0000" stop="20250415053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Incident In A Small Jail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>In prison for jaywalking, a salesman finds himself locked in a cell with an accused murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415053500 +0000" stop="20250415060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman's Help</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After falling in love with his invalid wife's nurse, a man schemes to get rid of his wife altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415060500 +0000" stop="20250415070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Cry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix discovers evidence of a crime from an unlikely source: a deaf girl who "heard" the plot by reading the lips of a criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415070500 +0000" stop="20250415080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Iceman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon reopens an investigation when he discovers a convicted man may be innocent, but then refuses parole. Robert Foxworth is the villain. He plays a murderer, an ex-Green Beret who served in Vietnam with overtones of CIA activity. The murdered man was Cannon's friend, and that brings him into the case. When the convicted murderer turns down a parole, Cannon becomes very curious."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415080500 +0000" stop="20250415090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Time To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a dinner guest falls asleep, his host steals his diamond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415090000 +0000" stop="20250415093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Forgery - The Ranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Other people's credit cards are found in the possession of a forest ranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415093000 +0000" stop="20250415100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Night School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday arrests a member of his class for possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415100000 +0000" stop="20250415103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy invites a troubled boy along on an upcoming week-long group camping trip in the mountains after apprehending him during a burglary, but soon discovers the kid might be too much for him to handle. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a high-speed chase with a taxi, investigate a motorcycle versus pedestrian accident in a parking lot and respond to an armed robbery call.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415103000 +0000" stop="20250415110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Officers Malloy and Woods take a group of children to a youth camp, but Malloy becomes preoccupied with the 14-year-old boy he reluctantly brought along, who continues to compensate for his small stature by getting into trouble. Meanwhile, Reed goes on patrol alone, and deals with a woman who uses a unique weapon to fend off an attacker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415110000 +0000" stop="20250415120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>After School Special</sub-title>
    <desc>"In an effort to teach Toony the importance of kindness, Bill decides to create a classic after-school special."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415120000 +0000" stop="20250415123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The School Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver's class is having a group picture taken, Gilbert goads Beaver into making a face with him when they snap the picture. However, when the picture is actually taken, Gilbert backs out and Beaver is the only one making a face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415123000 +0000" stop="20250415130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Rat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver making trades with his classmates is beginning to get on Ward and June's nerves because he seems to be the one who always walks away shorthanded. June especially thinks Beaver got the short stick in his latest trade when he comes home with a pet rat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415130000 +0000" stop="20250415140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Accosted Accountant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When the son-in-law of a wealthy industrialist begins to question the man's judgement, Mason is called in to help reinforce the case. Soon, however, the industrialist is found dead and his son-in-law is the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415140000 +0000" stop="20250415150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner: Part 2  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a prison guard is accused of murder, Matlock goes into the prison to defend him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415150000 +0000" stop="20250415160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lessons Learned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie sends Parker to confirm suspicions that a local truck stop is really a front for a prostitution business. When a young prostitute is found dead Gillespie is shocked at her father’s reaction. Parker is dismayed when he recognizes one of the ladies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415160000 +0000" stop="20250415170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Cradle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia is happy to learn that she is pregnant again, but John worries that having another baby will be hard for her</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415170000 +0000" stop="20250415173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Photographer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dodge City meets a Photographer who shows the residents how a camera works. Jacoby wants to take pictures of how the Wild West looks. When Matt learns someone died he thinks the photographer may have hired someone to kill Grubby for a picture of the west."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415173000 +0000" stop="20250415180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sam Rickers comes to the Marshal's Office asking to see Matt. Chester looks inside the wagon to find a dead man, Sam thinks he killed a criminal hoping to get $1000 for the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415180000 +0000" stop="20250415190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Journey To Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>During a difficult drought, a friend of Joe's joins an outlaw gang to make ends meet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415190000 +0000" stop="20250415193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance get into trouble with the Army when they try to help a wounded young soldier who deserted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415193000 +0000" stop="20250415200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mark contracts typhoid fever and has a vision of his dead mother, he no longer seems interested in getting well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415200000 +0000" stop="20250415210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cliff Grundy Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Cliff Grundy is seriously injured in a buffalo stampede. Flint and another passenger tend to his injuries; however, the other passenger has a hidden motive—he wants the location of a gold mine and thinks Grundy knows it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415210000 +0000" stop="20250415220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Wedsworth-townsend Act, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Seeing a dire need in the community for on-the spot medical assistance, Roy and John attempt to convince their staunchest opponent, Dr. Brackett, to support paramedic legislation that means getting help to where it's needed most. Martin Miller and Kent McCord of Adam-12 guest star in this thrilling 2-hour pilot movie"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415220000 +0000" stop="20250415223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415223000 +0000" stop="20250415230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415230000 +0000" stop="20250415233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250415233000 +0000" stop="20250416000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416000000 +0000" stop="20250416003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes suspicious when a record promoter comes to town to gather material for a folk music album.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416003000 +0000" stop="20250416010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Barney's Morale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's overzealous policing enrages the people of Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416010000 +0000" stop="20250416013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Learns To Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>After Granny takes a cab home and gets charged for the ride, she decides that it is time for her to learn how to drive. The taxi driver who took Granny home is having trouble collecting the fair, and after a series of events begins to believe that he is in a mental hospital. Granny, during her driving lesson, mistakenly gets on the road.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416013000 +0000" stop="20250416020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret Life Of Gomer Pyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter suspects Gomer has been spending his Sundays at the beach. He then tries to meet the beauties Gomer appeared with in a magazine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416020000 +0000" stop="20250416023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Gowns By Yvette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use the wedding of Burkhalter's niece to smuggle a defector out of Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416023000 +0000" stop="20250416030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>One Army At A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter convinces the German he is one of them when he is captured in German uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416030000 +0000" stop="20250416033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Richard Crenna And Ruth Buzzi</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Models, Carol debates cheating on her model husband with another model, striking a pose along the way. Then in Adam and Eve 12, Carol asks for a divorce from her husband, just as they're about to catch the perp. Finally, in Celebrities and Peasants, Carol and Ruth can't work together to win the game show competition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416033000 +0000" stop="20250416043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Provocative Protégé</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Washed up pianist David Carpenter is knocked out and pushed over a cliff for insurance money. Carpenter's beautiful protege, Donna Ross, immediately comes under suspicion by the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416043500 +0000" stop="20250416050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>People Are Alike All Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When a space exploration crashes on Mars, the surviving passenger is surprised to find that Martians are human-looking, very friendly and apparently just like us.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416050500 +0000" stop="20250416053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Museum Piece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A museum piece causes problems for a curious visitor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416053500 +0000" stop="20250416060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Coming, Mama</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman begins to realize that her mother has no intentions of cutting her from her apron strings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416060500 +0000" stop="20250416070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Comes Up Roses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find an airport security officer's wife, but gets no cooperation. It seems that Rose Anderson does not wish to be found—or someone does not wish her to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416070500 +0000" stop="20250416080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Arena Of Fear</sub-title>
    <desc>Socialite Doris Hawthorne's fiance disappears. Only then does she learn he was actually married to a Swiss woman, and also a blackmailing extortionist with a long list of enemies, many of whom want his files.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416080500 +0000" stop="20250416090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death On Deposit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A cattleman is murdered in his own corral on the day he was to withdraw his money from the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416090000 +0000" stop="20250416093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>I.a.d. - The Receipt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a complaint that two veteran officers stole funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416093000 +0000" stop="20250416100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - The Harassing Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416100000 +0000" stop="20250416103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Team Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program, Malloy and Reed team with Motor Officer Grant to better combat crime. Out on patrol, they make a safety check at a residence, investigate a suspicious witness at the scene of a traffic accident, deal with a young member of a neighborhood watch, respond to an annoying complaint about illegally parked cars and perform a daylight stakeout to catch a serial burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416103000 +0000" stop="20250416110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Roll Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An anonymous call of shots fired over the radio leads to an 'Emergency!' roll call and frantic search for Motor Officer Grant. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed respond to a citizen report of an armed robbery in progress at a bar, and Reed goes undercover as a pizza delivery driver to bust a dangerous scam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416110000 +0000" stop="20250416120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Wolverine State</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416120000 +0000" stop="20250416123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>In The Soup</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is throwing a party and is successful in getting Beaver out of the house, who is planning to spend the night at Whitey's. However, on the way to Whitey's house, he and Beaver get into an argument over a billboard that is advertising soup, leading Beaver to fall into the giant soup bowl mounted at the top of the billboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416123000 +0000" stop="20250416130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Community Chest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver volunteers to go around the neighborhood and collect for the Community Chest in June's place after she decides to attend Wally's open house at his school. Beaver brings along Gilbert and thanks to Beaver's astronomical mistake of losing the collection can, chaos erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416130000 +0000" stop="20250416140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Capering Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Scandalous photos and blackmail lead to suicide...or is it murder? Mason is resolved to find out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416140000 +0000" stop="20250416150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Accused of murdering his uncle in a drunken rage, Matlock takes the case of Drew Carey, a spoiled, self-centered young man who refuses to listen to his lawyer's council.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416150000 +0000" stop="20250416160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Perversions Of Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A mild mannered school teacher is accused of child molestation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416160000 +0000" stop="20250416170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fulfillment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Curtis and Ann are unhappy to learn that they are unable to have children of their own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416170000 +0000" stop="20250416173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Big Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <desc>"Philip Locke is looking for Laura Simmons, but she doesn't want him to know where she works. Laura tells Matt she and Philip were to wed she asks Matt not to say anything about her job. Philip warns Matt that he will be killed if he doesn't tell the truth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416173000 +0000" stop="20250416180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>What The Whiskey Drummer Heard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt goes inside The Long Branch and meets Wilbur Hawkins a whiskey Drummer tells Matt he will die. Matt is almost shot while feeding the horses, in Doc Adams's office Matt plans to let everyone thinks he died. Kitty tells a man at The Long Branch is telling a different story."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416180000 +0000" stop="20250416190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Amigo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>While riding posse after a band of vicious marauders, Ben Cartwright captures one of their wounded and must protect the man's life from ranchers, his own gang and an angry Little Joe who lost a friend when his ranch was raided.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416190000 +0000" stop="20250416193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Lucas's returns to town in the company of a shady gambler and is accused of cheating at cards.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416193000 +0000" stop="20250416200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men are vying for a rancher's daughter's affections. When she is found dead, one of them becomes the prime suspect in her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416200000 +0000" stop="20250416210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Luke O'malley Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Luke O'Malley, fleeing Mexican bandits whom he double crossed, joins the wagon train disguised as a minister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416210000 +0000" stop="20250416220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Botulism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John plots his revenge after being the repeated target of practical jokes. A man breaks his back falling off a tower. A woman fakes an illness. Dr. Early's stethoscope becomes lodged in his ear. A man brought into the hospital from a movie set is the first indication of an outbreak of botulism. A boy is trapped in a condemned building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416220000 +0000" stop="20250416223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. race against the clock to save a soldier from paralysis. B.J.'s harvesting an aorta from a dead soldier doesn't sit well with the soldier's friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416223000 +0000" stop="20250416230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416230000 +0000" stop="20250416233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250416233000 +0000" stop="20250417000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Stars And Stripes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friction arises between B.J. and Winchester when they are asked to write an article for a prestigious medical journal on how they saved a soldier's life with a daring operation. Meanwhile, Hot Lips receives an eventful visit from Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417000000 +0000" stop="20250417003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Gentleman Crook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An infamous con artist, held temporarily in Mayberry, manages to enchant everyone except Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417003000 +0000" stop="20250417010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to help Barney express his lovestruck feelings for Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417010000 +0000" stop="20250417013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cabin In Beverly Hills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed puts up the cabin for Granny's birthday, which Mrs. Drysdale is not happy about. During the celebrating, a sociology student stops by and sees the Clampetts. She thinks they are Drysdale's servants and works to liberate them from what she believes to be a life of servitude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417013000 +0000" stop="20250417020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Lost And Found</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee loses a piece of jewelry and makes an insurance claim. After spending all the money, she finds the lost item.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417020000 +0000" stop="20250417023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Standing Room Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to save Klink from an officer who plans on turning him in for not having balanced books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417023000 +0000" stop="20250417030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417030000 +0000" stop="20250417033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Dick Martin And Anthony Newley</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Wine Tasters, two wine tasters battle it out to enter the Hall of Fame for Wine Tasters. Then, in Send in the Clowns, Carol helps her boss prepare for his wedding and sings the classic song. Finally, in Stella Toddler, Carol's klutzy alter ego is honored with a footprint outside of Grauman's Chinese Theater.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417033000 +0000" stop="20250417043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nine Dolls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason's fishing trip to Scotland is interrupted by seven-year-old Peggy Smith. Peggy is living at a boarding school and searching for her real parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417043500 +0000" stop="20250417050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Just before being hanged for murder, a man in 1880 is transported to the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417050500 +0000" stop="20250417053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Deathmate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>An older woman tries to convince her young lover to end her husband's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417053500 +0000" stop="20250417060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Gratitude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>When the syndicate turns against the owner of a casino, he fears for his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417060500 +0000" stop="20250417070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Point</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded boy gives Mannix a clue suggesting corruption, and then disappears, kidnapped by a criminal gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417070500 +0000" stop="20250417080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Died Twice</sub-title>
    <desc>"With the help of his former police partner, Frank is asked by his former captain to reopen a case of a corrupt cop who has reappeared after being declared dead years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417080500 +0000" stop="20250417090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Web Of Deceit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A newsman takes pictures of evidence showing that an industrialist is involved with the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417090000 +0000" stop="20250417093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Police search for a safecracker who left his calling card at the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417093000 +0000" stop="20250417100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's cases range from purse snatching to homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417100000 +0000" stop="20250417103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspect Number One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to find a way to help a 60-year-old career criminal he arrested 10 years ago, who was recently released and begs to be re-arrested so he can spend his retirement years in the federal penitentiary. Meanwhile, he and Reed become suspicious while investigating an apparent home burglary, and later respond to a bank robbery in progress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417103000 +0000" stop="20250417110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. MacDonald is suffering a marital crisis and turns to Malloy for advice. On today's patrol, a female cashier is taken hostage inside a grocery store by a couple of trigger-happy robbers who attempt to escape on the roof, and an elderly woman turns up missing from her retirement home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417110000 +0000" stop="20250417120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bill Gets Drafted</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony takes an unconventional approach to helping Bill train for military duty."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417120000 +0000" stop="20250417123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Junior Fire Chief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to run for junior fire chief and, to his surprise, wins. However, as soon as he's elected, he lets the responsibilities go to his head and begins issuing citations to not only his family but his neighbors as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417123000 +0000" stop="20250417130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Frogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a canoe and makes a deal with Ward: If Beaver can come up with half the money, Ward will pay for the other half. So Beaver, comes up with a way of making money by selling frogs. However, little does he know that the man who's going to buy the frogs, uses them for class dissections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417130000 +0000" stop="20250417140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ice-cold Hands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After winning tickets at a horse track lead to accusations of theft and eventually murder, Mason must defend a woman caught in the middle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417140000 +0000" stop="20250417150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Dare  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An eccentric millionaire tells Matlock that he wouldn't be able to solve the perfect murder if it were handed to him on a silver platter. To prove his point, he kills Matlock's friend and successfully frames another man for the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417150000 +0000" stop="20250417160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>...and Justice For Some</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie and his officers are outraged when a drug courier who ran down the son of Virgil's next door neighbor makes a deal with the F.B.I. to avoid prosecution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417160000 +0000" stop="20250417170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Easter Story, An</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Olivia is stricken with polio, John-Boy refuses to accept the doctor's prognosis that she may never walk again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417170000 +0000" stop="20250417173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cheap Labour</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt meets Fos Capper, who wants to marry Flora Stancil. Flora's brother Ben may give Matt some trouble that may lead to Foss Capper's death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417173000 +0000" stop="20250417180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Moon</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Charlie Brewer is found dead, Jack Salter who was a friend of Charlie Brewer comes to Matt's office saying Vint killed Brewer. Matt then tries to find out if Jack is right."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417180000 +0000" stop="20250417190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben discovers that an old friend of the Cartwrights, Mary Wharton, is being abused by her husband when the couple comes to live at the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417190000 +0000" stop="20250417193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Shotgun man John Beaumont, who Lucas sent to prison, returns with vengeance on his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417193000 +0000" stop="20250417200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting a man in self-defense, Andy Moon turns to Lucas for protection from his vengeful brothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417200000 +0000" stop="20250417210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jesse Cowan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cowans and Beals have been feuding a long time. Bob and Jesse Cowan return from the war to find their family dead, and the Beals a part of the wagon train. Vengeance is just the start of what Major Adams must now deal with.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417210000 +0000" stop="20250417220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Cook's Tour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>John delivers a cyanotic baby. The firemen give Roy a bad time about his cooking. A boy gets his hand stuck in a vase; John rescues a kid in handcuffs. A man repairing a washer gets an electric shock. The paramedics rescue a man trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417220000 +0000" stop="20250417223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yessir, That's Our Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby born to a Korean woman and an American GI is abandoned at the 4077th. Knowing that Amer-Asian children are often mistreated in Korean society, the troop sets about the frustrating task of finding a new home for the infant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417223000 +0000" stop="20250417230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottle Fatigue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrified by the gigantic size of his monthly bar tab at the officer's club, Hawkeye vows to give up booze for a week. Meanwhile, Winchester desperately tries to halt his sister's impending marriage to a man he considers unworthy of the Winchester heritage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417230000 +0000" stop="20250417233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heal Thyself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter turns crotchety when he catches the mumps, and his condition is worsened when Winchester gets the same disease and has to be quarantined with him. A temporary replacement surgeon, Newsome, is quickly brought into the 4077th and seems to be a gem in terms of both personality and ability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250417233000 +0000" stop="20250418000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Old Soldiers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is appointed temporary commander of the 4077th when Colonel Potter rushes off to Tokyo on a mysterious mission. While in command, Hawkeye's main problem is housing a large group of Korean refugees comprised mainly of rambunctious children who need medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418000000 +0000" stop="20250418003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Housekeepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie go to great lengths to show Aunt Bee what a mess they'd be without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418003000 +0000" stop="20250418010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a handsome new doctor arrives in town, his friendship with Ellie arouses suspicion in Aunt Bee and Barney and jealousy in Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418010000 +0000" stop="20250418013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Foils A Home Wrecker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to save the cabin for the Clampetts, but his wife calls a professional home wrecker to tear down the mountain shack. Meanwhile, Ginny Jennings and her sociology professor come back to visit the Clampetts and see that they are still occupying the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418013000 +0000" stop="20250418020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>You Bet Your Won Ton</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer holds a farewell dinner in a Chinese restaurant, not knowing it is a front for a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418020000 +0000" stop="20250418023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Sergeant's Analyst</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After Burkhalter finds him sleeping on the job, Schultz is ordered to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418023000 +0000" stop="20250418030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418030000 +0000" stop="20250418033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Exercise with Jack Leilani, Carol tries her best to exercise, despite her large size. Then, in The Carpenters, Harvey and Lyle complain about women in the workforce, obliviously to Carol finishing the construction project behind them. Finally, in Bachelor Party, Steve uses his charm one last time to woo Carol, not knowing she's his fiance's sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418033000 +0000" stop="20250418043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Loquacious Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lester Martin's life takes a horrible turn for the worse when a man breaks into his apartment, forces him at gun-point to drink half a bottle of Scotch and then drives him into the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418043500 +0000" stop="20250418050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Tall Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy who believes in magic thinks he is helping a boxer win with his "big, tall wish."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418050500 +0000" stop="20250418053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Pearl Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man convinces his girlfriend to accept the marriage proposal from an old, sick and very rich man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418053500 +0000" stop="20250418060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Can't Trust A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Guilt and fear plague a woman when her husband returns from prison after serving time for a crime she committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418060500 +0000" stop="20250418070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To The Swiftest, Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellen Kovak suspects her husband's death in a racing accident wasn't an accident at all, and she hires Mannix to prove it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418070500 +0000" stop="20250418080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Touch Of Venom</sub-title>
    <desc>"A group of terrorists have drugged Cannon with a poison, giving him 72 hours to give them a defector and receive the antidote or die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418080500 +0000" stop="20250418090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Last Contract, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother asks Barnaby to help her find her runaway daughter, who's married to a contract killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250418090000 +0000" stop="20250418093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
