<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024100000 +0000" stop="20241024103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024103000 +0000" stop="20241024110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024110000 +0000" stop="20241024120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Monster Bash!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony throw a spooktacular Halloween Party with the help of a special expert!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024120000 +0000" stop="20241024123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After leaving the cap off the ink, Beaver is grounded to the house for a whole day after spilled ink ruins some of Ward's papers. However, Larry and Beaver sneak out to the movies and when Beaver wins a bike, he must find a way to keep it a secret from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024123000 +0000" stop="20241024130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's class holds a "Most Beautiful Baby" contest in which each student is supposed to bring in a baby picture. To make the deadline, June picks out a cute picture of Beaver at the last minute and sends it to Miss Landers, not realizing that the cute picture may cause Beaver embarrassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024130000 +0000" stop="20241024140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blushing Pearls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mitsuo Kamuri has been seeing a great deal of Grover Nichols, son of wealthy businessman Hudson Nichols. Nichols doesn't approve of his son's relationship and when Mitsuo is "caught" with a string of valuable pearls belonging to Mrs. Nichols, he agrees to absolve her if she stops seeing his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024140000 +0000" stop="20241024150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Murder Game  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to spend the weekend as part of a murder mystery with Cliff, Leanne and three people who each paid $10,000 for the privilege of matching wits with the famous Ben Matlock. When the pretend victim turns up dead, Matlock and his team must determine which of the three paying customers is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024150000 +0000" stop="20241024160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>No Other Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Harriet tries to keep Eugene from giving up when his father faces the death penalty. And the police search for three suspects in connection to a robbery/murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024160000 +0000" stop="20241024170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg; Doctors doubt her ability to walk ever again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024170000 +0000" stop="20241024180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snow Train: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A train that Matt, Doc and Festus are riding is stopped by Indians who request two passengers be turned over to their custody for selling them poisonous whiskey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024180000 +0000" stop="20241024190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Ones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mexican freedom fighters loyal to Benito Juárez take over the Ponderosa, gravely wound Little Joe and force Ben to guide them to a wagon train loaded with gold being smuggled to California by Emperor Maximilian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024190000 +0000" stop="20241024193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024193000 +0000" stop="20241024200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024200000 +0000" stop="20241024210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Albert Farnsworth Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Arrogant British Colonel Albert Farnsworth causes an indian attack that results in the capture of a young girl by the Cheyenne and the mortal wounding of his long time aide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024210000 +0000" stop="20241024220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The station adopts a stray dog, which they name Boot. The firemen rescue a boy from a hole; he turns out to be an abused child. Roy and John rescue another boy whose head is stuck in a basement window. Dr. Early extracts a child's arm from a steering wheel. At a brush fire, Boot helps locate an injured hiker, and then leaves with a hook and ladder truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024220000 +0000" stop="20241024223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024223000 +0000" stop="20241024230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024230000 +0000" stop="20241024233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241024233000 +0000" stop="20241025000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025000000 +0000" stop="20241025003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Brief Encounter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Aunt Bee falls for traveling handyman Henry Wheeler, Andy soon learns that Wheeler is not as nice as he appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025003000 +0000" stop="20241025010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Andy's big-city fishing buddies invites him to join the Esquire Club, an exclusive Raleigh men's organization. Barney also is asked to join but tries a little too hard to fit in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025010000 +0000" stop="20241025013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale And Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts and Miss Jane return from spending Christmas in Hooterville to learn that Drysdale has driven after them, along with Fairchild, Elly’s bear. Back in the hills, Drysdale gets arrested for vagrancy and bootlegging in a place called Ripley. When they learn, the people at the bank couldn’t be happier that their boss has been locked up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025013000 +0000" stop="20241025020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Charlie, Homer, And Natasha</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver won't take Lisa to New York for a big party, but the issue isn't over. She conspires with Eb to invent new invisible friends, hoping the scheme will end with a trip to the city to visit a psychiatrist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025020000 +0000" stop="20241025023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Tower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan blackmails General Burkhalter to keep Klink from being transferred to the Russian front for failing to keep Hogan from blowing up a radio tower.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025023000 +0000" stop="20241025030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Colonel Klink's Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink suffers at the hands of a tough sergeant sent to discipline prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025030000 +0000" stop="20241025033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Cass Elliot (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 10/13/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025033000 +0000" stop="20241025043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Runaway Racer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Test driver Pete Griston cracks up a vehicle owned by Pappy Ryan. Pappy accuses Havey Rettig of tampering with the car and files charges against Rettig and Griston. Then Rettig is killed and Griston is found standing groggily over the body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025043500 +0000" stop="20241025050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025050500 +0000" stop="20241025060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Crimson Witness  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Ernest Mullett is a playboy who loses his job, wife and girlfriend to his hated, overachieving brother, Farnum Mullett. Ernest's hatred turns to murder when he decides to reenact the biblical story of Cain and Abel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025060500 +0000" stop="20241025070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The wife of a money man for the mob is killed during a hit-and-run accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025070500 +0000" stop="20241025080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Died Twice</sub-title>
    <desc>"With the help of his former police partner, Frank is asked by his former captain to reopen a case of a corrupt cop who has reappeared after being declared dead years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025080500 +0000" stop="20241025090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A rapist threatens to get more violent with Betty's friend if she tells the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025090000 +0000" stop="20241025093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Insulin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Two hoodlums attempt to murder their former cellmate by withholding his insulin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025093000 +0000" stop="20241025100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025100000 +0000" stop="20241025103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Million Dollar Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a run-in with a suspected professional jewel thief and fear she will walk due to lack of evidence. They also find themselves in competition with a millionaire vigilante, who provides assistance with apprehending a drunk driver and ending a shootout, but seems destined to soon overstep the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025103000 +0000" stop="20241025110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandmothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a hype who robbed a hand-made craft store run by elderly women, only to later return the money after robbing an antique store. In the meantime, they engage in a high-speed pursuit, and pull over a priest in possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025110000 +0000" stop="20241025120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Creepy Carnival</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025120000 +0000" stop="20241025123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward saves an old pedometer from being thrown out and gives it to Beaver, but not before telling him a story about when he was a kid he would walk 20 miles a day. Taking the story literally, Beaver makes a bet with Whitey that he, too, can walk 20 miles in a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025123000 +0000" stop="20241025130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Borrowed Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver spend the day at the lake, which is where they encounter two kids who let them borrow their boat. However, little do Larry and Beaver know, the boat is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025130000 +0000" stop="20241025140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Startled Stallion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy rancher John Brant forecloses on Jo Ann Blanchard's mortgage and takes possession of her prized stallion. Jo Ann goes to Mason for help in getting the horse back but soon needs his aid in getting her off a murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025140000 +0000" stop="20241025150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Brennan  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock vies with a formidable district attorney while defending a client accused of killing a city councilwoman, discovering a secret hiding in the man's past that is affecting his judgment in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025150000 +0000" stop="20241025160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Turning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea thinks Virgil needs a new line of work after seeing the aftermath of a deadly shooting at a roadhouse. Virgil finds himself in danger when they arrest the man who committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025160000 +0000" stop="20241025170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Return - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to Walton's Mountain to write about the failing economy and lack of jobs</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025170000 +0000" stop="20241025180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snow Train: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A train that Matt, Doc and Festus are riding is stopped by Indians who request two passengers be turned over to their custody for selling them poisonous whiskey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025180000 +0000" stop="20241025190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Gallagher's Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss helps out two young girls, whose father has just died, by taking them on a journey to their Aunt's place. Unbeknownst to Hoss, one of the girls carries a stolen bag of money and he soon finds out that there are others who are interested in both the money and the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025190000 +0000" stop="20241025193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025193000 +0000" stop="20241025200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025200000 +0000" stop="20241025210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Allison Justis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When someone yells horse thief, Flint shoots a man only to find he is the husband of a childhood friend. Flint learns the man is mayor and highly respected. The question of whether he killed an innocent man bothers him and the man's son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025210000 +0000" stop="20241025220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A photo shoot at the station gets John excited. A country doctor helps Roy and John when they can't reach Rampart on a call. The paramedics rescue a man drowning in a swimming pool and two stuntmen trapped on a waterfall at a movie studio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025220000 +0000" stop="20241025223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025223000 +0000" stop="20241025230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025230000 +0000" stop="20241025233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241025233000 +0000" stop="20241026000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026000000 +0000" stop="20241026003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pickle Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>It's canning time again, and Aunt Bee has put up another batch of pickles. After realizing the only thing they're good for is killing flies brave enough to land on them, Andy and Barney decide to substitute store-bought for her homemade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026003000 +0000" stop="20241026010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets an offer to become the sheriff of Greendale, and Andy tries to discourage him. Unsure how to handle matters, Andy gets the idea to let Barney be sheriff of Mayberry for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026010000 +0000" stop="20241026013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Problem Bear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale has come down with the flu after spending so many nights outside while on the way to Hooterville. Granny wants to help him with her Possum Ridge Penicillin, also known as White Lightening. She leaves Drysdale a jug of it, but he puts it to the side and takes a sleeping pill. However, Elly’s bear Fairchild has taken up drinking Granny’s moonshine and climbs into his room as Drysdale is sleeping and drinks the entire jug.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026013000 +0000" stop="20241026020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Lisa's Vegetable Garden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>According to Oliver, every farm wife should be growing her own vegetables so Lisa starts her own garden. Armed with useless pamphlets from Mr. Kimball and a flask of perfume, Lisa begins work. It's hardly a money-saving proposition after she buys a tractor, farm supplies, and hires Alf and Ralph as her housekeepers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026020000 +0000" stop="20241026023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Top Secret Top Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a top-secret document from Klink's coat to save him from being arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026023000 +0000" stop="20241026030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026030000 +0000" stop="20241026033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Peggy Lee And Dom Deluise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Peggy Lee and Dom Deluise. Originally aired on 10/20/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026033000 +0000" stop="20241026043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Police Sergeant Dave Wolfe warns Joe Oliver to stay away from his kid sister, Susan. Now Susan's been beaten up in her apartment, Oliver has been shot to death and Dave is being charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026043500 +0000" stop="20241026050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>And When The Sky Was Opened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When three U.S. astronauts return to Earth after the first flight into space, they begin being erased from history one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026050500 +0000" stop="20241026060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Woodbine Twineth  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Nell Snyder is worried about the bizarre activities of her niece, who claims acquaintance with the "minute people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026060500 +0000" stop="20241026070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Overkill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix gets involved with the case of a serial killer after his friend becomes the latest victim. But not all is as it seems when he discovers the killer may not be responsible for every murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026070500 +0000" stop="20241026080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Touch Of Venom</sub-title>
    <desc>"A group of terrorists have drugged Cannon with a poison, giving him 72 hours to give them a defector and receive the antidote or die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026080500 +0000" stop="20241026090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On Campus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the supposed suicide of a college professor who had been the victim of his student's pranks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026090000 +0000" stop="20241026093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Curse Of Chester W. Farnsworth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe is convinced that the Shady Rest is haunted by a guest who visited 50 years ago, Chester W. Farnsworth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026093000 +0000" stop="20241026100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>That Was The Night That Was</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate Bradley's Shady Rest is patronized by a guest who gives every indication of being from outer space.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026100000 +0000" stop="20241026103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Critter Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke is sick, and Elly calls the "critter doctor" from the zoo. When Jed finds out he is a "college boy," he thinks it is a possible beau for Elly May, not knowing he is a graduate and an older man. Granny is against this doctor coming, and she mistakes a young salesman who is selling bug repellents for the doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026103000 +0000" stop="20241026110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Silver Dollar City Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the first day of the Silver Dollar City Fair, and Granny is working on getting Elly May a husband before Elverna Bradshaw’s daughter gets married. The two women continue to fight and argue, challenging one another more and more. But with the excitement of the fair, Elly enters a few contests, and Granny arranges plots to brag about Elly May.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026110000 +0000" stop="20241026113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Shiver Me Timbers!, Dizzy Divers, Puppet Love</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye is attracted to an old weather-beaten ship bearing a sign "Ghost Ship - Beware" and he explores it with Olive Oyl and Wimpy as his unwilling companions., Bluto attempts to get to sunken treasure before Popeye can., Popeye wants to propose Olive, but he doesn't have the courage to express his feelings. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026113000 +0000" stop="20241026120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Flying Sorceress, Bottles, Advance And Be Mechanized</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom steals a witch's flying broom so he can scare the wits out of Jerry., An old pharmacist falls asleep in his apothecary and dreams about all of the bottles coming to life with some of them good and some not so good., Tom is a space security guard and he uses his cat robot to chase Jerry's mouse robot as it attempts to sneak some cheese out of the Mining Facility."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026120000 +0000" stop="20241026130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Round Trip To Mars, Chilly's Cold War, Swing Your Partner, Phantom Of The Horse Opera, Coming Out Party, The Sleeping Princess, Woody's Magic Touch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody sabotagues Professor Dingledong's Mars rocket so that it won't take off and pretends to be a martian., Chilly Willy is cold and hungry and takes shelter in the home of Colonel Pot Shot where Smedley is the caretaker., Homer drags his horse out of bed to drive his buggy to the barn dance. In anger, Hank breaks up the dance and forces Homer to pull the buggy home., An outlaw disguises himself as a ghost to scare Woody away., Inspector Willoughby repeatedly foils Crash's attempts to escape Sing Song prison., A fairy curses a princess when she's not invited to a royal ceremony., Woody must trick a witch in order to transform the king's son back into a human again."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026130000 +0000" stop="20241026140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Abominable Snow Rabbit, Big Game Haunt, Hyde And Go Tweet, Shishkabugs, The Phantom Ship, The Haunted Mouse, Bewitched Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and Daffy decide to tunnel underground over to Palm Springs. Wrong directions end them up in the Himalayas where they run into trouble with the Abominable Snowman... , Cool Cat gets chased by Colonel Rimfire into a haunted house. They find a ghost who just wants to be friends, but out of fright they run. , Sylvester is sleeping on the ledge outside the office of Dr. Jekyll (whom we see in his office drinking the potion that turns him into a monster). , Yosemite Sam is working as a king's chef when he is asked to prepare a dish made from rabbit. When Bugs Bunny comes over to borrow carrots, Sam decides that Bugs would be perfect for the recipe. , Beans and his stowaway nephews, Ham and Ex, search for a lost treasure on a haunted ship in the frozen North. , A hungry cat goes to a restaurant in search of food. A ghost mouse sees the cat's arrival as an opportunity to get back at all the cats from his life. , Bugs enters the fairytale world to go save Hanzel and Grettel from the witch. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026140000 +0000" stop="20241026150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Infernal Machine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A federal judge is threatened by a bomb-throwing clockmaker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026150000 +0000" stop="20241026160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jose Morales Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Hawkes is leading three wagons through indian territory. They run into trouble with Mexician bandits lead by Lee Marvin. When the two groups must band together to fight off an indian attack, certain biases and assumptions are thrown away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026160000 +0000" stop="20241026170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Jubal Tanner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria sells land to an old friend who has deeply sentimental reasons for owning it, despite the fact that her own sons are part of a plan to flood that land with waters from a dam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026170000 +0000" stop="20241026180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Luke</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E08</episode-num>
    <desc>As Luke Dangerfield lies shot and dying, he requests that his protégé, Austin, brings him to Dodge so he can see his estranged daughter one last time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026180000 +0000" stop="20241026190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is seriously injured on a cattle drive and Ben takes him to a nearby town in search of a doctor. To his dismay, Ben finds out that the only doctor available is in jail, waiting to be hung for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026190000 +0000" stop="20241026193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026193000 +0000" stop="20241026200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026200000 +0000" stop="20241026210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Backshooter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Jefferson aids Rowdy after his horse takes a spill. Sam is a wanted man and asks Rowdy to turn him in but give the $5,000 reward to his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026210000 +0000" stop="20241026213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Episode In Laredo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Kovak is reserving the entire hotel in Laredo, Texas for Sam Tuttle, a famous unbeatable gunfighter. After Paladin is forced to kill Kovak, Tuttle must challenge Paladin in order to keep his reputation intact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026213000 +0000" stop="20241026220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Dead End</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher hires Randall to bring back a line rider charged with grand theft. The accused man's father accompanies Randall on the trek to the remote shack where the thief is thought to be hiding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241026220000 +0000" stop="20241027000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Hugs And Mugs, Punchy Cowpunchers, Pest Man Wins, Commotion On The Ocean, Hot Ice, Tooth Will Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges run a furniture store and come into possession of a stolen pearl necklace.  Three crooked dames convince the boys that the necklace is theirs, and when the real thieves arrive, the Stooges fight to defend the girl's property.  The Stooges defeat the bad guys and the girls decide to go honest and return the necklace to its rightful owner. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are three soldiers assigned to go undercover and spy on an outlaw gang that's terrorizing a nearby town.  The bad guys have the Arizona Kid locked up, so the boys set about rescuing him with the help of beautiful Nell, his girl.  They free the kid, and he rides to summon help.  The Stooges, with the help of Nell, manage to subdue the bad guys before the kid arrives with the cavalry. , The Stooges graduate from dental school and go out west to open a practice.  Everything goes well until Shemp "cures" an outlaw's toothache from the instructions in a carpentry book, and the boys must leave on the run. , The Stooges are pest exterminators who drum up business by planting vermin in a ritzy mansion where a party is going on.  The boys are hired, but must dress as guests to work unobserved.  They disrupt the party and a wild pie fight ensues.  [Basically a remake of "Ants in the Pantry".  ] , The Stooges are would-be reporters, who are tricked into becoming stowaways by "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that Borscht has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , The Stooges apply for job as 'Yard Men' at Scotland Yard, thinking they'll become detectives, but instead wind up as gardeners.  When they accidentally see a memo about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The bad guys want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027000000 +0000" stop="20241027023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Invaders From Mars</sub-title>
    <desc>"A young boy learns that space aliens are taking over the minds of earthlings."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027023000 +0000" stop="20241027050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Crystal</sub-title>
    <desc>"On another planet in the distant past, a Gelfling embarks on a quest to find the missing shard of a magical crystal, and to restore order to his world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027050000 +0000" stop="20241027060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Horror In The Heights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A Hindu Rakshasa terrorizes a Jewish neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027060000 +0000" stop="20241027070000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Trevi Collection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch desires to control the world of high fashion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027070000 +0000" stop="20241027080000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Chopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bent on revenge, a headless motorcycle rider murders those who wronged him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027080000 +0000" stop="20241027090000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Primal Scream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Defrosted ancient cell samples discovered in the Arctic grow into savage prehistoric primates and go on a rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027090000 +0000" stop="20241027100000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The first based on a Native American legend, a Diablero shaman spirit murders for jewels to pay back his debt and be released from his Earthly bonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027100000 +0000" stop="20241027110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>36 Hours</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Walt race to find the landing device before astronauts perish in the re-entry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027110000 +0000" stop="20241027113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Distraction   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack spies on Kelly, trying to hear who'll she'll take to the dance, she sets up a prank to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027113000 +0000" stop="20241027120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Woman   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Trying to cheer Screech up so he'll complete their science project, Zack pretends to know a girl who is interested in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027120000 +0000" stop="20241027123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a freak accident, Screech can predict the future, an ability Zack uses to his advantage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027123000 +0000" stop="20241027130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Lisa Card   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Lisa splurges with her dad's credit card, she asks the Bayside gang to help get the money back before her dad discovers the shopping spree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027130000 +0000" stop="20241027133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Masquerade Ball   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack and Slater bet on who can kiss Tori first, and their best chance will come at a masquerade ball. Lisa has a secret admirer, Screech, but she thinks it's Zack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027133000 +0000" stop="20241027140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Weekend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang wins a mystery weekend at a mansion where they will all play a part in a murder mystery. The trouble begins when the game goes awry and Zack is left as the prime suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027140000 +0000" stop="20241027150000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie's Cartoon BOO-Nanza</title>
    <sub-title>House Of Svengoolie's Cartoon Boo-nanza</sub-title>
    <desc>"A collection of Halloween themed cartoons hosted by the The Sven Squad."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027150000 +0000" stop="20241027153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Fonsillectomy</sub-title>
    <desc>Fonzie has to have his tonsils removed and will miss a big Halloween party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027153000 +0000" stop="20241027160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Shirley's Operation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Learning that her appendix is about to burst but not wanting to lose her part in "Alice in Wonderland," Shirley hides while the rest of the play's actors try to find her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027160000 +0000" stop="20241027163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Farmer Takes A Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jeff Pruitt, a farmer from the hills, comes to Mayberry in search of a wife. He enlists Barney and Andy's help and ends up picking Thelma Lou!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027163000 +0000" stop="20241027170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Thinks Ricky Is Trying To Murder Her</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy is deeply engrossed in a brand-new whodunit, called "The Mockingbird Mystery," and is, understandably, a nail-biting wreck. Having become deeply paranoid that she is in for an imminent doom, Lucy begins to believe that Ricky is trying to murder her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027170000 +0000" stop="20241027173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While his class is reciting a poem about trees, Beaver remembers a tree that Ward had given him for his birthday when they lived at their old house. Wanting "his" tree back, Beaver and Larry go to Beaver's old home and promptly dig it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027173000 +0000" stop="20241027180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Comes To Dinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a surprise when June invites Miss Landers over for dinner and Larry convinces him that something bad might happen. This leads Beaver to become a nervous wreck as he tries to make sure his parents don't do anything to embarrass him. Meanwhile, Larry charges a quarter to anyone who wants to spy on Miss Landers eating dinner at the Cleavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027180000 +0000" stop="20241027183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jane Finds Elly A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny continues her search to get a man for Elly, though fears her mission might be harder with Elly having entered the cake-baking contest. Back at the mansion, Jethro becomes restless in Beverly Hills and decides to join his family in the hills, especially after hearing about the fair going on. Miss Jane comes along, being told by Drysdale to keep her watch on the family and not to let Elly get serious about a man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027183000 +0000" stop="20241027190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Another Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Maria comes to Beverly Hills, making Mrs. Drysdale very excited. But she wants to keep the countess away from the hillbillies. However, it's spring tonic time, and Granny passes it around the neighborhood, including at Countess Maria's house. She falls in love with the brew and visits the Clampetts. They become friends instantly. She starts falling for Jed, and has plans to marry her 6th husband, hoping it is an American.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027190000 +0000" stop="20241027193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A famous Hollywood producer crash-lands on the island. When he insults Ginger, the castaways stage a "Hamlet" musical play to restore her confidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027193000 +0000" stop="20241027200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A witch doctor makes voodoo dolls from the castaways' personal affects, which he has stolen from their huts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027200000 +0000" stop="20241027203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama Cries Uncle  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The sudden appearance of Carl's nomadic brother, Roy, excites everyone but Mama. Although she seems upset that Roy is popular with the rest of the family, she finally admits her affection for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027203000 +0000" stop="20241027210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Aunt Fran  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Aunt Fran is temporarily given the responsibility of writing an advice column in the local newspaper. Unfortunately, she doesn't have any good advice and comes to rely on Mama to supply material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027210000 +0000" stop="20241027220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Promoter / Judges / Family Plan / Forever Engaged / May The Best Man Win (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 1. A "Marriage-A-Thon" cruise has 25 engaged couples competing for prizes before a mass wedding."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027220000 +0000" stop="20241027223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Keeper Of The Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie joins a secret club that meets in Jubal Foster's barn. When Jubal burns his own barn down, he attempts to blame the group of boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027223000 +0000" stop="20241027230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Rich Correll- Horror/sci-fi Movie Props And Costumes</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rich Correll built a successful career as a comedy actor, director, and producer, but a lifelong passion for horror inspired him to collect some of the Hollywood’s most iconic horror, sci-fi, and fantasy props and costumes. With Rich at her side, Lisa tours Icons of Darkness, a museum where Rich displays hundreds of his favorite pieces for the public to enjoy, like the original raptor from Jurassic Park (1993) and the coveted, highly valuable original Xenomorph costume from Alien (1979). His collection celebrates movie history from the Universal Monster classics to the fun and futuristic hits like Back To The Future. Hollywood memorabilia appraiser and expert, Joe Moe, assigns the highest ever value in Collector’s Call history to Rich’s collection and brings a remnant of Rich’s childhood to offer in trade for an equally rare artifact from Jurassic Park."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027230000 +0000" stop="20241027233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241027233000 +0000" stop="20241028000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028000000 +0000" stop="20241028003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria's Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Gloria are having a discussion over who will take care of Joey, just in case there comes a time when both of them are unable to care for the little tyke before his 18th birthday. Mike has serious reservations over allowing in-laws Archie and Edith to get custody of Joey, particularly due to what he perceives as Archie's bad influences. Gloria is having a hard time convincing Mike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028003000 +0000" stop="20241028010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Edith Bunker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith saves a man's life and becomes the toast of the town,but Archie isn't happy standing in the shadow of her limelight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028010000 +0000" stop="20241028013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Secret Passion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith discovers Archie once had a brief encounter with an old high school friend she's invited to dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028013000 +0000" stop="20241028020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie enters Joey in a newspaper's beautiful baby contest, against the express wishes of Mike and Gloria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028020000 +0000" stop="20241028023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Alice Ghostley And Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Alice Ghostley and Jim Nabors. Originally aired on 09/23/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028023000 +0000" stop="20241028030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Diahann Carroll (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Diahann Carroll. Originally aired on 10/27/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028030000 +0000" stop="20241028033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Uhny Uftz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Did Rob see a UFO?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028033000 +0000" stop="20241028040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Long Night's Journey Into Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura tries to spend the night alone while her family is on a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028040000 +0000" stop="20241028043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is baby-sitting to pay for a phone but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028043000 +0000" stop="20241028050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What You Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A two-bit thug thinks he's found the key to a better life in an old sidewalk salesman who has the uncanny ability to tell people what they need the most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028050000 +0000" stop="20241028060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>An Unlocked Window  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Three nurses care for a patient in a creaky old manor where more than a few nurses have been killed in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028060000 +0000" stop="20241028070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Glass Tightrope</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Working as a stock clerk in a department store, Kimble witnesses his boss, Martin Rowland, accidentally kill a business associate in the parking lot after hours. When Kimble learns that a local vagrant found near the crime scene is the prime suspect, Kimb</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028070000 +0000" stop="20241028080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Code</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincente Bravo, dictator of Nueva Tierra, is planning an invasion against a neighboring democracy, San Cristobal. The United Peoples' Republic is sending Nikor Janos with a coded invasion plan to help Bravo and set him up as puppet dictator.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028080000 +0000" stop="20241028083000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The 7th Green</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Highway Patrol exposes a ruthless man who operates a professional hideout for criminals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028083000 +0000" stop="20241028090000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028090000 +0000" stop="20241028093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028093000 +0000" stop="20241028100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028100000 +0000" stop="20241028103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Radical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At roll call, Malloy and Reed are asked to look out for a suspected militant and, after spotting him, attempt to follow him to his stash of weapons. Malloy also is asked by a security guard to investigate a possible shakedown and smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028103000 +0000" stop="20241028110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed report to a robbery at a grocery store, where Malloy is required to engage in a high-speed pursuit with one of the suspects while Reed apprehends the other on foot. When Malloy is seriously injured in a rollover accident at a remote location and loses two-way radio communication, Reed and others from the department race against the clock to locate him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028110000 +0000" stop="20241028120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Quizzer's Scavenger Haunt Pt 1</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer sends Bill and Toony on a disguising Halloween scavenger hunt."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028120000 +0000" stop="20241028123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his fortune read by a machine and becomes convinced nothing but good luck is headed his way. However, he doesn't feel that way when Larry sets it up so that Beaver will have to fight a 5th grader, Sonny Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028123000 +0000" stop="20241028130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Makes A Loan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward loans Beaver 25 cents but gives him a dollar, expecting 75 cents as change. However, Larry manages to convince Beaver to loan him the 75 cents. When Larry doesn't pay him back when he said he was going to, a feud erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028130000 +0000" stop="20241028140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gambling Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Counterfeit casino chips and chronic gambling lead to murder, and Mason suspects one of his clients may be culpable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028140000 +0000" stop="20241028150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Other Woman  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend psychiatrist Lucas Forbes when he's arrested for killing the husband of one of his patients with whom he was reportedly having an affair. Matlock soon realizes that the patient in question has a host of deep-rooted psychiatric problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028150000 +0000" stop="20241028160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman Much Admired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie's old flame returns to Sparta to settle some business matters and see Bill. When she is murdered he travels to Gulfport and meets his daughter Lana for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028160000 +0000" stop="20241028170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Return - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to Walton's Mountain to write about the failing economy and lack of jobs</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028170000 +0000" stop="20241028180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young man kills a gunfighter, he becomes the victim of publicity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028180000 +0000" stop="20241028190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Samaritan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss introduces Wade Tyree to Abigail and her daughter, Bonnie, in the hopes that it will stop Wade's constant drinking. After Wade and Abigail get married, Wade goes back to his old ways. It's up to Hoss to bring the broken family back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028190000 +0000" stop="20241028193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vaqueros</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While Lucas and Mark are traveling across the Mexican desert they encounter a trio of Mexican bandits. They demand payment from Lucas for crossing "their" desert. Lucas refuses. In retaliation, the three slam Lucas in the throat with his rifle, strip him of all his possessions (including Mark), tie him to a tree and leave him to die of thirst and exposure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028193000 +0000" stop="20241028200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>First Wages</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to find out why Mark has taken a job as a stableboy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028200000 +0000" stop="20241028210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess Of A Lost Tribe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ordered by Major Adams to guide three passengers to a campsite up a haunted mountain, Flint does so but with caution: rumors that an escaped group of Aztecs now live there, almost 400 years after Cortez wiped them all out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028210000 +0000" stop="20241028220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Virus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A sick lady with a monkey provides the key to a mysterious, highly contagious and deadly virus that strikes both Dr. Brackett and John. Meanwhile, the firemen rescue a boy from a treehouse and a man from a scaffold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028220000 +0000" stop="20241028223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028223000 +0000" stop="20241028230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028230000 +0000" stop="20241028233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241028233000 +0000" stop="20241029000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029000000 +0000" stop="20241029003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bailey's Bad Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich kid Ronald Bailey is jailed when he blatantly defies the law. As Bailey waits for his influential father to bail him out, Andy teaches him the lesson of self-responsibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029003000 +0000" stop="20241029010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manicurist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful manicurist from the city comes to Floyd's to set up shop. She makes all the wives in town extremely nervous as she manicures their husbands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029010000 +0000" stop="20241029013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Becomes A Movie Mogul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale buys a movie studio, Mammoth Pictures, for Jed, and the Clampetts decide to go check out their new property. At first they can’t get in, but they finally succeed. They meet Lawrence Chaplin, the head of Mammoth Pictures, who refers to Jed as a Zucker and a Roach, and Jed admires him for saying it to his face.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029013000 +0000" stop="20241029020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Saucer Season</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Once Eb's wild story about meeting space aliens hits the press, tourists descend on the Douglas farm to meet the new celebrity. Oliver's more concerned about the crowd trampling his crops, but the Air Force takes his claim seriously...at first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029020000 +0000" stop="20241029023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Crittendon Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon disrupts Hogan's plan to blow up a tunnel and stop a convoy of rocket fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029023000 +0000" stop="20241029030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Some Of Their Planes Are Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Germans plan to send their men into England via captured planes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029030000 +0000" stop="20241029033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Diahann Carroll (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Tim Conway and Diahann Carroll. Originally aired on 10/27/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029033000 +0000" stop="20241029043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fugitive Fraulein</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della travel behind the Iron Curtain and get involved in a murder case, which ends up being tried in an East German court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029043500 +0000" stop="20241029050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Four Of Us Are Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who can change his face to resemble others gets into hot water with gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029050500 +0000" stop="20241029060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Final Performance  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While a past vaudevillian plans to hit the comeback trail, his young fiancée seeks to make her escape with the help of a man passing through town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029060500 +0000" stop="20241029070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Dark So Early, Dark So Long</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix sets out to clear an old school friend of murder. The problem is that she, being an alcoholic, can't remember what she was doing when the murder occurred.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029070500 +0000" stop="20241029080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stone Seahorse</sub-title>
    <desc>A smuggler is attacked by mobsters interested in learning where he has hidden his booty. He escapes in Raymond Durstin's gallery. He turns to Cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029080500 +0000" stop="20241029090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Valentine, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer is sending valentines to his victims before killing them - and Betty may be the next target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029090000 +0000" stop="20241029093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Foster Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews puts out an APB to catch an armed fugitive: a 10-year-old male.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029093000 +0000" stop="20241029100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029100000 +0000" stop="20241029103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an environmentalist known as "The Ferret" who has been posing as an employee to infiltrate and sabotage industrial complexes he feels are creating too much pollution. In the meantime, they respond to a woman who is nearly comatose and ultimately gives birth to a stillborn baby. They then investigate the witchdoctor who has been convincing her and other women that eating clay will ensure a successful pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029103000 +0000" stop="20241029110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Truant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After apprehending a couple of juvenile delinquents who are ransacking a house, Reed is inspired to submit an idea on how to deal with truants, which ultimately gets implemented on a trial basis by the captain, but draws the ire of Officer Wells. Back on patrol, they apprehend a couple of high-level drug dealers who run into bad luck, and nearly get run over by two men using stolen automobile parts to build a high-powered go cart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029110000 +0000" stop="20241029120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Quizzer's Scavenger Haunt Pt 2</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer’s scavenger hunt continues with Bill and Toony working hard for tasty rewards."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029120000 +0000" stop="20241029123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Magician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a common magic trick but is disappointed by everyone's "that's nice" reaction. He gets a totally different reaction out of Bengie, however, when Larry and Beaver convince him that Beaver has been turned into a rock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029123000 +0000" stop="20241029130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>June's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June's birthday has Wally and Beaver fighting over what to buy with the $5 dollars that Ward gave them. Wally buys her a wallet while Beaver buys an ugly blouse that June kindly thanks him for, but she has a hard time bringing herself to wear it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029130000 +0000" stop="20241029140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Fraud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Richard Vanaman's shot at a big promotion is sabotaged when he is framed for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029140000 +0000" stop="20241029150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The P.i.  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A private investigator's daughter shoots some photos that get the wrong man accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029150000 +0000" stop="20241029160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Baby For Sale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Bubba's cousin adopts a baby her husband is blackmailed by the child's real parents - they want him to help them steal the payroll where he works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029160000 +0000" stop="20241029170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Strange things are occurring at the Walton home. The family uses a Ouija board to ask questions about the happenings</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029170000 +0000" stop="20241029180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Scavengers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In order for a black man to save his life he must say that indians held up a wagon train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029180000 +0000" stop="20241029190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Jury</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss faces scorn and accusations of bribery when he refuses to vote with his fellow jurors to convict a man for murder based solely on the testimony of the victim's brother, who witnessed the act on a dark night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029190000 +0000" stop="20241029193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sheer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and Milly are held prisoner in her general store when two gunmen attempt a daring robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029193000 +0000" stop="20241029200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stand-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two prison wagon drivers stop at the McCain ranch looking for whiskey. Lucas turns them down because they are escorting Rudy Croft, a murderer who is to be hanged in Yuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029200000 +0000" stop="20241029210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cathy Eckhart Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>One murder begets a second murder while a treacherous journey awaits the wagon train. An unknown scout and Kiowa indians threaten the pass. Now there may be a renegade and murderer in their midst, a situation Adams must resolve before continuing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029210000 +0000" stop="20241029220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Peace Pipe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A drunk driver rams a parked car, trapping a child inside. Chet pesters John about his Native American heritage. A kid gets his finger stuck in a gumball machine. A woman's new girdle causes breathing difficulties. A worker's error leads to fuel being mixed with the water supply, causing explosive results. A sniper makes a scaffold rescue dangerous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029220000 +0000" stop="20241029223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029223000 +0000" stop="20241029230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029230000 +0000" stop="20241029233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241029233000 +0000" stop="20241030000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030000000 +0000" stop="20241030003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Jinx</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After a series of mishaps, Henry Bennett gets a reputation in town as a jinx. The more Andy tries to dispel the rumor the deeper the hole gets, until Henry decides it would be best if he left town altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030003000 +0000" stop="20241030010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jailbreak</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>State police come to town in search of payroll robbers. They want Andy and Barney to stay out of the way, but end up needing them more than they thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030010000 +0000" stop="20241030013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Mammoth Pictures is losing money, Drysdale decides to tear down the studio and turn it into Clampett City. The Clampetts are excited about getting a town and streets named after them, and when they go to explore their town, they come to a Western set, which they fall in love with.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030013000 +0000" stop="20241030020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Engagement Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb is sent packing when Darlene's dad learns he proposed to is daughter with a watch fob instead of a ring. Lisa gives Eb the $2000 ring Oliver used to get engaged to her and everyone is happy--until the father has the ring appraised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030020000 +0000" stop="20241030023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>D-day At Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan pulls a hoax to get a general to believe Klink is replacing him as chief of staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030023000 +0000" stop="20241030030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030030000 +0000" stop="20241030033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bing Crosby And Paul Lynde</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bing Crosby and Paul Lynde. Originally aired on 11/03/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030033000 +0000" stop="20241030043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baffling Bug</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The suspected theft of industrial secrets leads to an investigation by Drake, spying and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030043500 +0000" stop="20241030050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Third From The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>With all-out nuclear war about to ignite, a scientist and his pilot friend plot to escape on an experimental spaceship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030050500 +0000" stop="20241030060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Thanatos Palace Hotel  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Having ineffectively attempted suicide, Robert Manners checks in at the Thanatos Palace Hotel, which caters solely to people who desire to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030060500 +0000" stop="20241030070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cold Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A young woman is kidnapped, drugged and interrogated, her father an ex-spy for the Soviets during the Cold War. A defector now in America, the man hires Mannix to find his daughter in this case of international espionage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030070500 +0000" stop="20241030080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Fall Guy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon has been hired when a VP of a petroleum company is charged with misappropriation of funds and faces dismissal and prison time."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030080500 +0000" stop="20241030090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Leap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A man attempting suicide is really a diversion for a jewelry heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030090000 +0000" stop="20241030093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Two girls stage a series of armed robberies using an ingenious trick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030093000 +0000" stop="20241030100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030100000 +0000" stop="20241030103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are ambushed by two men who want to silence the prisoner they are transporting from Malibu to Los Angeles. Their problems are compounded by the lack of radio communication in Malibu Canyon, which ultimately results in Reed being taken hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030103000 +0000" stop="20241030110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed brainstorm what to get Sgt. MacDonald for his anniversary, subdue an understandably belligerent wrestler in a bar and get followed by a man with a recent streak of bad luck. Afterward, they investigate an unethical used car salesman and liquor store robbery and also thwart an attempted camper theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030110000 +0000" stop="20241030120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Quizzer's Scavenger Haunt Pt 3</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer's scavenger hunt takes a chilling turn when Bill and Toony explore a haunted historical house, where spooky surprises await around every corner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030120000 +0000" stop="20241030123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tire Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants to raise chinchillas and begins building a cage in the garage. However, when Beaver changes his mind, Ward tries his best to get Wally and Beaver to clean up the mess. Things get worse when Ward unknowingly runs over some of the wood and nails left laying around with the car, causing the boys to try to patch a flat tire before Ward finds out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030123000 +0000" stop="20241030130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry Hides Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver is staying at the Mondellos, Larry sneaks a peak at his sister's diary and his mother discovers him and yells at him right in front of Beaver. This prompts Larry to run away to Beaver's house, where Beaver secretly hides him in his bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030130000 +0000" stop="20241030140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bartered Bikini</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally Dunbar seeks Mason's help in securing ownership of his new summer line of swimwear, but the sketches are stolen and, worse yet, chief designer Rick Stassi is murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030140000 +0000" stop="20241030150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Psychic  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a psychic claiming to have had a premonition of a murder before it took place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030150000 +0000" stop="20241030160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Obsession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A flirtatious schoolteacher is stalked by a madman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030160000 +0000" stop="20241030170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Walker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An unknown person is walking around Walton's Mountain at nights and causing worry</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030170000 +0000" stop="20241030180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A family is held hostage so they can't testify at the trial of a killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030180000 +0000" stop="20241030190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Ben Cartwright's old war buddies, who claims to be a business tycoon developing a new territory, woos a wealthy Virginia City widow and jeopardizes a Ponderosa land deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030190000 +0000" stop="20241030193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark goes to work for Will Temple, a badly scarred and very mysterious rancher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030193000 +0000" stop="20241030200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Corey Hazlett insists he's innocent of murder, despite Lucas's eyewitness testimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030200000 +0000" stop="20241030210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bleymier Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Heed the signs! Or so says Samuel Bleymier. When the rain won't stop, a splintered group of the wagon train has to travel through a Sioux indian burial ground. That may have consequences all its own but what of the signs?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030210000 +0000" stop="20241030220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Saddled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dixie injures her toe. John decides he can make a lot of money by riding in rodeos. The squad goes to a hole-in-the-wall restaurant when a soda bottle explodes in a girl's face; later, they return for a gas explosion. After falling from a tree, a young boy lapses into a coma. The firemen rescue several children and a nun from a bus crash.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030220000 +0000" stop="20241030223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030223000 +0000" stop="20241030230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030230000 +0000" stop="20241030233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241030233000 +0000" stop="20241031000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031000000 +0000" stop="20241031003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Medal For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his heart set on winning a medal in a foot race at the town picnic. When he loses, he exhibits poor sportmanship. Andy teaches him a lesson about being a good sport.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031003000 +0000" stop="20241031010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031010000 +0000" stop="20241031013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Clampett Enterprises</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale evicts Mr. Show Business, the Boy Genius of Hollywood, Jethro, and his talent agency, from the fifth floor of the bank building and, so he can collect his $5,000-a-month rent, rents it to Jed, who, along with Granny, turns it into a combination wood shop/dentist office/hospital/barber shop/and pet shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031013000 +0000" stop="20241031020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Kimball Gets Fired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is distraught when her beloved "Hankie" Kimball is fired as the county agricultural agent. His replacement is so rude and insulting that even Oliver is plotting to get Kimball rehired. His scheme is to scare the new guy away by fixing him up with Ralph.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031020000 +0000" stop="20241031023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Funny Thing Happened On The Way To London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winston Chuchill's right-hand man, Group Captain "Robbie" Roberts, is shot down, captured and brought to Stalag 13. The Luftwaffe scheme to assassinate Churchill by keeping Roberts in the cooler while an impostor escapes to England to carry out the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031023000 +0000" stop="20241031030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Casanova Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Burkhalter plans to get Klink to marry his sister, while a Gestapo plant has infiltrated the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031030000 +0000" stop="20241031033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bernadette Peters And Cass Elliot</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bernadette Peters and Cass Elliot. Originally aired on 11/10/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031033000 +0000" stop="20241031043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Difficult Detour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Contactor Pete Mallory is charged with the murder of a vacation resort developer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031043500 +0000" stop="20241031050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>I Shot An Arrow Into The Air</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Three astronauts crash-land on what they believe to be an asteroid and have limited water supplies to sustain them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031050500 +0000" stop="20241031053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In 4-d</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband has a vague memory of helping a woman get rid of a corpse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031053500 +0000" stop="20241031060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a terrible accident leaves a man completely paralyzed, people who encounter him think he is dead, though he is very much alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031060500 +0000" stop="20241031070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Step In Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is told a murder of a woman he recently witnessed happened a year before. The sheriff insists that maybe the gumshoe is suffering hallucinations. Joe is befuddled until the victim's sister hires him to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031070500 +0000" stop="20241031080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Melted Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates when an heiress finds an ax buried into the head of a snowman outside of her home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031080500 +0000" stop="20241031090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Inside Man, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An aspiring robber is declared a hero for facing his double-crossing partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241031090000 +0000" stop="20241031093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Tear Gas Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Three gunmen slug a Highway Patrol officer and take a housewife hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
