<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004160000 +0000" stop="20251004170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Image Of Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria learns that the leader of a gang of hired guns, hired to protect ranches against another gang of marauders, is an old flame. She becomes increasingly disturbed by the lawlessness of his men and challenges him to live up to the ideals he once had.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004170000 +0000" stop="20251004180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Louis Pheeters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The town drunk witnesses a man killing his wife's alleged lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004180000 +0000" stop="20251004190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hop Sing falls in love with a young woman, but his heart is broken when a judge confirms that the law prohibits interracial marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004190000 +0000" stop="20251004193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark McCain is eager to help lawman Jay Jefferson, who has arrived in North Fork intent on killing an outlaw for the reward, whether he is the right man or not.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004193000 +0000" stop="20251004200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When escaped convicts hold up the general store in North Fork and take Marshal Torrance hostage, Lucas comes to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004200000 +0000" stop="20251004210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Corporal Dasovik</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A corporal who shuns responsibility seeks Favor's help after he's put in command of a squad escorting indian prisoners to a reservation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004210000 +0000" stop="20251004213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Trying to locate the thieves who stole a jade chess set, Paladin ends up in a small Montana town where he becomes involved in a romance with a landlady's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004213000 +0000" stop="20251004220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Mental Lapse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh plays detective when he signs on to help an amnesiac discover his identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251004220000 +0000" stop="20251005000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Spook Louder, Idle Roomers, A Bird In The Head, Ghost Talks, Three Pests In A Mess, If A Body Meets A Body</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are left in charge of a spooky mansion, when an eccentric inventor goes to Washington with a death ray. , The Stooges are working as bellboys in a large hotel when a side show promoter shows up with 'Lupe', a wild wolfman who promptly escapes.  The Stooges try to capture the wolfman by playing music to calm him, but music makes the wolfman go berserk and soon the Stooges are the ones trying to run away.  The boys end up caught in an elevator with the wolfman who shoots them into the sky. , When Moe reads that Curly's rich uncle has died, and has left his estate to Curly, the boys go there to collect. They find that the uncle was murdered and his body and will are missing., The maniacal masters of madcap are back, digitally remastered, repackaged and hilarious as ever. , The Stooges are movers for an express company and on a rainy night are sent to move some junk, including a suit of armor, from a spooky old house.  The armor is haunted by the ghost of Peeping Tom, who has no intention of leaving.  The ghost foils the Stooges attempts to take the armor, until Lady Godiva shows up and the two ride off together. , The Stooges are three inventors trying to a get a patent on their preposterous fly catching invention.  When they learn they'll have to catch 100,000 flies to earn enough to get a patent, some crooks overhear and think the boys are the $100,000 sweepstakes winners.  When the crooks give chase, the Stooges hide in a sporting goods store where Curly shoots a dummy, which they mistake for a real person.  The boys decide to bury the "body" in a pet cemetery, but the cemetery owner arrives from a costume party with his partners, all dressed as spooks, and they proceed to scare the devil out of the Stooges. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005000000 +0000" stop="20251005023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost And Mr. Chicken</sub-title>
    <desc>"A timid typesetter who longs to be a reporter hopes to land a big story by spending a night in a haunted house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005023000 +0000" stop="20251005050000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>What Ever Happened To Baby Jane?</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former child star torments her paraplegic sister in their decaying Hollywood mansion."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005050000 +0000" stop="20251005060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Sky Pirate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinsons meet a space traveler who turns out to be an Earth man, Alonzo P. Tucker, who was abducted from Punxsutawney, Pennsylvania, by aliens in 1876.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005060000 +0000" stop="20251005070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Terrible Toys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Aliens aboard a UFO rig six windup toys in an effort to destroy the Seaview.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005070000 +0000" stop="20251005080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Clones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Two giant scientists capture Barry, Valerie, Fitzhugh, and Dan, and use them in a cloning experiment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005080000 +0000" stop="20251005090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Pirates Of Deadman's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1805, the travelers try to escape from a pirate's Barbary Coast lair before it is shelled by U.S. warships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005090000 +0000" stop="20251005100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Task Force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent and the believers meet with a publishing magnate</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005100000 +0000" stop="20251005110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Air Hero</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hot air balloonist, Andre,sets down near Adam's place. After meeting and talking with him,Andre says his flight is a test. One day,an option to The Pony Express mail system. Will all help with repairs or is air mail too crazy an idea?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005110000 +0000" stop="20251005113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chase By Copter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim take to the air in a helicopter for two thrilling hunts over Canada…one in search of a giant moose and then in the mountains of western Canada for a mountain goat roundup."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005113000 +0000" stop="20251005120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lion Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Probably the greatest of the great cats is the king of beasts … the African lion.  Roaming the open savannas, its roar is a threat to all who live within its range.  Its amazing physical abilities make it the most feared hunter on the African continent."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005120000 +0000" stop="20251005123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Unwanted Cougar</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the cougar’s northernmost range, the Rocky Mountains of British Columbia, a mother cougar roams with her yearling cub, until the new litter comes along.  Then she must savagely chase the year old cub away."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005123000 +0000" stop="20251005130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Year Of The Otter</sub-title>
    <desc>"In a small Wisconsin lake, two otters are born.  We follow the appealing animals through the first year of their lives."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005130000 +0000" stop="20251005133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Danger: Wild Animals</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim demonstrate how to handle dangerous animals of the zoo and the wild."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005133000 +0000" stop="20251005140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Flight</sub-title>
    <desc>"An analysis of the ‘miracle of flight’ from the soaring condors of the Andes to the backward-flying fairy terns of Midway."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005140000 +0000" stop="20251005143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Dropout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike has been designing a new home for Don Drysdale, who stops by the house to look at the plans. After Drysdale gives Greg baseball tips, he considers dropping out of high school to become a professional ball player.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005143000 +0000" stop="20251005150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Babysitters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>With Alice away at Sam's, and Cindy developing the sniffles, Mike and Carol are ready to cancel their night out. Greg and Marcia argue that they are responsible and old enough to look after their siblings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005150000 +0000" stop="20251005153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Fonzie Gets Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Fonzie is accidentally shot during a weekend trip to Potsie's uncle's cabin, Fonzie, Chachi and Roger each describe their versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005153000 +0000" stop="20251005160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Spy In My Beer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After no one believes Laverne saw an industrial spy in the brewery, she and Shirley embark on a late-night stakeout to catch the spy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005160000 +0000" stop="20251005163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darling Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Darlings come to Mayberry looking for a boy whom they could engage to Charlene's new baby. Opie becomes the prime target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005163000 +0000" stop="20251005170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ricardos give the Mertzes a television set for their anniversary, but Ricky's zealous tuning causes it to blow up. Fred retaliates by breaking the Ricardos' set (by kicking it!) The foursome end up in court, where they manage to destroy the judge's TV, too!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005170000 +0000" stop="20251005173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Mustache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's on-again off-again girlfriend, Julie Foster, seems to have thrown him over for a new guy in school who just happens to have a mustache. Wally's ego is bruised when Eddie tells him that Julie thinks he's naive and immature. This is the last straw and Wally decides to grow a mustache, much to the dismay of his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005173000 +0000" stop="20251005180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Buys A Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend has a car for sale and Wally is interested; however, Ward and June are, as usual, hesitant about the whole thing. Ward decides to give in to Wally and allow him to buy the used car, with the condition that he inspect it first. Ward quickly finds problems with the car and he helps Wally look elsewhere giving Wally tips on the process of used car shopping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005180000 +0000" stop="20251005183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Meet Mrs. Drysdale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mr. Drysdale describes Mrs. Drysdale as being a hypochondriac, the Clampetts assume she must be a drunk. With his wife coming home, Drysdale and Jane try to prevent her from meeting the family before they can shape the hillbillies up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005183000 +0000" stop="20251005190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Flying Saucer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts see part of the Drysales' new advertising gimmick: Martians and a flying saucer. Drysdale plans to have them fly over the Rose Bowl, throwing out Drysdale Dollars. Jethro thinks they have come for him, since he sees himself as the giant brain of the world. The Clampetts take the Martians in for food, though Granny is not happy about their manners. She ends up blowing up their space ship, a giant balloon, in the Drysdales’ back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005190000 +0000" stop="20251005193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Ship Ahoax</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways begin to suffer from "island madness" due to the isolation. The Professor attempts to come up with a plan to lift everyone's spirits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005193000 +0000" stop="20251005200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Feed The Kitty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A cage containing a lion washes ashore in the lagoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005200000 +0000" stop="20251005203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Psychic Pheno-mama  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The Harpers hire a psychic whose predictions all come true. That is, until Mama discovers that she is a fraud and plots revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005203000 +0000" stop="20251005210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Take My Mama, Please!  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama thinks she can do better than the comedian at the local dinner theater, she signs up for the open microphone night. And when the church congregation learns of it, she is forced to get serious about coming up with an act.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005210000 +0000" stop="20251005220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Captains Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubing hears about a former love; a man wants to leave his companion aboard; a man claims he was attacked.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005220000 +0000" stop="20251005223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005223000 +0000" stop="20251005230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Peter Morcey- Star Wars Toys</sub-title>
    <desc>"There are all kinds of Star Wars collectors. Peter Morcey is the kind of guy who collects Star Wars toys, lots of them, and displays them in a meticulous fashion that shows off all his complete toy lines, toy lines from other countries, and toys that no one else has. Today, he'll show Lisa some of his most prized possessions like the one-of-a-kind ,multi-colored C3P0  figures, a vinyl caped Jawa, and a coveted Italian card back that doesn't even have the toy attached. Our expert, John Ragusa, Peter's pal, and a Star Wars fan and collector himself will have the honors of appraising this magnificent collection and then attempting to make a swap with Peter. John's brought a hard-to-get collectible he knows Peter wants, but may be reaching for another galaxy  with his trade request."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005230000 +0000" stop="20251005233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bless You, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye can't stop a sneezing fit that has no apparent cause, psychiatrist Sidney Freedman digs into the surgeon's past for a clue to this unusual malady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251005233000 +0000" stop="20251006000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is overcome by the devotion of a terminally ill G.I., who has leukemia, for his critically wounded buddy, but he has trouble coming to terms with the fact that he can't cure the man. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is worried about the impending visit of a Cardinal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006000000 +0000" stop="20251006003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Birth Of The Baby (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>It appears that Gloria may have her first baby in an Italian restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006003000 +0000" stop="20251006010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Birth Of The Baby (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith and Archie cause havoc at the hospital when Gloria is about to have her baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006010000 +0000" stop="20251006013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>New Year's Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike continues to make decisions without consulting Gloria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006013000 +0000" stop="20251006020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie, The Babysitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike &amp; Gloria get one of Mike's students to babysit Joey. Archie feels that the babysitters are too radical and takes care of babysitting himself along with his poker foursome.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006020000 +0000" stop="20251006023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ken Berry And Totie Fields</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Ken Berry and Totie Fields. Originally aired on 02/15/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006023000 +0000" stop="20251006030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll, Tim Conway, And Karen Wyman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll, Tim Conway, and Karen Wyman. Originally aired on 03/01/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006030000 +0000" stop="20251006033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jealousy!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura suspects the worst when Rob has to work late with a glamorous movie star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006033000 +0000" stop="20251006040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>To Tell Or Not To Tell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone wants Laura to dance on "The Alan Brady Show" -- everyone, except Rob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006040000 +0000" stop="20251006043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Deciding Vote</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is busy buying Alice a vacuum while Norton is the deciding vote in the Raccoon election for convention manager.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006043000 +0000" stop="20251006050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>In Praise Of Pip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An alcoholic bookie regrets that he wasn't a better father to his son, Pip, critically wounded in South Vietnam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006050000 +0000" stop="20251006053000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Pearl Necklace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man convinces his girlfriend to accept the marriage proposal from an old, sick and very rich man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006053000 +0000" stop="20251006060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>You Can't Trust A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Guilt and fear plague a woman when her husband returns from prison after serving time for a crime she committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006060000 +0000" stop="20251006070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Armand Anderssarian is an illegal arms dealer who is about to complete a multi-million dollar deal selling arms to guerrilla groups around the world—and it's up to the IMF to stop him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006070000 +0000" stop="20251006080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Wings Of An Angel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble is riding on a bus when the police stop it, not to arrest Kimble, but to capture an escaped convict who takes a woman hostage. Kimble disarms the man, but gets stabbed during the struggle while the convict is shot dead. Not knowing his true identit</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006080000 +0000" stop="20251006090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Forbidden City</sub-title>
    <desc>"Private investigator Harry Orwell investigates the death of a friend and finds himself surrounded by the mysterious justice of the Orient."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006090000 +0000" stop="20251006093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-05</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Cases: an abandoned baby; a teenager on drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006093000 +0000" stop="20251006100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-10</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday grapples with the Uncle Tom syndrome in selling ethnic groups on police careers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006100000 +0000" stop="20251006103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 173 -- Shoplift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed track down a young shoplifter who escapes custody and hides at the lair of an eccentric spiritualist whom she worships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006103000 +0000" stop="20251006110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 174 -- Loan Sharks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating the severe beating of a factory worker, Reed and Malloy uncover an extensive loansharking operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006110000 +0000" stop="20251006120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toony's Really Really Late Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony hosts his own late-night talk show, as sidekick Bill fills him on the history of the format."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006120000 +0000" stop="20251006123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Parking Attendants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The social event of the season, according to Fred Rutherford, is a big party that a wealthy family is throwing and he rubs it in due to the fact that June and Ward didn't get an invitation. However, Wally and Eddie will be there after they get jobs parking the guest's cars. However, trouble ensues when Eddie parks Fred's car in a no parking spot and the car gets towed away by the city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006123000 +0000" stop="20251006130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>More Blessed To Give</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert go to a carnival and Beaver surprisingly wins a fourteen caret gold locket in one of the carnival games. Beaver thinks about giving it to June but, thanks to Gilbert, decides to give it to a girl whom he has a crush on. However, soon it becomes apparent that this was a mistake when the girl's parents discover Beaver's gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006130000 +0000" stop="20251006140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Purple Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An art collector, Rufus Varner, is told by a reputable art critic that one of his most prized paintings, "The Purple Woman," is a forgery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006140000 +0000" stop="20251006150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Fighter  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When fighter Billy Leon is accused of murdering the reporter who made public his alleged steroid use, Matlock agrees to take the seemingly open-and-shut case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006150000 +0000" stop="20251006160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>King's Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The F.B.I. tries to talk an ex-boxer into testifying against a mobster he once worked for, but the fighter sees the situation as an opportunity for blackmail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006160000 +0000" stop="20251006170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ike has a heart attack and is hospitalized</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006170000 +0000" stop="20251006180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Renegades</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Quint tries to convince an Army officer that white renegades are responsible for starting the latest Indian uprising.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006180000 +0000" stop="20251006190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Second Sight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When Jamie goes missing, the Cartwrights enlist the help of a reluctant clairvoyant to locate the youngster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006190000 +0000" stop="20251006193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark manages to capture a hawk, but then falls into danger from a rattlesnake. When a stranger comes to his rescue, the grateful Mark invites the man home, unaware that he is on the run from the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006193000 +0000" stop="20251006200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Three-legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rambunctious teenager wrecks a schoolroom, Lucas McCain, as a member of the North Fork school board, asks the boy's reluctant uncle to pay for the damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006200000 +0000" stop="20251006210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bruce Saybrook Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"Lord Bruce Saybrook, London millionaire, takes his brother, wife and employee out west on a hunting trip hoping to repair his relationships. They run into hostile Indians. During the ensuing battle, everyone's the true character comes out."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006210000 +0000" stop="20251006220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>All Night Long</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Gage tries to create his own television game show. An elderly musician experiences heart trouble. When a car runs a stop sign, three injuries result. A tightrope walker gets stuck between two buildings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006220000 +0000" stop="20251006223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Foresight Saga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is given a gift of fresh-grown vegetables by a grateful Korean; and Potter questions the veracity of an upbeat letter from Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006223000 +0000" stop="20251006230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Life You Save</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles is nearly felled by a sniper's bullet, he develops a philosophical obsession with death. Meanwhile, the officers have all been assigned new responsibilities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006230000 +0000" stop="20251006233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251006233000 +0000" stop="20251007000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007000000 +0000" stop="20251007003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007003000 +0000" stop="20251007010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007010000 +0000" stop="20251007013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Drysdale's Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny demands to see her money in cash, and Drysdale tries to talk her out of it. He fails and upsets the Clampetts by accidentally throwing magazines at them, which were really aimed at his wife and her dog. He tries to make things better by showing Granny what a million dollars looks like to turn her off from the idea, but ends up throwing more stuff at her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007013000 +0000" stop="20251007020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Joins The Marines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing Gomer's stories about how nice Sgt. Carter is, Opie Taylor runs away from Mayberry to join Gomer in the Marines. Ron Howard guest stars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007020000 +0000" stop="20251007023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The General Swap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan captures a German general to trade for an American general who dislikes Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007023000 +0000" stop="20251007030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007030000 +0000" stop="20251007033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Chita Rivera And Bob Newhart (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Chita Rivera and Bob Newhart. Originally aired on 02/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007033000 +0000" stop="20251007043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ominous Outcast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a notorious bank robber's son returns to his hometown it seems as though everyone is interested in missing loot supposedly hidden by the man's father. This leads to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007043500 +0000" stop="20251007050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Steel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxing robot "Battling Maxo" breaks down before a match, forcing its manager to take its place in the ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007050500 +0000" stop="20251007053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Gloating Place</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Susan Harper craves attention so desperately that she makes up a story about being attacked by a man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007053500 +0000" stop="20251007060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Self Defense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Bravery is not a man's only motivation when he picks up a weapon and goes after a liquor store robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007060500 +0000" stop="20251007070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to help a girl who witnessed her father's murder and was driven over the edge mentally by the event.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007070500 +0000" stop="20251007080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Died Twice</sub-title>
    <desc>"With the help of his former police partner, Frank is asked by his former captain to reopen a case of a corrupt cop who has reappeared after being declared dead years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007080500 +0000" stop="20251007090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Without A Name</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a cruise, Betty falls for a man who's being targeted by South American street police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007090000 +0000" stop="20251007093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Management Services - Dr-11</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Luther King's assassination sends Friday and the Emergency Control Center into action.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007093000 +0000" stop="20251007100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007100000 +0000" stop="20251007103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 35 -- Easy, Bare Rider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate the mysterious source behind a boy's suspicious spending spree, wield a blanket instead of gun during a disrobed driver's DUI arrest and bust up a car parts theft ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007103000 +0000" stop="20251007110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 95 -- Purse Snatcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy have to think outside the box to capture an intelligent yet neglected teenage purse snatcher. Their efforts to talk sense into him before he commits a much more serious crime prove to be futile.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007110000 +0000" stop="20251007120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Bison Bill's Wild West Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Bill tries to unleash his inner cowboy, Toony insteads hires a real-life rodeo clown to show him the ropes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007120000 +0000" stop="20251007123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Good Deed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver seems to be on a selfish streak after backing out of a babysitting and later not wanting to do a simple favor for Wally. Ward gives Beaver a stern lecture and he soon takes Ward's advice when a tramp comes to the door wanting some kindness. However, the tramp quickly takes advantage and helps himself to more than a glass of water.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007123000 +0000" stop="20251007130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Credit Card</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie brags about getting a credit card to his high school friends. When Wally's battery dies on his car, Eddie comes to the rescue by getting him a brand new battery. Everything is fine until Mr. Haskell finds out that Eddie charged it on their charge account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007130000 +0000" stop="20251007140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fancy Figures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Ellis is sent to jail for stealing the sum of $300,000. Ellis is later exonerated thanks to evidence discovered by his wife and the real thief, Charles Brewster, is arrested for the theft. Brewster manages to get out of jail on bail but later turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007140000 +0000" stop="20251007150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Critic  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a theatre critic is murdered after panning a play, Matlock is hired to defend the suspected murderer, Sam Spelvin, the play's writer as well as one of Matlock's childhood friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007150000 +0000" stop="20251007160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Epitaph For A Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A longtime friend of the Chief makes threats against a doctor he believes is responsible for his wife's death .When the doctor is killed he becomes the prime suspect. But Gillespie doubts his guilt - even after he confesses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007160000 +0000" stop="20251007170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ashley Longworth returns to Emily Baldwin</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007170000 +0000" stop="20251007180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Cotter's Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt attempts to civilize a teenage mountain girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007180000 +0000" stop="20251007190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Saddle Stiff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben is challenged by a former employee to get himself hired elsewhere as a ranch hand, thus proving that his aging body can handle the intense physical labor of the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007190000 +0000" stop="20251007193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The McCains try to be tolerant of their embittered neighbor, Abel MacDonald, who tells Lucas to keep off his land and won't allow his son to become friends with Mark. However, McCain decides he's gone too far when he won't allow his injured boy to get medical treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007193000 +0000" stop="20251007200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfounded rumor causes North Fork's outspoken feminist schoolteacher to be attacked by a mob of angry townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007200000 +0000" stop="20251007210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lizabeth Ann Calhoun Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Lizabeth Ann Calhoun meets the wagon train staff as they stop for supplies. She asks permission to join the train so she can avoid the advances of a young man she claims is in love with her, however his real motives may be very different."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007210000 +0000" stop="20251007220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Most Deadly Passage (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Roy and Johnny are sent to Seattle to study the techniques used there. A skydiver jumps off the Space Needle, a worker is trapped at the top of the Kingdome, and a fuel pumper loads a ferry with gasoline instead of diesel fuel, which sets the ferry on fire in the middle of the Elliot Bay."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007220000 +0000" stop="20251007223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Identity Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy counsels a GI who is plagued by guilt because he has swapped tags with a dead colleague. Meanwhile, B.J. and Charles consider ways of keeping a soldier-salesman quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007223000 +0000" stop="20251007230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rumor At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The latest scuttlebutt affects everyone's behavior when a visiting Army rep is rumored to be recruiting for a new M*A*S*H unit. The gang fears that the 4077th will be split up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007230000 +0000" stop="20251007233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em Hell, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes a heartfelt letter to President Harry Truman to protest at the continued fighting in Korea. Meanwhile, Colonel Ditka has promised a much-needed water heater if the 4077th beautifies the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251007233000 +0000" stop="20251008000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Wheelers And Dealers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>On the eve of a big poker game, B.J.'s pride is bruised when he finds out his wife is working as a waitress. And Potter takes driving lessons from Klinger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008000000 +0000" stop="20251008003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008003000 +0000" stop="20251008010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008010000 +0000" stop="20251008013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E27</episode-num>
    <desc>While Elly is washing her dogs, Granny calls that the food is ready, and the dogs trample her. Granny tells Jed and Elly that if the dogs don’t go, she will. Drysdale is also having dog troubles, annoyed with the fact that his wife’s dog gets beauty parlor treatment. Jed finally convinces Granny to let the dogs stay, but after changing her mind, she gets trampled by Elly’s new dogs, causing her to want them all out again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008013000 +0000" stop="20251008020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>A Date With Miss Camp Henderson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter bets Gomer he can't get a date with Ms. Camp Henderson, which of course he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008020000 +0000" stop="20251008023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008023000 +0000" stop="20251008030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008030000 +0000" stop="20251008033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Chita Rivera And Bob Newhart (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Chita Rivera and Bob Newhart. Originally aired on 02/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008033000 +0000" stop="20251008043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Thermal Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Attorney Ken Kramer comes to the aid of an alleged thief accused of stealing a $50,000 necklace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008043500 +0000" stop="20251008050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Kind Of A Stopwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is given a stopwatch that allows him to halt time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008050500 +0000" stop="20251008053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires a detective to follow his wife in hopes of finding grounds for divorce.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008053500 +0000" stop="20251008060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Servant Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer is shocked and far from happy when his long-missing wife reappears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008060500 +0000" stop="20251008070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Gang’s All Here</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix becomes the target of a vicious street gang known as the Nomads.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008070500 +0000" stop="20251008080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Touch Of Venom</sub-title>
    <desc>"A group of terrorists have drugged Cannon with a poison, giving him 72 hours to give them a defector and receive the antidote or die."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008080500 +0000" stop="20251008090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is The Punchline</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A comic is suspected of killing the nightclub owner who fired him after his act proved to be a flop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008090000 +0000" stop="20251008093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008093000 +0000" stop="20251008100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008100000 +0000" stop="20251008103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 45 -- Bright Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy report to a burglary call that was witnessed by a boy with a photographic memory. Afterward, they are called to the scene of two drunk men shooting at a box of dynamite at close range in a residential area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008103000 +0000" stop="20251008110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 65 -- Cigarettes, Cars And Wild, Wild Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy help take down a chop-shop that employs cute girls in mini-skirts to steal cars from trusting men. They also arrest a young man who grows pot and holds parties in the home of his unsuspecting shut-in aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008110000 +0000" stop="20251008120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Despearately Seeking Simon</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Bill fills in for Simon Shock, his deejay skills reshape the radio show."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008120000 +0000" stop="20251008123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Caddie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver has gotten a job as a caddy and is quickly running around the golf course chasing balls. However, all innocence is broken when one of the guys, Beaver is caddying for cheats in order to win a bet. Soon, Beaver begins wrestling with his conscience over whether or not to tell anyone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008123000 +0000" stop="20251008130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with the news that he applied to appear on a local television show called 'Teen Forum' and has been accepted. Beaver gets out of classes for the taping and all his classmates are treated to being able to watch him on TV during class. However, what Beaver, his friends and family don't know is that the show tapes each episode a week in advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008130000 +0000" stop="20251008140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Perjured Parrot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The courtroom action in this episode takes place at a coroner's inquest as a parrot holds the key to freeing suspect Ellen Sabin from blame in the murder of her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008140000 +0000" stop="20251008150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Parents  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a woman who was planning to give her unborn baby to couple Howard and Amy has second thoughts and is soon found dead, the couple in question are the natural suspects. Matlock sets out to prove that someone else may have had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008150000 +0000" stop="20251008160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A man murders his wife and her lover after he catches them together, then flees to a remote cabin with his daughter who does not know what he has done. The chief and the boys hope to talk him into surrendering without resorting to violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008160000 +0000" stop="20251008170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Outsider</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben surprises his family by bringing home a woman - his new bride</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008170000 +0000" stop="20251008180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Bad One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt investigates why a woman refuses to identify a stagecoach robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008180000 +0000" stop="20251008190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Frenzy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The husband of Ben's friend, Anna Kosovo, suddenly becomes a raging lunatic, barricading himself and Anna inside their home, threatening to kill anyone who tries to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008190000 +0000" stop="20251008193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When his employer begins to suspect him of embezzlement, bookkeeper Asa Manning decides to hire a professional gunman to take care of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008193000 +0000" stop="20251008200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Although a drought has forced local cowhands to seek work on a railroad construction project, railroad executives are afraid that their workers will desert them if they believe an old man's claim that he has found a way to make rain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008200000 +0000" stop="20251008210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Traitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>"Convicted of horse-stealing, Flint receives from Chris 20 lashes followed by banishment from the train. The lashes on his back then serve Flint as a "badge of dishonor" as he infiltrates a gang headed by a man known as Angel de Muerte."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008210000 +0000" stop="20251008220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Most Deadly Passage (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Roy and Johnny are sent to Seattle to study the techniques used there. A skydiver jumps off the Space Needle, a worker is trapped at the top of the Kingdome, and a fuel pumper loads a ferry with gasoline instead of diesel fuel, which sets the ferry on fire in the middle of the Elliot Bay."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008220000 +0000" stop="20251008223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester infuriates the camp when he hoards his stateside newspapers, and Hawkeye reunites two Korean brothers who have been fighting on opposite sides of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008223000 +0000" stop="20251008230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Judgment: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The military police think they've solved a rash of thefts at the 4077th when they apprehend Klinger with Hawkeye's stolen camera.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008230000 +0000" stop="20251008233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snappier Judgment: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. and Hawkeye resolve to clear Klinger's name after he chooses Winchester to defend him at his military court-martial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251008233000 +0000" stop="20251009000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Follies Of The Living - Concerns Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While suffering a fever, Klinger communicates with the spirit of a dead soldier, Private Weston, who stays on to witness his own last rites.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009000000 +0000" stop="20251009003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rehabilitation Of Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to use psychology to reform Otis of his drinking habit but this eventually leads Otis to "take his business" elsewhere—the jail in Mt. Pilot!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009003000 +0000" stop="20251009010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney receives a chain letter, but Andy goads him into throwing it away. Suddenly things begin going wrong for Barney and he's convinced he'll soon be out of a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009010000 +0000" stop="20251009013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Crystal Gazers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny believes she has the power to predict the future, and she is set on doing whatever she needs to make her predictions come true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009013000 +0000" stop="20251009020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer And The Father Figure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer saves a man from jumping off a bridge, and soon befriends him. Before long it's discovered that the man makes a habit out of this, taking advantage of people's kindness along the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009020000 +0000" stop="20251009023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009023000 +0000" stop="20251009030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009030000 +0000" stop="20251009033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Mike Douglas And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Mike Douglas and Bernadette Peters. Originally aired on 03/08/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009033000 +0000" stop="20251009043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Venom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is hired to look into the death of his client's son, which occurred two years earlier. It is revealed that several people may have had reason to want the man out of the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009043500 +0000" stop="20251009050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Night Of A Jockey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A dejected jockey wants to be tall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009050500 +0000" stop="20251009053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Coming Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man just released from prison becomes desperate when his stash of money disappears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009053500 +0000" stop="20251009060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Final Arrangements</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A man decides to get away from his nagging, invalid wife once and for all.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009060500 +0000" stop="20251009070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Desert Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hires Mannix to investigate the disappearance of her husband's plane in the Rockies, but then the detective learns that she is not the missing man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009070500 +0000" stop="20251009080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Endangered Species</sub-title>
    <desc>Bill Coates, Cannon's old friend, a boat builder, finds himself charged in his son's hunting-accident death. Unbeknown to Coates his lawyer is the man behind the homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009080500 +0000" stop="20251009090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Victim, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A columnist writing about prostitution focuses on a murdered girl whose reputation Barnaby is trying to save.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009090000 +0000" stop="20251009093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009093000 +0000" stop="20251009100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009100000 +0000" stop="20251009103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 55 -- Missing Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After responding to a gas leak in a home, reed and malloy search for a missing child. Finally, they investigate an attempted car theft that ended with a fatal shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009103000 +0000" stop="20251009110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 75: Have A Nice Weekend</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers investigate robberies, attempted arson and a violent argument."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009110000 +0000" stop="20251009120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Fall Rush</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony rush Cleamma!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009120000 +0000" stop="20251009123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Box Office Attraction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward have noticed the Wally has been spending quite a bit of his time at the movie theater but it's not to see the movies. He's been eyeing the pretty young lady who works in the box office. Thanks to Eddie, Wally works up enough courage to ask her out but quickly sees another side to the young lady that is a bit too mature for Wally's taste.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009123000 +0000" stop="20251009130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Scholarship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is let down when he learns that he didn't get the sports scholarship from State University. However, he does learn that Lumpy did get one and this leads him to throw a party in Lumpy's honor. However, half way through the party, Fred calls with some unfortunate news for Lumpy, the scholarship is no longer available due to Lumpy's grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009130000 +0000" stop="20251009140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shattered Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Sarah Werner asks Mason to find her husband, Hugo Werner, who ran off with her inheritance. Hugo, now using the name Hans Breel, is working on a gem scam but his scheme backfires when he is murdered and Sarah is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009140000 +0000" stop="20251009150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Of The Year  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is all set to be honored as the man of the year, but when his car breaks down and he's forced to ask his housekeeper for a ride, a simple 20-minute trip turns into a flat tire, hostage situation and afternoon in jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009150000 +0000" stop="20251009160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hello In There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba refuses to believe that a former teammate embezzled funds from the bank where he worked. And sets out to prove that his friend was framed and murdered. Harriet hopes that art therapy can help the man's traumatized son, who becomes a target himself when the killer realizes he witnessed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009160000 +0000" stop="20251009170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An old girlfriend of John Walton buys the Drew Drop Inn where Jason works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009170000 +0000" stop="20251009180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Cousin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt's foster brother forces him into a showdown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009180000 +0000" stop="20251009190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Customs Of The Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Hoss enter a new world when they arrive in Agua Santos, Mexico. Joe breaks a law by removing his hat in church and Hoss encounters more oddities when trying to gain his release.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009190000 +0000" stop="20251009193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain gives blood to save a dying man and is surprised by Marshal Torrance's odd behavior toward the man. Then three men arrive from a nearby town and demand custody of the stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009193000 +0000" stop="20251009200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger At Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's finding the body of a murder victim starts Lucas, his friend, Artemus, and Marshal Torrance on a search for the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009200000 +0000" stop="20251009210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bettina May Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bettina May leads three generations of her family across the plains. Other members of the wagon train as well as some family members become concerned with her over bearing nature and the level of control she exerts on the family."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009210000 +0000" stop="20251009220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Greatest Rescues Of Emergency! (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Johnny and Roy are promoted to Captain, they reminisce about their years working together. Flash-back sequences include the rescue of airplane passengers after a crash-landing, a potential suicide threatening to leap from a crane tower, and a girl whose toe is stuck in a faucet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009220000 +0000" stop="20251009223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret's birthday plans are spoiled when she and Klinger get stranded on a desolate roadside. Meanwhile, Charles gives a lecture for Margaret, and the surgeons assist in the delivery of a calf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009223000 +0000" stop="20251009230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood And Guts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is outraged when a sensationalistic war correspondent, Clayton Kibbee, reports irresponsible G.I. stunts as tales of military valor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009230000 +0000" stop="20251009233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Holy Mess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An AWOL soldier, Nick Gillis, seeks sanctuary in the mess tent, after Father Mulcahy's service. At the same time, a special Sunday brunch is due to be served, following the donation of some eggs to the camp by a grateful farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251009233000 +0000" stop="20251010000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth Shall Set You Free</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles has a serious toothache, but hates the thought of having anything done about it. The doctors suspect prejudice when an inordinate number of black casualties are brought in from a single unit, led by Major Weems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010000000 +0000" stop="20251010003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010003000 +0000" stop="20251010010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Runs For Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers taking an out-of-town job, and with the election nearing, no one has yet filed to run for Sheriff. Barney throws his hat in the ring, and then Andy's job prospect takes a turn.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010010000 +0000" stop="20251010013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampett money keeps rolling in as more oil is discovered on their land. And Mr. Brewster is coming out to marry his fiancée, Edythe. Granny is planning to go back home to the hills, but Jed decides to put up the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010013000 +0000" stop="20251010020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Desk Job For A Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter takes a new job as a training coordinator. But when he finds out the platoon is doing fine under Cpl. Boyle's command, he decides he wants his old job back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010020000 +0000" stop="20251010023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everyone Has A Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plot to destroy an ammunition train is foiled by Burkhalter's brother-in-law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010023000 +0000" stop="20251010030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses an incredibly original ruse to get Schultz a weeklong furlough in Heidelberg. While there, Schultz is to deliver needed radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010030000 +0000" stop="20251010033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, And David Frost (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, and David Frost. Originally aired on 03/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010033000 +0000" stop="20251010043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tell-tale Tap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When the niece of the head of an investment firm is found dead, the company's financial comptroller is charged with her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010043500 +0000" stop="20251010050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Man In The Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A mysterious guardian helps a tiny community survive after nuclear war destroys much of the Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010050500 +0000" stop="20251010053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Make My Death Bed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E36</episode-num>
    <desc>It is New Year's Eve and Mr. Taylor's resolution is to end Mrs. Taylor's extramarital flirtations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010053500 +0000" stop="20251010060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Ambition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E37</episode-num>
    <desc>D.A. Rudolf Cox expects to get a politically valuable conviction with the help of stool pigeon Lou Heinz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010060500 +0000" stop="20251010070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>On a fishing trip, Mannix has his car break down in the desert. Searching for help he stumbles across the headquarters of a modern day Murder Inc.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010070500 +0000" stop="20251010080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Fall Guy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon has been hired when a VP of a petroleum company is charged with misappropriation of funds and faces dismissal and prison time."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010080500 +0000" stop="20251010090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Accuser, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty responds to an SOS from her teacher friend, only to find her dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010090000 +0000" stop="20251010093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010093000 +0000" stop="20251010100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010100000 +0000" stop="20251010103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 105 -- Elegy For A Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Malloy pays tribute to Officer Tom Porter, who has recently fallen in the line of duty. Malloy recounts the close friendship they developed while training at the academy, as well as the moments where they crossed paths on duty, including the night of the officer's unfortunate demise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010103000 +0000" stop="20251010110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 25 -- Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed hunt down a suspect who has been bombing downtown storefronts. Then they report to a scuffle between two native americans at a bar that the bartender thinks may be a prelude to something a lot more serious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010110000 +0000" stop="20251010120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Magnolia State</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010120000 +0000" stop="20251010123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all set to go with Eddie and Wally to hook up a AM/FM car radio in Eddie's car but June stops him and insists he go to the grocery store to pick up the items he had promised. This leads Beaver to give June the cold shoulder treatment while playing up to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010123000 +0000" stop="20251010130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for a couple of days and leave Uncle Billy to stay with Wally and Beaver. Beaver quickly realizes Billy runs a much looser ship than Ward and June and feels as if he can get away with more things. However, he's soon in for a rude awakening when he helps Gilbert sneak into the movies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010130000 +0000" stop="20251010140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Brunette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Eva Martell is hired out of numerous candidates by Melvin Slater to impersonate a woman named Helen Reynolds. Eva is paid extremely well and given a nice apartment for assuming the identity of Helen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010140000 +0000" stop="20251010150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Arsonist  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of two business partners planning to hire an arsonist and collect insurance money is found dead, the surviving business man is pinned as the likely killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010150000 +0000" stop="20251010160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>December Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Sparta police investigate a suspicious death in a nursing home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010160000 +0000" stop="20251010170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Tailspin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob finds out he is not eligible to fly in the Air Corps due to bad vision</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010170000 +0000" stop="20251010180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Shona</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>As the citizens of Dodge deal with the strain of Indian raids, a farmer brings his ailing Indian wife into town for treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010180000 +0000" stop="20251010190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Shanklin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rogue ex-Confederate soldier critically wounds Hoss in a robbery attempt, Ben learns that the very man who shot Hoss may be the only one in town able to perform a life-saving surgery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010190000 +0000" stop="20251010193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010193000 +0000" stop="20251010200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010200000 +0000" stop="20251010210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Clyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"Charlie's life undergoes an epiphany when he finds an injured buffalo and the animal befriends him. He takes the buffalo, who he calls Clyde, into the wagon train as a pet. Others, however, don't appreciate the trouble the creature causes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010210000 +0000" stop="20251010220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Greatest Rescues Of Emergency! (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Johnny and Roy are promoted to Captain, they reminisce about their years working together. Flash-back sequences include the rescue of airplane passengers after a crash-landing, a potential suicide threatening to leap from a crane tower, and a girl whose toe is stuck in a faucet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010220000 +0000" stop="20251010223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Points</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter sends for Sidney Freedman when he loses confidence in his surgical abilities, and Winchester loses patience with his bunkmates' sloppiness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010223000 +0000" stop="20251010230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's A Will, There's A War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye goes to help at an aid station, and under heavy shelling he draws up a will, leaving various items to his friends at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010230000 +0000" stop="20251010233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Promotion Commotion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester, Pierce and Hunnicutt find themselves in the sticky position of having to decide which enlisted men to recommend for promotion. For Winchester it could be a matter of life and death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251010233000 +0000" stop="20251011000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heroes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is the golden boy of the world press when he treats a celebrity prizefighter, "Gentleman" Joe Cavanaugh, who has a stroke at the 4077th. Father Mulcahy finds the news hard to take, as Cavanaugh was a hero of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011000000 +0000" stop="20251011003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>If I Had A Quarter-million</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney finds $250,000 stolen in a bank heist, he goes undercover to find the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011003000 +0000" stop="20251011010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves pretend to be Hollywood producers in order to rob the Mayberry Bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011010000 +0000" stop="20251011013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed And The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>It is time for spring tonic, and the Countess Maria returns to meet with her good friends the Clampetts, as well as get some tonic. And after the Clampetts learn Maria is single again, having lost her husband at a party, Granny sees this as the time for Jed to make his move on the Countess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011013000 +0000" stop="20251011020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, The Would-be Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Sgt. Carter stops a robber in a diner, he makes Gomer the hero so he won't get caught with another woman by Bunny. It's not long before Carter wants the credit he is due, but by then no one will believe that he was the hero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011020000 +0000" stop="20251011023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reverend Kommandant Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan sneaks a French pilot's girl into camp and gets Klink to marry them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011023000 +0000" stop="20251011030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Escape-proof Camp I've Ever Escaped From</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Klink's "no escape" record is jeopardized when Malcom Flood, a British escape artist, lands in Stalag 13 and intends to continue his impressive escape record, a plan likely to endanger Hogan's scheduled rendezvous with an OSS agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011030000 +0000" stop="20251011033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, And David Frost (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, and David Frost. Originally aired on 03/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011033000 +0000" stop="20251011043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Irate Inventor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>James Frazer wants a divorce and his cheating wife refuses to give him one. She's also stealing the plans to his invention in order to bait her engineer lover into staying around.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011043500 +0000" stop="20251011050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Simon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After her mean-spirited uncle dies, an old maid inherits the crotchety inventor's estate, with the stipulation that she cares for his latest invention, a robot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011050500 +0000" stop="20251011053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hatbox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Two young men suspect one of their professors of murdering his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011053500 +0000" stop="20251011060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Bang, You're Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy believes the gun he found was meant for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011060500 +0000" stop="20251011070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A World Without Sundays</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to find the gal-pal of a mobster who disappeared while en route to Los Angeles with a well-known football player.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011070500 +0000" stop="20251011080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Melted Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon investigates when an heiress finds an ax buried into the head of a snowman outside of her home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011080500 +0000" stop="20251011090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadline For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of men pretending to be Barnaby and J.R. murder a writer employed by a publishing empire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251011090000 +0000" stop="20251011093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Why Girls Leave Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobbie Jo decides to move to New York to take singing lessons.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
