<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227140000 +0000" stop="20251227150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Devil And Mr. Hare, Plop Goes The Weasel, Greedy For Tweety, Hare Conditioned, What's My Lion?, Of Thee I Sting, Bowery Bugs</sub-title>
    <desc>"Taz pours ketchup on Bugs to prep him for eating, instead Bugs pretends to be bleeding and Taz has to find a doc. Bugs poses as the doctor and leads Taz down a path of painful tricks., Foggy and Br'er Dog can't stand each other, and they use the weasels in their fights. , A three way chase of Tweety, Sylvester, and the bulldog lands them in the animal hospital. , Bugs gets chased all around the department store he works at when he's told by the store official that he's being transferred to the taxidermy department to be stuffed. , When a mountain lion realizes that hunting season has started, he hides in a tourist lodge, pretending to be a stuffed lion. , A bunch of mosquitoes take lessons on how to attack a farmer. , Bugs recounts a story of how he tricked a man so much so that he jumped off a bridge. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227150000 +0000" stop="20251227160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Diva</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>West meets up with Gordon, who has just arrived in New Orleans with a famous Italian diva and niece of the ambassador on his arm, an escort urged by President Grant. West agrees to substitute as the lady's guardian for her appearance that evening at the opera, but the performance is interrupted when Montebello's would-be kidnappers bring down the curtain and West jumps into the fray. Discovering that several divas had recently disappeared in New Orleans, the agents must rush to unravel a plot involving the secret Order of Lucia and reveal who among their new acquaintances is playing a role on and off the stage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227160000 +0000" stop="20251227170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Barbara Lindquist Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>"Cooper Smith is on his way to the town of Washburn to pick up long awaited mail for the wagon train when he stumbles upon a stagecoach robbery in progress. The very proper Miss Barbara Lindquist is on her way to meet her fiancé, mistakes Coop for one of the robbers and ends up forcing him to help her. Further misadventures see Coop wounded and both he and Barbara struggling to get to back to the wagon train for help. Believing his wound will end his days as a scout, Coop finds himself falling in love with Barbara and she with him. But will their love stand the test ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227170000 +0000" stop="20251227180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown In Limbo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Sheriff Frank Sawyer thinks that all it takes is time to toughen up his young son, newly returned from the east. His attitude is likely to endanger them and Heath, too, as they travel to Stockton to deliver a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227180000 +0000" stop="20251227190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Double Entry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Brad McCain tries to take advantage of his friendship with Matt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227190000 +0000" stop="20251227200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Savage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Adam is wounded by Indians and left for dead, a reclusive mountain woman nurses him back to health. She is known to the Indians as While Buffalo Woman, and they believe she possesses magical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227200000 +0000" stop="20251227203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of A Young Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is forced to give refuge to Will Fulton, a young bank robber who was injured while saving Mark's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227203000 +0000" stop="20251227210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Marshal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Micah Torrance, a once famous lawman, is introduced as a drunken derelict who stumbles into North Fork. Micah, nursing an arm crippled in a gunfight, is hired by Lucas to help out at the ranch. Three outlaws ride into town looking for revenge against Micah.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227210000 +0000" stop="20251227220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Violent Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Mace and Gorman the new drovers have more than cows on thier minds. Mace shows Favor a reward poster for $10,000 for a white girl captured by the Apaches. Rowdy visits the grave of his sister killed by indians, and then refuses to sell 12 head to Yuma, the Apache chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227220000 +0000" stop="20251227223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Statue Of San Sebastian</sub-title>
    <desc>"Paladin agrees to capture an outlaw in return for a statue belonging to the local mission."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227223000 +0000" stop="20251227230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Pariah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Randall learns "hate comes high" in a town whose people have hired a trio of killers to murder their fellow resident Randy Holleran, a sniveling drunkard whom Josh has promised to protect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251227230000 +0000" stop="20251228010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Calling All Curs, Oily To Bed, Some More Of Samoa, Baby Sitters Jitters, Income Tax Sappy, Brideless Groom, Oily To Rise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Veternarians Moe, Curly and Larry find their business going to the dogs when one of their prize patients is stolen and held for ransom. , The Stooges are tramps looking for handouts.  Although the boys are down and out, Curly seems to get everything he wishes for.  After some trouble with a farmer, the boys come across an abandoned car, one of Curly's wishes.  The car actually belongs to some con men who have just gypped the widow Jenkins out of her land.  The boys wind up at the Mrs. Jenkins house just in time for a free meal.  To repay Mrs. Jenkins the boys try to fix her well and instead unleash an oil geyser.  Learning that Mrs. Jenkins has been swindled, the boys go to retrieve the deed before it can be recorded.  They find the bad guys and after a wild fight recover the deed.  The boys return the deed to Mrs. Jenkins and marry her daughters; April, May and June. , The Stooges are tree surgeons who are enlisted by a rich old man to find a mate for his rare puckerless persimmon tree.  The boys sail to the tropical island of Rhum-Boogie to find the tree.  When they arrive they are captured by the natives and will be eaten unless Curly marries the Chief's ugly daughter.  The Stooges escape with the tree and, after a confrontation with an alligator; sail off with their prize. , The Stooges are facing eviction and decide to raise some money by becoming baby-sitters.  Their first client is a women separated from her husband, who entrusts her son "Junior" to the boys' care.  When the husband steals the baby, the Stooges set out to find their missing charge and return him to his mother.  The boys confront the husband and find Junior, and in the process the estranged couple is re-united. , Tax cheats Moe, Larry and Shemp decide they're so good at cheating the government, that they start a business as crooked tax advisors.  They become rich, but an undercover agent from the IRS gets the goods on them, and it's off to jail for the Stooges. , To inherit a fortune, voice teacher Shemp must marry before six o'clock, but no girl will accept his proposal.  Finally one of his repulsive students agrees to marry him, just in the nick of time.  When the rest of the prospective brides hear about the inheritance, they show up at the ceremony and a free for all ensues.  Shemp marries before the deadline, but wishes he was still a free man. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228010000 +0000" stop="20251228030000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Creation Of The Humanoids</sub-title>
    <desc>"Androids help the human race by giving them android babies."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228030000 +0000" stop="20251228033000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Off The Griddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After Catwoman opens a school for cat-burglars, the Dynamic Duo uses a fake story to draw her out, only to realize the story's writer was in league with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228033000 +0000" stop="20251228040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Cat And The Fiddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Catwoman attempts to steal priceless violins, but an undercover Robin interferes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228040000 +0000" stop="20251228050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Court Martial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kirk's career is at stake when he is put on trial for the loss of a crewman during an ion storm.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228050000 +0000" stop="20251228053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prince Albert Coat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A ten year old donates a coat for flood relief, but the coat contained his great-grandfather's life savings. Lois and Jimmy attempt to recover the coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228053000 +0000" stop="20251228060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stolen Elephant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby elephant is stolen from the circus. Clark, Lois, and Jimmy get involved, with help from young Johnny Wilson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228060000 +0000" stop="20251228070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Follow The Leader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>John Robinson is possessed by an alien spirit. The alien forces the family to prepare to return to the spirit's home world, even if it requires he sacrifice Will to keep his secret from the rest of the family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228070000 +0000" stop="20251228080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Death From The Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview battles two Nazi officers left over from world war II who attempt to launch ICBMs at the allied capitol cities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228080000 +0000" stop="20251228090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A rival power plots to destroy the nearby city, and the Earthlings are forced to help Inspector Kobick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228090000 +0000" stop="20251228100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Raiders From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are at Khartoum in 1883 when the world is menaced by conquerors from outer space.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228100000 +0000" stop="20251228110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Experiment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>David Vincent tries to befriend an astrophysicist who has proof that aliens are invading the planet, but a betrayal threatens everything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228110000 +0000" stop="20251228120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>A Time Of Thirsting</sub-title>
    <desc>"A long dry spell in the mountains affects its inhabitants. Adams and friends devise ways to conserve what water they have,until the rains return. ..but not before someone's ignorance sets the forest on fire."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228120000 +0000" stop="20251228123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Arctic Adventure</sub-title>
    <desc>"A trip to the top of the world … above the Arctic Circle, north of Hudson Bay for a polar bear hunt and a walrus capture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228123000 +0000" stop="20251228130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Lightning</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mother cheetah leads her playful cubs over the vast Rhodesian veldt teaching them the ways of defense and hunting."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228130000 +0000" stop="20251228133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Grizzly Disappears</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bears read signs! They read the signs signaling the beginning of winter – within twenty-four hours of first warning, all bears have disappeared into their caves.  We spend this last day with a young grizzly as he prepares for his long nap."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228133000 +0000" stop="20251228140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Porpoise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and his crew sail the waters of the California coast in search of the porpoise of the Pacific."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228140000 +0000" stop="20251228143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lost World Of Angel Falls</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan fly into the remote interior of Venezuela to a jutting plateau whose sheer cliff echoes the perpetual thunder of Angel Falls.  It is a region so remote that it has often been called the Lost World."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228143000 +0000" stop="20251228150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Exploring The Llanos</sub-title>
    <desc>"In South America there are fresh water porpoises living inland in the rivers and streams.  During the dry season, as the rivers recede, these porpoises may perish as the water level drops.  Marlin and Jim go on an expedition to rescue the trapped llanos porpoises."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228150000 +0000" stop="20251228153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Winner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby realizes he is the only Brady without a trophy, so Mike and Carol encourage him to enter numerous contests in order to win one. Among his efforts are selling magazines and a televised ice cream eating contest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228153000 +0000" stop="20251228160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Double Parked</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The neighborhood park is going to be bulldozed so the new court house can be built, prompting the Brady family to go all out to try to save the park. But it's Mike's firm that's in charge of the construction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228160000 +0000" stop="20251228180000 +0000">
    <title>MeTV Presents: A Very Special Sunday</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Days 30th Anniversary Reunion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Castmembers reunite to celebrate the hit series."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228180000 +0000" stop="20251228190000 +0000">
    <title>MeTV Presents: A Very Special Sunday</title>
    <sub-title>The Andy Griffith Show Reunion</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cast members from "The Andy Griffith Show" gather to reminisce about the classic 1960s TV series."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228190000 +0000" stop="20251228210000 +0000">
    <title>MeTV Presents: A Very Special Sunday</title>
    <sub-title>I Love Lucy: 50th Anniversary Special</sub-title>
    <desc>"Celebrities celebrate the legacy of "Lucy!""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228210000 +0000" stop="20251228220000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>First Six Years, The (hour)</sub-title>
    <desc>"An hour of the best moments of "Everybody Loves Raymond"'s first six years, with interviews from celebrities about why they love the show and how they can relate to the characters."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228220000 +0000" stop="20251228233000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>200th Episode Celebration Of All In The Family, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Norman Lear hosts an affectionate look at the high points of his ground-breaking TV series.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251228233000 +0000" stop="20251229000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Boop- Janet Ellis</sub-title>
    <desc>"Janet Ellis first met and bonded with her husband Len over her collection of Betty Boop memorabilia. Now Len is Janet’s co-collector and a Betty Boop expert in his own right – in fact, he literally wrote the book on Betty collectibles. Lisa joins the couple in the shrine to the classic cartoon character they've built in their home. They share with us such 1930s rarities as an unlicensed bowl featuring both Betty and Mickey Mouse, and a gorgeously preserved wooden figure that is the very first Betty Boop doll. Also on hand is toy treasure hunter Joel Magee, who sets a value on Janet and Len’s entire collection – then tries to lure them into a trade for a beautiful one-of-a-kind modern Betty Boop item. And if that doesn’t have Janet and Len’s head spinning, there’s also a video greeting from the family of Betty Boop’s legendary creator, Max Fleisher."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229000000 +0000" stop="20251229003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Foresight Saga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is given a gift of fresh-grown vegetables by a grateful Korean; and Potter questions the veracity of an upbeat letter from Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229003000 +0000" stop="20251229010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Life You Save</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles is nearly felled by a sniper's bullet, he develops a philosophical obsession with death. Meanwhile, the officers have all been assigned new responsibilities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229010000 +0000" stop="20251229013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Gets The Business (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When Kelsey finally decides to sell his bar, nothing will stop Archie from getting it--even if it means forging Edith's signature against her will.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229013000 +0000" stop="20251229020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Gets The Business (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is upset when she discovers Archie has forged her signature to get the bar. But Mike will influence Mrs. Bunker to change her mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229020000 +0000" stop="20251229023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Liz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Cousin Liz dies, Edith and Archie learn more about her than they ever thought. When a roomate of Liz, Veronica, comes out of the closet to Edith, she also admits that she was more than just roomates with Liz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229023000 +0000" stop="20251229030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>New Year's Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike continues to make decisions without consulting Gloria.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229030000 +0000" stop="20251229033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>No Roll!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra sit down to play "Sensuoopoly."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229033000 +0000" stop="20251229040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Odd Man Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank forces Marco to choose either Marie or him as a friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229040000 +0000" stop="20251229043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>I Am My Brother's Keeper: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's shy brother experiences a strange change when he falls asleep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229043000 +0000" stop="20251229050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sleeping Brother: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob wants his brother to try out for "The Alan Brady Show", but can he be funny and awake?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229050000 +0000" stop="20251229053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Life And Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ralph thinks he's dying and sells the story to a magazine, he discovers it was a dog who was sick instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229053000 +0000" stop="20251229060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Man In The Bottle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A discontented curio shop owner thinks he's finally found happiness when a genie  grants him four wishes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229060000 +0000" stop="20251229070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Cadaver  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A medical undergraduate tries to get his roommate off the bottle by making him believe he killed a young woman while in a drunken trance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229070000 +0000" stop="20251229080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wendell Hayes, the brother of an imprisoned Syndicate enforcer, has stolen a canister of nerve gas and threatens to use it if his brother, Cayman, isn't freed—the IMF must stop him and recover the gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229080000 +0000" stop="20251229090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Good Guys And The Bad Guys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In the small town of Drover City, Montana, Kimble stumbles onto the annual "vigilante roundup," a carnival of sorts where locals "hunt" down anybody not wearing Western cowboy clothing. After being "lassoed" literally, Kimble is held "prisoner" in the loc</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229090000 +0000" stop="20251229100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Ballinger's Choice</sub-title>
    <desc>"Illicit romance leads to murder as Harry Orwell follows the trail of a married publisher having an affair with a 16-year-old girl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229100000 +0000" stop="20251229103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-32</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl's life hangs in the balance as the detectives search for the dog that bit her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229103000 +0000" stop="20251229110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-35</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An infant girl is found in a garbage can; Joe and Bill use the child's blanket to track down the mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229110000 +0000" stop="20251229113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gus Corbin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy is asked to fill in for Sgt. MacDonald, leaving Reed to partner with a young probationary officer who lets his judgment be clouded by his constant need to prove himself. On patrol, they search for a purse snatcher inside a church, encounter a burglary in progress at a closed pharmaceutical company and search for an armed robbery suspect in a lumber yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229113000 +0000" stop="20251229120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Dana Hall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy continues his fill-in assignment for Sgt. MacDonald, Reed is paired with the department's first female officer, which presents both of them with a series of unique challenges. On patrol, they detain an underage drunk driver with a dismissive mother, search a parking garage for car strippers and help round up a large group of young people causing trouble outside a rock concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229120000 +0000" stop="20251229130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Buggin' Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony tries to cure Bill's fear of insects with the help of live tarantula."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229130000 +0000" stop="20251229133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Team</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E39</episode-num>
    <desc>While coaching Beaver's football team, Wally makes up a secret play and Beaver just happens to mention it to Penny who inadvertently passes it on to the opposing team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229133000 +0000" stop="20251229140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Won't Eat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is determined not to eat brussels sprouts and adamantly refuses to eat them when June serves them for dinner. In order to go to a football game, Ward makes Beaver promise that he will eat brussels sprouts the next time they are served. Beaver quickly finds himself confronted with the "deadly" vegetables when the Cleavers go out to eat at a posh restaurant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229140000 +0000" stop="20251229150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Envious Editor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Slimy publishing tycoon Donald Fletcher buys controlling interest in a respectable but financially troubled publishing house. Fletcher turns things upside down by turning the publications into scandal sheets featuring photographs of scantily clad women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229150000 +0000" stop="20251229160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Vendetta  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle is taken hostage by Ned Billings, who blames Matlock for his brother's suicide after being convicted of murder, thanks to Matlock. Tyler and Julie end up as Ned's hostages, too, and the three try to use tactics they've seen Matlock use in courtrooms and interrogations to help them stay alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229160000 +0000" stop="20251229170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Cocoon: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Steve McGarrett, head of Hawaii Five-O, investigates the death of a close friend who seems to have drowned. Only when he digs deeper does McGarrett discover the chilling truth of the matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229170000 +0000" stop="20251229180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Four carnival performers are stranded after the carnival leaves Walton's Mountain, so they stay with the Waltons while they try to get back home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229180000 +0000" stop="20251229190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Run, Sheep, Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man causes trouble for a young couple when he buys a ranch from them but refuses to pay for a year.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229190000 +0000" stop="20251229200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Captivated by the pretty, deaf-mute daughter of a reclusive mountain man, Little Joe teaches her sign language. Thrilled with her newfound ability to communicate, Annie mistakes her gratitude to Little Joe for love, much to the chagrin of Albie, who is determined to have her for his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229200000 +0000" stop="20251229203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's uncle, Johnny Gibb, a big-time rodeo rider, comes to visit. While Mark idolizes his uncle, Lucas discovers that Johnny is on the run from the law for an Express Office robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229203000 +0000" stop="20251229210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eight Hours To Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Judge Burton seeks "justice" against the hangman who hanged his son; the judge who sentenced his son; and Lucas, the man who caught his son. When Judge Burton discovers that Lucas has a son, he decides that the best way to serve justice is an eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth, a son for a son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229210000 +0000" stop="20251229220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Brian Conlin Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"Brian Conlin walks into Hale's camp, delirious and dehydrated. After he recovers, he leads Coop to his group of Irish immigrants, whose wagons have broken down, and Hale invites them to join the wagon train. However, having been repeatedly turned away from place after place, most members of Conlin's group are slow to trust anyone or accept help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229220000 +0000" stop="20251229230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Hard Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Early is diagnosed with a heart condition and undergoes a bypass. A pro football player is embarrassed to admit that his son tackled him too hard. The firemen rescue a boy trapped in his homemade rocket, a woman with her toe stuck in a bathtub faucet and an electrocution victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229230000 +0000" stop="20251229233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251229233000 +0000" stop="20251230000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230000000 +0000" stop="20251230003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Identity Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy counsels a GI who is plagued by guilt because he has swapped tags with a dead colleague. Meanwhile, B.J. and Charles consider ways of keeping a soldier-salesman quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230003000 +0000" stop="20251230010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rumor At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The latest scuttlebutt affects everyone's behavior when a visiting Army rep is rumored to be recruiting for a new M*A*S*H unit. The gang fears that the 4077th will be split up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230010000 +0000" stop="20251230013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230013000 +0000" stop="20251230020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230020000 +0000" stop="20251230023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ray's Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra decides to take matters into her own hands when Ray loses his ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230023000 +0000" stop="20251230030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Marie's Sculpture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra are horrified when Marie presents them with a sculpture she made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230030000 +0000" stop="20251230033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Rockets Or Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan becomes the partner of a beautiful underground agent when he and his men team up with the underground to destroy a guided missile battery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230033000 +0000" stop="20251230040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230040000 +0000" stop="20251230043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Monkey Man, Tim is bitten by a chimp and acts like a monkey in front of his fiance's father. Then, in The Ad Men, Tim's old boss tries to woo him back to his old job, angering his current boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230043000 +0000" stop="20251230053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baited Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert Dawson confronts Albert Tydings, his partner, about $80,000 missing from Carol Stanley's trust account. Tydings admits he embezzled the money and blackmails Dawson into keeping quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230053500 +0000" stop="20251230060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nervous Man In A Four Dollar Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ordered to commit a murder, a smalltime hood nervously looks in the mirror and sees the man he could have been.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230060500 +0000" stop="20251230070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Dividing Wall  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A break-in gang's newest heist may be their last: the booty contains a radioactive capsule.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230070500 +0000" stop="20251230080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>License To Kill—limit Three People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired when a sniper begins killing citizens, the prime suspect being an escaped mental patient.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230080500 +0000" stop="20251230090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Dead Samaritan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Manning, a former policewoman, hires Cannon when her husband becomes the victim of blackmailers. The man is an electrician specialized in wiretapping. Three criminals find that the electrician has recorded one of his conversations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230090500 +0000" stop="20251230100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Image Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A film director arranges for the death of his leading man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230100000 +0000" stop="20251230103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-36</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon track down a department store employee who stole $100,000 worth of merchandise in six months.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230103000 +0000" stop="20251230110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Intelligence - Dr-34</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives search out the suppliers of stolen arms for paramilitary groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230110000 +0000" stop="20251230113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Something Worth Dying For: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After a well known hype is released because of a lack of probable cause, Reed decides to temporarily join the narcotics squad to hone his skills. The demands of the assignment quickly take their toll on him personally, and his worst fears are realized when Malloy assists in a narcotics bust.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230113000 +0000" stop="20251230120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Something Worth Dying For: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy recovers from his gunshot wound and returns to patrol with Reed, where they investigate a suspicious burglary call at a school for women, and confront a pair of armed intruders in a warehouse full of mannequins. Meanwhile, Reed contemplates taking the investigator's exam as he prepares to give a speech in acceptance of the medal of valor for saving Malloy's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230120000 +0000" stop="20251230130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Model Behavior</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230130000 +0000" stop="20251230133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend Beaver made at summer camp, Chopper, stays with the Cleavers for the weekend. Beaver is quickly introduced to Chopper's unusual life; he is the son of parents who have been married and divorced many times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230133000 +0000" stop="20251230140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Becomes A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Beaver and Wally are fishing an abandoned canoe floats up and they responsibly return it to the owner, whose name had been carved in the paddle. However, after telling his friends the story, they adjust it to make it sound as if Beaver had saved a girl from drowning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230140000 +0000" stop="20251230150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Resolute Reformer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason represents a citizen's group in hearings on a proposed aqueduct to be named after county engineer William Harper Caine. He gets a stop-work order until a section of the proposed location can be checked for an underground spring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230150000 +0000" stop="20251230160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Other Woman  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend psychiatrist Lucas Forbes when he's arrested for killing the husband of one of his patients with whom he was reportedly having an affair. Matlock soon realizes that the patient in question has a host of deep-rooted psychiatric problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230160000 +0000" stop="20251230170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Cocoon: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett learns about the assassination campaign against U.S. agents. U.S. intelligence asks him to act as bait. McGarrett cooperates in the fanciful and dangerous attempt to provide false information to Chinese agent Wo Fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230170000 +0000" stop="20251230180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Calf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The children are upset when their father sells a newborn</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230180000 +0000" stop="20251230190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Deputy Festus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus, now Matt's deputy, learns that the drunken trappers he put in jail are his cousins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230190000 +0000" stop="20251230200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss decides to help Arnie, a man who has never learned to control his great strength. Things seem to be working out until Arnie falls for a saloon girl. Hoss realizes that he is facing an uphill battle to help Arnie lead the kind of life that he has always wanted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230200000 +0000" stop="20251230203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Italian count arrives in North Fork, his strange attire attracts the attention of Groder, a town bully. Groder, trying to have fun with this stranger, destroys some of the count's currency, mocks him and tries to humiliate him. Eventually the count challenges Groder to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230203000 +0000" stop="20251230210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Safe Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Floyd Doniger comes to North Fork, looking to start a new life. He's got a steady job as the guard at the new bank and he's entertaining ideas of settling down on a spread of his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230210000 +0000" stop="20251230220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Alice Whitetree Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop falls for a young half-Indian woman wandering alone in the wilderness. He brings her to the wagon train, where Hale discovers she is a survivor of a tribe totally massacred ten years earlier. A sheriff says she has killed two people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230220000 +0000" stop="20251230230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Floor Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy consider going into the floor cleaning business on the side. A hermit is trapped in his cave home. Dr. Morton treats a famous singer. John is injured on a high rescue, and the station battles a chemical warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230230000 +0000" stop="20251230233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em Hell, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes a heartfelt letter to President Harry Truman to protest at the continued fighting in Korea. Meanwhile, Colonel Ditka has promised a much-needed water heater if the 4077th beautifies the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251230233000 +0000" stop="20251231000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Wheelers And Dealers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>On the eve of a big poker game, B.J.'s pride is bruised when he finds out his wife is working as a waitress. And Potter takes driving lessons from Klinger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231000000 +0000" stop="20251231003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester infuriates the camp when he hoards his stateside newspapers, and Hawkeye reunites two Korean brothers who have been fighting on opposite sides of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231003000 +0000" stop="20251231010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Follies Of The Living - Concerns Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While suffering a fever, Klinger communicates with the spirit of a dead soldier, Private Weston, who stays on to witness his own last rites.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231010000 +0000" stop="20251231013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231013000 +0000" stop="20251231020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231020000 +0000" stop="20251231023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Frank Goes Downstairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After hurting themselves during a tryst, Ray and Debra lie about their injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231023000 +0000" stop="20251231030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Jealous Robert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray urges Debra and Marie to mind their own business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231030000 +0000" stop="20251231033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hold That Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The POWs smuggle a tiger tank, about which Klink has been boasting, into camp in order to photograph and study it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231033000 +0000" stop="20251231040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Of The Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stalag 13 is named one of the top 10 prison camps in Germany, but it's just a distraction for Hogan and his men to destroy a secret rocket bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231040000 +0000" stop="20251231043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Paul Sand</sub-title>
    <desc>In After the Wedding, Carol's husband becomes jealous when she kisses another man goodbye. Then, in Energy Crisis Blackouts, everyone's life is complicated when the electricity stops. Finally, in Wedding Plans, divorcees discuss their future wedding plans, only to discover they may still love their old spouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231043000 +0000" stop="20251231053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fan-dancer's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After witnessing an automobile accident, Mason comes to represent the driver of the vehicle, an exotic dancer charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231053500 +0000" stop="20251231060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Thing About Machines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer feels that the machines in his house are conspiring against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231060500 +0000" stop="20251231070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, George  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A motion picture star receives a surprising stopover from her ex-convict companion, whom she thought was dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231070500 +0000" stop="20251231080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Deadfall: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Intertect is accused of stealing plans and a formula to create a laser ray, forcing Mannix and Lew Wickersham into a deadly feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231080500 +0000" stop="20251231090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Stone Seahorse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A smuggler is attacked by mobsters interested in learning where he has hidden his booty. He escapes in Raymond Durstin's gallery. He turns to Cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231090500 +0000" stop="20251231100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fantasy Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of strange events lead the victim of a nervous-breakdown to the edge of a relapse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231100000 +0000" stop="20251231103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231103000 +0000" stop="20251231110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231110000 +0000" stop="20251231113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 1 -- The Impossible Mission</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy plans to resign at the end of shift due to the death of his previous partner but is assigned a rookie partner, Reed. Malloy decides the green Reed is worthy of his effort to train him, leading Malloy to stay on the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231113000 +0000" stop="20251231120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 141 -- The Color Tv Bandit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed learn of a serial home burglar stealing color TVs. They stumble upon the suspect's car with unusual results. Also, Reed must come to terms with his anger over a drug using mother that endangered her children to score dope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231120000 +0000" stop="20251231130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>2025 Rewind</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231130000 +0000" stop="20251231133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally The Lifeguard</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally is all set to begin his job as a lifeguard but is let down when he learns that had been a mistake and he's not old enough to fill the position, so instead he is hired to sell candy and hot dogs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231133000 +0000" stop="20251231140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Freckles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Clarence gets fed up with Beaver calling him Lumpy, he gives Beaver a new nickname, Freckles. This leads Beaver to become self-conscious about his freckles and takes steps to try to remove them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231140000 +0000" stop="20251231150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fickle Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph Duncan is a civil servant whose job is to inventory the estates of wealthy decedants. One day, he returns home with $153,000 worth of old greenbacks he discovered while going through a recently deceased old woman's home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231150000 +0000" stop="20251231160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Psychic  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend a psychic claiming to have had a premonition of a murder before it took place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231160000 +0000" stop="20251231170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Full Fathom Five</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rich widows from the mainland are turning up missing soon after visiting the Hawaiian Islands. McGarrett suspects that a single person or group is behind the disappearances. Thus, Five-O sends a policewoman undercover on a cruise as bait.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231170000 +0000" stop="20251231180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy goes on his first turkey hunt with his father and two of his friends</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231180000 +0000" stop="20251231190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>One Killer On Ice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Two bounty hunters talk Matt into protecting them and their prisoner from ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231190000 +0000" stop="20251231200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Blood Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The son of Luke Grayson wants revenge when he discovers that Ben Cartwright killed his father, even though it was in self-defense. Despite this, Ben and Hoss are determined to help the young man find a new life for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231200000 +0000" stop="20251231203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Rebecca Snipe is returning to North Fork after a long visit away. Upon her arrival, Mark is smitten with her and gets it in his head to play matchmaker between her and his pa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231203000 +0000" stop="20251231210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>New Orleans Menace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Tiffauges, a wealthy and sadistic Frenchman who is used to getting whatever he wants, decides he wishes to purchase the McCain Ranch. Tiffauges' lead man, Xavier, proclaims Lucas to be muy macho, and does not believe Lucas will give in so easily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231210000 +0000" stop="20251231220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Those Who Stay Behind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale is unable to take everybody on the next phase and has to turn down some of those applying. One is Ben Campbell, an ex-convict who is being hunted by his escaped former partner, who believes Ben turned him in to the law among others."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231220000 +0000" stop="20251231230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Propinquity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy spends the night at John's place while his house is being fumigated, which is one night too many. A woman is trapped inside a car while it burns around her; the ambulance carrying Roy and the victim is hit by a car. A man having a heart attack refuses to leave a poker game unless John agrees to play out the man's hand. An explosion at an abandoned refinery injures several workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231230000 +0000" stop="20251231233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Judgment: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The military police think they've solved a rash of thefts at the 4077th when they apprehend Klinger with Hawkeye's stolen camera.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251231233000 +0000" stop="20260101000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snappier Judgment: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. and Hawkeye resolve to clear Klinger's name after he chooses Winchester to defend him at his military court-martial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101000000 +0000" stop="20260101003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A War For All Seasons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>On New Year's Eve, the staff looks back on the highlights of 1951: The doctors invent an artificial kidney machine; Mulcahy plants a garden; Margaret takes up knitting; and Klinger and Winchester bet on which baseball team will win the pennant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101003000 +0000" stop="20260101010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret's birthday plans are spoiled when she and Klinger get stranded on a desolate roadside. Meanwhile, Charles gives a lecture for Margaret, and the surgeons assist in the delivery of a calf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101010000 +0000" stop="20260101013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101013000 +0000" stop="20260101020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101020000 +0000" stop="20260101023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>It's Supposed To Be Fun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is mortified when Geoff has trouble getting the hang of the game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101023000 +0000" stop="20260101030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Raybert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert meets a beautiful woman who is a big fan of Ray Barone's sports column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101030000 +0000" stop="20260101033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Inspector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting general upsets plans to blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101033000 +0000" stop="20260101040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flight Of The Valkyrie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Because of all the "funny business" going on, Klink brings in Colonel Crittendon to replace Hogan as officer in charge of POWs. His arrival louses up plans to help a German baroness escape to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101040000 +0000" stop="20260101043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest James Coco</sub-title>
    <desc>In Parkay Margarine, Carol fights with a container of margarine. Then, in One Way Ticket, a parody of "An Affair to Remember", a dying woman falls for a death-row inmate, and they plan to meet in Tijuana on New Year's Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101043000 +0000" stop="20260101053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Demure Defendant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Nadine Marshall lives with her Uncle Martin and Captain Hugo. She comes home excited one day with the news of her engagement to John Locke. When she tells her uncle, he shows her disquieting papers about her family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101053500 +0000" stop="20260101060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Howling Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man on a walking trip of post-World War I Europe gets caught in a storm. He takes shelter in a remote monastery and finds a mysterious prisoner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101060500 +0000" stop="20260101070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>How To Get Rid Of Your Wife  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A submissive gentleman and his shrewish wife put together separate plans to murder each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101070500 +0000" stop="20260101080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Deadfall: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is fired from Intertect while his boss suffers from a medically induced psychosis, causing Joe to use desperate measures to crack the case and save Wickersham's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101080500 +0000" stop="20260101090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer believes there's no other way out than putting the blame of a crime he committed on his sister, a retarded girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101090500 +0000" stop="20260101100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Doomed Alibi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An actor-turned-business frames his double for the murder of his partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101100000 +0000" stop="20260101103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101103000 +0000" stop="20260101110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101110000 +0000" stop="20260101113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 131 -- Reed, The Dicks Have Their Job And We Have Ours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy teaches raw rookie Reed about the job that detectives play when a murder scene must be secured and turned over. Reed learns to be content with his role and responsibilities in a uniformed radio car when they arrest fleeing fugitives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101113000 +0000" stop="20260101120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 11 -- It's Just A Little Dent, Isn't It?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed dents the fender of the patrol car while putting gas in it and frets the entire shift about the impact of it on his career. Meanwhile they deal with a man who wants revenge against a woman who testified against his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101120000 +0000" stop="20260101130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Palm Springs Paradise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill visit the retro resorts and other sites of the Coachella Valley."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101130000 +0000" stop="20260101133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Big Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Constantly entering contests, Beaver's latest one has him selling raffle tickets in hopes of winning a prize. Surprisingly, he does indeed win third prize and the prize is a $3,500 sports car. However, his dreams are dashed when Eddie's premonition comes true, Ward breaks the news that Beaver can't keep the car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101133000 +0000" stop="20260101140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Lander's Fiancee</sub-title>
    <desc>"While doing some yard work for Miss Landers, Beaver and Whitey witness their favorite teacher in the midst of a gentleman caller, which makes Beaver a bit jealous. However, Beaver gets sick to his stomach when he discovers Miss Landers is engaged to be married and the man he saw was her fiance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101140000 +0000" stop="20260101150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Waylaid Wolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Womanizing playboy Loring Lamont has his sights set on Arlene Ferris, his father's shapely secretary. He lures her to his beachfront bachelor pad with seduction on his mind. Arlene slaps the rotter and flees taking Loring's car back into town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101150000 +0000" stop="20260101160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thief: Part 1  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a rare coin dealer is charged with murdering a thieving employee, he hires Matlock to defend him. Tyler is less than thrilled when Matlock enlists the help of a female investigator, and has his own suspicions of her motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101160000 +0000" stop="20260101170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Strangers In Our Own Land</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating the assassination of a native Hawaiian official, McGarrett learns that some fellow Hawaiians resented the victim's pro-development policies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101170000 +0000" stop="20260101180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Typewriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy borrows an antique typewriter from the Baldwin sisters so he can submit a proper manuscript to a magazine</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101180000 +0000" stop="20260101190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chief Joseph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A desperately ill chief causes tension when he lodges in the Dodge House.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101190000 +0000" stop="20260101200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss finds himself falling in love with widow Helen Layton and intends to marry her, unaware of her true nature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101200000 +0000" stop="20260101203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Apprentice Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Willard is filling in as temporary marshal while Micah is away. Some Texas cowhands are in North Fork looking for some fun and relaxation, but Dan keeps coming down hard on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101203000 +0000" stop="20260101210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark, returning from selling their herd, share the stagecoach trip with a Marshal and his prisoner, Johnny Cotton. Johnny's gang arrives to free their partner and steal the contents of the stage's strongbox, as well as Lucas' money and rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101210000 +0000" stop="20260101220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Nancy Styles Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"Spoiled Nancy Styles, claiming to be the daughter of the owner of the company that owns the wagon train, is determined to get to Denver by forcing her way onto it and then Hale makes it clear he plans to bypass the city due to early snow."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101220000 +0000" stop="20260101230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inventions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen enter a contest to invent new firefighting tools. The paramedics handle victims of possible radiation poisoning. A comatose man is suffering from a mysterious ailment. A woman’s overweight son is wedged in her living room ceiling. The firemen respond to a leak at a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101230000 +0000" stop="20260101233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood And Guts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is outraged when a sensationalistic war correspondent, Clayton Kibbee, reports irresponsible G.I. stunts as tales of military valor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260101233000 +0000" stop="20260102000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Holy Mess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An AWOL soldier, Nick Gillis, seeks sanctuary in the mess tent, after Father Mulcahy's service. At the same time, a special Sunday brunch is due to be served, following the donation of some eggs to the camp by a grateful farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102000000 +0000" stop="20260102003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth Shall Set You Free</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles has a serious toothache, but hates the thought of having anything done about it. The doctors suspect prejudice when an inordinate number of black casualties are brought in from a single unit, led by Major Weems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102003000 +0000" stop="20260102010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Points</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter sends for Sidney Freedman when he loses confidence in his surgical abilities, and Winchester loses patience with his bunkmates' sloppiness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102010000 +0000" stop="20260102013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102013000 +0000" stop="20260102020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102020000 +0000" stop="20260102023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Kicker, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank catches a football from a record setting field goal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102023000 +0000" stop="20260102030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Tissues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra agrees to let Ray be more involved in the daily decision making.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102030000 +0000" stop="20260102033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>German Bridge Is Falling Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The heroes plan to blow up a bridge near camp when a bomber raid fails.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102033000 +0000" stop="20260102040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Movies Are Your Best Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must discover what is contained within the documents of a visiting German general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102040000 +0000" stop="20260102043000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Season 2, Episode 21</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Tim Conway breaks up Harvey in one of the series' all-time funniest sketches: "The Dentist." Also: jealous understudy Carol looks to steal the show from a Broadway star (guest Ethel Merman.)"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102043000 +0000" stop="20260102053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sun Bather's Diary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Arlene Dowling reports the theft of all her belongings, including a diary detailing a bank heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102053500 +0000" stop="20260102060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Eye Of The Beholder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A bandaged young woman awaits the outcome of an experimental treatment that has been administered to her in a last-ditch effort to make her appear normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102060500 +0000" stop="20260102070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wives Too Many  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Marion Brown takes radical action when she learns that her spouse has three wives too many.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102070500 +0000" stop="20260102080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>You Can Get Killed Out There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix's attempt to locate a stolen necklace leads him to a case of murder and fraud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102080500 +0000" stop="20260102090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A writer was murdered. His latest book would deal with the biography of an industrialist. Cannon must protect the co-author and investigate the activities of the industrialist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102090500 +0000" stop="20260102100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadlier Species, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer is killed when he finds out who's been swindling women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102100000 +0000" stop="20260102103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102103000 +0000" stop="20260102110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102110000 +0000" stop="20260102113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 91 -- You're Not The First Guy's Had The Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's ability to focus on his job is put to the test when his close friend and fellow academy partner is critically wounded during a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102113000 +0000" stop="20260102120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 161 -- And You Want Me To Get Married!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After an evening at Jim's with his wife, Pete's girlfriend, Donna, is making marriage comments that has Pete running for cover. Mixed in with their calls is a domestic noise complaint Pete uses to support his bachelorhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102120000 +0000" stop="20260102130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Stuntman Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102130000 +0000" stop="20260102133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Double Cross</sub-title>
    <desc>"Eddie crawls through the Cleaver house spreading the news that he's going steady with Caroline Schuster, something that worries June who doesn't want Wally to get any ideas about going steady. However, Wally has other worries when he overhears Caroline saying that she's only using Eddie while her boyfriend is grounded. Leaving Wally with the decision to tell Eddie or not."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102133000 +0000" stop="20260102140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's I.q.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After learning that he's going to be taking an I.Q. test, Beaver hits the books, scared after his friends tell him that if he doesn't pass he will be sent to "dumb school."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102140000 +0000" stop="20260102150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wintry Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Inventor Walter Randall wants a divorce from his cold-blooded wife, Laura, in order to be with Phyllis Hudson. Laura decides to get back at Walter by blackmailing one of his assistants into building a bomb that will destroy Walter's underwater sounding invention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102150000 +0000" stop="20260102160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Thief, The (part 2)  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock and Tyler realise that part of Linda's deception is routed in the recent kidnapping of her son. While Tyler helps her locate the child, Matlock finds the rare coin he needs to put the finish on the case."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102160000 +0000" stop="20260102170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Tiger By The Tail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A struggling young singer plans his own kidnapping as a publicity stunt. After his unsuspecting wealthy father offers to pay any amount of money, the singer's associates turn on him in an attempt to get the ransom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102170000 +0000" stop="20260102180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A meteorite crashes through the roof of the Baldwin sisters' "Recipe"" room</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102180000 +0000" stop="20260102190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Circus Trick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus' girlfriend joins a circus troupe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102190000 +0000" stop="20260102200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman shows up to the Ponderosa claiming to have just married Ben. The problem is, Ben has never seen her before in his life!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102200000 +0000" stop="20260102203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Young Englishman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas gets in trouble when he accuses the foreman of a neighboring ranch of rustling some of his cattle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102203000 +0000" stop="20260102210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gaucho</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Rumson, without even saying to whom he had sold his property, left the bill of sale with the bank and moved away from North Fork. Curge, who's highest offer was upped by $1,000, is upset because Rumson sold out to a "peppergut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102210000 +0000" stop="20260102220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Richard Bloodgood Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"A blind man called Sangre has joined the wagon train along with his guide. He is actually Coop's boyhood blood brother Richard Bloodgood, and he openly states his plan to kill Coop. Coop gets very hostile and refuses to discuss it whenever Charlie or Barnaby ask the reason Richard wants to kill him, but they know it has to do with the death of a beautiful woman long ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102220000 +0000" stop="20260102230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Screenwriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A screenwriter spends a day observing Squad 51 at work, including a motorcycle accident, a worker suffering from exposure to chemicals, the delivery of a baby and a fire at a toy factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102230000 +0000" stop="20260102233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's A Will, There's A War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye goes to help at an aid station, and under heavy shelling he draws up a will, leaving various items to his friends at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260102233000 +0000" stop="20260103000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Promotion Commotion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester, Pierce and Hunnicutt find themselves in the sticky position of having to decide which enlisted men to recommend for promotion. For Winchester it could be a matter of life and death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103000000 +0000" stop="20260103003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heroes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is the golden boy of the world press when he treats a celebrity prizefighter, "Gentleman" Joe Cavanaugh, who has a stroke at the 4077th. Father Mulcahy finds the news hard to take, as Cavanaugh was a hero of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103003000 +0000" stop="20260103010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sons And Bowlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing to the Marines once again, Colonel Potter wishes there was one sport the 4077th were any good at. When Klinger mentions he can bowl, the Colonel decides to have a bowling competition. Unfortunately, he and Klinger are the only two good bowlers in the camp, so BJ and Father Mulcahy are "recruited" to the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103010000 +0000" stop="20260103013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103013000 +0000" stop="20260103020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103020000 +0000" stop="20260103023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Snow Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie reveals her true feelings for Debra.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103023000 +0000" stop="20260103030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Cookies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray's parents' house is targeted by Troup Leader Peggy and her daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103030000 +0000" stop="20260103033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Go Light On The Heavy Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a heavy water supply by convincing Klink it is a youth potion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103033000 +0000" stop="20260103040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103040000 +0000" stop="20260103043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Carl Reiner</sub-title>
    <desc>In Accident Prone, an accident prone Carol tries to get insurance before she's hurt. Then, in Funny Lady, a comedian can't stop cracking jokes in her marriage counseling session. Finally, in Supermarket Checker, Carol plays a slow, obnoxious checker, determined to embarrass Harvey who's on a date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103043000 +0000" stop="20260103053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cautious Coquette</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason navigate his way through a hornet's nest of murder, hit-and-run, secret marriage and a missing witness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103053500 +0000" stop="20260103060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nick Of Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A superstitious newlywed becomes obsessed by a penny fortune-telling machine when he and his new wife are stranded with car trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103060500 +0000" stop="20260103070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Magic Shop  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A little boy vanishes in a magic shop, only to reappear later with supernatural powers and evil intentions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103070500 +0000" stop="20260103080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Another Final Exit (aka The Box)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bernie Farmer is mistaken as being responsible for a missing million dollars used as bait in a drug ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103080500 +0000" stop="20260103090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103090500 +0000" stop="20260103100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Poisoned Pigeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of con artists murder a victim who's found them out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260103100000 +0000" stop="20260103103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Spur Line To Shady Rest: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The C&amp;W Railroad sends a troubleshooter, Homer Bedloe, to Hooterville to see why the main line and the branch line do not connect to each other.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
