<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210070500 +0000" stop="20241210080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to uncover the past life of an amnesia victim who is a Vietnam veteran.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210080500 +0000" stop="20241210090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Stone Cold Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The reopening of the cold case of a salesgirl reveals that a bicycle she sold may be a clue to her death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210090500 +0000" stop="20241210100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Nest Of Scorpions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. goes to a mountain resort to find real estate developer who's gone missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210100000 +0000" stop="20241210103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Mental Patient</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>An escapee from a mental hospital is the primary suspect in the violent death of a farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210103000 +0000" stop="20241210110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210110000 +0000" stop="20241210113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Taking It Easy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed gets stuck manning the front desk after spraining his wrist, where he must deal with a caller who claims to have planted a bomb at the station, a young man who wants to file a claim of police brutality and an elderly man who walks in with a shotgun. Meanwhile, Malloy is assigned a partner who is a first-day rookie, and they deal with three young children from Oklahoma who are abandoned by their mother, and engage in a high-speed pursuit that ends in a most unexpected way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210113000 +0000" stop="20241210120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Krash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's brand new car gets dinged up when he has to bail out to chase down a purse snatcher, but Sgt. MacDonald promises him his kid brother in Beverly Hills can fix it on the cheap. Out on patrol, he and Reed search for a drunk man accused of randomly shooting arrows, respond to a robbery at a deli that results in tragedy and search for a drug store robbery suspect who gets away after being shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210120000 +0000" stop="20241210130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Historic Feuds</sub-title>
    <desc>"From royal rule to fictional families, Bill and Toony tackle legendary rivalries!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210130000 +0000" stop="20241210133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's English Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been having trouble in English and Ward persuades Wally to tutor him. Wally has Beaver look over an old exam that he once took. To Beaver's surprise, the next day his teacher gives him the exact same test, which, of course, he aces. However, Beaver is left with a guilty conscience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210133000 +0000" stop="20241210140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Chauffeur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally plans on going to a big dance with Evelyn Boothby and they plan on getting there cramped with six other people in Lumpy's car. When June and Ward refuse to allow that, Wally and Evelyn must find another way to get there. However, what Evelyn has in mind doesn't go over well with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210140000 +0000" stop="20241210150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Loquacious Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lester Martin's life takes a horrible turn for the worse when a man breaks into his apartment, forces him at gun-point to drink half a bottle of Scotch and then drives him into the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210150000 +0000" stop="20241210160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer: Part 2  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Sam Chandler is found murdered, his lawyer, David O'Malley, is the prime suspect—in part because Sam was sleeping with David's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210160000 +0000" stop="20241210170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>When The Music Stopped</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Singer Eddie Larran returns to Sparta for a concert, but not everyone is a fan. An angry man insists that Eddie owes him money. And their dispute soon ends in violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210170000 +0000" stop="20241210180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Tailspin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob finds out he is not eligible to fly in the Air Corps due to bad vision</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210180000 +0000" stop="20241210190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Man's Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Phoebe nurses a wounded man with amnesia back to health. But with his memory returning it could lead to even more danger for the confused man and heartache for the lonely Phoebe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210190000 +0000" stop="20241210200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lila Conrad Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe finds a saloon girl named Lila Conrad in the back of a wagon. Trouble is, she seems to be wanted—for murder. Joe wants to get her back to Virginia City for a fair trial, but it seems that other people have different plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210200000 +0000" stop="20241210203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210203000 +0000" stop="20241210210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210210000 +0000" stop="20241210220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clementine Jones Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>"Clementine Jones is in the process of being thrown out of a town when a bank robbery occurs. She ends up joining the Hale wagon train on a wagon with one of the bank robbers using it to escape who she was in love with in the past."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210220000 +0000" stop="20241210230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Computer Error</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young couple is rescued from a car wreck; the boy has a spinal cord injury and Dr. Early suspects the girl is pregnant. Roy and John rescue a woman trapped at the bottom of a well and an amateur magician from a safe. A rescue at a junkyard fire turns hazardous when phosphorus materials explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210230000 +0000" stop="20241210233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241210233000 +0000" stop="20241211000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211000000 +0000" stop="20241211003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211003000 +0000" stop="20241211010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211010000 +0000" stop="20241211013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A grumpy Andy agrees to take a few days off and heads up to the lake to relax. Barney and Gomer are in charge, and manage to capture (and lose) an escaped convict who hides in the same woods where Andy just happens to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211013000 +0000" stop="20241211020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is convinced that Andy saved his life by putting out a small fire at the filling station. He then begins to repay Andy by becoming his servant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211020000 +0000" stop="20241211023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Annul That Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Gloria get married, everyone but the two of them want the marriage annulled. Gloria decides she’d like to experience what her new life will be like, and Jed tells her that he’ll show her. When he calls the mansion to tell them to put up the cabin, Granny thinks he got married as well. But when both “couples” come home, Granny, Jethro, and Elly learn that Shorty got married, but Elverna didn’t, and Gloria got married, but Jed didn’t, making Jethro and Granny believe both couples are in a Hollywood marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211023000 +0000" stop="20241211030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Spring Festival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone in Hooterville, except Oliver, is overcome with spring fever; even Sam Drucker is wearing his spring toupee. Deciding to revive the Hooterville spring festival, Lisa visits the neighbors to drum up support. Meanwhile, Oliver tries to do his planting with Eb who can't understand how to work the automatic planter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211030000 +0000" stop="20241211033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211033000 +0000" stop="20241211040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211040000 +0000" stop="20241211043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Barby And Ben / Rancid Harvest</sub-title>
    <desc>In Barby and Ben, a toy couple's marriage is threatened by the arrival of a G.I. doll. Then, in Rancid and Harvest, a parody of "Random Harvest", with Carol as Greer Garson, a woman who falls for a man with no memory of his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211043000 +0000" stop="20241211053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Moth-eaten Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Restaurateur Morey Allen, a friend of Mason and Della's, contacts Mason after his waitress, Dixie Dayton, is struck by a car while fleeing the restaurant after spotting a man stalking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211053500 +0000" stop="20241211060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flight 33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial aircraft mysteriously travels back through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211060500 +0000" stop="20241211063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A housewife buys a stolen mink for $400.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211063500 +0000" stop="20241211070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Decoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Gil is in love with a married singer who wants to kill her abusive husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211070500 +0000" stop="20241211080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Upside Down Penny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix works a case involving a child's missing stamp album. It appears as though someone is more than willing to kill for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211080500 +0000" stop="20241211090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Death Is A Double Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired to be a bodyguard for the daughter of a broker and his grandchildren, but is drawn in when the broker reveals that he believes his son in law is involved in a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211090500 +0000" stop="20241211100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A millionaire hires Barnaby to rescue his son from kidnappers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211100000 +0000" stop="20241211103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>License Plates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews pursues a recidivist thief with a tip from a young boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211103000 +0000" stop="20241211110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211110000 +0000" stop="20241211113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Routine Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by responding to a call of a drunken woman threatening the patrons of a bar with a handgun. Afterwards, they search for a group of four carjackers who go on a robbery spree after targeting a man with a cache of guns in his trunk, and investigate the suspicious death of a mentally disabled man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211113000 +0000" stop="20241211120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed returns from vacation with a full-body sunburn, making for a miserable work day. Out on patrol, he and Malloy respond to a fiery traffic accident, use an informant's tip to track down a drug dealer, search for an armed robbery suspect based on a vehicle description and attempt to rescue two boys after their rowboat capsizes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211120000 +0000" stop="20241211130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony embrace the extraordinariness of Nevada, from the glitz and glam of Vegas to alien encounters."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211130000 +0000" stop="20241211133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's First Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A party is being thrown at the dancing school where Beaver and Wally once took lessons and they're both invited. This prompts Beaver to ask one particular girl who caught his eye, Betsy Patterson, if he could escort her to the dance. However, once at the dance, he finds that Betsy has promised other boys that she would dance with them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211133000 +0000" stop="20241211140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Golf Clubs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>During a particularly awful golf game, Ward happens to break his driver and decides it's not worth repairing it, so he just puts it in the closet. Later, Gilbert talks Beaver into hitting around some golf balls with Ward's clubs and one hit with the broken driver has Beaver thinking he broke it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211140000 +0000" stop="20241211150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Red Riding Boots</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ann Farwell is miserable over the separation of her parents. Things aren't made any better when her father starts seeing Rita Conover, a scheming woman half his age. When Rita turns up dead both Ann and her mother think the other committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211150000 +0000" stop="20241211160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Scrooge  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a scrooge of a store owner is accused of murdering his partner, Matlock defends the man and makes a strange request as part of his fee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211160000 +0000" stop="20241211170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Blessings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In this Christmas episode the officers share memories with a reporter from the Sparta Herald.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211170000 +0000" stop="20241211180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Founder's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The town prepares for a Founder's Day Celebration</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211180000 +0000" stop="20241211190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Alias Festus Haggen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus is mistaken for a killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211190000 +0000" stop="20241211200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ponderosa Matador</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam, Hoss, and Joe vie for the attention of a pretty young lady named Dolores. Hoss talks Joe into entering a bull fight, but it doesn't work out quite as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211200000 +0000" stop="20241211203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211203000 +0000" stop="20241211210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211210000 +0000" stop="20241211220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jenna Douglas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jenna Douglas is found by scouts for the wagon train. She appears to have been a victim of a scavenger attack and is adopted by the train. As time goes on people on the train begin to have doubts about her story and her mental state."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211220000 +0000" stop="20241211230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy are disappointed when they are the only squad not called to a major brushfire. Dixie gets her hand caught in a vending machine. A lawyer collapses in the courtroom with an apparent heart attack. Roy and John finally make it to the brushfire and become trapped while rescuing another firefighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211230000 +0000" stop="20241211233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241211233000 +0000" stop="20241212000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212000000 +0000" stop="20241212003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212003000 +0000" stop="20241212010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212010000 +0000" stop="20241212013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bargain Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, in a flurry of cost-cutting measures, saves money on beef by buying a whole side of it. Unfortunately, this happens at the same time her freezer breaks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212013000 +0000" stop="20241212020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Divorce, Mountain Style</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy finds himself embroiled in a strange backwoods divorce ritual, ending up as the object of Charlene Darling's affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212020000 +0000" stop="20241212023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Honest John Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro comes home to tell Jed that he saw Honest John, but never caught up to him. Meanwhile, Honest John tells his wife he's turned straight, but she gets mad and threatens him. She wants him to con the wealthy Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212023000 +0000" stop="20241212030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Our Son, The Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb's latest career choice is that of a barber. He talks Oliver into paying his tuition to MIT, a mail-order barber college. Eb's sent a dummy head and hair to practice on and receives his grades by mailing the trimmed toupees back to the school. Lisa is excited about Eb's education while Oliver is irritated by all the hidden costs he keeps being asked to pay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212030000 +0000" stop="20241212033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212033000 +0000" stop="20241212040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gamble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must prevent the Germans from getting ahold of a secret device that was aboard a plane shot down near camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212040000 +0000" stop="20241212043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In George and Zelda, a disguised Carol and Harvey complain to the audience before the show. Then, in The Spy, a WWII bomber pilot jumps without a parachute. Finally, in The Ham Actor, a TV debut for an acting duo goes horribly wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212043000 +0000" stop="20241212053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Baited Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert Dawson confronts Albert Tydings, his partner, about $80,000 missing from Carol Stanley's trust account. Tydings admits he embezzled the money and blackmails Dawson into keeping quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212053500 +0000" stop="20241212060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Dingle, The Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Martians give Luther Dingle the strength of 300 men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212060500 +0000" stop="20241212063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Momentum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>A man ends up running to the Mexican border after trying to collect money his employer owes him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212063500 +0000" stop="20241212070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Wet Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A vulnerable man is pinned with a murder he did not commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212070500 +0000" stop="20241212080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>One Step To Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to protect the granddaughter of an exiled mobster. It seems as though she's being stalked by hoods who want to get to her grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212080500 +0000" stop="20241212090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An accountant wants to teach the world a lesson about the production of a deadly nerve gas when he steals a can of the substance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212090500 +0000" stop="20241212100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Frame For Murder, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. attempts to save his reputation when he's framed for rape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212100000 +0000" stop="20241212103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hitchhiker Dies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A hitchhiker implicates a man who gave him a ride.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212103000 +0000" stop="20241212110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212110000 +0000" stop="20241212113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program to help ground based officers better understand the abilities and limitations of helicopter assistance, malloy and reed are selected to be observers on several air support division missions. This morning's missions include a sea</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212113000 +0000" stop="20241212120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Skywatch: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed take flight in separate helicopters to provide assistance in the search of a light plane stolen from the los angeles airport by a distraught man. Afterwards, they search for a group of robbery suspects who flee in separate cars, then reed</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212120000 +0000" stop="20241212130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1951</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony journey back to the nifty year of 1951."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212130000 +0000" stop="20241212133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Farewell To Penny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Penny learns that she will be moving away and Beaver deals with mixed feelings for the girl with whom he shares a mutual dislike. However, after a farewell party at school, Beaver and Penny openly show their true feelings for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212133000 +0000" stop="20241212140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver is cast as a rabbit for a school play and June has his costume all ready, complete with floppy ears and puffy tail. On the night of the play, Beaver needs to be at the school early and gets a ride with Lumpy and Wally in full costume, however, Lumpy's car breaks down and Beaver must walk the few blocks to the school to get there in time."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212140000 +0000" stop="20241212150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Larcenous Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A mayor's political career is jeopardized when his conniving wife goes too far.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212150000 +0000" stop="20241212160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The D.a.  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Julie becomes the target of a witness with psychological problems, leaving Matlock and Conrad to learn who is threatening her, and why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212160000 +0000" stop="20241212170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Flowers From A Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A city councilwoman becomes dangerously obsessed with Bubba.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212170000 +0000" stop="20241212180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Home Front - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John has been appointed to the local draft board</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212180000 +0000" stop="20241212190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The River: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt is tracked, with bad intent, along a river gorge by a gang of villains while in custody of one of the gang and $24,000 of their money. Escaping the gang by jumping into the river, Matt is rescued by two kids on a raft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212190000 +0000" stop="20241212200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>My Son, My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben's plans to wed widow Katherine Saunders are jeopardized after her son is accused of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212200000 +0000" stop="20241212203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart arrives in North Fork in search of renegade indians suspected of the brutal killing of a Texas Ranger and his family. The townspeople are suspicious of him, however, when they discover that he, too, is an indian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212203000 +0000" stop="20241212210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarding House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Reformed card shark Julia Massini now runs a respectable boarding house in North Fork, but Sid Fallon is threatening to reveal her sordid past unless she lets him turn the establishment into a saloon and gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212210000 +0000" stop="20241212220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Artie Matthewson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke finds Flint's dying foster mother who asks Flint to check on her real son Artie who she hasn't seen in five years and has a reputation for getting into trouble with the law. Flint finds him on the right side of the law - or is he?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212220000 +0000" stop="20241212230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Messin' Around</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Chet starts a series of practical jokes against John, who eventually retaliates. A child is trapped in a burning tree house. A retiree pretends to be ill so he can amuse the children in the emergency department. A woman feeds her sick husband dieffenbachia sap to keep him quiet. At a trash fire, a gas station worker shows signs of a perforated ulcer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212230000 +0000" stop="20241212233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As You Were</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While there are no casualties, Hawkeye and Trapper crate up Frank while he sleeps and receive gorilla suits through the mail. Henry gets a tan and gives another sex orientation lecture. When the wounded start pouring in again, their own side shells the camp, hitting the generator, and Radar tries to get through to tell someone to stop the shelling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241212233000 +0000" stop="20241213000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The supply lines to the camp are cut. Radar, the housing officer, starts doubling people up to save fuel and Klinger is thrown out of the nurse's tent. People start burning everything to stay warm while Frank wears his heated socks. The toilet paper supply is worst hit, and then wounded start arriving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213000000 +0000" stop="20241213003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Burns tries to slap a dishonorable discharge on a decorated soldier who admits to being a homosexual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213003000 +0000" stop="20241213010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a new batch of mail leaves Trapper depressed, and thinking of desertion, despite Hawkeye's efforts to dissuade him. Meanwhile, Hawkeye learns that he has successfully tricked Frank into buying stocks in a fictitious company, Pioneer Aviation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213010000 +0000" stop="20241213013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Deal Is A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>In their efforts to win a pony, Opie and his friends become involved in a scam that has them shilling a useless miracle salve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213013000 +0000" stop="20241213020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are working late at the courthouse when they get a visit from two wild women. Out of pure kindness, they drive the "fun girls" home, but don't know that Helen and Thelma Lou saw them with the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213020000 +0000" stop="20241213023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Honesty Is The Best Policy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While the Clampetts are talking about Honest John and why he didn't accept the money, Shifty and his wife are talking about why Shifty gave it back. They decide to work as a team, with Flo posing as John's Spanish mom. Flo is worried that they'll spot her and realize she is not at all Spanish.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213023000 +0000" stop="20241213030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Oliver's Jaded Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lisa's long-awaited vacation to New York is not what she'd hoped for. She's none too thrilled hearing about Oliver's womanizing playboy days or all the wild parties they're invited to. When Oliver's offered a job with his old law firm, he's the Douglas who's tempted by the excitement of city life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213030000 +0000" stop="20241213033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Defector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must get a defecting field marshal to England, whom Hochstetter has followed to Stalag 13.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213033000 +0000" stop="20241213040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Parachute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets the Germans to look for an allied agent by planting an opened parachute in camp. This gives him the opportunity to get at the briefcase that was handcuffed to a courier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213040000 +0000" stop="20241213043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Charo</sub-title>
    <desc>In Uni-Sex Salon, a hairdressing Carol drives Tim up the wall. Then, in Boring Speech, a member of the Garden Club can't stay awake for their meeting. Finally, in Interview with Chiquita, Tim interviews Charo and meets her equally feisty mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213043000 +0000" stop="20241213053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fan-dancer's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After witnessing an automobile accident, Mason comes to represent the driver of the vehicle, an exotic dancer charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213053500 +0000" stop="20241213060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Static</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An old radio returns a bitter bachelor to happier times when it starts picking up programs from the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213060500 +0000" stop="20241213063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Fog Closing In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hears strange noises in her house while her husband is away on business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213063500 +0000" stop="20241213070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>De Mortius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An old college professor decides to take action when he finds out that his wife cheated on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213070500 +0000" stop="20241213080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harvest Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When two crop-dusting pilots disappear, Mannix is hired to find them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213080500 +0000" stop="20241213090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flight Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A political refugee gets a unwilling helping hand from Frank when he creates a change of identity to help flee the country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213090500 +0000" stop="20241213100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man returns from prison and learns that his partner in a ten-year-old kidnapping never gave back the abducted child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213100000 +0000" stop="20241213103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Blast Area Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunman and his female hostage unwittingly wander into a designated blasting area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213103000 +0000" stop="20241213110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213110000 +0000" stop="20241213113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>L.a. International</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed barely get acquainted with their fill-in assignment at LAX when a security camera spots a car being stolen from a parking structure. While on foot-beat as Zebra-12 inside the airport, they find a surprise inside of a stolen suitcase, deal with a man who picks the pocket of a returning soldier, chase down a man buying airline tickets with stolen credit cards, escort a runaway boy back to his mother and track down a suspect who robbed a parking structure attendant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213113000 +0000" stop="20241213120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clinic On 18th St</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Abe Strayhorn and his assistants from the major fraud and consumer protection division of the Los Angeles District Attorney's Office launch an investigation into a local doctor following the death of one of his patients, who was found wearing a strange belt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213120000 +0000" stop="20241213130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Moms &amp; Dads</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate the best moms and dads from classic TV."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213130000 +0000" stop="20241213133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Electric Trains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>June runs across Beaver's old electric trains while cleaning and because he hasn't played with them in years, finds someone who will take them, with Beaver's consent. However, Beaver quickly re-discovers the fun of playing with the trains and wants to withdraw from the arrangement, even though the new owners-to-be are expecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213133000 +0000" stop="20241213140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Richard has just gotten, as Beaver describes it, a "keen" new jacket and this prompts Beaver to ask his parents for one exactly like it. June and Ward are hesitant after learning the price but decide to give in. However, when Richard loses his jacket, he coerces Beaver into a plot to trick his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213140000 +0000" stop="20241213150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Envious Editor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Slimy publishing tycoon Donald Fletcher buys controlling interest in a respectable but financially troubled publishing house. Fletcher turns things upside down by turning the publications into scandal sheets featuring photographs of scantily clad women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213150000 +0000" stop="20241213160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Blackmailer  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Cartoonist Ron Winfield has been keeping Atlanta enthralled with his recent storyline involving a Senator's affair. But just before the woman in the affair is named in print, the strips disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213160000 +0000" stop="20241213170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Private Sessions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Virgil's classmates from law school is arrested following the death of his former girlfriend, but the man insists that her death was the result of her relationship with her psychiatrist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213170000 +0000" stop="20241213180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Home Front - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The family members all seem involved in the war effort</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213180000 +0000" stop="20241213190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The River: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt is tracked, with bad intent, along a river gorge by a gang of villains while in custody of one of the gang and $24,000 of their money. Escaping the gang by jumping into the river, Matt is rescued by two kids on a raft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213190000 +0000" stop="20241213200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Alias Joe Cartwright</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who looks similar to Joe uses his name, which eventually lands Joe in front of a firing squad.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213200000 +0000" stop="20241213203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas puts his life in jeopardy when he agrees to testify in a murder case involving a witness killed before he could testify and a killer still at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213203000 +0000" stop="20241213210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw Sam Morley falls in love with a young woman who has a serious illness. He asks Lucas to turn him in for the reward and then use the money to pay for her medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213210000 +0000" stop="20241213220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Bruce Saybrook Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>"Lord Bruce Saybrook, London millionaire, takes his brother, wife and employee out west on a hunting trip hoping to repair his relationships. They run into hostile Indians. During the ensuing battle, everyone's the true character comes out."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213220000 +0000" stop="20241213230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is injured when his chimney explodes. A brash young intern at Rampart thinks he knows more than the paramedics and makes a near-fatal diagnosis of a heart patient; Dr. Brackett send him on a ride-along with Squad 51. A girl gets her hand stuck in a mailbox. Johnny and Roy must rescue a heart attack victim trapped on an oil refinery tower in the midst of an explosive fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213230000 +0000" stop="20241213233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Smattering Of Intelligence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A classic episode in which Colonel Flagg and another secret agent from another intelligence agency come to the 4077th to keep their eyes on the camp. Hawkeye and Trapper trick them both into thinking that Burns is a traitor—one thinks he's a fascist, the other thinks he's a communist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241213233000 +0000" stop="20241214000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General Flipped At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The MASH 4077th is visted by General Steele. He wishes to move the camp five miles down the road. Hawkeye and Henry are charged with mutiny. And Hawkeye also is charged with impersonating a reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214000000 +0000" stop="20241214003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rainbow Bridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>As Hawkeye and Trapper are planning to leave for Tokyo, an unusual offer to swap POW patients between the Chinese and the 4077th comes in. Henry, after much debate, agrees to send Hawkeye, Trapper, Frank, Radar and Klinger into enemy territory. Frank almost botches the swap when he brings a squirt gun to the exchange. Fortunately, the Chinese Dr. Lin Tam has a sense of humor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214003000 +0000" stop="20241214010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officer Of The Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Henry is away in Seoul, Burns and Houlihan are in charge, and Hawkeye is the officer of the day. His refusal to release a wounded Korean soldier, wanted by US Intelligence, leads to a confrontation with Colonel Flagg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214010000 +0000" stop="20241214013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Malcolm Merriweather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets upset when Malcolm Merriweather returns to Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214013000 +0000" stop="20241214020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney sees Andy kissing Helen in a jewelry store, he gets the idea that they are engaged. So he starts planning an engagement party and gets the whole town involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214020000 +0000" stop="20241214023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Pollution Solution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale is trying to get his money back, while Jed is trying to prevent him from doing so. And Jethro is trying to come up with a way to beat the smog problem. Drysdale sends Jane over to get the money, posing as a guard. When Jed doesn't give it to him, Drysdale tells him what he's got is a drop in the bucket, and only the President could really do anything. Jed returns the money and says he plans to give all his money to the President.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214023000 +0000" stop="20241214030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Hungarian Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>The man who saved the life of Lisa's uncle moves in on the Douglases seeking repayment for his good deed. Lisa feels an obligation to help Lazlo, but Oliver is simply irritated by his constant money-grubbing. Oliver's also unfazed by Lazlo's threats to cast a Hungarian curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214030000 +0000" stop="20241214033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Antique</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to open an antiques business selling "rare" cuckoo clocks, a business venture that is actually a ruse enabling the POWs to smuggle information out in the timepieces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214033000 +0000" stop="20241214040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214040000 +0000" stop="20241214043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Helen Reddy And John Byner</sub-title>
    <desc>In Nora Desmond, Carol plays a has-been actress, who's so sure she's dying, she plans a death scene. Then, in Rona Rumor, a Hollywood gossip columnist ruins a happy marriage by twisting their words. Finally, in TV Commercials, the gang parodies classic TV commercials, including Shaving, Dirt Around the Collar, Sludge, Improper Margarine, Left-Guard Deodorant, Minnie Made Orange Juice, and Ritalls Dry Control.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214043000 +0000" stop="20241214053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Demure Defendant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Nadine Marshall lives with her Uncle Martin and Captain Hugo. She comes home excited one day with the news of her engagement to John Locke. When she tells her uncle, he shows her disquieting papers about her family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214053500 +0000" stop="20241214060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Mover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man discovers that his business partner has the ability to control objects with his mind, the pair head to Vegas to win big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214060500 +0000" stop="20241214063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Kill With Kindness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Fitz Oldham plans to torch his home and fake his death to collect insurance money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214063500 +0000" stop="20241214070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>None Are So Blind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Seymour Johnson disguises himself before killing his wealthy aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214070500 +0000" stop="20241214080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Puzzle For One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a fellow private eye assumes room temperature, Mannix investigates his death and tries to solve the deceased's final case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214080500 +0000" stop="20241214090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Playground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A former motorcycle officer who was disabled when a thief tried to steal the payroll from an armored car, seeks Frank's help for the purpose of exacting his revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214090500 +0000" stop="20241214100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R.'s old flame asks him to protect her from her desperate ex-husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214100000 +0000" stop="20241214103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Ring-a-ding-ding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo and Steve swear never to remove their wedding rings, but the next day she accidentally drops hers down the drain of the kitchen sink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214103000 +0000" stop="20241214110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Mr. Chimp</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe tries to get rid of the pet chimp who is gradually wrecking the Shady Rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214110000 +0000" stop="20241214113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Play The Rams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro gets a date with the Drydales’ new maid, Linda, but she is only interested in the fact that he has a color television set. Instead of paying attention to Jethro, she watches a football game the first night and an ice hockey game the next. Jethro attempts trying out the games, but isn’t very successful at football and doesn’t like the hockey gear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214113000 +0000" stop="20241214120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship Of Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny tries to conjure a man for Elly May, but accidentally attracts Miss Jane's man, who is actually a hired escort Mr. Drysdale got for Elly. When the Clampetts find out, they work to get rid of him so Miss Jane can have her man back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214120000 +0000" stop="20241214123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Seasin’s Greetinks!, I-ski Love-ski You-ski, Be Kind To “aminals”, Lunch With A Punch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Olive Oyl go ice skating and all is well until Bluto arrives., Popeye and Olive Oyl, trying to climb a high snow-covered mountain, are thwarted at every turn by the villainous Bluto., Popeye and Olive see Bluto driving a wagon hitting his weak-looking horse because he cannot pull the wagon., Popeye uses a tale of how he defeated Bluto as a boy to convince his nephews to eat their spinach."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214123000 +0000" stop="20241214130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cat And The Mermouse, One Ham's Family, Snowbody Loves Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom drowns in a lake, and goes to the bottom. There, he finds a mermouse, and then tries to capture it and eat it. The mermouse doesn't give in so easily, though., The big bad wolf dresses up as Santa Claus to try to get a ham dinner from a family of pigs but has trouble dealing with the family’s problem child., In the cold Swiss Alps Jerry and Tom try to stay warm by finding a place indoors to light a fire."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214130000 +0000" stop="20241214140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Fine Feathered Frenzy, Mouse In The House, Juke Box Jamboree, The Loan Stranger, Scrambled Eggs, Flea For Two, Ozark Lark</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody offers to marry an older bird for her money, but finds her unattractive when they meet in person. She, however, finds him irresistable and he avoids her while eating as much of her food as he can., Charlie tries to exterminate a mouse in the house himself., A noisy jukebox keeps a sleepy mouse awake., A wolf in loan officer's clothing pursues Woody after he forgets to repay a loan., A mischievous satyr switches the eggs of several different nests to confuse the expectant forest animals., A country flee must rescue his bride from the playboy flea who kidnapped her., Woody restarts the feud between the Martins and the Coys after he accidentally fires a gun into the shack of the last surviving Martin family member."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214140000 +0000" stop="20241214150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Spaced Out Bunny, Bedtime For Sniffles, Hare Force, Snow Business, Along Came Daffy, Hold The Lion, Please</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marvin the Martian and Hugo, the abominable snowman, capture the earth creature Bugs Bunny. , Sniffles the mouse tries and tries to stay awake on Christmas Eve, so that he can meet Santa. , On a cold snowy night, a frozen Bugs gets taken in by a kind old lady and set by the fireplace. , Tweety and Sylvester are snowed in at their cabin and search for food. , Yosemite Sam and his brother are starving in their desolate snow-bound cabin. When Daffy shows up as a salesman he finds himself as their target for dinner., It seems the whole animal kingdom make fun of the lion as a has-been. Anxious to prove them wrong, the lion decides to try and catch Bugs. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214150000 +0000" stop="20241214160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Vicious Valentine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Agents West and Gordon are sent to investigate the killings of wealthy industrialists and find that all are linked back to an evil matchmaker, Emma Valentine. She sets the rich men up with her young female employees, then kills them to gain their money and power. West and Gordon manage to escape from the trap she lays, and they must prevent her next target from getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214160000 +0000" stop="20241214170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lizabeth Ann Calhoun Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Lizabeth Ann Calhoun meets the wagon train staff as they stop for supplies. She asks permission to join the train so she can avoid the advances of a young man she claims is in love with her, however his real motives may be very different."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214170000 +0000" stop="20241214180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Way To Kill A Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The only chance Mariano Montoya’s herd has to survive anthrax is the immunization that Eugene learned about at college. Montoya says that if the Barkleys want to prove that the procedure is safe, they must test it on their own prize bull.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214180000 +0000" stop="20241214190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S17E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A father disapproves of the man her daughter marries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214190000 +0000" stop="20241214200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentleman From New Orleans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss meets a flamboyant, sword-brandishing drunk claiming to be none other than the notorious pirate Jean LaFitte.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214200000 +0000" stop="20241214203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>One Went To Denver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas welcomes his old friend, Tom Birch, who once saved his life, unaware that the man is now a bank robber who is on the run with his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214203000 +0000" stop="20241214210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Wait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Maury, released from Yuma prison, arrives in North Fork intent on getting even with Marshal Torrance, who helped send him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214210000 +0000" stop="20241214220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Rio Doloroso</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Don Francisco Maldonaldo sentences Favor and Rowdy to die for the death of his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214220000 +0000" stop="20241214223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Hankerchief</sub-title>
    <desc>"Paladin is hired by the Deverall family to clear their son, Pierre. He has been sentenced to hang for robbery and murder. But Pierre doesn't think they will really hang a "Deverall"."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214223000 +0000" stop="20241214230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Til Death Do Us Part</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman on the lam for murdering her abusive husband seeks the help of Randall, who is willing to investigate her belief that her husband is still alive and responsible for the wanted posters that have made her a lucrative target for bounty hunters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241214230000 +0000" stop="20241215010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Hoi Polloi, Some More Of Samoa, What's The Matador, Hold That Lion, Who Done It, Flying Saucer Daffy</sub-title>
    <desc>"A professor bets that he can turn the Stooges into gentlemen.   , The Stooges are tree surgeons who are enlisted by a rich old man to find a mate for his rare puckerless persimmon tree.  The boys sail to the tropical island of Rhum-Boogie to find the tree.  When they arrive they are captured by the natives and will be eaten unless Curly marries the Chief's ugly daughter.  The Stooges escape with the tree and, after a confrontation with an alligator; sail off with their prize. , Joe accidentally takes a picture of a paper plate, which Moe and Larry submit to a magazine as an authentic picture of a flying saucer.  Moe and Larry collect a big prize, but when the picture is proven to be phony, they're hauled off to Jail.  Joe then gets a picture of a real spaceship and this time he gets the fame and fortune, while Moe and Larry wind up in a sanitarium. , The Stooges are actors traveling to perform at a fiesta in Mexico.  After they accidentally switch suitcases with that of Dolores, a lovely senorita they met on trip down, they must sneak into her house to retrieve their suitcase.  When they are confronted by her jealous husband he vows to kill them if he sees them again.  At the fiesta where they are performing a comedy bullfight (Curly is the matador, Moe and Larry are in a bull costume) the husband bribes the attendants to let a real bull into the ring.  Curly knocks the bull out with a head butt and becomes a hero. , The Stooges are gypped out of their inheritance by Icabob Slipp, a crooked lawyer.  The boys follow Slipp onto a passenger train and corner him, but not before they accidentally let a lion loose on the train. , The Stooges are private detectives looking for a missing millionaire.  They wander around the millionaire's spooky mansion confronting various crooks and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215010000 +0000" stop="20241215033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Dinosaurus!</sub-title>
    <desc>"An american construction engineer, building a new harbor on an isolated tropical island, unwittingly blasts a brontosaurus, a tyrannosaurus rex, and a prehistoric cave man up from the depths. The island is almost wiped out by the two monsters, but all ends well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215033000 +0000" stop="20241215053000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Saturday The 14th</sub-title>
    <desc>"A family's new home is filled with scary creatures."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215053000 +0000" stop="20241215060000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>A Riddle A Day Keeps The Riddler Away</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler kidnaps King Boris, who is in town to present a gift to Gotham. Knowing they're the king's only hope, Batman and Robin set a trap using a fake jeweled crown.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215060000 +0000" stop="20241215070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Astral Traveler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Smith and Will become trapped in a cave during a cosmic storm, Will soon finds himself pulled through a time warp that send him back to Earth, where he lands in a Scottish castle and meets a headless ghost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215070000 +0000" stop="20241215080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Indestructible Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Scientists aboard the Seaview discover that a robot, recovered from a space capsule, has been converted into a destructive monster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215080000 +0000" stop="20241215090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A friendly Giant scientist tries to help the Earthlings with his teleporter, but the SID find out about his sympathies and set a trap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215090000 +0000" stop="20241215100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Island</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The travelers materialize in 1895 on Devil's Island, where they try to help French captain Alfred Dreyfus escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215100000 +0000" stop="20241215110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Possessed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent meets a troubled man whose experiments have led to an unprecedented relationship with aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215110000 +0000" stop="20241215120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Jackal</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matthew Star, a super-powered prince from outer space, must blend into high school while avoiding assassins sent to kill him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215120000 +0000" stop="20241215123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 1   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie meets her new stepbrother, Eric, soon discovering that he possesses a dark side.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215123000 +0000" stop="20241215130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Wicked Stepbrother: Part 2   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie's new stepbrother, Eric, runs afoul of the gang and even takes Mr. Belding's car apart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215130000 +0000" stop="20241215133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Date Auction   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The school holds a dance-date auction to pay for new cheerleading uniforms, with Zach, Slater and Screech up for auction. Jessie is appalled at the whole idea; meanwhile, Lisa becomes an intellectual to impress a smart boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215133000 +0000" stop="20241215140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Hold Me Tight   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a girl is rejected from wrestling tryouts because she is female, Zack, who has a crush on her, will do whatever it takes to see that she makes the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215140000 +0000" stop="20241215143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Love Machine   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie becomes alarmed at the presence of Slater's old flame, especially when Screech's "love machine" shows that both Slater and his ex still have feelings for each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215143000 +0000" stop="20241215150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Zack   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack sprains his knee and learns that he will be going into surgery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215150000 +0000" stop="20241215153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Not-so-rose-colored Glasses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan needs glasses but doesn't want to wear them because of how they make her look — until she has an accident that destroys Mike's surprise anniversary gift to Carol, a framed portrait of the Brady kids.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215153000 +0000" stop="20241215160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Teeter-totter Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Bobby and Cindy are not invited to a wedding because they're too young, they set out to do something important. Their goal, break a teeter-totter record. As the rest of the family takes their attempts lightly, news reporters make a visit to the Brady household to report on their efforts. Meanwhile, Carol attempts to buy the perfect wedding gift for her cousin, Gertrude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215160000 +0000" stop="20241215163000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Murder On The Moosejaw Express: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a train heading to Canada, Laverne and Shirley end up in the middle of espionage—murder!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215163000 +0000" stop="20241215170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Murder On The Moosejaw Express: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a train heading to Canada, Laverne and Shirley end up in the middle of espionage—murder!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215170000 +0000" stop="20241215173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And Thelma Lou, Phfftt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After Gomer naively tells Thelma Lou that Barney thinks "he has her in his hip pocket." Thelma Lou decides to teach Barney a lesson by flirting with Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215173000 +0000" stop="20241215180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Redecorating The Mertzes' Apartment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's redecorating time at the Mertzes' and Lucy and Ricky volunteer to help. But when Fred turns on a fan as Lucy is unstuffing a chair, the paint and feathers they were using go flying. Lucy feels responsible for the ruined furniture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215180000 +0000" stop="20241215183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Loves Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes convinced that he's ugly and unwanted after constantly being reminded how cute he used to be and from being yelled at by his parents for how messy he is currently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215183000 +0000" stop="20241215190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is rounding up some guys to go to an amusement park and he's one short from getting a discount so he settles on Beaver. However, Beaver begins having second thoughts when he hears stories about one of the roller coasters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215190000 +0000" stop="20241215193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Possum Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to keep the Clampetts in Beverly Hills by telling them there is going to be a Possum Day held there. Granny decides to run for Possum Queen in Beverly Hills, and Drysdale convinces her that she is running against Mrs. Drysdale. Meanwhile, Drysdale is desperate to actually get a Possum Day to happen for the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215193000 +0000" stop="20241215200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Present</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are preparing for Christmas, but are lacking in one thing: Christmas spirit. Jed thinks it is because they aren’t doing anything special for anyone this Christmas. He thinks they should do something special for Mrs. Drysdale, unaware she is still trying to get rid of them. They try to get jobs to raise money for her gift, so she doesn’t find out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215200000 +0000" stop="20241215220000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Brady Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"The entire Brady family manages to overcome personal obstacles to spend a happy holiday together."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215220000 +0000" stop="20241215230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Presence, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mickey Rooney plays a mystical Christmas presence among a motley group of passengers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215230000 +0000" stop="20241215233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Back To Nature</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, Barney and Gomer take a group of boys camping in the mountains to show them the pioneer life. Barney winds up getting himself and Gomer lost in the woods, and it's up to Andy to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241215233000 +0000" stop="20241216000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Garfield- Cathy And Robert Kothe</sub-title>
    <desc>"With over 6000 unique pieces of Garfield memorabilia, it’s no surprise Cathy Kothe holds the Guinness World Record for the largest collection dedicated to the lasagna-loving cat. As a young child, she became enamored with the Sunday comic, and that love snowballed into a house filled with orange tabby cats. We’re joined by Cathy’s husband, Robert, who embraces life amongst the orange felines and refers to himself as Cathy’s greatest “enabler.” The couple co-authored a book, “Loves Garfield,” documenting their collecting adventures over the years. Nancy Vega, the President of the Garfield Gathering, joins us as we explore this massive collection, and she’s found one Garfield collectible that Cathy doesn’t have to offer in an enticing trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216000000 +0000" stop="20241216003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Iron Guts Kelly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>General 'Iron Guts' Kelly arrives for an inspection, and ends up dying in Margaret's tent. Hawkeye and Trapper help the General's aide smuggle him out of camp. The next day he is reported killed at the front, as that is where he would have wanted to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216003000 +0000" stop="20241216010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>O.r.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The O.R. is filled with more wounded than the unit can handle. Hawkeye does heart massage on a soldier, which saves his life, but he dies four hours later. Sidney Freedman drops in during the deluge, and is dragged into the fray by Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216010000 +0000" stop="20241216013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Bunker's Go West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mike and Gloria cancel their trip home for Christmas, the Bunkers decide to travel west for the holidays.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216013000 +0000" stop="20241216020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers head out to California for Christmas to find out that Mike and Gloria are having marital problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216020000 +0000" stop="20241216023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Separation is Archie's reaction when he discovers that Gloria has been unfaithful to her husband. For the first time in nine years, he turns his back on his daughter and sides with Michael.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216023000 +0000" stop="20241216030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Road Back (part 2 Of Bitter Pill)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A despondent Archie retreats to his bedroom, until Harry offers to bail him out with a partnership offer for the bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216030000 +0000" stop="20241216033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Boy Meets Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary who makes ordering lunch an ordeal. Then, in Boy Meets Girl, Harvey tries to pick up Carol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216033000 +0000" stop="20241216040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>In Yung Fool, Carol and the gang parody the classic TV hit "Kung Fu", with Harvey as the Chinese Master, Jim as the Student.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216040000 +0000" stop="20241216043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pen Is Mightier Than The Mouth: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sally becomes famous overnight, leaving Rob and Buddy struggling to work without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216043000 +0000" stop="20241216050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Part-time Wife: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>While Sally is away, Laura helps out at the office but drives Rob crazy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216050000 +0000" stop="20241216053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman's Work Is Never Done</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of Ralph's endless domestic complaints, Alice takes a job and leaves a maid to take care of the housework.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216053000 +0000" stop="20241216060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Long Distance Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young boy finds he can communicate with his dead grandmother through a toy phone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216060000 +0000" stop="20241216070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Captive Audience  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The tape-recorded material for a renowned mystery author's upcoming book sounds a bit too factual to his publisher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216070000 +0000" stop="20241216080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Search In A Windy City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Believing that the one-armed man is in Chicago, Kimble contacts Mike Decker, a newspaper columnist who defended Kimble during his trial. Kimble and Decker organize a city-wide search for the one-armed man. But things get complicated with the arrival of De</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216080000 +0000" stop="20241216090000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The East European Republic wants the location of a horde of Nazi gold from their prisoner Kruger Schtelman, who is due to be released in three days. Despite the efforts of interrogator Colonel Sardner, they haven't acquired the information.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216090000 +0000" stop="20241216093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Anti-toxin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews and his officers attempt to ensure the delivery of life-saving serum to a young boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216093000 +0000" stop="20241216100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216100000 +0000" stop="20241216103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216103000 +0000" stop="20241216110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216110000 +0000" stop="20241216113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy invites a troubled boy along on an upcoming week-long group camping trip in the mountains after apprehending him during a burglary, but soon discovers the kid might be too much for him to handle. Meanwhile, he and Reed engage in a high-speed chase with a taxi, investigate a motorcycle versus pedestrian accident in a parking lot and respond to an armed robbery call.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216113000 +0000" stop="20241216120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Camp: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Officers Malloy and Woods take a group of children to a youth camp, but Malloy becomes preoccupied with the 14-year-old boy he reluctantly brought along, who continues to compensate for his small stature by getting into trouble. Meanwhile, Reed goes on patrol alone, and deals with a woman who uses a unique weapon to fend off an attacker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216120000 +0000" stop="20241216130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Holiday Countdown</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony kick off the holiday festivities with two special guests!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216130000 +0000" stop="20241216133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Three Boys And A Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Gilbert and Richard find a burro for sale in Mayfield and they each decide to go in $10 for it. After getting their parent's permission, Richard and Gilbert fight over who gets to keep the burro, which they name Pepe. However, once they get a load of just how destructive a burro can be, they dump the problem of room and board on Beaver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216133000 +0000" stop="20241216140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Quits School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie pompously announces that he's dropping out of school to get a high paying job at a gas station. However, all is not as it seems when Wally and Lumpy get a glance at Eddie's new free spending life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216140000 +0000" stop="20241216150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Resolute Reformer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason represents a citizen's group in hearings on a proposed aqueduct to be named after county engineer William Harper Caine. He gets a stop-work order until a section of the proposed location can be checked for an underground spring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216150000 +0000" stop="20241216160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Monster  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a cookie mogul is found dead after announcing plans to take over a number of baking companies, Matlock works the defense for another cookie maker suspected in the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216160000 +0000" stop="20241216170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge schemes to get rid of his wife after she tries to blackmail him into giving her a divorce and a generous settlement by revealing a secret from his past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216170000 +0000" stop="20241216180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Kinfolk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose arrives at the Waltons' home with her grandchildren</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216180000 +0000" stop="20241216190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bohannan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A faith-healer comes to Dodge. Doc is skeptical.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216190000 +0000" stop="20241216200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Cheating Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Kathie Browne returns in the role of Laura Dayton, erstwhile sweetheart of Adam Cartwright. When a stranger arrives in town telling Laura that her late husband willed her a fortune, she finds herself attracted to the man, unaware he is harboring ulterior motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216200000 +0000" stop="20241216203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wrong Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark McCain is eager to help lawman Jay Jefferson, who has arrived in North Fork intent on killing an outlaw for the reward, whether he is the right man or not.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216203000 +0000" stop="20241216210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When escaped convicts hold up the general store in North Fork and take Marshal Torrance hostage, Lucas comes to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216210000 +0000" stop="20241216220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Traitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>"Convicted of horse-stealing, Flint receives from Chris 20 lashes followed by banishment from the train. The lashes on his back then serve Flint as a "badge of dishonor" as he infiltrates a gang headed by a man known as Angel de Muerte."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216220000 +0000" stop="20241216230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>How Green Was My Thumb?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John rescue a man who swallowed his partial dental plate. Roy takes care of a young woman's plants while she is in the hospital. A young girl's religious parents prevent necessary treatment. The station responds to a fire in a winery, and Dr. Brackett and the paramedics perform backyard surgery on a man with an unexploded grenade in his abdomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216230000 +0000" stop="20241216233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Springtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When spring arrives, Klinger gets word from home that his sweetheart back in Toledo wants to marry him. Henry arranges for Father Mulcahy to do this over short wave radio. Radar falls in love with a nurse, while a grateful patient won't leave Hawkeye alone, and even threatens Major Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241216233000 +0000" stop="20241217000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Check-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper gets an ulcer and a ticket home. Unfortunately, his going-away party is spoiled by a new Army regulation, which forces him to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217000000 +0000" stop="20241217003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life With Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail from home worries Henry that Lorraine may be seeing other men. Father Mulcahy presides over a Jewish circumcision ceremony for the Korean-born son of a US GI.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217003000 +0000" stop="20241217010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Alcoholics Unanimous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry's departure to Tokyo leaves Major Burns in charge of the 4077th. He declares total prohibition of alcohol, which leads to a near riot in the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217010000 +0000" stop="20241217013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Pyle, U.s.m.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer comes to the courthouse one day with an announcement—he has decided to join the Marines, believing it a test of his manhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217013000 +0000" stop="20241217020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217020000 +0000" stop="20241217023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts In Washington</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts head to Washington D.C to give their money to the President, and Honest John and Flo follow. Honest John convinces the Clampetts that he knows the President and that they can give him money, which he will give to the President. Flo poses as Sitting Hawk, the last of the District of Colombia Native Americans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217023000 +0000" stop="20241217030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Rutabaga Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>It's planting season in Hooterville, but Oliver doesn't know what to grow. After testing the soil, he discovers Hooterville is perfect for growing rutabagas. The locals are overcome with rutabega fever, going so far as to plan a "Rutabaga Bowl". To spread the word, Lisa is sent up in a hot air balloon to drop vegetables on people with the message "Eat Hooterville Rutabagas" written on them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217030000 +0000" stop="20241217033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to let him play camp commander so he can get a French agent released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217033000 +0000" stop="20241217040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Crittendon Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon disrupts Hogan's plan to blow up a tunnel and stop a convoy of rocket fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217040000 +0000" stop="20241217043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Ham Actor, Carol loses her contact lenses moments before she must go on stage. Then, in Airline Security, Tim detains Harvey, determined to search through his briefcase before he boards the plane. Finally, in The Old Flame, Carol dreams up the perfect meeting when she runs into a former love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217043000 +0000" stop="20241217053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sun Bather's Diary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Arlene Dowling reports the theft of all her belongings, including a diary detailing a bank heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217053500 +0000" stop="20241217060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Hundred Yards Over The Rim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1847 an American pioneer sets out to find medicine for his dying son—and stumbles into modern-day New Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217060500 +0000" stop="20241217063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Toby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Albert finds his childhood love, and she agrees to marry him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217063500 +0000" stop="20241217070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Alibi Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Georgie is a gang member looking for an alibi after the death of his alter ego.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217070500 +0000" stop="20241217080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Sunday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The death of a factory foreman is ruled accidental, but his sister believes that it was murder and hires Mannix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217080500 +0000" stop="20241217090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Of San Ignacio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Stolen precious artifacts from a church in Mexico, has Cannon in search of three suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217090500 +0000" stop="20241217100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Memory Of A Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's escort is killed in a car crash, leaving her with partial amnesia and on suspicion of drunken driving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241217100000 +0000" stop="20241217103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Patrolman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A Highway Patrol officer is murdered while pursuing a car stolen from a lonely bookstore owner.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
