<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221043000 +0000" stop="20241221053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Green-eyed Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur West, a disreputable private investigator, has found J. J. Stanley in a cheap motel. He knows Stanley and his partner, Ned Bain, were involved in the embezzlement of the Texas National Bank. He wants to blackmail Bain into giving him money to keep quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221053500 +0000" stop="20241221060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Five Characters In Search Of An Exit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A hobo, clown, bagpipe player, ballerina and military officer are trapped in a huge cylinder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221060500 +0000" stop="20241221063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Festive Season</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man believes that his sister murdered his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221063500 +0000" stop="20241221070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>John Brown's Body</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has her husband committed to a mental institution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221070500 +0000" stop="20241221080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Wasn’t There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An old adversary from Mannix's time serving in the Korean War, whom he thought was dead, sets out to kill him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221080500 +0000" stop="20241221090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Deadly Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The parents of a teen girl hire Cannon when they discover a charismatic young man is trying to lure their daughter into a cult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221090500 +0000" stop="20241221100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Enslaved, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating a death at a posh sanitarium, Betty discovers a sinister plot to defraud the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221100000 +0000" stop="20241221103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Cannonball Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe's latest plan for decommissioning the Hooterville Cannonball falls on the holidays, as the gang are decorating the train for the annual Christmas Eve caroling run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221103000 +0000" stop="20241221110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Santa Claus Special</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Scrooge-like Homer Bedloe derails Kate's plan for Christmas Eve caroling and gift distributing aboard the Hooterville Cannonball.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221110000 +0000" stop="20241221113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Real Nice Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts get a new next-door neighbor, and when Aggie, the maid of Mrs. Phillip Brentwood Carrington III, drops by to the use the phone, the Clampetts mistake her for Carrington. This is the first rich neighbor who has proven to be kind and considerate. Drysdale is happy because this rich woman has moved next door and might be a wife for Jed. Granny also sees her as a match for Jed. The two try to set Jed and Aggie up in different ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221113000 +0000" stop="20241221120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Poor Farmer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale organizes a financial syndicate, which includes a billionaire who he wants in his bank. Jed is one of the potential members of this group, but never makes the meeting because a new invention of Jethro’s, a chemical that turns water into gasoline, doesn’t work. When Jed finally arrives, it is too late, and Mr. Sebastian has left. Jane suggests that he visits him at his health club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221120000 +0000" stop="20241221123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Klondike Casanova, I’ll Be Skiing Ya, Mister And Mistletoe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Fur farmer Bluto kidnaps Olive Oyl., Popeye and Olive go skiing, and ski instructor Bluto tries to break them up., Bluto disguises himself as Santa to woo Olive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221123000 +0000" stop="20241221130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Night Before Christmas, Pup's Christmas, Southbound Duckling</sub-title>
    <desc>"It is Christmas Eve and Tom gets to know the spirit of giving after he tosses Jerry outside in the cold when he catches him trying to get to a present., Two pups experience their very first Christmas and are both excited and fascinated., Tom is hungry for a duck meal and Quacker, Jerry's friend, plans to head south for the winter unlike all the other ducks."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221130000 +0000" stop="20241221140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>His Better Elf, A Fish Story, Banquet Busters, Room And Wrath, Hi-seas Hi-jacker, Adventures Of Tom Thumb Jr., Ballyhooey</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody finds a four-leafed clover that transforms into a small green woodpecker claiming to be a leprechaun named "Clancy." As his three wishes to become rich go awry, Woody realizes this was all a lesson to get him to work to earn a fortune., A doctor tells Charlie a pet fish will make him less nervous. After struggling to get the fish tank home, Charlie is forced by Bessie to return it., Woody and Andy are true starving musicians who agree to a gig in a fancy mansion in the hopes of nabbing some food., Smedley tries to evict Chilly from his Snowtel when he can only pay the bill in fish., Inspector Willoughby pursues a pirate holding up a battleship., Tom Thumb discovers a new island, but he's taken by a giant who always wanted a son., Woody tries to watch his quiz show, but it is interrupted by silly commercials."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221140000 +0000" stop="20241221150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>A Hare Grows In Manhattan, Snow Time For Comedy, Hen House Henery, Wabbit Who Came To Supper, Tweetie Pie, The Old Grey Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Now a Hollywood star, Bugs tells a reporter of his humble beginnings on the east side of New York. , Two curious dogs chase a bone in a snowy wilderness setting. , Henery Hawk sets out to catch Foghorn but he scolds Henery and tells him to start small., Elmer Fudd and his dogs are hunting for Bugs Bunny in the woods. , When Tweety is brought in from the cold, the owner warns Sylvester to leave him alone. , Elmer Fudd asks God when he will finally be able to catch Bugs. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221150000 +0000" stop="20241221160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Brain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim and Artie are pitted against a super-genius who sends them fake newspapers with predictions of the deaths of their friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221160000 +0000" stop="20241221170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hobie Redman Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"When three wagons are late in the desert, Chris sends Duke to find them and bring them to the wagon train as the train cannot wait for them. It may be a suicide mission due to water holes drying up and the missing people's personal issues."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221170000 +0000" stop="20241221180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Wolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nick is bit by a rabid wolf, a virtual death sentence. Not wanting his family to witness his decline, he leaves, making Heath swear he won’t tell the others what has happened. Nick hopes that in his final 60 days he will do something worthwhile.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221180000 +0000" stop="20241221190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Eleven Dollars</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Headed to Abilene to bring a woman $11 owed to her, Fetus teaches two boys a lesson along the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221190000 +0000" stop="20241221200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>No Less A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Certain that he is too old to stand against a notorious gang of bank robbers when news arrives that Virginia City will soon be next in a long string of successful raids, the terrified townsfolk demand Sheriff Coffee's resignation to make way for a younger lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221200000 +0000" stop="20241221203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221203000 +0000" stop="20241221210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221210000 +0000" stop="20241221220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Alkali Sink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Burt Harvey is accused of cowardice at Gettysburg by his new father-in-law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221220000 +0000" stop="20241221223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Golden Toad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin gets involved in a dispute between the patriarch of a farming family and a matriarch saloon owner and her family who believe land they claim rights to holds an Aztec treasure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221223000 +0000" stop="20241221230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Favor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Owing a favor to a sheriff, Josh agrees against better judgment to go to the lawless town of Bent Horn to bring back a man wanted for bank robbery and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241221230000 +0000" stop="20241222010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Scotch, Three Little Beers, Termites Of 1938, Heavenly Daze, Merry Mavericks, Rhythm And Weep</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are running the local drugstore and mix up a potion that a desperate businessman decides to sell as scotch.  , The Stooges are inept deliverymen at a brewery.   , The Stooges pair with three dancers to put on a Broadway show, not realizing their sponsor is an escaped mental patient., The Stooges are pest exterminators, mistakenly hired by a rich lady looking for an escort to a fancy society party.  The Stooges wreck the fancy mansion where the party is taking place and befuddle the guest of honor, an English Lord. , A divine comedy classic! Shemp goes to Heaven but isn't allowed through the Pearly Gates until he can reform bad boys Larry and Moe.  , Set in the old west, the Stooges are mistaken for lawmen and manage to capture a gang of crooks.  The boys then get the job of guarding some money in an old house reputed to be haunted by the ghost of an Indian Chief.  The crooks escape and go after the money disguised as ghosts, but Shemp, disguised as the Indian Chief, manages to knock them out. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222010000 +0000" stop="20241222033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Phantom Of The Opera ('43)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Academy Award-nominee Claude Rains gives a moving performance in this suspenseful, lyrical update to Gaston Leroux's macabre classic. As the tale goes, Rains plays the famously disfigured musician who haunts the Paris Opera House and kidnaps the beautiful young soprano whom he has trained. Featuring gorgeous music and elaborate sets, this "Phantom of the Opera" is a more-than-worthy version of a much-interpreted and beloved story."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222033000 +0000" stop="20241222040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>When The Rat's Away, The Mice Will Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler blackmails Commissioner Gordon: unless he's paid $1 million dollars, he'll destroy The Queen of Freedom Monument along with King Boris.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222040000 +0000" stop="20241222050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Is There In Truth No Beauty?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise is boarded by two strange visitors: Medusan Ambassador Kollos, a creature that must be kept in a box because its ugliness is enough to drive a human mad, and his aide, beautiful telepath Miranda, who senses murderous intent aboard the ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222050000 +0000" stop="20241222060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>They Have Been, They Are, They Will Be</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>An invisible alien sucks down the bone marrow of its victims while it makes repairs and looks for directions home. This is the only story where Kolchak fails to stop the "monster."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222060000 +0000" stop="20241222070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Galaxy Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After an alien gives Penny a belt as a gift, telling her to guard it with her life, it isn't long before a group of aliens turns up looking for the item, and they will stop at nothing to get it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222070000 +0000" stop="20241222080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Buccaneer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A mad art collector hijacks the Seaview in a dramatic plan to pirate Leonardo de Vinci's Mona Lisa from a French ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222080000 +0000" stop="20241222090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Dart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan is accused of murdering two Giants and begins acting oddly, arousing his crewmates' suspicions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222090000 +0000" stop="20241222100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Reign Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In Paris during the French Revolution, the time travelers agree to aid Marie Antoinette in exchange for safe-conduct passes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222100000 +0000" stop="20241222110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Counter-attack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent recovers important information regarding the aliens just as a conspiracy targets his future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222110000 +0000" stop="20241222120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Hand</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matthew and Walt go to Las Vegas to investigate rigged games."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222120000 +0000" stop="20241222123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Check Your Mate   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the annual chess competition between Valley and Bayside. Screech is Bayside's champion so Valley decides to dig up some dirt on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222123000 +0000" stop="20241222130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Pipe Dreams   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While putting up a new field goal post, oil is discovered. Soon the entire school is interested in the lucrative prospect of oil drilling, but Jessie doesn't like the idea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222130000 +0000" stop="20241222133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>All In The Mall   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Zack finds $5,000 in the mall, he plans to use the money to buy and then scalp tickets for a U2 concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222133000 +0000" stop="20241222140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Zack's Birthday Party   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang takes summer jobs at a beach resort, but they have trouble dealing with their boss. Meanwhile, Zack falls for the boss' daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222140000 +0000" stop="20241222143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Home For Christmas: Part 1   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The gang all gets jobs at the Palisades mall during the holiday seasons. Zack befriends a girl who is working for Kelly. Also, Zack and Screech make friends with a homeless man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222143000 +0000" stop="20241222150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Home For Christmas: Part 2   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack learns that his new girlfriend is the homeless man's daughter. When she decides to get her dad a new coat but it turns up missing, her boss, Mr. Mooney, accuses her of stealing it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222150000 +0000" stop="20241222153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Big Little Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby becomes extremely self conscious about his height and tries different ways to make himself "big." When there's a dangerous situation at Sam's Butcher Shop, though, Bobby is exactly the right size to save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222153000 +0000" stop="20241222160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Vote For Brady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg and Marcia rush home after school with the news that they're both running for student body president. The boys and girls each take sides and soon each one of them is accusing the other of sabotage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222160000 +0000" stop="20241222163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Goin' To Chicago</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie, Potsie and Ralph go on a trip to Chicago with the school choir. Not wanting to stay in their hotel room all night, they decide to sneak out and see a show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222163000 +0000" stop="20241222170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Child's Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Because of Squiggy's forgetfulness, Laverne and Shirley must play all the parts in Shirley's play, 'Murder in Mother Goose Land,' which a Broadway producer attends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222170000 +0000" stop="20241222180000 +0000">
    <title>A Very Merry Bugs Bunny Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Bugs Bunny's Christmas Carol, Gift Wrapped, Abominable Snow Rabbit, Freeze Frame, Weasel While You Work, The Fright Before Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Sam lacks the Christmas spirit, Bugs Bunny makes a plan to change his mind., It's Christmas time and Sylvester tries to switch his present with Granny's present which is Tweety in a birdcage., Bugs and Daffy decide to tunnel underground over to Palm Springs. Wrong directions end them up in the Himalayas where they run into trouble with the Abominable Snowman... , The coyote orders a blizzard machine to cover the entire desert with snow after he finds out that Road Runners are easy to catch in the cold. , During a snow-covered winter, Foghorn Leghorn uses the weasel against the barn's guard dog. , Taz breaks free of his a plane shipping crate and falls from the sky into Santa's laundry. He hijacks Santa's sleigh and ends up in Bugs' house tearing down everything, but Bugs gets wise to the Devil. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222180000 +0000" stop="20241222200000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>Snoopy, Come Home</sub-title>
    <desc>"Snoopy leaves Charlie Brown to return to his original master."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222200000 +0000" stop="20241222220000 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>A Boy Named Charlie Brown</sub-title>
    <desc>"Charlie Brown competes in a spelling bee, and he'll need the help of Linus and Snoopy' to overcome his unlucky streak. This Academy Award nominated animated feature was the Peanuts film debut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222220000 +0000" stop="20241222230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Lonely At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>In a Christmas-themed cruise, a group of orphans and a man convicted for a crime he didn't commit are among those aboard the ship. Florence Henderson, Donna Mills and Shecky Greene guest star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222230000 +0000" stop="20241222233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Sheriff Taylor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers moving to Raleigh for another job. An upset Barney tries to demonstrate to Andy just how bad Mayberry would be without him, creating more harm than good in his effort to get Andy to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241222233000 +0000" stop="20241223000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Toys- Nick Mayor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Husband and wife Nick Mayor and Jen LeMasters were drawn together by their love of all things weird and wonderful. Now their home is an eccentric floor-to-ceiling showpiece of vintage toys, nostalgia items, and the occasional unclassifiable oddity. Lisa joins them for a look at some of their standout treasures – including a very rare “Alien” action figure and a spectacular Masters of the Universe ride-on Battle Cat. Joining them is vintage toy vendor Michael Tomaso, who puts a value on Nick and Jen’s entire collection, then attempts to lure them into a trade for one of their most prized items with a double-barrel offer he’s sure they can’t refuse. Though what he wants in return might be a problem."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223000000 +0000" stop="20241223003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223003000 +0000" stop="20241223010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Command</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank settles in as commanding officer, only to have a new one appointed over his head, one that, to his chagrin, fits in very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223010000 +0000" stop="20241223013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Christmas season has everyone in the Christmas spirit. For a joke, Archie purchases some fake nose and mustache glasses that were on sale, but Mike also happened to go to that same store and hit that same sale. Meanwhile, Edith returns from a doctor checkup and confides in Gloria the fact that she has a lump in her breast and she fears it may be breast cancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223013000 +0000" stop="20241223020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Draft Dodger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The clash of two worlds explodes in this episode. Mike's friend is a Draft Dodger and it is Christmas dinner and unbeknownst to Archie this guy is sitting at his Christmas dinner table. The guy is exactly everything Archie hates about Mike's generation. On top of this Archie's friend is also spending Christmas dinner with the Bunkers and he lost his son to the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223020000 +0000" stop="20241223023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Crisis Of Faith (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith's religious faith is shaken after her friend, female impersonator Beverly LaSalle, is brutally murdered by street thugs at Christmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223023000 +0000" stop="20241223030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Crisis Of Faith (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike is put in the hospital and Beverly LaSalle is murdered by a thug at Chistmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223030000 +0000" stop="20241223033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Fruitcake, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball is thrown out of the house for playing poker. Then, in The Fruitcake, Carol tries to avoid a nervous breakdown, despite her husband's annoying behavior.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223033000 +0000" stop="20241223040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Double Calamity, the gang parodies the film-noir classic "Double Indemnity", with Carol as Barbara Stanwyck and Steve as Fred McMurray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223040000 +0000" stop="20241223043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Honeymoons Are For The Lucky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recalls when his honeymoon with Laura was canceled.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223043000 +0000" stop="20241223050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>How To Spank A Star</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's favorite star wants to guest on the show but only seems to cause problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223050000 +0000" stop="20241223053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Please Leave The Premises</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and the Nortons fight a rent increase, though Ralph is the only one who really wants to fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223053000 +0000" stop="20241223060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind And The Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A book on the power of thought enables an irritable man to re-create the world exactly as he wants it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223060000 +0000" stop="20241223070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Final Vow  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Blaming herself for the robbery of a priceless figurine, an apprentice nun leaves her convent to track down the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223070000 +0000" stop="20241223080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodline</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble works as a kennel man for Max Bodin, a breeder of prize-winning Irish Setter show dogs, and whom is currently putting his kennel up for sale. Max's son, Johnny, and Johnny's wife Cora discover that one of the dogs has developed hip dysplasia which</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223080000 +0000" stop="20241223090000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Robot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Deputy Premier Kamirov is keeping his premier "alive" by substituting a double, "Gemini." Kamirov plans to force Gemini as premier to announce his retirement and name Kamirov his successor. Kamirov will then kill Gemini and ally with the Iron Curtain again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223090000 +0000" stop="20241223093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman attempts to help her innocent fiancé and discovers a killer may still be at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223093000 +0000" stop="20241223100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An officer accused of taking a bribe has chosen Sgt. Friday to represent him at his trial board hearing. Witnesses saw the officer accept the money, but he insists it was for the payback of a loan made years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223100000 +0000" stop="20241223103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223103000 +0000" stop="20241223110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223110000 +0000" stop="20241223113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While paying a visit to the laundromat before going into work, Malloy encounters a man using the facilities to dry something much different from clothing. On patrol, he and Reed deal with a minister-in-training who uses a very unorthodox method to get his message across, try to reunite a Finnish-speaking child with her family, mediate a strange dispute between feuding neighbors and engage in a high-speed chase with a well known drug dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223113000 +0000" stop="20241223120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>G.t.a.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate a large car theft operation that targets older cars, then stages them around the city as abandoned vehicles so they can be towed and scrapped. Meanwhile, they try to figure out why the son of Malloy's girlfriend is getting bad grades, search for a suspect who robbed an elderly woman and attempt to rescue two foolish teenagers who enter a house that is being fumigated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223120000 +0000" stop="20241223130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>North Pole Pals</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony travel to the North Pole in hopes of meeting Santa Claus!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223130000 +0000" stop="20241223133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Yard Birds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward doesn't take any excuses when he puts his foot down and demands that Wally and Beaver clean the yard. They each reluctantly cancel their plans with Richard and Eddie and get to work but soon find themselves with distractions. This causes them to miss the deadline to call the hauler who is suppose to take all the yard waste away and this leads them to pay Eddie and Lumpy to take care of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223133000 +0000" stop="20241223140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tennis, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally finds himself smack dab in the middle of a lover's quarrel when a woman tries to make her estranged boyfriend jealous by continually making tennis dates with Wally. Wally finds himself in an awkward position when the boyfriend threatens him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223140000 +0000" stop="20241223150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blind Man's Bluff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Crooked jewelry store owner Karl Addison learns that he needs an operation that will temporarily blind him. Addison makes plans to rob his own store knowing that his sightlessness will provide him with a perfect alibi.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223150000 +0000" stop="20241223160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Personal Trainer  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When personal trainer Harry Slade is murdered, Matlock agrees to defend his roofer, George Wilton, in a complicated case involving quite a few sexual indiscretions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223160000 +0000" stop="20241223170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Leftover Man: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A white supremacist politician plans to have his wife's lover murdered and blame it on black radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223170000 +0000" stop="20241223180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Sheep</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ashley Longworth Jr returns to the mountain. He proposes to Erin and she accepts</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223180000 +0000" stop="20241223190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Milligan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Morgan guest stars as a farmer accused of shooting someone in the back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223190000 +0000" stop="20241223200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Return To Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben travels to pay his respects after receiving word that his nephew is dead. At the grave, however, Ben finds his nephew, wounded but alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223200000 +0000" stop="20241223203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rancher dies after the bank forecloses the mortgage on his property, his son blames the banker for his father's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223203000 +0000" stop="20241223210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind Reader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E40</episode-num>
    <desc>When a wealthy rancher is killed, Mark suggests that they seek the aid of a mind reader to identify the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223210000 +0000" stop="20241223220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Malachi Hobart Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke comes across Malachi Hobart, a preacher who has dedicated his life to his fellow man. However, he soon begins to believe that the preacher is in fact a con artist using religion to swindle people out of their money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223220000 +0000" stop="20241223230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Screenwriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A screenwriter spends a day observing Squad 51 at work, including a motorcycle accident, a worker suffering from exposure to chemicals, the delivery of a baby and a fire at a toy factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223230000 +0000" stop="20241223233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>It Happened One Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It happened one night: freezing cold, an artillery barrage that's coming too close, a patient going downhill and Frank's searching Hot Lips' tent for his letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241223233000 +0000" stop="20241224000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Captain Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye's father is notified that he's dead, he finds it's no easy matter either to get word to him or to establish otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224000000 +0000" stop="20241224003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Doc</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Its quid pro quo at the 4077th: two bottles of Scotch for secret surgery, and a tank to scare off snipers for an unauthorized shot of penicillin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224003000 +0000" stop="20241224010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving back from a medical conference, Radar, Hawkeye, B.J., Sherman and Frank find themselves lost. When they decide to turn around, the bus does not want to start. And when Radar goes off in the middle of the night for the latrine, he does not immediately return.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224010000 +0000" stop="20241224013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pageant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets the lead role in the Centennial Pageant as Lady Mayberry. She is, however, not up to the challenge, and Andy must find a way to tell her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224013000 +0000" stop="20241224020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darling Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Darlings come to Mayberry looking for a boy whom they could engage to Charlene's new baby. Opie becomes the prime target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224020000 +0000" stop="20241224023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Doctor, Cure My Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny checks on Mark to make sure he is all human. When she sees that he is, she is ready for him to marry Elly May, giving hints. Elly and Mark sit in the parlor, trying to be alone, but keep getting interrupted by the family, mostly Granny and Jethro. Even when they think they are alone, Jethro is watching them, but Elly chases him out. Granny decides to head to the bank and, since she helped her out, brings Miss Jane a frog to kiss, only if she wants to.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224023000 +0000" stop="20241224030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Rummage Sale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Douglases are asked to donate old clothing to a charity rummage sale. Lisa is glad to give away Oliver's entire wardrobe, but can't part with any of her dresses. Each has a memory attached, leading to flashbacks of Oliver asking Lisa's father for her hand in marriage, the Douglases' honeymoon in Switzerland and their first party in their new Park Avenue apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224030000 +0000" stop="20241224033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>D-day At Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan pulls a hoax to get a general to believe Klink is replacing him as chief of staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224033000 +0000" stop="20241224040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Crittendon's Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Crittendon is the only one to avoid capture when he and his commandos parachute into the area during a mission to capture Rommel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224040000 +0000" stop="20241224043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Opening Talk on Plane, passengers discuss their plans in Australia. Then, Carol and friends perform "Waltzing Matilda" and "It's Today". Next, in The Oldest Man, the Sydney orchestra is led by the Oldest Man. Finally, in The Ham Actor, an ailing Carol tries to perform, despite already being replaced by Vicki.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224043000 +0000" stop="20241224053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fugitive Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Janet Norris is charged with poisoning her doctor husband just before he flew to his death in his private plane. Further investigation reveals that Dr. Norris did not die in the plane crash and that he is in Mexico with his nurse mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224053500 +0000" stop="20241224060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Changing Of The Guard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly private school teacher wonders if his life has meant anything as he contemplates suicide on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224060500 +0000" stop="20241224063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Claus And The Tenth Avenue Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal fresh out of prison takes a job as Santa Claus for the holiday season.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224063500 +0000" stop="20241224070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Back For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to get rid of his nagging wife — permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224070500 +0000" stop="20241224080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Principle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Two elderly spinster sisters are determined to prosecute a traffic violator. There's only one problem: The man also is a syndicate killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224080500 +0000" stop="20241224090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Flight Of Hawks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A suicide by a pilot leads to the discovery of a plan by a mercenary group to launch a coup of a small African country.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224090500 +0000" stop="20241224100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Echo Of A Distant Battle (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tangles with violent veterans of the Vietnam war as he attempts to clear the name of an Army deserter who's still missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224100000 +0000" stop="20241224103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Rabies (christmas)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews desperately searches for a little girl who has been bitten by a rabid dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224103000 +0000" stop="20241224110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are convinced that "Brother" William Bentley's Temple of the Expanded Mind is just a sham—a front for Bentley to sell LSD to the students of a nearby elementary school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224110000 +0000" stop="20241224113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Of The Crime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are left frustrated after investigating the theft of an elderly woman's old television set, but they have hope that a recently passed law may provide her and other victims with compensation. Elsewhere on patrol, they search for an armed robber who shot an over-trusting shopkeeper, and respond to a call of an unusual armed robbery at a drive-in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224113000 +0000" stop="20241224120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Point</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Woods' new partner is a nervous and quiet recruit, and the embarrassing secret he's trying to keep from his fellow officers might actually imperil them. On today's patrol, a real estate broker's well meaning but poorly thought out gesture nearly leads to a mob scene, a drug store owner discovers a way to profit from armed robbers and an armed robbery suspect opens fire during his escape attempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224120000 +0000" stop="20241224130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toony's Really, Really Late Christmas Eve Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Toony can't sleep on Christmas Eve, he hosts a late-night talk show with special guests Mr. and Mrs. Claus!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224130000 +0000" stop="20241224133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>One Of The Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie and Wally finally get a chance to join the most exclusive social club in school, the Barons. However, after hanging out with the Barons on a Friday night, Eddie and Wally realize they don't want to be in this club because the guys really aren't who everybody thinks they are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224133000 +0000" stop="20241224140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Sweatshirt Monsters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Richard, Whitey and Alan each buy sweatshirts that have monster faces on the front of them. They like them so much they each decide to wear them to school the next day. However, each one finds that their parents forbid them from wearing such hideous sweatshirts to school. However, Beaver manages to sneak out of the house with his on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224140000 +0000" stop="20241224150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Barefaced Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In a small California town throwing a festival during which all men wear beards, Paul Drake tries to locate missing money embezzled by a former bank president.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224150000 +0000" stop="20241224160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Narc  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a police officer is murdered after exposing a group of dirty cops to top brass, Matlock agrees to take the case in defense of suspected killer Officer Johnny Bauer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224160000 +0000" stop="20241224170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Leftover Man: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A white supremacist politician plans to have his wife's lover murdered and blame it on black radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224170000 +0000" stop="20241224180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Children's Carol - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas approaches, Mary Ellen and the baby leave to be near Curt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224180000 +0000" stop="20241224190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tatum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E10</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-gunfighter is dying. He must reconcile with the daughters he abandoned, and find a way to be buried next to his wife, who is buried in a town that hates him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224190000 +0000" stop="20241224200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Saga Of Muley Jones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Yarnell makes his first appearance as the Cartwrights' cousin, Muley, from Missouri. "Blessed" with a singing voice that can literally shatter glass, Muley manages to make life difficult for his rich relations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224200000 +0000" stop="20241224203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224203000 +0000" stop="20241224210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224210000 +0000" stop="20241224220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Ellen Thomas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen is an orphan traveling west to join family; members of the train reject her due to her surly disposition. Her only friend is Sally Mayhew, another girl traveling west with her family dying of consumption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224220000 +0000" stop="20241224230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Fix It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's husband is trapped under their house, where a natural oil well has erupted. John tries to fix a boy's bike. A boy who wants to become a doctor is admitted to Rampart. The firemen rescue a child stuck in a pipe. Roy and John remove a ring from a young man’s finger. Roy and Capt. Stanley struggle with a shutoff valve at a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224230000 +0000" stop="20241224233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Mildred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Potter's anniversary. While Potter writes home, Frank and Hot Lips have a wood carving made for him, and Radar rescues a horse and makes him a present of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224233000 +0000" stop="20241225000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th plays host to kids bombed out of their orphanage, and at the same time has to deliver a baby and care for battle casualties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225000000 +0000" stop="20241225003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Death Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester fulfills a family Christmas tradition but has trouble maintaining the anonymity required to keep it a truly charitable act. Even Klinger lends a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225003000 +0000" stop="20241225010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225010000 +0000" stop="20241225013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225013000 +0000" stop="20241225020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225020000 +0000" stop="20241225023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Possum Day Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is preparing for her Possum Queen campaign, and also wondering why Mrs. Drysdale hasn’t fought back yet. When Jed asks Drysdale about this, he starts her campaign with a false radio interview and continues to try to get a Possum festival going. Granny continues with her campaign, and Mrs. Drysdale realizes that she has been campaigning without even knowing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225023000 +0000" stop="20241225030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Hail To The Fire Chief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Scheming to get Oliver to pay his way to a convention, Fire Chief Joe Carson appoints him as his assistant. Instead, Oliver finds the Hooterville Fire Department to be inept and ill-prepared. Oliver's call for improvements results in Uncle Joe being voted out and him being named the new chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225030000 +0000" stop="20241225033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to think he is about to capture a POW escape ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225033000 +0000" stop="20241225040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cuisine A La Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau decides to escape leaving the camp without a chef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225040000 +0000" stop="20241225043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Harry's Mirage And Grill</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Wiggins, just before Christmas, Mr. Tudball conducts a fire drill to keep the insurance company appeased. Then, in Harry's Mirage and Grill, Harvey and Tim find a desert oasis with a beautiful woman -- or is it just a mirage?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225043000 +0000" stop="20241225053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The One-eyed Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Della and Mason's dinner at a fancy French restaurant is interrupted by a phone call and an envelope containing $500 from a mysterious woman named Marian Fargo. She wants him to make an exchange: the money for some documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225053500 +0000" stop="20241225060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Meek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After a derelict Santa Claus is fired on Christmas Eve, he finds a bottomless sack of gifts. With this bag he sets out to fulfill his one wish—to see the less fortunate inherit the bounties of Christmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225060500 +0000" stop="20241225080500 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>An American Christmas Carol</sub-title>
    <desc>"In an American town, an old bitter miser is given a ghostly chance at redemption on Christmas Eve."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225080500 +0000" stop="20241225090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a man who is charged with arson and murder by burning down his textile company which killed his wife who was trapped inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225090500 +0000" stop="20241225100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Echo Of A Distant Battle (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tangles with violent veterans of the Vietnam war as he attempts to clear the name of an Army deserter who's still missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225100000 +0000" stop="20241225103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews and Sergeant Corey spend Christmas Eve searching for a lost girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225103000 +0000" stop="20241225110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A statue of the child Jesus was stolen from a church. Joe and Bill have to get it back by Christmas. They have less than 48 hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225110000 +0000" stop="20241225113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>During their Christmas Eve Patrol, Malloy and Reed contemplate using their patrol car to deliver a Christmas tree to the residents of a soon-to-be-closed retirement home. Meanwhile, an elderly man's bagpipe playing is considered a public nuisance, a couple of teenagers steal a delivery truck containing radioactive material, a nervous man is desperate to cover up the smell of perfume on his clothing and an armed robbery suspect becomes intent on committing suicide-by-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225113000 +0000" stop="20241225120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lady's Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>On today's patrol, Malloy and Reed try to corral cattle that are wandering into the downtown area, pull over a speeding bicyclist, chase down a man with a stolen guitar and break up a bar fight. After their shift is over, Reed and his wife witness a gas station holdup on their way to dinner with Malloy and his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225120000 +0000" stop="20241225130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Merry Christmas To All!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate Chrsitmas and warm up with a holiday beverage!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225130000 +0000" stop="20241225133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Night In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends are all psyched to go on a camping trip with Gilbert's father as an escort. However, when Gilbert's father suddenly has to work, Wally agrees to take them. Meanwhile, Eddie and Lumpy decide to secretly tag along and scare the boys with animal noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225133000 +0000" stop="20241225140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Long Distance Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends decide to make a call to California to talk to Don Drysdale and they agree to chip in on the cost of the call, assuming that it's only going to be a couple dollars. However, when they're put on hold, the cost quickly jumps up to $9.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225140000 +0000" stop="20241225150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Difficult Detour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Contactor Pete Mallory is charged with the murder of a vacation resort developer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225150000 +0000" stop="20241225160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225160000 +0000" stop="20241225170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A son (Edward Albert) is opposed to his father's plan to give land to slave descendants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225170000 +0000" stop="20241225180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Children's Carol - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas approaches, Mary Ellen and the baby leave to be near Curt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225180000 +0000" stop="20241225190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Sodbusters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt has trouble getting a fight about water rights under control when things escalate to violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225190000 +0000" stop="20241225200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Roper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Army soldiers and an outlaw gang have a shootout at the Ponderosa while Will is home alone. To make matters worse, Will realizes that the money in Ben's safe is in jeopardy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225200000 +0000" stop="20241225203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225203000 +0000" stop="20241225210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225210000 +0000" stop="20241225220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dr. Denker Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The wagon train takes in a terrified young boy who has just seen his father murdered by a bandit gang. While Bill and Flint try to help him recover, embittered Civil War vet Ed Beaufort tells the boy that taking vengeance is the best medicine. Soon a traveling musician, Dr. Denker, joins the wagon train and he and Billy hit it off, but it becomes evident that Billy and the doctor had a prior connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225220000 +0000" stop="20241225230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Gossip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy encourages John to represent the station in the Fireman's Olympics track events. An armored car sideswipes a motorist and Station 51 must break into the van. A nurse spreads the rumor that Dr. Morton is having financial problems. Doctors treat a child with cyanide poisoning from peach pits. Dr. Brackett treats a bigamist with a skull fracture. The firemen rescue an electrocution victim hanging in mid-air and a man trapped in a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225230000 +0000" stop="20241225233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Quo Vadis, Captain Chandler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Intelligence officer Colonel Flagg and psychiatrist Sidney Freedman grapple over the fate of a wounded officer, Captain Chandler, who claims to be Jesus Christ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225233000 +0000" stop="20241226000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Peggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. writes home to his wife, Peg, reporting Klinger's escape attempts, the visit of a formidable chaplain and one of Frank's goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226000000 +0000" stop="20241226003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Of Moose And Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tangles with a tough Army colonel, Colonel Spiker; B.J. helps Zale, who's received a Dear John letter; and Frank looks endlessly for Korean saboteurs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226003000 +0000" stop="20241226010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Soldier Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has a fever and makes a will, leaving all his money to his wife and all his clothes to Hot Lips.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226010000 +0000" stop="20241226013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226013000 +0000" stop="20241226020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226020000 +0000" stop="20241226023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Drysdale stops the clan from going back home to deliver a baby, the Clampetts try to help the Brewsters with their baby, while Jethro unsuccessfully tries to open his own version of the Kitty Kat Club. Of course, the Brewsters don't need the help because they are adopting, though after hearing the explanation given, the Clampetts believe they really need help and advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226023000 +0000" stop="20241226030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Eb's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb announces his engagement to Loreli Appleby, a girl he met the day before. In an attempt to impress his future father-in-law, Eb succeeds in destroying the farmer's cabbage crop. To get back in the man's good graces, Eb pawns Oliver's cow Eleanor so he can make the Appleby's mortgage payment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226030000 +0000" stop="20241226033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Experts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan saves a German radio expert whom the Nazis want to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226033000 +0000" stop="20241226040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Masterpiece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that the kommandant is a great painter so the prisoners can meet an underground contact at an art gallery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226040000 +0000" stop="20241226043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Carol And Sis / Back Alley</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol has the Hong Kong Flu, and Harvey is terrified he'll get it. Then, in Back Alley, a parody of "Back Street", Harvey finds himself married every time he falls in love with Carol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226043000 +0000" stop="20241226053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Robert Crane is charged with the murder of his sister's estranged husband, Mason needs the testimony of sister Helen Reed to clear him of the charge. Unfortunately for all concerned, Helen suffers from multiple personality disorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226053500 +0000" stop="20241226060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Martian Please Stand Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Troopers follow the tracks from a frozen pond into a diner. Inside they find a soda jerk, a bus driver and his seven passengers. The bus driver is certain only six people boarded his bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226060500 +0000" stop="20241226063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Crackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Two newlyweds stay at the same hotel as a man with whom they got into a scuffle with earlier that day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226063500 +0000" stop="20241226070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In 4-d</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband has a vague memory of helping a woman get rid of a corpse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226070500 +0000" stop="20241226080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Carol Lockwood, Past Tense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix seeks to prove that the death of one of his former gal-pals was not an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226080500 +0000" stop="20241226090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Cain's Mark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired when a young brother of a gun manufacturer and collector vanishes from sight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226090500 +0000" stop="20241226100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dance With Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When a friend of a disco dancer is found murdered, she believes she's a killer's real target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226100000 +0000" stop="20241226103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Prospector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A poor prospector arouses suspicion when he suddenly begins paying off long-standing debts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226103000 +0000" stop="20241226110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226110000 +0000" stop="20241226113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen With A Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Wells appears to have met his match with a new partner who always insists on doing things his own way. Today's shift features a hot-headed husband who's decided he needs a gun to protect his home, and a neglected girl who causes a scare while playing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226113000 +0000" stop="20241226120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Follow Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he's got a great deal lined up on a used boat, but Malloy's convinced there's something fishy going on. While on patrol, they search for a man who sold a stolen horse to a riding academy, use an informant's tip to investigate a suspicious restaurant parking lot attendant and face an accusation of stealing a socialite's diamond ring during a burglary investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226120000 +0000" stop="20241226130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Old News</sub-title>
    <desc>"Breaking News! Bill and Toony become newscasters and profile legendary news anchor, Bill Kurtis."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226130000 +0000" stop="20241226133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Stocks And Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally become interested in the stock market and Ward decides that they should try their hand at it. However, Wally and Beaver have different ideas about what to invest in compared to Ward who wants them to play it safe and invest in Mayfield Power and Electric, while they want to invest in a more risky venture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226133000 +0000" stop="20241226140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Untogetherness</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Cleavers are all excited about their annual summer vacation up to the cabin, that is except Wally. Wanting to be close to his latest girl, Wally wants to stay behind and gets permission to stay at Eddie's house during the two weeks the Cleavers are on vacation, but June and Ward are a bit unsure of Wally's plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226140000 +0000" stop="20241226150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cowardly Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hilde Fursten and Tony Osgood work at the San Diego Zoo. When a baby monkey goes missing, Fursten is blamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226150000 +0000" stop="20241226160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 2  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226160000 +0000" stop="20241226170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Even Nice People: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Corrupt developers set their sights on Lana's farm. When she refuses to sell they enlist the services of an arsonist to force her out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226170000 +0000" stop="20241226180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Violated</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier is sending his wife mail, but getting no replies</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226180000 +0000" stop="20241226190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After killer Jay Wrecken is shot dead, man's brother begins methodically murdering everyone connected to the incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226190000 +0000" stop="20241226200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Pink Cloud Comes From Old Cathay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A headstrong Chinese girl (Marlo Thomas) visiting the Cartwrights incites labor unrest among local workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226200000 +0000" stop="20241226203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226203000 +0000" stop="20241226210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226210000 +0000" stop="20241226220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jeff Hartfield Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jeff Hartfield becomes concerned when his sister Jenny begins dating Dallas who threatens him with an orphanage at journey's end. Jeff takes off but Dallas follows with deadly intent, believing Jeff knows the location of $30,000."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226220000 +0000" stop="20241226230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nagging Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy picks winning horses from the newspaper and Johnny wants to know how he does it. The paramedics rescue a woman who has fallen into a lion’s cage, a dancer in a bar and an adult skateboarder who landed in a cactus patch. They also save a bleeding policeman from a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226230000 +0000" stop="20241226233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226233000 +0000" stop="20241227000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227000000 +0000" stop="20241227003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227003000 +0000" stop="20241227010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Ma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes home to his mother, as Hawkeye conducts the camp foot inspection, and Colonel Potter gets some shrapnel in his backside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227010000 +0000" stop="20241227013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227013000 +0000" stop="20241227020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227020000 +0000" stop="20241227023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Frog Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny thinks Jethro has turned into a frog after he went swimming and takes him to Dr. Klinger in the bank building. Jethro stops by the bank and takes the frog home. Granny sees him at home and thinks he is cured. Jed decides to learn to be a frogman too, but when he tells Jethro, Granny jumps on him to stop him. Jethro takes Granny to her room, and Granny begs someone to end her suffering.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227023000 +0000" stop="20241227030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Candidate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Fed up with the lousy condition of the Hooterville highway, Oliver launches an attack on their beloved state district representative, Ben Hanks. The folksy, duck-calling, guitar-playing politician proves too wily for Oliver, even when caught padding the state payroll with relatives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227030000 +0000" stop="20241227033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An English traitor, who could pass for Colonel Crittendon's twin brother, parachutes into camp with information for Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227033000 +0000" stop="20241227040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan becomes convinced that Crittendon can't fool Hitler, things get complicated when Chitterly escapes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227040000 +0000" stop="20241227043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ruth Buzzi And Richard Crenna</sub-title>
    <desc>In Salute to Bad Girls, Carol and the gang pay homage to classic films and their scheming starlets, including "The Graduate", "All About Eve", "Born to Be Bad",</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227043000 +0000" stop="20241227053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Empty Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Doris Hocksley is shown a personal ad in a Los Angeles newspaper for locating the daughter of Adam Hocksley and providing proof of same. A friend, John Lowell, suggests she pursue the idea to prove she is the rightful heir to the Adam Hocksley estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227053500 +0000" stop="20241227060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsolete Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a future state where religion and books have been banned, a librarian is judged obsolete and sentenced to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227060500 +0000" stop="20241227063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother, Richard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man kills his brother’s opponent for the governor’s office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227063500 +0000" stop="20241227070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Manacled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal offers $50,000 to a detective in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227070500 +0000" stop="20241227080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Cage A Sea Gull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The site of a helicopter accident uncovers the body of a member of the Nazi party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227080500 +0000" stop="20241227090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Moonlight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A young convict is being harassed by a prisoner who is running a gambling operation inside of the lock up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227090500 +0000" stop="20241227100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Protectors, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An assault on a businessman leads Barnaby to work with a firm that specializes in preventing terrorist kidnappings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227100000 +0000" stop="20241227103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Several law-abiding citizens unknowingly help a charming murderer escape.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
