<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607000000 +0000" stop="20250607003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Spoiled Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Arnold the spoiled kid moves to town, he thinks he can walk all over the townsfolk, including Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607003000 +0000" stop="20250607010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Filling Station Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is accused of being the mysterious crook who's been robbing Wally's filling station. Andy and Barney try to determine his guilt or innocence in a variety of methods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607010000 +0000" stop="20250607013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Pollution Solution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale is trying to get his money back, while Jed is trying to prevent him from doing so. And Jethro is trying to come up with a way to beat the smog problem. Drysdale sends Jane over to get the money, posing as a guard. When Jed doesn't give it to him, Drysdale tells him what he's got is a drop in the bucket, and only the President could really do anything. Jed returns the money and says he plans to give all his money to the President.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607013000 +0000" stop="20250607020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Deciding Vote</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is busy buying Alice a vacuum while Norton is the deciding vote in the Raccoon election for convention manager.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607020000 +0000" stop="20250607023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607023000 +0000" stop="20250607030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Rocket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to detour the German bombers that normally attack London to a nearby Allied airbase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607030000 +0000" stop="20250607033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Judgment Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In 1942, a German wonders why he's on the deck of a British steamship, with no memory of how he got there, and an overwhelming sense of impending doom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607033000 +0000" stop="20250607043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Captain's Coins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Historian Phillip Andrews argues that his fiancée, Evelyn Faraday, is entitled to a share of a shipping company fortune. Phillip then finds himself accused of murdering the company's top man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607043500 +0000" stop="20250607050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607050500 +0000" stop="20250607053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>There Was An Old Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old and eccentric woman is targeted by a crooked couple who think she has a lot of money stashed away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607053500 +0000" stop="20250607060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Whodunit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur comes back from the afterlife to find out the identity of his murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607060500 +0000" stop="20250607070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Cry Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Thanks to an old gal-pal, Mannix gets trapped in the middle of a feud between rival smugglers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607070500 +0000" stop="20250607080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Of San Ignacio</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Stolen precious artifacts from a church in Mexico, has Cannon in search of three suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607080500 +0000" stop="20250607090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadline For Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A journalist's investigation of a land scandal ends in murder and blackmail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607090000 +0000" stop="20250607093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bedloe And Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Homer Bedloe returns to Hooterville with his son, Homer Jr., who is a carbon copy of his dad.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607093000 +0000" stop="20250607100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Local Girl Makes Good</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A former resident returns to Hooterville and seems to be a self-made woman. Mary Jane is a business executive who can handle any situation and seems to have a way with men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607100000 +0000" stop="20250607103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Cook-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Even though the Clampetts are enjoying Maria’s cooking, Granny is upset that there is another cook in her kitchen. She wants Maria to leave, and Jed knows Maria leaving is the best thing to make everything right. However, Jethro is in love with Maria, hoping to marry her. Jane figures out a way to get Maria in good with Granny. She arranges a meeting between the two cooks, and Jane tells Maria to answer "Yes" to everything.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607103000 +0000" stop="20250607110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Jethro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed and Granny decide Jethro needs a job. They send him down to the bank to try to get work. While he is there, he runs into a magician, Marvo the Magnificent. After Marvo learns of his uncle’s many, many millions, he agrees to go home with Jethro. Marvo puts on a show for the Clampetts, and afterwards Jethro decides to become a magician.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607110000 +0000" stop="20250607113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Protek The Weakerist, Peep In The Deep, A Dream Walking</sub-title>
    <desc>"Olive asks Popeye to walk her dog, but he's embarrassed by Flyppy., When Popeye searches for treasure, Bluto tries to beat him to it., Popeye and Bluto are awaken from their sleep by the sound of Olive Oyl sleepwalking."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607113000 +0000" stop="20250607120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Calypso Cat, The Mad Maestro, Cat And The Mermouse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom falls for a female cat but she quickly loses interest in him when they arrive at an island and Jerry torments him., A maestro conducts an orchestra of various animals but some of them aren’t very good at following his directions., Tom drowns in a lake, and goes to the bottom. There, he finds a mermouse, and then tries to capture it and eat it. The mermouse doesn't give in so easily, though."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607120000 +0000" stop="20250607130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Woody's Magic Touch, Pigeon Holed, Salmon Yeggs, Wet Blanket Policy, Scrappy Birthday, Adventures Of Tom Thumb Jr., Ace In The Hole</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody must trick a witch in order to transform the king's son back into a human again., Homer Pigeon goes to the doctor for glasses, only to realize his poor vision has led him to the induction center for the Pigeonaire Corps instead., Windy tries to show his son Breezy how to steal from a salmon cannery, but gets sealed in a can himself., Buzz Buzzard tries to collect on Woody Woodpecker's life insurance policy by any means necessary!, Andy buys a hound to catch a fox and make a fox fur coat for his girlfriend's birthday present., Tom Thumb discovers a new island, but he's taken by a giant who always wanted a son., Woody Woodpecker is a stable boy who longs to fly a plane. But the bulldog sergeant on the airfield stands in his way."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607130000 +0000" stop="20250607140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Half-fare Hare, Fox Terror, A Peck O' Trouble, Roman Legion-hare, Odor-able Kitty, Fast Buck Duck, Wet Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs is chased on a train by two bums that want him for food. , A sneaky fox tries to use the arguments between Foghorn and the Dog to get into the chicken coop. He tries to trick Foghorn with a variety of salesman ploys to steer both the chicken and dog away from the coop. , Dodsworth, a lazy cat, tries to teach a kitten how to catch a woodpecker so that he can have breakfast without doing any physical work. , Yosemite Sam selects Bugs Bunny to be a victim for the Roman Colosseum. , A tomcat dresses up like a skunk because he thinks it will be easier to get food that way. What he actually does is attract the attention of Pepe LePew who chases him all over the land., Desperate and down in the gutter, Daffy hears of a millionaire offering a great job position. He only needs to get in to the house to get the interview, but the bulldog just won't let him in., Bugs Bunny is taking a shower under a waterfall when suddenly the water stops. He goes up to see what the problem is and meets a lumberjack who wants all the water for himself. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607140000 +0000" stop="20250607150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Headless Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>On a dusty Californian trail, Jim and Artemus intercept a stagecoach whose driver has been hired to smuggle boll weevils. Quickly theorizing that someone is trying to destroy the country's cotton crop, they set out to find the mastermind of the operation and destroy his distribution system before his plan succeeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607150000 +0000" stop="20250607160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jasper Cato Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting a safe escort through indian country, a stranger rides upon the wagon train. After telling the major his reasons for being there, the truth is soon uncovered and it causes two men to change their lifelong habits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607160000 +0000" stop="20250607170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Martyr</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Jarrod defends a basque sheepherder—a self-described anarchist—who is accused of murdering a cattleman. He finds that not all of the basque community wants his client to be acquitted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607170000 +0000" stop="20250607173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Horse Deal</sub-title>
    <desc>"Deesha accuses Emmett Bowers of stealing his horses. Bowers tells Matt he bought them. Slim and Jake Wirth have the same trouble. Matt must find the horse thief before a lynch mob forms."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607173000 +0000" stop="20250607180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Johnny Red</sub-title>
    <desc>"Johnny Red asks the Marshall where the Crale ranch is. Says he's Mrs Crale's long lost son Billy. Matt doesn't think so because the War Dept said that Billy was killed at the Battle of Shilo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607180000 +0000" stop="20250607190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Severe Case Of Matrimony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Rosalita hopes to win the Cartwrights as patrons of her opera career. There's just one problem with her plan: she lacks the skill to make a career of opera!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607190000 +0000" stop="20250607193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sidewinder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gridley Mau is gunning for Lucas, who killed his father during an attempted robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607193000 +0000" stop="20250607200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sixteenth Cousin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese nobleman seeks revenge when his servant is insulted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607200000 +0000" stop="20250607210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Painted Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Partners of Thad Clemens are holding Favor's herd until they're paid the $15,000 that Thad swindled them out of. Baxter Springs Cattleman's Association will not help Favor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607210000 +0000" stop="20250607213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Full Circle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who left Paladin to die in his place writes to Paladin and asks for his help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607213000 +0000" stop="20250607220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Amos Carter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh's big talk lands him in big trouble when his browbeating the locals about ending the decades-long Carter-Blake feud gets him drafted to go reconcile the hate-fueled hillbillies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250607220000 +0000" stop="20250608000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Higher Than A Kite, Idle Roomers, Shivering Sherlocks, Who Done It, Three Little Twirps, Some More Of Samoa</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are auto mechanics working for the R.A.F. in England.  After wrecking an officers car they need a place to hide, but their choice, a sewer pipe, turns out to a bomb, which is dropped on the enemy.  Finding themselves behind enemy lines, Moe and Curly disguise as German officers and Larry dresses as a seductive fraulein.  While general Bommel chases after Larry, Moe and Curly steal the secret plans from the high command. , The Stooges are working as bellboys in a large hotel when a side show promoter shows up with 'Lupe', a wild wolfman who promptly escapes.  The Stooges try to capture the wolfman by playing music to calm him, but music makes the wolfman go berserk and soon the Stooges are the ones trying to run away.  The boys end up caught in an elevator with the wolfman who shoots them into the sky. , The Stooges are tree surgeons who are enlisted by a rich old man to find a mate for his rare puckerless persimmon tree.  The boys sail to the tropical island of Rhum-Boogie to find the tree.  When they arrive they are captured by the natives and will be eaten unless Curly marries the Chief's ugly daughter.  The Stooges escape with the tree and, after a confrontation with an alligator; sail off with their prize. , The Stooges witness an armed robbery and are brought in by the cops as suspects.  After passing a lie detector test, the boys are freed but are now the only ones who can identify the crooks.  Meanwhile, their friend Gladys has inherited a house in the country and the boys go with her to inspect it so she won't be gypped when it's sold.  The house turns out to be the crook's hideout, and when they abduct Gladys, the Stooges must rescue her. , The Stooges are private detectives looking for a missing millionaire.  They wander around the millionaire's spooky mansion confronting various crooks and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man. , The Stooges get a job putting up posters for a circus but discover that instead of money, their pay is tickets to the show.  When trying to scalp their tickets gets them in trouble, they hide out backstage where Curly has an encounter with a bearded lady and Moe and Larry hide in a horse suit.  When they're caught, the circus manager gives them a choice of going to jail or joining the circus.  What they don't know is that they are to be targets for the Zulu spear thrower.  When Curly hits the spear thrower with one of his own spears, the boys are on the run once again. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608000000 +0000" stop="20250608023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Strait-jacket</sub-title>
    <desc>"A crazed axe murderer, released after spending 20 years in a mental institution for lopping the heads off her husband and his lover, returns home to her daughter, who witnessed the slayings as a three-year-old. Shortly after her return, heads begin to roll again, with all the evidence pointing to the woman, who begins to think she's gone insane."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608023000 +0000" stop="20250608030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Is Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Joker escapes from prison, Batman and Robin search for him, certain he'll attack. However, Batman's secret identity is in jeopardy when the Joker finally surfaces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608030000 +0000" stop="20250608040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Turnabout Intruder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise is in danger when Janice Lester, one of Kirk's former lovers, steals his body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608040000 +0000" stop="20250608050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Zombie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A grandmother seeks revenge for her grandson's death by turning him into a zombie to do her bidding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608050000 +0000" stop="20250608060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Junkyard In Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Jupiter 2 lands on a planet which serves as a junkyard. The Robinson's food supply is dwindling, so Dr. Smith tries to sell the robot and the ship in order to get food.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608060000 +0000" stop="20250608070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Monster From Outer Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A Saturn space probe re-enters the Earth with a strange creature attached to its surface.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608070000 +0000" stop="20250608080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Seven Little Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Kobick captures Chipper and uses the dog as bait to lure in the Earthlings one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608080000 +0000" stop="20250608090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Sky Fell In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At Pearl Harbor on December 6, 1941, Tony and Doug find Tony's father, reported missing after the attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608090000 +0000" stop="20250608100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Wall Of Crystal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent discovers a crystal with alien connections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608100000 +0000" stop="20250608110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Genius</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt temporarily loses his powers to something unknown."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608110000 +0000" stop="20250608113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>From Nurse To Worse   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack falls for a new student, only to discover that she's actually the new school nurse! Meanwhile, Slater is afraid of getting his flu shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608113000 +0000" stop="20250608120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Save The Max   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The return of Bayside's radio station is a smash...except for Slater's boring sports broadcast. When he finds out no one likes it, he quits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608120000 +0000" stop="20250608123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>1-900-crushed   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack sets up a 900-number hotline in his latest moneymaking scheme, with Lisa offering advice to the students of Bayside. Things go awry, however, when Zack takes over and offers terrible advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608123000 +0000" stop="20250608130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Driver's Education   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jealous of Slater's skills in Driver's Education, Zack sabotages his driving test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608130000 +0000" stop="20250608133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Palm Springs Weekend: Part 1   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jessie is excited to meet her new stepmother at her father's wedding, until she learns he is marrying a much younger woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608133000 +0000" stop="20250608140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Palm Springs Weekend: Part 2   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack tries to stop Jessie from postponing her dad's wedding. Meanwhile, Slater discovers that his new girlfriend is in fact royalty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608140000 +0000" stop="20250608143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>In the series opener, Mike Brady, a widower with three boys, marries Carol Martin, a widow with three girls. There are a few chaotic events at the wedding, and things get off to a rough start for everyone, but somehow, this group forms a family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608143000 +0000" stop="20250608150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Elopement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia and Jan mistakenly overhear Sam and Alice discussing elopement and jump to the conclusion that Sam and Alice are secretly planning to marry. The family begins planning a wedding reception, until Alice sets them straight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608150000 +0000" stop="20250608153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Married Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>It's their 23rd anniversary, and Howard and Marion are angry at each other over a rate-your-mate test they took in a magazine. They are to go on a second honeymoon, but Marion angers Howard even further when she wants everything to be exactly the same as it was on their first.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608153000 +0000" stop="20250608160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>The Mummy's Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Shirley marries Walter Meeney at a VA hospital. The bride is dressed in white, and so is the groom—white bandages from head to toe!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608160000 +0000" stop="20250608163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Wife For Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy should be getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608163000 +0000" stop="20250608170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Marriage License</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy thinks she and Ricky aren't legally married because his name was misspelled on their marriage license. So she wants them to renew their vows at the same place in Connecticut where Ricky first proposed to her. However, they run out of gas getting there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608170000 +0000" stop="20250608173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Parking Attendants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The social event of the season, according to Fred Rutherford, is a big party that a wealthy family is throwing and he rubs it in due to the fact that June and Ward didn't get an invitation. However, Wally and Eddie will be there after they get jobs parking the guest's cars. However, trouble ensues when Eddie parks Fred's car in a no parking spot and the car gets towed away by the city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608173000 +0000" stop="20250608180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brotherly Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>June has had it with Wally and Beaver's fighting and demands they make a pact to be nice to one another and do things together. However, when each boy gets an invitation for individual social outings, they each attempt to break the pact.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608180000 +0000" stop="20250608183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Plans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Matthew Templeton says he’d be proud to marry Elly, the Clampetts begin to plan and rehearse Elly's wedding. Meanwhile, Drysdale tries to stop this wedding from happening, or at least from losing his largest account. He goes to Silver Dollar City and decides to buy the Bank of Bugtussle so he can still handle his favorite account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608183000 +0000" stop="20250608190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Annul That Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Shorty and Gloria get married, everyone but the two of them want the marriage annulled. Gloria decides she’d like to experience what her new life will be like, and Jed tells her that he’ll show her. When he calls the mansion to tell them to put up the cabin, Granny thinks he got married as well. But when both “couples” come home, Granny, Jethro, and Elly learn that Shorty got married, but Elverna didn’t, and Gloria got married, but Jed didn’t, making Jethro and Granny believe both couples are in a Hollywood marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608190000 +0000" stop="20250608193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs.???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A radio bulletin states that the minister who married the Howell's was a fraud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608193000 +0000" stop="20250608200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Forget Me Not</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>The Professor tries to cure the Skipper's amnesia by hypnotizing him and taking him through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608200000 +0000" stop="20250608203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Alien Marriage  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Vint schemes to make money by pretending to be married to a girl from Portugal in need of a green card—until Mama catches wind of the plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608203000 +0000" stop="20250608210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>I Do, I Don't  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After attending a big wedding, Bubba, Iola and Mama each fantasize what it would be like to be married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608210000 +0000" stop="20250608220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Father Of The Bride / Best Man / Members Of The Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A wedding at sea ... the bride's father warns the best man to stay away from his other daughter; the groom's grandfather is picked up from a small boat at sea; and Ace moons over the one that got away: the bride.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608220000 +0000" stop="20250608223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mountain Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney visit the Darlings to rid them of Ernest T. Bass, who has his mind set on marrying daughter Charlene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608223000 +0000" stop="20250608230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Michael Lefevre- Snoopy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mike Lefevre was five years old when his father brought his little sister home from the hospital, holding her in one hand and a plush Snoopy in the other. For Mike, it was love at first sight , for both his sibling and her stuffed toy. And from that moment on, America’s favorite anthropomorphic beagle became a fixture in Mike's life. By the time he was ten, he had acquired more than a dozen Snoopy collectibles. Today, his collection contains more than 15,000 Snoopy items.  And they are on full display for all to see in a museum he has built at his waterfront restaurant in suburban Detroit. Our pop culture toy expert, Johnpaul Ragusa, has his own connection to the Peanuts character. His wife is an avid fan, and his home is filled with Snoopy paraphernalia."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608230000 +0000" stop="20250608233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love And Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper prevent a GI from marrying a call girl who has TB, while trying to help a Korean soldier join his pregnant wife. Radar, of course, provides his usual invaluable help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250608233000 +0000" stop="20250609000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609000000 +0000" stop="20250609003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Maude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith's cousin, Maude, invites Archie and Edith to the wedding of her daughter, Carol. However, Carol and Maude are not looking forward to Archie, since the man she is marrying happens to be Jewish. Later, the men and the women have their respective bachelor and bachelorette parties, but a grumpy Archie decides to stay in the motel. Meanwhile, Carol realizes just what her fiancée envisions as married life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609003000 +0000" stop="20250609010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Flashback: Mike &amp; Gloria's Wedding (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is in a celebratory mood for Mike and Gloria's second wedding anniversary. While sitting around the dinner table enjoying a special cake, the family recalls Mike and Gloria's wedding. They also recall how Mike's Uncle Casimir met Archie and how they butted heads over who would perform the ceremony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609010000 +0000" stop="20250609013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Flashback: Mike &amp; Gloria's Wedding (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The family continues to reminisce on Mike and Gloria's second wedding anniversary and they recall the actual day Mike and Gloria got married. As Archie and Mike's Uncle Casimir continue to butt heads, Edith must gather up strength to tell Gloria about 'the birds and the bees'.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609013000 +0000" stop="20250609020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Lionel's Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith, Mike and Gloria are each extended a special invitation to attend Lionel's engagement party. However, Archie isn't invited, that is until a big argument between Louise and George results in Louise deciding to invite him. Later, during the party, George is in for a big shock when it turns out that Lionel's fiancée, Jennie has interracial parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609020000 +0000" stop="20250609023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Michele Lee  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Michele Lee. Originally aired on 04/13/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609023000 +0000" stop="20250609030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Paul Sand</sub-title>
    <desc>In After the Wedding, Carol's husband becomes jealous when she kisses another man goodbye. Then, in Energy Crisis Blackouts, everyone's life is complicated when the electricity stops. Finally, in Wedding Plans, divorcees discuss their future wedding plans, only to discover they may still love their old spouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609030000 +0000" stop="20250609033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Attempted Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recounts his hectic wedding days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609033000 +0000" stop="20250609040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jilting The Jilter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Sally dates a comedian who never paid Rob and Buddy for writing his material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609040000 +0000" stop="20250609043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Here Comes The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph's advice to a lodge brother on how to be head of the household has his wife (Alice's sister) in tears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609043000 +0000" stop="20250609053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Thirty-fathom Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A U.S. naval destroyer investigates a mysterious tapping sound that appears to be coming from a sunken submarine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609053000 +0000" stop="20250609060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Help Wanted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man desperate for money takes on a strange job offer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609060000 +0000" stop="20250609070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Decoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Anna Kerkoska plans to defect with a list of American agents given to her by her father, the late premier. Her brother, Alexi, also plans to defect, but it's actually a plan to grab the list, turn it over to Police Chief Petrovitch and sell out his sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609070000 +0000" stop="20250609080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble unwittingly hitches a ride with Hanes McClure, a wanted criminal out to settle a score in his Georgia hometown. When Hanes attempts to crash a barricade, Kimble grabs the wheel to save an innocent life, but it gets both of them arrested. Both Kimbl</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609080000 +0000" stop="20250609090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of A Frame</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell fights to clear his friend Lt. Trench when the police detective is framed for the murder of a narcotics informant."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609090000 +0000" stop="20250609093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Personnel - The Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The problems of policemen's wives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609093000 +0000" stop="20250609100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - The Student</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The police go after a college student who has turned to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609100000 +0000" stop="20250609103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 95 -- Purse Snatcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy have to think outside the box to capture an intelligent yet neglected teenage purse snatcher. Their efforts to talk sense into him before he commits a much more serious crime prove to be futile.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609103000 +0000" stop="20250609110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 45 -- Bright Boy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy report to a burglary call that was witnessed by a boy with a photographic memory. Afterward, they are called to the scene of two drunk men shooting at a box of dynamite at close range in a residential area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609110000 +0000" stop="20250609120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Challenge Of The Channels</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony put their athletic skills to the test with the help of a special network guest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609120000 +0000" stop="20250609123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Water, Anyone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wally and his friends are trying to earn enough money to buy baseball uniforms so they put a plan into action by doing their chores at a slow pace in order to maximize their hourly pay. Meanwhile, Beaver, also wanting to be on the team, begins selling water to his family and neighbors."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609123000 +0000" stop="20250609130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Crush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has a crush on his teacher, Miss Canfield. When Judy, Whitey and Larry tease him for being a "teacher's pet," Beaver tries to prove them wrong and places a spring snake in her desk. However, Beaver has second thoughts and becomes determined to remove the snake before she finds it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609130000 +0000" stop="20250609140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Murderous Mermaid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>After a swimming stunt goes horribly wrong, a young woman is charged with orchestrating the mayhem, and Mason must set the record straight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609140000 +0000" stop="20250609150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 1  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired by a friend to defend his enlisted son. The boy's been charged with killing a sadistic lieutenant whose mistreatment led to the death of another soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609150000 +0000" stop="20250609160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Family Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict attempts to retrieve his loot from his wife and her new husband in this tongue-in-cheek episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609160000 +0000" stop="20250609170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Competition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen and Erin both fall for a forestry student</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609170000 +0000" stop="20250609173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tail To The Wind</sub-title>
    <desc>"Burke Reese and his son want Pezzy Nellar &amp; his wife Cora to sell their farm but they don’t want to sell. Matt asks Pezzy to swear out a complaint against Reese and his son when Pezzy’s chicken coop gets burned but he says he can’t swear it was Reese."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609173000 +0000" stop="20250609180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Annie Oakley</sub-title>
    <desc>"Kate wants her husband Jeff Kinsman to kill Ed Dolliver because she says Dolliver insulted her. When Jeff winds up dead Kate accuses Dolliver. Kate gets mad when Matt doesn’t arrest Dolliver and tells him she’ll make trouble if Matt doesn’t do something about it. Matt comes up with a plan to find out who really killed Jeff."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609180000 +0000" stop="20250609190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Stage Door Johnnies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss and Little Joe vie for the attention of visiting entertainer Mademoiselle Denise, but she has no time for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609190000 +0000" stop="20250609193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Hostages To Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>At Halloween, rustlers take advantage of the seasonal disguises to raid a cattle ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609193000 +0000" stop="20250609200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>And The Devil Makes Five</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A snake crawls into Lucas' bed, and Mark must lure it away before it strikes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609200000 +0000" stop="20250609210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Vivian Carter Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Getting set to leave the wagon train, Vivian Carter finds out that a friend from the train is heading off to a new life and marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609210000 +0000" stop="20250609220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Insomnia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A boat has an explosion en route to the marina. John obsesses about the lack of night runs and can't sleep. A man and his son are injured when they swerve to avoid a dog. Doctors race against time to save a marijuana smoker dying of an unidentifiable malady. A worker is pinned in a loading dock by a semi. A man and child fall into a gravel pit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609220000 +0000" stop="20250609223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609223000 +0000" stop="20250609230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609230000 +0000" stop="20250609233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250609233000 +0000" stop="20250610000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Ma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes home to his mother, as Hawkeye conducts the camp foot inspection, and Colonel Potter gets some shrapnel in his backside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610000000 +0000" stop="20250610003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Discovers America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie doesn't like his new teacher, "Old Lady Crump," because she gives too much homework. Andy comments on the teacher, words which Opie twists in his retelling to Ms. Crump, and she is furious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610003000 +0000" stop="20250610010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Medicine Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, saddened by the death of a friend, is feeling old and tired. She stumbles across a medicine man's presentation and is intrigued by his bottle of elixir, which she believes to add pep to her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610010000 +0000" stop="20250610013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>That Old Black Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny believes that Mrs. Drysdale has turned herself into a bird after she said a few zodiacal words, which Granny believes is black magic. Granny does what she can to change her back to normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610013000 +0000" stop="20250610020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Something Fishy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton don't want to take their wives on a Raccoon fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610020000 +0000" stop="20250610023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Information Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After detecting an information leak in the area of Stalag 13, the Germans replace Klink with a more efficient officer, who Hogan sets up to take the fall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610023000 +0000" stop="20250610030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Art For Hogan's Sake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a French painting from ending up in Goering's art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610030000 +0000" stop="20250610033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>And When The Sky Was Opened</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When three U.S. astronauts return to Earth after the first flight into space, they begin being erased from history one by one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610033000 +0000" stop="20250610043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tarnished Trademark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Axel Norstaad sells his much respected furniture trademark to Martin Somers, described by some as the slide trombone of the furniture business. Somers immediately begins stripping the company of its assets and churning out inferior products.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610043500 +0000" stop="20250610050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer is shot while making a routine check on a pair of paroled convicts parked near a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610050500 +0000" stop="20250610053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of Jocelyn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds his disappeared wife in a painting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610053500 +0000" stop="20250610060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Orderly World Of Appleby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lawrence Appleby will do anything to keep his antiques shop, even murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610060500 +0000" stop="20250610070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>All The Dead Were Strangers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates when a plane crash is followed by murder attempts on the survivors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610070500 +0000" stop="20250610080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Blood On The Vine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor who is conducting a medical research project at the state prison is the victim of harassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610080500 +0000" stop="20250610090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of Thy Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A pilot's body, slashed by a propeller, is found on an airship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610090000 +0000" stop="20250610093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>S.i.u. - The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon recruit a woman cop to nab a burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610093000 +0000" stop="20250610100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Medical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate cases in a hospital emergency ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610100000 +0000" stop="20250610103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 65 -- Cigarettes, Cars And Wild, Wild Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy help take down a chop-shop that employs cute girls in mini-skirts to steal cars from trusting men. They also arrest a young man who grows pot and holds parties in the home of his unsuspecting shut-in aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610103000 +0000" stop="20250610110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 55 -- Missing Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After responding to a gas leak in a home, reed and malloy search for a missing child. Finally, they investigate an attempted car theft that ended with a fatal shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610110000 +0000" stop="20250610120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Bay State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore Massachusetts!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610120000 +0000" stop="20250610123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Clubhouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and his friends build a clubhouse, and Beaver wants to join. Although the dues are $1 for 8th graders, Beaver has to come up with $3 in order to join their club. How can Beaver earn the money?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610123000 +0000" stop="20250610130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Girl Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver dread attending dance school, so when Wally suddenly takes a liking in it, June and Ward are dumbfounded. It seems Wally has developed a crush on a girl named Penny and Beaver soon feels neglected and left out when Wally begins spending all his time with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610130000 +0000" stop="20250610140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Careless Kitten</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman receives a phone call from a man claiming to be her wealthy uncle who disappeared 10 years prior, Mason is called in to investigate. A proposed encounter with the man leads to the discovery of a corpse and soon the niece of the phantom uncle is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610140000 +0000" stop="20250610150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Court Martial: Part 2  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>As the murder case involving the death of a sadistic Army lieutenant progresses, Matlock discovers that the lieutenant and four other officers may have been involved in smuggling drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610150000 +0000" stop="20250610160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sanctuary: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A political prisoner who entered the country illegally, seeks sanctuary in a monastery. Gillespie and Tibbs find themselves at odds with Sheriff McComb when they try to help the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610160000 +0000" stop="20250610170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Emergence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Marsha, John-Boy's old girlfriend, returns to sell her family home at the urging of her fiance</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610170000 +0000" stop="20250610173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kangaroo</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a crazy man and his two sons whip a cowboy with a bullwhip almost killing the cowboy, Matt rescues the cowboy from the severe whipping. When Matt asks Chester to untie the cowboy, the man makes threats to punish Chester for his sinful ways. As Chester is walking home from the Long Branch, the man and his two sons kidnap Chester."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610173000 +0000" stop="20250610180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Saludos</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Chester find a young Indian woman (Sochi) on the prairie suffering from a gunshot wound. Matt and Chester take the young woman to Doc Adams for medical treatment, but the overall outlook for recovery does not look promising Once Matt hears that a white man shot the woman, Matt and Chester set after the man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610180000 +0000" stop="20250610190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Different Pines, Same Wind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe tries to drive an old woman away from a destructive strip miner, which she mistakes as an attempt to grab up her land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610190000 +0000" stop="20250610193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>End Of The Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is thrown into jail to stop him from murdering an old enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610193000 +0000" stop="20250610200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is baffled when the marshal of a neighboring town refuses to hold a gambler who just attempted murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610200000 +0000" stop="20250610210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Conchita Vasquez Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Suspecting a hurt girl he finds on the trail is part of a group of bandits, Flint cautiously helps her. He soon learns that she is all he suspects, but when her guardian is killed Flint becomes her only protection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610210000 +0000" stop="20250610220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inheritance Tax</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A child is trapped in a car under downed power lines. A stockbroker with heart problems is reluctant to be treated. An elderly woman that Roy and John treated the previous year dies and remembers them in her will. Dr. Early administers first aid to two young boys. A teenager loses a hamburger eating contest. The Paramedics treat a burn victim at an explosive fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610220000 +0000" stop="20250610223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Der Tag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter decides Frank would be less of a pain if the others were friendlier to him; they oblige, with some startling results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610223000 +0000" stop="20250610230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is injured in a jeep accident and, aware he has a concussion, babbles to a Korean family to keep himself awake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610230000 +0000" stop="20250610233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Some 38th Parallels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank tries to distinguish himself by selling the camp garbage, but it's Hawkeye who finds a use for it: he dumps it on a troublesome Colonel Coner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250610233000 +0000" stop="20250611000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Novocaine Mutiny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has Hawkeye up on charges of mutiny for usurping his authority when Potter was away on leave and Frank was the commanding officer. B.J., Potter and Radar are in attendance of the preliminary hearing, at which they hear conflicting versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611000000 +0000" stop="20250611003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darlings Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry is visited by an unusual family from the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611003000 +0000" stop="20250611010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's English Valet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A tourist from England has to do chores to pay off a fine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611010000 +0000" stop="20250611013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheik</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After entering an oil deal with Jed and O.K. Oil, the Sheik befriends the Clampetts, giving Jed four of his dancing girls for wives and tries to get the beautiful Elly May as one of his wives. Jed tries to give the girls back, while Jethro tries to enjoy some of the Sheik's life, mainly the company of his beautiful dancing girls, after selling his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611013000 +0000" stop="20250611020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Safety Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph has an accident on his way to receiving his Safest Bus Driver Award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611020000 +0000" stop="20250611023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The General Swap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan captures a German general to trade for an American general who dislikes Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611023000 +0000" stop="20250611030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611030000 +0000" stop="20250611033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>What You Need</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A two-bit thug thinks he's found the key to a better life in an old sidewalk salesman who has the uncanny ability to tell people what they need the most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611033000 +0000" stop="20250611043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Glamorous Ghost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eleanor Corbin pleads amnesia after police find her running and screaming through woods near her apartment building. Her loss of memory is of little help to her when she is later charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611043500 +0000" stop="20250611050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit And Run Driver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon use newspapers, radio and TV to publicize their clues to the identity of a hit-and-run driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611050500 +0000" stop="20250611053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Never Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen has a problem with alcohol, one that leaves her wondering what happened the previous night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611053500 +0000" stop="20250611060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentlemen From America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Howard Latimer accepts a peculiar bet: to spend the night at a supposedly haunted manor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611060500 +0000" stop="20250611070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Winifred, private secretary and lover of the publisher George Diamond, becomes a runaway witness when a woman falls into the sea and drowns after a quarrel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611070500 +0000" stop="20250611080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Guinea Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon discovers that a man is posing as the son of a wine maker is likely the suspect of the three death attempts already tried against his "father."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611080500 +0000" stop="20250611090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Dive, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Treasure hunters falsify the facts of a diver's death to prevent anyone from meddling in their quest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611090000 +0000" stop="20250611093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Mister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The police zero in on a rat: a forger, bigamist and thief who even robs from the blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611093000 +0000" stop="20250611100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Little Pusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates the junior high drug scene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611100000 +0000" stop="20250611103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 75: Have A Nice Weekend</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers investigate robberies, attempted arson and a violent argument."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611103000 +0000" stop="20250611110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 105 -- Elegy For A Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Malloy pays tribute to Officer Tom Porter, who has recently fallen in the line of duty. Malloy recounts the close friendship they developed while training at the academy, as well as the moments where they crossed paths on duty, including the night of the officer's unfortunate demise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611110000 +0000" stop="20250611120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Tour Of 1994</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill rolls the pop-culture clock back 30 years to the era when... he had a Rachael cut?? "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611120000 +0000" stop="20250611123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Short Pants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When June goes on a trip to visit her sister, Peggy, June's Aunt Martha steps in and stays with Ward and the boys. They do their best not to hurt Martha's feelings, but Beaver has the hardest time, when she buys him a suit, knee socks, a cap and short pants and makes him wear the outfit to school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611123000 +0000" stop="20250611130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfume Salesmen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to win a fancy film projector and in order to get it they have to sell 24 bottles of perfume. However, the appalling aroma of the perfume quickly leads to zero sales and has Ward trying to think up a sales gimmick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611130000 +0000" stop="20250611140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Debt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A man suspects his father was killed by a gangster to whom he owed $10,000. When the gangster turns up dead, the timing couldn't be worse for the bereaving son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611140000 +0000" stop="20250611150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Therapist  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired to defend a popular actor accused of killing the owner of a sex-therapy clinic at which he was staying. Meanwhile, the lawyer also finds himself hounded by a law student looking for a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611150000 +0000" stop="20250611160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Law On Trial: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie, Tibbs and Father DiMarco must stand trial for harboring a fugitive and obstructing justice. Althea fears Virgil's career could suffer if he is found guilty. Meanwhile the other officers monitor the situation with Lawyer Epp and his mafia associates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611160000 +0000" stop="20250611170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Loss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Cousin Olivia, who married on the mountain in The Shivaree episode, returns to Walton's Mountain following her husband's sudden death</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611170000 +0000" stop="20250611173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Whelp</sub-title>
    <desc>"Sted Rutgers comes back to Dodge after 3 years to find that his brother Tom married his girl Tassy. Now Sted wants to kill Tom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611173000 +0000" stop="20250611180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Boots</sub-title>
    <desc>"Drunken ex-gunfighter Zeno promises 12 yr old orphan Tommy boots for his birthday. Gunfighter Hank Fergus who made Zeno lose his nerve comes back to Dodge to get Zeno to rob the General Store for him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611180000 +0000" stop="20250611190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is in line for a hanging when he is accused of murdering a wealthy man. But the town is more concerned over finding the location of the man's fortune than Hoss' punishment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611190000 +0000" stop="20250611193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem At Mission Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark is paralyzed, Lucas attempts to cure him at the mission.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611193000 +0000" stop="20250611200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>New arrival Mario Arsatti becomes very friendly with Lucas, but this turns out to be merely pleasure before business: he's been hired to kill Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611200000 +0000" stop="20250611210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sister Rita Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Leaving the safety of their village, a group of nuns sets out to help indians at a mission. Now Flint must help them fight off some Ute indians who don't take kindly to the nuns' presence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611210000 +0000" stop="20250611220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Zero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman screams for therapeutic reasons. When the paramedics are interviewed on a TV program, Johnny freezes in front of the camera and Roy must bail him out. A young boy attempts suicide by leaping off an apartment ledge at the hospital; the doctors suspect he may be an abused child. The paramedics rescue a man trapped in a doughnut machine and a child from a fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611220000 +0000" stop="20250611223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Smilin' Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th turns up a sick helicopter pilot, 'Smilin' Jack, who doesn't want to quit, and a twice-wounded GI who does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611223000 +0000" stop="20250611230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The More I See You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is reunited with a woman he thought was out of his life forever, but who never altogether leaves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611230000 +0000" stop="20250611233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deluge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A sudden deluge of wounded at the 4077th is followed by a fire and a rainstorm, which makes matters difficult for the staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250611233000 +0000" stop="20250612000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Interview</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Clete Roberts has arrived in Korea to interview the staff of the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital because of its high 97% efficiency rating. In Roberts' interviews with Hawkeye, B.J., Frank, Radar, Klinger, Mulcahy and Potter, they talk about how they cope with their situation, what they miss about home, how they feel about who they work with and whether they see any good in coming from war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612000000 +0000" stop="20250612003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rivals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his first crush, who ignores him. Barney steps in and tries to give him advice about women, which leads to Opie developing a crush on Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612003000 +0000" stop="20250612010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dogs, Dogs, Dogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Visiting officials take pause when they visit Mayberry and find that the courthouse is full of dogs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612010000 +0000" stop="20250612013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Private Eye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro continues his fantasy of being a double naught spy by getting an office at the bank. When two bank robbers arrive, who are interested in that office because it is above the vault, they make Jethro believe they are from London headquarters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612013000 +0000" stop="20250612020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Kramdens and Nortons enter a Raccoon costume contest a feud arises between Ralph and Ed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612020000 +0000" stop="20250612023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612023000 +0000" stop="20250612030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612030000 +0000" stop="20250612033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Four Of Us Are Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who can change his face to resemble others gets into hot water with gangsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612033000 +0000" stop="20250612043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Poison Pen-pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A casual pen pal relationship leads to insider information and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612043500 +0000" stop="20250612050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bookie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday goes undercover with the department's chaplain in order to bust a gambling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612050500 +0000" stop="20250612053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Lottie Slocum is excited to be the center of attention after the woman she babysits for is murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612053500 +0000" stop="20250612060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Belfry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A jealous man kills the fiancé of his unrequited love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612060500 +0000" stop="20250612070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harlequin's Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix searches for Australian sailor Paul Gantry, who is supposedly due to inherit a million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612070500 +0000" stop="20250612080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Island Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con is threatened when his safe cracking skills are needed for a theft of 1 million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612080500 +0000" stop="20250612090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Ransom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man returns from prison and learns that his partner in a ten-year-old kidnapping never gave back the abducted child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612090000 +0000" stop="20250612093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612093000 +0000" stop="20250612100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612100000 +0000" stop="20250612103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 25 -- Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed hunt down a suspect who has been bombing downtown storefronts. Then they report to a scuffle between two native americans at a bar that the bartender thinks may be a prelude to something a lot more serious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612103000 +0000" stop="20250612110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 135 -- Arson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In what would prove to be a very busy shift, Malloy and Reed search for a serial arsonist who spawns a copycat, settle a domestic dispute that results from a love triangle, rescue a man who wandered onto the ledge of a high rise and deal with a mentally ill man who is holding his wife at knife-point.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612110000 +0000" stop="20250612120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Land</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore ancient ruins and lost cities."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612120000 +0000" stop="20250612123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward make Wally and Beaver promise that they won't go see a scary movie. However, Wally and Beaver are talked into seeing it, thanks to Wally's so-called best friend, Eddie Haskell. The movie has quite an influence on Beaver, who makes a voodoo doll, names it Eddie Haskell and sticks it with pins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612123000 +0000" stop="20250612130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Part Time Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After taking an IQ test, Beaver scores the highest in his class and Mrs. Rayburn suggests that it would be best if Beaver went to a special school, where his abilities can be challenged. However, little does anyone know, everything is not as it seems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612130000 +0000" stop="20250612140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Gambling Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Counterfeit casino chips and chronic gambling lead to murder, and Mason suspects one of his clients may be culpable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612140000 +0000" stop="20250612150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>People Vs. Matlock  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>While defending a union boss (Dan Keaton) accused of murdering a rival, a juror (Harry Craven) comes forward with a bombshell: he claims Matlock paid him off to vote a certain way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612150000 +0000" stop="20250612160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Small War: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Big city crack dealers invade Sparta. Eugene witnesses the drive by shooting of a friend and his offer to help the police identify the shooters leaves Harriet frightened and angry at Bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612160000 +0000" stop="20250612170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Abdication</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>King Edward VIII abdicates the throne and the Waltons follow the story</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612170000 +0000" stop="20250612173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Odd Man Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cyrus Tucker tells the Marshall his wife has disappeared. When Hody Peel shows up in town selling used women's clothes it looks like he had something to do with her disappearance."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612173000 +0000" stop="20250612180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Muguel's Daughter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two drunken cowboys assault Chavela (Miguel's Daughter). When they come to talk to her later, they hit her father and while running away Chavela falls and hits her head. Miguel says the law has to be by a man's own hands. Matt says that he is the law not Miguel.   "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612180000 +0000" stop="20250612190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Salute To Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Candy gets a blast from the past when he runs into old friends from his days in the Army. Add gunfights, old flames, true love and the Cartwrights to the mix, and it spins an exciting tale!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612190000 +0000" stop="20250612193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Old Man Running (aka The Wanted Man)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas, who blames his wife's death on his father-in-law, refuses to help the old man elude gunmen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612193000 +0000" stop="20250612200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Which Way'd They Go?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The notoriously lazy Jackman brothers discover their mortgage has been foreclosed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612200000 +0000" stop="20250612210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Matthew Lowry Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Matthew Lowry seems timid to everyone, especially a bully on the wagon train. Riding upon some cholera-sick wagons in a pass, they find out who he really is and why he has been acting this way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612210000 +0000" stop="20250612220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Promise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Responding to a vehicle fire, the firemen discover a catatonic mechanic; at Rampart the doctors are mystified by his condition. Roy lectures a woman who keeps calling the paramedics because she is lonely. A woman mixes ammonia with bleach and inhales poisonous gas. An elderly couple is trapped in their house by a bunch of tumbleweeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612220000 +0000" stop="20250612223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Sight, Out Of Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While fixing a stove that explodes, Hawkeye's face is badly burned. His eyes are bandaged, and it is not known if he will ever see again. Meanwhile Frank bets on the outcome of a baseball game, which he has already heard on the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612223000 +0000" stop="20250612230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lt. Radar O'reilly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Following an offer of promotion made by Master Sergeant Woodruff at a poker game, Radar is promoted to the rank of lieutenant. Finding this position awkward, Radar opts to return to his position as an enlisted man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612230000 +0000" stop="20250612233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sigmund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman, feeling depressed, visits the 4077th to observe how they fare under the pressures of war. He begins a letter to Sigmund Freud as a form of self-therapy, and releases his tension in the form of a practical joke with B.J., aimed at Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250612233000 +0000" stop="20250613000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mulcahy's War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Frank discovers that Danny Fitzsimmons has shot himself to get out of combat, Father Mulcahy is called in. Realizing his lack of understanding of the fighting, Mulcahy accompanies Radar to an aid station, where they encounter the real war at first hand. Mulcahy performs an emergency tracheotomy, guided by Hawkeye over the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613000000 +0000" stop="20250613003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Opie and his friend, Arnold, hit a baseball into the window of an old, abandoned house, they hear noises and run for help. Barney and Gomer go to investigate—and hear noises, too!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613003000 +0000" stop="20250613010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon For Today</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting preacher gives a sermon about taking time to relax. In trying to create an atmosphere of relaxation on a Sunday afternoon, the townsfolk all end up running themselves ragged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613010000 +0000" stop="20250613013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Possum Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to keep the Clampetts in Beverly Hills by telling them there is going to be a Possum Day held there. Granny decides to run for Possum Queen in Beverly Hills, and Drysdale convinces her that she is running against Mrs. Drysdale. Meanwhile, Drysdale is desperate to actually get a Possum Day to happen for the Clampetts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613013000 +0000" stop="20250613020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph cuts a record to sweet talk Alice after insulting her mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613020000 +0000" stop="20250613023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613023000 +0000" stop="20250613030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613030000 +0000" stop="20250613033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Third From The Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>With all-out nuclear war about to ignite, a scientist and his pilot friend plot to escape on an experimental spaceship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613033000 +0000" stop="20250613043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mystified Miner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason tries to clear his young, beautiful client after a twisting and wheeling plot of murder, kidnapping and embezzlement unfolds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613043500 +0000" stop="20250613050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Subscription Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday learns about a scam artist with a novel twist: he uses an authentic Congressional Medal of Honor to solicit magazine subscriptions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613050500 +0000" stop="20250613053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hidden Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Dana needs to find the license plate number of the car that killed his fiancée.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613053500 +0000" stop="20250613060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A prince sets his eye on Irene and her money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613060500 +0000" stop="20250613070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix struggles to recall events that led to him being shot with his own gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613070500 +0000" stop="20250613080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Deadly Quiet Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The parents of a teen girl hire Cannon when they discover a charismatic young man is trying to lure their daughter into a cult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613080500 +0000" stop="20250613090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Band Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby and J.R. help a cowgirl look for a missing broncobuster, unaware that he's already been murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250613090000 +0000" stop="20250613093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
