<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809090000 +0000" stop="20240809093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Taxi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>A botched gas station robbery results in murder and abduction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809093000 +0000" stop="20240809100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809100000 +0000" stop="20240809103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809103000 +0000" stop="20240809110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 132 -- Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed tries to pawn off his new litter of puppies to co-workers, strangers and even victims. The officers work a silent alarm, rescue a boy with his head stuck in a fence and track down a prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809110000 +0000" stop="20240809120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Buggin' Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony tries to cure Bill's fear of insects with the help of live tarantula."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809120000 +0000" stop="20240809123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Loves Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes convinced that he's ugly and unwanted after constantly being reminded how cute he used to be and from being yelled at by his parents for how messy he is currently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809123000 +0000" stop="20240809130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is rounding up some guys to go to an amusement park and he's one short from getting a discount so he settles on Beaver. However, Beaver begins having second thoughts when he hears stories about one of the roller coasters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809130000 +0000" stop="20240809140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Haunted Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hitchhiking because her purse was stolen, Claire Olger is picked up by Michael Greeley. Intoxicated, he loses control of the car and collides with an oncoming truck. Arriving at the scene of the accident, the police find Claire alone in the car and the truck driver dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809140000 +0000" stop="20240809150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Judge  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock accepts the pro bono case of Kevin Meredith, a young man accused of murdering his lover, who, as Matlock discovers, had a shocking secret. In order to capture the real killer, Matlock must end a long-time friendship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809150000 +0000" stop="20240809160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie suspects that JoAnn's new cook is connected to the murder of a young prostitute. But Virgil suspects the culprit maybe a local pimp who has been intimidating the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809160000 +0000" stop="20240809170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia and Elizabeth take a car trip; Jim-Bob is forced to also go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809170000 +0000" stop="20240809180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When Harry Speener learns that the man who saved his life is a wanted fugitive, he kills the man for the reward, then finds out that the people of Dodge don't like those who kill for money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809180000 +0000" stop="20240809190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Ape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss decides to help Arnie, a man who has never learned to control his great strength. Things seem to be working out until Arnie falls for a saloon girl. Hoss realizes that he is facing an uphill battle to help Arnie lead the kind of life that he has always wanted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809190000 +0000" stop="20240809193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809193000 +0000" stop="20240809200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809200000 +0000" stop="20240809210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Richardson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When the wagon horses start to die of a disease, Adams is forced to send two feuding men to buy new horses with his emergency money. Two horses return, but with only one man, leading Adams to wonder whether he made a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809210000 +0000" stop="20240809213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>During their Christmas Eve Patrol, Malloy and Reed contemplate using their patrol car to deliver a Christmas tree to the residents of a soon-to-be-closed retirement home. Meanwhile, an elderly man's bagpipe playing is considered a public nuisance, a couple of teenagers steal a delivery truck containing radioactive material, a nervous man is desperate to cover up the smell of perfume on his clothing and an armed robbery suspect becomes intent on committing suicide-by-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809213000 +0000" stop="20240809220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While paying a visit to the laundromat before going into work, Malloy encounters a man using the facilities to dry something much different from clothing. On patrol, he and Reed deal with a minister-in-training who uses a very unorthodox method to get his message across, try to reunite a Finnish-speaking child with her family, mediate a strange dispute between feuding neighbors and engage in a high-speed chase with a well known drug dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809220000 +0000" stop="20240809223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809223000 +0000" stop="20240809230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809230000 +0000" stop="20240809233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips Is Back In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar, who is smitten with the cute new nurse, Linda Nugent, relies on Hawkeye's expertise on how to cope with the situation. Hot Lips, meanwhile, celebrates her just-granted divorce by taking a step that arouses Colonel Potter's ire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240809233000 +0000" stop="20240810000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810000000 +0000" stop="20240810003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Rival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is afraid that Andy's new girlfriend, Peggy, will take his place in his father's heart, and sets out to sabotage their relationship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810003000 +0000" stop="20240810010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Convicts-at-large</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Floyd run out of gas while coming home from a fishing trip. While looking for a telephone they are captured by three female escaped convicts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810010000 +0000" stop="20240810013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Man For Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is glued to the television set the Clampetts received for Christmas, especially because of one TV Western star, Quirt Manly. She really wants to meet him, and Drysdale arranges for it to happen. And Granny already has him set up for Elly May, because she knows he is probably the only who can tame the vine-swinging girl. However, when he arrives at the mansion, the Clampetts see he isn’t who they thought he was. Quirt Manly is actually a short actor with a high-pitched voice who doesn’t do any of his own stunts or riding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810013000 +0000" stop="20240810020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Hawaiian Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lisa cons Oliver into taking a 'fifth' honeymoon together, this time in Hawaii. When they check into the honeymoon suite, they are unaware that the hotel manager's daughter, has given her friends the suite for their honeymoon also. Since the suite has two bedrooms it's just a case of both couples avoiding each other while on their honeymoon(s), for a while anyway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810020000 +0000" stop="20240810023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Major Bonacelli</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Italian officer who studied under Klink helps Hogan photograph an air base.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810023000 +0000" stop="20240810030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Dear Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's men plan to surprise him for his birthday by blowing up an ammunition dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810030000 +0000" stop="20240810033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Perry Como And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Perry Como and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 01/20/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810033000 +0000" stop="20240810043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ice-cold Hands</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After winning tickets at a horse track lead to accusations of theft and eventually murder, Mason must defend a woman caught in the middle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810043500 +0000" stop="20240810050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jungle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a business man plans to build a dam in Africa, a witch doctor puts a curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810050500 +0000" stop="20240810060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Ride The Nightmare  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An elderly acquaintance plunges Chris Martin into a nightmare stuffed with blackmail, kidnapping and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810060500 +0000" stop="20240810070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>End Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A member of Mannix's old combat unit, brought up on charges and court-martialed, wants revenge on Mannix and the only other survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810070500 +0000" stop="20240810080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich lady, Cecilia Lasher, hires Cannon to locate the son her husband abandoned years before. She turns to Cannon after being blackmailed and terrorized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810080500 +0000" stop="20240810090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Web Of Deceit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A newsman takes pictures of evidence showing that an industrialist is involved with the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810090000 +0000" stop="20240810093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Valley Has A Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The pregnant Betty Jo is ready to have her baby, but problems arise when Wendell, the conductor, won't wake up and Betty Jo has to drive the train herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810093000 +0000" stop="20240810100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Granny, The Baby Expert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo and baby return from the hospital for a stay at the Shady Rest, where they are to be looked after by Dr. Granny Clampett, a kooky distant relative whose nearsightedness finds her mistaking Dog for the baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810100000 +0000" stop="20240810103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Topless Anyone?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Happy Gizzard isn’t doing well, and Jethro wants to improve his business. He thinks he has an idea to make his restaurant a huge success. After seeing signs outside other restaurants, he believes his restaurant should have topless waitresses. But he thinks this means the waitresses don’t wear hats. Jethro tells Drysdale just as he is working on landing a $20 million dollar account, scaring the millionaire Vanderponts away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810103000 +0000" stop="20240810110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Snow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny misses the seasons, especially the snowy winter. She wants to go home to the hills and see some snow. Jed decides to let Granny win and calls Drysdale to tell him that Granny wants to head back home to the hills. He learns that she wants the snow back. Drysdale comes up with a plan to keep the hillbillies in Beverly Hills, telling them that a big blizzard is going to strike Beverly Hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810110000 +0000" stop="20240810113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Alona On The Sarong Seas, Many Tanks, A Date To Skate</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Bluto are on a battleship anchored off a tropic isle. The big-muscled gob is dreaming about Princess Alona who is really Olive Oyl in a sarong., Popeye is in the Navy and Bluto is in the Army, but Bluto is confined to camp limits., It's Olive's first visit to a skating rink, and Popeye accidentally crashes into the pillar to which she is clinging. Popeye manages to rescue Olive in an amusing climax."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810113000 +0000" stop="20240810120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>That's My Pup, One Mother's Family, Puppy Tale</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom is the lesson when Spike is teaching his son Tyke the facts about chasing cats., A hen takes her chicks for a walk and has a difficult time keeping them all out of harm’s way., Jerry rescues some puppies and Tom doesn't want the one that followed him home around."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810120000 +0000" stop="20240810130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tepee For Two, Salmon Loafer, Roof Top Razzle Dazzle, Skin Folks, Sh-h-h-h-h-h, Freeloading Feline, Rock-a-bye Gator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody's neighbors evict him from the entire city, so Woody moves to the top of an indigineous man's teepee. He doesn't appreciate Woody's noise either., Chilly steals fish from Smedley's salmon cannery., Charlie tries to set up his TV's broadcast connection himself., Woody goes to his Uncle Scrooge Woodpecker in search of a handout, but he finds a house guarded by 10 crocodiles., A jazz musician desperately tries to quiet his nosey neighbors before his volatile condition causes him to blow up., Champ gets mistaken for a waiter at a fancy party and fulfills his duties by keeping Doc, a free-loader, out., While all the other gators are hibernating, Gabby Gator tries to trap and eat Woody while his guard is down."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810130000 +0000" stop="20240810140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare Do, The Prize Pest, Gorilla My Dreams, Fox Pop, Sniffles Bells The Cat, Acrobatty Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Elmer Fudd hunts for Bugs with an army surplus wabbit detector but it doesn't seem to work when Bugs leads him off a cliff.
, Porky won a radio quiz show contest, and his prize is Daffy popping out of a cake.
, Bugs is adrift at sea in a barrel when he suddenly finds an island.
, A fox is convinced by listening to the radio that he'll be soon skinned and worn as a fashionable clothing article. In a strange twist of fate he ends up trying to get into the Sterling Silver Fox Fur farm.
, Sniffles and his mouse friends are chased into their hole by the house cat.
, While Bugs Bunny sleeps a circus comes to town and leaves a Lion's cage on top his home. The lion investigates Bug's hole. Bothered by the lion's invasive curiosity, Bugs opts to "fix" the wise guy."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810140000 +0000" stop="20240810150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Raven</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Loveless' newest plan involves a powder that lets him miniaturize anyone who opposes him... and Jim West is his first target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810150000 +0000" stop="20240810160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kitty Angel Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty Angel finds herself not welcome on the wagon train because of her past. When Flint returns to the train toting a sick indian baby, she has everyone's prejudices to deal with as well as the baby's life-threatening illness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810160000 +0000" stop="20240810170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Mineral Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing how the town of Mineral Springs has been ruined by the “boss” of a neighboring town, the Barkleys open a freight business connecting Mineral Springs with Stockton and the rest of the valley.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810170000 +0000" stop="20240810180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hill Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hillbilly girl Merry Florene comes to town to get some schooling to better herself. Meanwhile, her two cousins also arrive in Dodge and force her to rob Mr. Jonas' store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810180000 +0000" stop="20240810190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Blood Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The son of Luke Grayson wants revenge when he discovers that Ben Cartwright killed his father, even though it was in self-defense. Despite this, Ben and Hoss are determined to help the young man find a new life for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810190000 +0000" stop="20240810200000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Quivira</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Monty Fox comes stumbling up to the night camp playing the concertina, saying he's found the promised land. He says he's found Quivera, Coronado's golden city. He says he'll share with those who help him against those who chased him out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810200000 +0000" stop="20240810203000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin goes after Benjamin Coey, who brutally murdered James Bryson and attacked Mrs. Bryson. Coey has already killed two members of the posse which is after him. Mrs. Bryson's two brothers, Joseph and William Gage, are also after him and don't intend to allow him to live long enough to stand trial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810203000 +0000" stop="20240810210000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Voice Of Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh protects a beautiful deaf and mute teenage girl from men who want her father's stolen money, which he hid before going in prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810210000 +0000" stop="20240810213000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810213000 +0000" stop="20240810220000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240810220000 +0000" stop="20240811000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Flatfoot Stooges, A Ducking They Did Go, I Can Hardly Wait, Gypped In The Penthouse, Rusty Romeos, Who Done It</sub-title>
    <desc>"Moe, Larry and Curly take care of the horses. 
, After recruiting the police chief, governor and mayor into what turns out to be a sham duck hunting club, the Stooges cleverly find a way to avoid jail. 
, The Stooges are private detectives looking for a missing millionaire.  They wander around the millionaire's spooky mansion confronting various crooks and a dangerous dame.  The Stooges vanquish the crooks (Shemp uses his "trusty shovel") and find the missing man.
, The Stooges are defense workers who have trouble getting to sleep when Curly gets a toothache.  Moe and Larry try various ways to remove the offending tooth, but nothing works so they take Curly to the dentist.  While Moe gets in the chair to show Curly how easy it's going to be, the dentist enters and pulls Moe's tooth by mistake.  Curly then wakes up and realizes its all been a dream and a punch to the mouth from Moe dislodges the tooth.
, Larry and Shemp reminisce about their experiences with Jean, a diamond crazy gold digger each of them was gypped by.  After telling their stories, they have a run in with Moe, who is now married to the same women.  When Jean shows up, they deliver some stooge-style revenge.
, The Stooges don't know it, but they are all engaged to the same girl, a gold-digger who plans to get an engagement ring from each of them and then abandon them.  When all three show up at her house at the same time, a wild fight ensues, as each stooge accuses the others of making time with "his" girl.  The gold-digger gets it in the end (literally) with tacks shot from a repeating rifle.  [A remake of "Corny Casanovas".]
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811000000 +0000" stop="20240811023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Mad Magician</sub-title>
    <desc>"A master magician murders his greedy employer, who legally owns every trick he can invent, and finds himself having to kill again."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811023000 +0000" stop="20240811030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Surf's Up! Joker's Under!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker kidnaps a surfing champion in hopes of transferring his ability into his own body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811030000 +0000" stop="20240811040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>A Piece Of The Action</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise travels to a planet suffering from cultural contamination from an earlier expedition—the inhabitants mimic the culture of 1930's gangland Chicago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811040000 +0000" stop="20240811050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Devil's Platform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A politician on a meteoric rise murders his opposition through a pact with Satan which gives him the ability to turn into an invulnerable dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811050000 +0000" stop="20240811060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From The Green Dimension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Girl from the green dimension Athena, who is in love with Dr. Smith, arrives on the planet with the aim of bringing Smith back home with her. Though Smith will do just about anything to get off the planet, things get complicated when her suitor, Urso, shows up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811060000 +0000" stop="20240811070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Sky Is Falling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview is rendered helpless by the power of a mysterious spacecraft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811070000 +0000" stop="20240811080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Giants And All That Jazz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A down-and-put trumpet player is in trouble with crooks, and a sympathetic Dan offers him a way out by teaching him Earth-style jazz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811080000 +0000" stop="20240811090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Death Merchant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug set out to checkmate the crafty Machiavelli, who is making a game of the Civil War battle at Gettysburg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811090000 +0000" stop="20240811100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Watchers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A hotel owner is taken over by invaders awaiting a guest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811100000 +0000" stop="20240811110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Prediction</sub-title>
    <desc>"When another student begins having violent visions, Matt has to stop them from coming true."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811110000 +0000" stop="20240811113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Dates   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack agrees to go on a date with Mr. Belding's niece, Penny, but when Kelly invites him to her birthday party, he sends Screech instead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811113000 +0000" stop="20240811120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Prom   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When her dad loses his job, Kelly chooses to cancel prom with Zack in order to save money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811120000 +0000" stop="20240811123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>From Nurse To Worse   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack falls for a new student, only to discover that she's actually the new school nurse! Meanwhile, Slater is afraid of getting his flu shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811123000 +0000" stop="20240811130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Save The Max   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The return of Bayside's radio station is a smash...except for Slater's boring sports broadcast. When he finds out no one likes it, he quits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811130000 +0000" stop="20240811133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>1-900-crushed   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack sets up a 900-number hotline in his latest moneymaking scheme, with Lisa offering advice to the students of Bayside. Things go awry, however, when Zack takes over and offers terrible advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811133000 +0000" stop="20240811140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Driver's Education   (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Jealous of Slater's skills in Driver's Education, Zack sabotages his driving test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811140000 +0000" stop="20240811143000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>Bedrock Hillbillies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred inherits a shack from his hillbilly relatives--along with their one-hundred-year-old feud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811143000 +0000" stop="20240811150000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>Flintstone &amp; The Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred befriends what he thinks is a kitten, but which soon grows into a troublesome lion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811150000 +0000" stop="20240811153000 +0000">
    <title>The Flintstones</title>
    <sub-title>Cave Scout Jamboree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The Flintstones and Rubbles go camping, but their seclusion is ruined by Boy Scouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811153000 +0000" stop="20240811160000 +0000">
    <title>The Jetsons</title>
    <sub-title>Astro's Top Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Astro swallows Elroy's flying toy car, Mr. Cogswell gets him dognapped to figure out the secret, as he thinks Spacely will try to put him out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811160000 +0000" stop="20240811163000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>A Fistful Of Reasons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Cindy comes home in tears after a bully, Buddy Hinton, begins picking on her because of her lisp. One afternoon, Peter encounters Buddy teasing Cindy and defends her, but gets a black eye in the process. Mike and Carol try to reason with Buddy's parents but get nowhere, and Peter goes into training so he can defend himself against Buddy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811163000 +0000" stop="20240811170000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Not-so-ugly Duckling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan has been smitten with Clark Tyson and they've been studying together. However, when Marcia casually, steps in the family room, Clark is instantly smitten. Jan becomes insecure about her looks and seeks out ways to get rid of her freckles. However, later, not wanting people to feel sorry for her, Jan makes up an imaginary boyfriend, George Glass.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811170000 +0000" stop="20240811173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Three Boys And A Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Gilbert and Richard find a burro for sale in Mayfield and they each decide to go in $10 for it. After getting their parent's permission, Richard and Gilbert fight over who gets to keep the burro, which they name Pepe. However, once they get a load of just how destructive a burro can be, they dump the problem of room and board on Beaver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811173000 +0000" stop="20240811180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Quits School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie pompously announces that he's dropping out of school to get a high paying job at a gas station. However, all is not as it seems when Wally and Lumpy get a glance at Eddie's new free spending life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811180000 +0000" stop="20240811183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Doctor Jed Clampett</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed gets an honorary doctorate when he donates money to a college, and the family thinks he is now a legit doctor. However, Granny isn’t pleased with hearing that Jed is now a real college doctor because she didn’t go to college. Granny does her best to get a degree herself, but doesn’t find much success.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811183000 +0000" stop="20240811190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Tag-team Match</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the day after Granny beat up the Boston Strong Girl, making her the new champ, and the Clampetts are celebrating Granny’s great victory. But not all is well. The woman who plays the Boston Strong Girl is in trouble for getting beat up. The woman who plays Rebecca of Donnybrook Farm, a former topless waitress, has learned the truth, getting an invitation from Granny to visit. Their manager, Gene Booth, sees this as an opportunity to get Granny to fight, after hearing the huge ratings the fight got.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811190000 +0000" stop="20240811193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Not Guilty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A crate containing coconuts is wrapped in an old Honolulu newspaper that says one of the castaways is being sought in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811193000 +0000" stop="20240811200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>You've Been Disconnected</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A storm washes up a trans-continental telephone cable into the lagoon. The Professor manages to break into the cable and rig up a telephone so they can dial out for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811200000 +0000" stop="20240811203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Country Club  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Ellen's news that she's been named "Woman of the Year" by the Raytown Country Club doesn't interest the family until they all receive invitations to the awards dinner. Once there, the Harpers end up disrupting the formal affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811203000 +0000" stop="20240811210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Naomi And The Stork  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Naomi announces she may be pregnant, she and Vint, living in the basement, request a room upstairs. It's not long before the family is fighting over which room the couple will get.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811210000 +0000" stop="20240811220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Not So Fast, Gopher / Haven't We Met Before? / Foreign Exchange</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gopher invites his widowed mother onto the ship in the hopes of cheering her up, but is hurt by her seemingly cheerful attitude, which he interprets as an insult to his father. A group of buddies takes a cruise. One of the men meets a woman who is a regular customer at the restaurant where he works. He lies about his identity because he thinks she would be put off by the fact that he is a waiter. A comic's romance with the reporter who is writing a feature about him appears doomed after she takes offense to his act."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811220000 +0000" stop="20240811223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bed Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bea longs for a special present: a blue bed jacket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811223000 +0000" stop="20240811230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Arcade Games- Doc Mack</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc Mack is the owner and proprietor of Galloping Ghost, the world's largest video game arcade, a place so massive it generates 19 separate electric bills. Lisa gets a private tour of the gallery's many vintage treasures and rarities, learning the meaning, and value, of “shmup” (shoot-’em-up) games like Turkey Shooter and Blaster. She also checks out the ultra-rare Primal Rage 2, which never made it to market, and gets a privileged look at the Sega R 360, an actual flight-simulator module where the player is spun, flipped, and rolled while engaging in game-play, Doc’s being the only one available to the public anywhere in the world. Doc’s friend and colleague, Zespy, a video game aficionado and owner of his own arcade, is on hand to set a price on Doc's unparalleled collection, then to try to tempt him into a trade. Will he hit on something Doc actually doesn't yet have? And what will he ask for in return? 
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811230000 +0000" stop="20240811233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240811233000 +0000" stop="20240812000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812000000 +0000" stop="20240812003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Does It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's steals a box of nails from work and finds himself at the center of a household debate on morality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812003000 +0000" stop="20240812010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Quiz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie feels the weight of his own mortality after a magazine quiz on life expectancy gives him another seven years - tops.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812010000 +0000" stop="20240812013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is reunited with her childhood sweetheart when she returns to her hometown for a wedding</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812013000 +0000" stop="20240812020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>No Smoking</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunker house is locked in a battle of wills after Mike vows he can go without food longer than Archie can abstain from smoking.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812020000 +0000" stop="20240812023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Don Rickles And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Don Rickles and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 12/07/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812023000 +0000" stop="20240812030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Chita Rivera And Vice Edwards</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Chita Rivera and Vice Edwards. Originally aired on 02/03/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812030000 +0000" stop="20240812033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Give Me Your Walls!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura try to get rid of their painter who eccentric behavior causes problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812033000 +0000" stop="20240812040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sam Pomerantz Scandals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob, Laura and the office gang put together a variety show to help an old friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812040000 +0000" stop="20240812043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Better Living Through Televison</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton go on T.V. to sell a kitchen utensil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812043000 +0000" stop="20240812050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor living in the year 1890 accidentally activates a time traveling helmet, which transports him to 1962—and then promptly breaks down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812050000 +0000" stop="20240812060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Hangover  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A man wakes up with a hangover, an unknown woman in his room and his wife lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812060000 +0000" stop="20240812070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Chinese Sunset</sub-title>
    <desc>Kimble is working as the "general factotum" in a swank Beverly Hills hotel on Sunset Blvd. An undercover policeman, named Fred Bragin, checks into the hotel to survey Eddie Slade, a notorious mob bookie. When Slade leaves town for a few days to sort out s</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812070000 +0000" stop="20240812080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The System</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>With the key witness in the trial against mob boss Constantine Victor murdered, the IMF has just 24 hours to convince Victor's close friend to testify against him in court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812080000 +0000" stop="20240812083000 +0000">
    <title>Peter Gunn</title>
    <sub-title>Bullet For A Badge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>An attempt on Lt. Jacoby's life is made after he receives a mysterious phone call.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812083000 +0000" stop="20240812090000 +0000">
    <title>Peter Gunn</title>
    <sub-title>Kill From Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy invalid Louise Reardon has an attempt made on her life and Gunn is hired to find her Aide, Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812090000 +0000" stop="20240812093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Missing Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman attempts to help her innocent fiancé and discovers a killer may still be at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812093000 +0000" stop="20240812100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812100000 +0000" stop="20240812103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812103000 +0000" stop="20240812110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 111: Snake In The Trunk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A ditzy young woman reports her 1958 Ford convertible stolen while she went into a liquor store. She left the keys in the car, has no paperwork, doesn't know the license number or other details but she needs it by 6 PM for a date. She finally tells the officers that her eight-foot boa constrictor is in the trunk as she was coming from the vet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812110000 +0000" stop="20240812120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Picture Day</sub-title>
    <desc>"It's picture day! Bill and Toony pose for their retro-styled portrait, as Bill reminisces about the good ol' days of taking a real photograph."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812120000 +0000" stop="20240812123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Stays At Lumpy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A communication gap ensues when Wally wants to spend the night at Lumpy's and Beaver wants to have Gilbert spend the night. Beaver asks June and she tells him he can sometime when Wally spends the night somewhere and Wally asks Ward, who tells him he can sometime when Beaver has someone spend the night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812123000 +0000" stop="20240812130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Laundry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver agrees to help Richard cart his family's clothes down to the laundromat; however, half way there they discover that Richard has lost the three dollars his mother gave him. This leads him to ask Beaver if he could use the Cleaver washer. They soon find themselves in another jam when the washing machine overflows after Beaver put in too much soap and starch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812130000 +0000" stop="20240812140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lonely Heiress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Heiress Marilyn Cartright places an ad in a magazine in order to find love and companionship. In reality, Marilyn is looking for the con artist who swindled and drove her sister to suicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812140000 +0000" stop="20240812150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Affair (aka The Maid)  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents a maid accused of killing her employer at the request of the man's widow. The request is a little odd, but it seems the widow wants everyone to know exactly what kind of man her husband was.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812150000 +0000" stop="20240812160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Tear Down The Walls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A minister who was integrating his church(by inviting Virgil and Althea to attend services)is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812160000 +0000" stop="20240812170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob wonders if he is adopted because he does not look like other family members</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812170000 +0000" stop="20240812180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Gunrunners (buffalo Man)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After a renegade band of ex-soldiers seriously injure Tahrohon, his friend, buffalo man Noah Meek, vows revenge on the group.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812180000 +0000" stop="20240812190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss finds himself falling in love with widow Helen Layton and intends to marry her, unaware of her true nature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812190000 +0000" stop="20240812193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812193000 +0000" stop="20240812200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Assailants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An assassination plot unfolds as four gunmen disguised as cavalrymen enter North Fork. Their target: Sen. Jim Borden. Their weapon: a Gatling gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812200000 +0000" stop="20240812210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Flint Mccullough Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint, in love with a Mormon girl he can't marry, joins the Confederate Army. When he finds out that he won't be seeing any action on the battlefield, it may be too late for him and the girl he loves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812210000 +0000" stop="20240812213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>G.t.a.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate a large car theft operation that targets older cars, then stages them around the city as abandoned vehicles so they can be towed and scrapped. Meanwhile, they try to figure out why the son of Malloy's girlfriend is getting bad grades, search for a suspect who robbed an elderly woman and attempt to rescue two foolish teenagers who enter a house that is being fumigated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812213000 +0000" stop="20240812220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Of The Crime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are left frustrated after investigating the theft of an elderly woman's old television set, but they have hope that a recently passed law may provide her and other victims with compensation. Elsewhere on patrol, they search for an armed robber who shot an over-trusting shopkeeper, and respond to a call of an unusual armed robbery at a drive-in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812220000 +0000" stop="20240812223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812223000 +0000" stop="20240812230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812230000 +0000" stop="20240812233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240812233000 +0000" stop="20240813000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813000000 +0000" stop="20240813003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to convince everyone of a lack of security at Mayberry Bank, and is furious that no one listens to him. Taking matters into his own hands, he ends up stuck in the bank vault.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813003000 +0000" stop="20240813010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813010000 +0000" stop="20240813013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Retires</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny announces to the family that she is planning to retire from her doctor’s practice and tells Elly and Jethro she expects one of them to take over. Jed tells this to Jane and Drysdale, also mentioning how she wants her money to take back to the hills. Drysdale plans to get Granny to stay, so he gets Dr. Clyburn to go to the mansion. After Granny reveals why she is really going back to the Hills, to cure what she calls "Granny’s complaint," Clyburn visits the mansion for medical advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813013000 +0000" stop="20240813020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Ex-secretary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver contacts Carol, his one-time secretary, to find out where she'd had his watch repaired years earlier. In this pilot for a proposed series, Carol now works for a California realtor. She prevents her current boss from being conned by man that Oliver Douglas had tried to indict back in New York.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813020000 +0000" stop="20240813023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813023000 +0000" stop="20240813030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan steals a Luftwaffe codebook, but must organize a special mission when Newkirk drops it down a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813030000 +0000" stop="20240813033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Shirley Jones And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Shirley Jones and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 02/17/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813033000 +0000" stop="20240813043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bountiful Beauty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After Stephanie Carew's body is found floating in a swimming pool, the coroner’s report finds that she died in the ocean and her corpse was then placed in the pool. Meanwhile, the police have learned unsettling information about best-selling novelist Deborah Dearborn, and it ties her to the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813043500 +0000" stop="20240813050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Five Characters In Search Of An Exit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A hobo, clown, bagpipe player, ballerina and military officer are trapped in a huge cylinder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813050500 +0000" stop="20240813060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Bonfire  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Preacher Robert Evans will go to murderous lengths to obtain a woman's manor for his gospel sanctuary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813060500 +0000" stop="20240813070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>All Around The Money Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Roger Bard brings Mannix to Mexico. Bard claims men are hunting him—and they are. But he also claims not to know why—and that is certainly a lie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813070500 +0000" stop="20240813080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A serial murder targets Cannon as his next victim. At first the homicide wanted to be finally released from his compulsion to kill. Cannon accepted to help him. But Cannon got too involved in the killer's demands."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813080500 +0000" stop="20240813090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Last Contract, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A mother asks Barnaby to help her find her runaway daughter, who's married to a contract killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813090000 +0000" stop="20240813093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Prospector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A poor prospector arouses suspicion when he suddenly begins paying off long-standing debts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813093000 +0000" stop="20240813100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813100000 +0000" stop="20240813103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813103000 +0000" stop="20240813110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 61: The Runaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Walters and Brinkman are on a roll lately and like to brag, much to the irritation of Reed. He and Malloy help them out by finishing one of their calls, then rescue a sick teenage girl and arrest the young man who took her in. Back on patrol, they meet an informant who gives them a tip on a big drug buy scheduled for 11 PM. They give the info to Sgt. Miller who asks them to help in the bust.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813110000 +0000" stop="20240813120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day...august 13th</sub-title>
    <desc>"From animals to music, Bill and Toony disucss famous occurences on August 13th."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813120000 +0000" stop="20240813123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Car Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows his car to be driven by Lumpy, who must get Eddie, Wally and Beaver to a sporting event in a neighboring town. However, on the way back, Lumpy disobeys Ward's orders and takes a shortcut home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813123000 +0000" stop="20240813130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Baby-sitter</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Wally has a previous engagement and is unable to babysit, Beaver fills in and quickly finds himself the object of a 10-year old's affection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813130000 +0000" stop="20240813140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Green-eyed Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur West, a disreputable private investigator, has found J. J. Stanley in a cheap motel. He knows Stanley and his partner, Ned Bain, were involved in the embezzlement of the Texas National Bank. He wants to blackmail Bain into giving him money to keep quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813140000 +0000" stop="20240813150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Seduction, The (aka The Quaterback)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matlock is hired to defend Brad Bingham, an aging football star with a reputation as a womanizer who was about to be cut from the team. Charlene is resistant to her father's choice, as she believes everything the tabloids have to say about Brad...not only that, but years earlier, he'd had a brief relationship with her friend Ellen Hawley, who had tried to kill herself after they broke up."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813150000 +0000" stop="20240813160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Trip Upstate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In this thought provoking episode. Gillespie is surprised when a man he arrested asks to see him on the eve of his execution. He must confront his feelings about the death penalty when the prisoner asks him to witness his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813160000 +0000" stop="20240813170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben starts to hunt animals for their skins to sell for profit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813170000 +0000" stop="20240813180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Jackals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After a group of outlaws assassinates a Texas border town sheriff at his retirement party, Matt Dillon chases the desperadoes to Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813180000 +0000" stop="20240813190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Spitfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After Joe shoots and kills a man starting a fire on the Ponderosa in self-defense, the Cartwrights have their hands full protecting Joe from the dead man's vengeful clan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813190000 +0000" stop="20240813193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mark's Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharpshooter Marty Blair tries to persuade Lucas to buy Mark a rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813193000 +0000" stop="20240813200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Amazing Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Fast-draw artist Wade Randall is less than anxious to display his prowess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813200000 +0000" stop="20240813210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunter Malloy Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hunter Malloy and his partner get jobs as drivers on the wagon train as part of their plan to rob the boss. Striking gold instead while stopping to repair their wagons, the fever is high as some stop to strike it rich and uncover more than just a few nuggets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813210000 +0000" stop="20240813213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Point</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Woods' new partner is a nervous and quiet recruit, and the embarrassing secret he's trying to keep from his fellow officers might actually imperil them. On today's patrol, a real estate broker's well meaning but poorly thought out gesture nearly leads to a mob scene, a drug store owner discovers a way to profit from armed robbers and an armed robbery suspect opens fire during his escape attempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813213000 +0000" stop="20240813220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lady's Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>On today's patrol, Malloy and Reed try to corral cattle that are wandering into the downtown area, pull over a speeding bicyclist, chase down a man with a stolen guitar and break up a bar fight. After their shift is over, Reed and his wife witness a gas station holdup on their way to dinner with Malloy and his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813220000 +0000" stop="20240813223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Are You Now, Margaret?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Congressional aide, Williamson, visits the 4077th on a supposedly routine fact-finding tour, but it's discovered that his motives are far deeper—too uncover Margaret as a communist sympathizer. His case is full of innuendo, so the gang set out to help Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813223000 +0000" stop="20240813230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813230000 +0000" stop="20240813233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240813233000 +0000" stop="20240814000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814000000 +0000" stop="20240814003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814003000 +0000" stop="20240814010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814010000 +0000" stop="20240814013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampett Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is getting tired of the clan’s sixty-eight million dollars. When three struggling college girls visit the Clampetts asking for a donation to help them out, Jed hands over a check for their entire fortune. The Clampetts are flat broke, and they have never been happier, though Drysdale is now in a wreck. They pack up to head back to the hills, but end up running out of gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814013000 +0000" stop="20240814020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Oliver Buys A Farm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>New York lawyer Oliver Douglas quits his job at the law firm of Felton, O'Connell, Clay, Blakely, Harmon, Dillion &amp; Pasteur and buys a farm in Hooterville, sight unseen. The locals are astounded that Haney had managed to unload the place on someone and try to talk him out of it. Laying her eyes on the dilapidated farmhouse for the first time, Lisa bursts into tears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814020000 +0000" stop="20240814023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Klink Commandos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men volunteer for a German suicide squad train bound for the Russian front in order to steal key documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814023000 +0000" stop="20240814030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gasoline War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men plan to destroy a gasoline station that has just been built in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814030000 +0000" stop="20240814033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Barbara Mcnair And Soupy Sales</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Barbara McNair and Soupy Sales. Originally aired on 02/24/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814033000 +0000" stop="20240814043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nervous Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private investigator Paul Drake is sent to locate Charles Fuller's missing mother. Not only is she missing, she is suspected in a murder that happened the day before she went missing. When Drake locates the missing women, he learns that she was found badly beaten in a field six months earlier and has lost her memory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814043500 +0000" stop="20240814050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Quality Of Mercy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier gets a new perspective on war when he is forced to experience it from his enemy's point of view.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814050500 +0000" stop="20240814060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Tender Poisoner  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Two business executives throw themselves into a battle of wits and trickery as they compete for a gorgeous lady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814060500 +0000" stop="20240814070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Odds Against Donald Jordan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find missing building contractor Donald Jordan. He gets poor help from the man's partner, wife and sister. Each offers a different reason for his disappearance. When Jordan reappears, he assures Mannix that he's fine and asks him to drop the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814070500 +0000" stop="20240814080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady journalist is forced to reveal her sources in a murder news or she will go to jail on a contempt charge. She enlist Cannon's service to unravel the murder of a missing excursionist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814080500 +0000" stop="20240814090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Trap Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After a marital spat, a wife leaves her spouse to meet a football player in an ultimately fatal rendezvous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814090000 +0000" stop="20240814093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews and Sergeant Corey spend Christmas Eve searching for a lost girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814093000 +0000" stop="20240814100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Frauds - Dr-28</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate the delay of death notifications in the state employment department.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814100000 +0000" stop="20240814103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Juvenile - Dr-19</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The battered-child syndrome: Friday and Gannon investigate a youngster with severe back lacerations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814103000 +0000" stop="20240814110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 122 Christmas: The Yellow Dump Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>On Christmas Eve, Reed and Malloy make rounds distributing police department donation packages to needy families, and pull many heartstrings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814110000 +0000" stop="20240814120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Summer Thrills</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill &amp; Toony try out some extreme summer sports.
"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814120000 +0000" stop="20240814123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Younger Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to join the basketball team but finds himself trying to live up to Wally's performance. However, after not making the team, Beaver allows his family to believe that he did.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814123000 +0000" stop="20240814130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Typewriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Seeing an ad for typewriters on sale, Beaver talks his parents into letting him get one as long as he learns how to use it. However, Beaver discovers learning to type is not as easy as it looks and soon finds himself making a deal with the shady Eddie Haskell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814130000 +0000" stop="20240814140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fugitive Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Janet Norris is charged with poisoning her doctor husband just before he flew to his death in his private plane. Further investigation reveals that Dr. Norris did not die in the plane crash and that he is in Mexico with his nurse mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814140000 +0000" stop="20240814150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Don: Part 1  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock represents Nicholas Baron, a well-known mobster who has been accused of murdering a rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814150000 +0000" stop="20240814160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Aka Kelly Kay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The past comes back to haunt JoAnn in the form of an escaped convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814160000 +0000" stop="20240814170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Burn Out - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy smokes a pipe and Grandpa leaves a heater plugged in and turned on and a fire breaks out</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814170000 +0000" stop="20240814180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The First People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt has to intervene when an honest but strict indian agent charges an innocent indian of murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814180000 +0000" stop="20240814190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman shows up to the Ponderosa claiming to have just married Ben. The problem is, Ben has never seen her before in his life!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814190000 +0000" stop="20240814193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Squeeze Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A speculator will stop at nothing to grab Lucas's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814193000 +0000" stop="20240814200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark blames himself for a friend's accidental death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814200000 +0000" stop="20240814210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ben Courtney Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The sheriff of Bitter Springs feels he has lots of reasons to hate. When settlers from the South want to live there, he accuses them of enslaving a black child, but his reasons for keeping them from the town go much deeper than that.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814210000 +0000" stop="20240814213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen With A Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Wells appears to have met his match with a new partner who always insists on doing things his own way. Today's shift features a hot-headed husband who's decided he needs a gun to protect his home, and a neglected girl who causes a scare while playing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814213000 +0000" stop="20240814220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Follow Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he's got a great deal lined up on a used boat, but Malloy's convinced there's something fishy going on. While on patrol, they search for a man who sold a stolen horse to a riding academy, use an informant's tip to investigate a suspicious restaurant parking lot attendant and face an accusation of stealing a socialite's diamond ring during a burglary investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814220000 +0000" stop="20240814223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814223000 +0000" stop="20240814230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814230000 +0000" stop="20240814233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240814233000 +0000" stop="20240815000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815000000 +0000" stop="20240815003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>High Noon In Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets hysterical when Andy receives a letter from a man he arrested and sent to prison. The convict is to be released soon and says in the letter that he is coming to settle the score with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815003000 +0000" stop="20240815010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815010000 +0000" stop="20240815013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Indians Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When she hears Native Americans are visiting Beverly Hills, Granny is worried about an Indian attack on their land. Drysdale, on the other hand, is worried about losing the Clampett land. However, the two Native Americans who visit, Chief Running Wolf and his son, Little Fox, come to talk and visit with Jed and Jethro.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815013000 +0000" stop="20240815020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Lisa's First Day On The Farm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lisa gets her first look at their dilapidated-and empty--farmhouse and is horrified. Oily Mr. Haney, who previously owned the dump, took everything with him, including the bathroom fixtures, and tries to resell them to Oliver. Eb, one of Haney's workers, is hired on as their farm hand. Lisa goes out to meet the locals, most of whom have entered a pool wagering on how long the Douglases will stay. Lisa is ready to immediately return to New York, but after a chat with Kate Bradley, she decides to give farm life a try.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815020000 +0000" stop="20240815023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Unfair Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan kidnaps Burkhalter's sister in order to exchange her for a captured Allied agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815023000 +0000" stop="20240815030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Kommandant Dies At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink is to be executed when the Gestapo finds him with information Hogan planted on him to deliver to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815030000 +0000" stop="20240815033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Mike Douglas</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Mike Douglas. Originally aired on 03/17/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815033000 +0000" stop="20240815043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fifty-millionth Frenchman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Frenchman Phillipe falls for a married woman, taking her away from a violently abusive husband. When the ex-husband dies piloting his airplane, Phillipe is blamed for drugging him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815043500 +0000" stop="20240815050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely old woman refuses to leave her apartment for fear of meeting "Mr. Death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815050500 +0000" stop="20240815060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Thirty-first Of February  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The passing away of Andrew Anderson's spouse sets off strange events calculated to drive the widower insane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815060500 +0000" stop="20240815070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Last Rites For Miss Emma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix suspects Floyd Brown of stealing 45 cases of morphine. That's bad news for Peggy because Floyd is her boyfriend. This case almost costs Joe his secretary, and Peggy her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815070500 +0000" stop="20240815080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hounds Of Hell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank travels to a small ranching town to help out a writer friend charged with a double murder. Frank's only clue is a cryptic note left by the man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815080500 +0000" stop="20240815090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Once Removed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman murders her father-in-law when he refuses to give her any money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815090000 +0000" stop="20240815093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Several law-abiding citizens unknowingly help a charming murderer escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815093000 +0000" stop="20240815100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Dr-31</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A costumed thief calling himself "The Crimson Crusader" has been stealing comic books, movie posters and publicity photos of various superheroes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815100000 +0000" stop="20240815103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Vice - Dr-30</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing as orange growers, Friday and Gannon attempt to bust a gambling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815103000 +0000" stop="20240815110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 81: The Long Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After roll call, Reed and Malloy provide backup at a robbery, help a lost man return home, handle a call about a prowler and respond to a silent alarm. Malloy demonstrates for Reed the importance of "officer presence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815110000 +0000" stop="20240815120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Golden State</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815120000 +0000" stop="20240815123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Marine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward comes down hard on Wally after he comes home two hours late, this fuels June and Ward's suspicions that Wally is contemplating joining the Merchant Marines. June had discovered some pamphlets hidden in his dresser drawer. However, little does anyone know, Wally has been getting the information for Lumpy who's seriously thinking of joining.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815123000 +0000" stop="20240815130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Versus Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a new girl in his class and is instantly smitten. He begins walking her home from school but he soon realizes that the girl has an agenda on her mind. Her sole purpose is to get close to Beaver in order to get close to Wally. This leads Beaver to accuse Wally of stealing his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815130000 +0000" stop="20240815140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The One-eyed Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Della and Mason's dinner at a fancy French restaurant is interrupted by a phone call and an envelope containing $500 from a mysterious woman named Marian Fargo. She wants him to make an exchange: the money for some documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815140000 +0000" stop="20240815150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Don: Part 2  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Even though they've lost a key witness, Matlock keeps defending mobster Nicholas Baron against the charge that he murdered a rival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815150000 +0000" stop="20240815160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>These Things Take Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage mother from an impoverished family is arrested for murder after her infant is found dead, but Virgil believes there is more to the case than meets the eye. Meanwhile Althea believes the situation could have been prevented if the school had offered sex education classes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815160000 +0000" stop="20240815170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Burn Out - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy smokes a pipe and Grandpa leaves a heater plugged in and turned on and a fire breaks out</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815170000 +0000" stop="20240815180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Sam'l</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Durning a drought, a watch witch (someone who can find water), comes to town. Meanwhile, a businessman attempts to buy up farms during this time, no matter the method.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815180000 +0000" stop="20240815190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Bank Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Hoss get in some trouble when they "rob" the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815190000 +0000" stop="20240815193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Anvil Chorus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nils Swenson, North Fork's blacksmith, volunteers to take the marshal's place for a few days while Micah attends a wedding in another town. To help maintain peace, Nils institutes a policy that anyone coming into town must turn in their weapons, getting them back when they leave. This plan backfires on Nils when some dishonest men come to town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815193000 +0000" stop="20240815200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas's self-confidence begins to slip away when he misses an easy shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815200000 +0000" stop="20240815210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ella Lindstrom Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ella Lindstrom loses her husband on the wagon train ride west from Boston. With her seven children she decides to stay the course against the wishes of Major Adams. It gets more complicated when she thinks she is expecting number eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815210000 +0000" stop="20240815213000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suicide</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a traveling business man driving a green pinto, who called his wife in Nebraska and told her he was going to commit suicide at 2 PM. Meanwhile, they search for a woman who abandoned her newborn baby in a garbage can, and get a tip from an elderly woman about a group of car strippers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815213000 +0000" stop="20240815220000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Action</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to an auto mechanic, Malloy is ambushed and kidnapped by a group of drug runners who plan to use him to secure the release of one of their associates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815220000 +0000" stop="20240815223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Yalu Brick Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. lose their way while rushing urgently needed antibiotics to the 4077th, which is wracked with low-mileage Thanksgiving turkey-induced salmonella. Wandering back to M*A*S*H, the pair are found by a peculiar North Korean soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815223000 +0000" stop="20240815230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. race against the clock to save a soldier from paralysis. B.J.'s harvesting an aorta from a dead soldier doesn't sit well with the soldier's friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815230000 +0000" stop="20240815233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240815233000 +0000" stop="20240816000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816000000 +0000" stop="20240816003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Class Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy meets up with his high school sweetheart at their reunion and it appears they could be rekindling their relationship. But do they want the same things, and did they ever?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816003000 +0000" stop="20240816010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816010000 +0000" stop="20240816013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Giant Jackrabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>At the mansion, the clan is in need of food because the hunting in Beverly Hills is horrible. They call a catering company, but get mean-mouthed. At the bank, Drysdale gets a call and learns that he got a kangaroo from a friend and it is at his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816013000 +0000" stop="20240816020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Decorator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver wants to start farming but Lisa demands he have their house redecorated first. Sam Drucker recommends a decorator from Pixley. Kate Bradley tries to tutor Lisa in the kitchen since she doesn't know the first thing about cooking. Kate starts by showing her how to make something easy: hotcakes. Adding to the chaos is Oliver's mother, who arrives to rescue Lisa from her nightmarish country life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816020000 +0000" stop="20240816023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Bombsight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to get the blueprints for and interfere with the testing of a new weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816023000 +0000" stop="20240816030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to steal the picture that the Gestapo is using to blackmailing Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816030000 +0000" stop="20240816033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Larry Hovis And Barrie Chase</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Larry Hovis and Barrie Chase. Originally aired on 03/24/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816033000 +0000" stop="20240816043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Frightened Fisherman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the former boss and wife of a scientist attempt to prevent him from taking the credit for a new antibiotic, the wife turns up dead and her scientist husband has trouble clearing his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816043500 +0000" stop="20240816050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One More Pallbearer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric millionaire invites three people to visit him in his bomb shelter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816050500 +0000" stop="20240816060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>What Really Happened  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a distressed housekeeper murders her boss, the deceased man's wife is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816060500 +0000" stop="20240816070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Solid Gold Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaper publisher John Randolph asks Mannix to learn why his daughter is acting so strangely. Mannix discovers she may have killed a mobster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816070500 +0000" stop="20240816080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Target In The Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank struggles to prove his friend did not commit murder, but someone (the real killer) is working equally hard to thwart him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816080500 +0000" stop="20240816090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Counterfall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict asks Barnaby to help him prove he didn't kill a judge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20240816090000 +0000" stop="20240816093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Kidnap Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Highway Patrol races to the rescue when a kidnapped victim is injured in the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
