<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010080500 +0000" stop="20241010090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must beat a bounty hunter to an escaped convict who can vindicate a prison trustee charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010090000 +0000" stop="20241010093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage Family Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews finds a trigger-happy madman holding a terrified family at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010093000 +0000" stop="20241010100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010100000 +0000" stop="20241010103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 65 -- Cigarettes, Cars And Wild, Wild Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy help take down a chop-shop that employs cute girls in mini-skirts to steal cars from trusting men. They also arrest a young man who grows pot and holds parties in the home of his unsuspecting shut-in aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010103000 +0000" stop="20241010110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 55 -- Missing Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After responding to a gas leak in a home, reed and malloy search for a missing child. Finally, they investigate an attempted car theft that ended with a fatal shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010110000 +0000" stop="20241010120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Aloha State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony head to the tropical paradise of Hawaii as part of their Trekkin' all 50 tour."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010120000 +0000" stop="20241010123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Grass Is Always Greener</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally make friends with the garbage man's kids, Chris and Pete. They quickly learn that they take for granted what they have. Simple things like just having a yard to play in leave Chris and Pete in awe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010123000 +0000" stop="20241010130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Boat Builders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally, Chester and Tooey are building their own boat and plan to sail on it, despite Ward and June's forbidding Wally. Once at the lake, Beaver is the only one small enough to get in it and once on the water, the boat tips over leaving a soaked Beaver behind. However, it's trying to keep their afternoon of boating a secret from Ward and June, that's really going to wipe Wally and Beaver out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010130000 +0000" stop="20241010140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Calendar Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A building contractor is charged with the murder of a wealthy political Mr. fix-it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010140000 +0000" stop="20241010150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Fisherman  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a Vietnamese fisherman and his son when they are accused of murdering a racist fisherman. And It isn't just the fishermen that Matlock ends up defending, as he, too, becomes a target of the racist townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010150000 +0000" stop="20241010160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Final Arrangement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Sweet is heartbroken when an elderly woman who befriended him is murdered in her bookstore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010160000 +0000" stop="20241010170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Drucilla's Pond</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Soldiers practice war at Drusilla's pond</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010170000 +0000" stop="20241010180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Albert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a bank teller foils a robbery, he steals money from the bank for himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010180000 +0000" stop="20241010190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When Adam is ambushed by an escaped convict who forces him to swap clothes, it isn't long before a posse is on Adam's trail. To make matters worse, the posse leader knows it is Adam, but wants to see him hang just the same.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010190000 +0000" stop="20241010193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Pitchman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mark finds gold on their property, a fast-talking salesman who tried to sell Lucas a new lightning rod offers instead to buy the ranch's mineral rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010193000 +0000" stop="20241010200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Micah is badly injured by an escaping prisoner, Lucas tracks the prisoner back to his home town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010200000 +0000" stop="20241010210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Trial For Murder: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When an esteemed member of the wagon train is found dead, Adams needs to prevent mob rule and make sure a lawful trial takes place. The accused is not well liked and found passed out with the rifle used in the murder. But is he the killer?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010210000 +0000" stop="20241010220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Cook's Tour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>John delivers a cyanotic baby. The firemen give Roy a bad time about his cooking. A boy gets his hand stuck in a vase; John rescues a kid in handcuffs. A man repairing a washer gets an electric shock. The paramedics rescue a man trapped on a crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010220000 +0000" stop="20241010223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Abduction Of Margaret Houlihan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing that North Korean prisoners have been released in the area, everyone is upset when Margaret disappears. Colonel Flagg is called in to investigate, and bungles things in his usual manner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010223000 +0000" stop="20241010230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sigmund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman, feeling depressed, visits the 4077th to observe how they fare under the pressures of war. He begins a letter to Sigmund Freud as a form of self-therapy, and releases his tension in the form of a practical joke with B.J., aimed at Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010230000 +0000" stop="20241010233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mulcahy's War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Frank discovers that Danny Fitzsimmons has shot himself to get out of combat, Father Mulcahy is called in. Realizing his lack of understanding of the fighting, Mulcahy accompanies Radar to an aid station, where they encounter the real war at first hand. Mulcahy performs an emergency tracheotomy, guided by Hawkeye over the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241010233000 +0000" stop="20241011000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Korean Surgeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Syn Paik, a North Korean surgeon, arrives with some wounded, he is passed off as a South Korean by Hawkeye and B.J., but to no avail. Hot Lips and Frank try to convince Potter that Paik is a spy. Paik, Hawkeye and B.J. agree that it would be in the interest of all for him to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011000000 +0000" stop="20241011003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol And Old Lace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney, on a spree of destroying illegal stills, are surprised when a trail leads them to two spinster sisters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011003000 +0000" stop="20241011010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy, The Marriage Counselor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy counsels a Mayberry couple who are constantly bickering with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011010000 +0000" stop="20241011013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Learns To Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>After Granny takes a cab home and gets charged for the ride, she decides that it is time for her to learn how to drive. The taxi driver who took Granny home is having trouble collecting the fair, and after a series of events begins to believe that he is in a mental hospital. Granny, during her driving lesson, mistakenly gets on the road.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011013000 +0000" stop="20241011020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>A Square Is Not Round</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The Douglases try to determine which of their hens is laying square eggs. Once word gets out, Haney and a chicken breeder both want in on the action. Oddly, the cube-shaped eggs don't worry Oliver nearly as much as their toaster that operates when you say the number "five".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011020000 +0000" stop="20241011023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses a broken water main under the camp to aid the escape of captured resistance fighters by creating a health spa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011023000 +0000" stop="20241011030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Klink, A Bomb And A Short Fuse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>General Burkhalter wants Hogan to defuse a bomb that has landed in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011030000 +0000" stop="20241011033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Chita Rivera And Bob Newhart (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Chita Rivera and Bob Newhart. Originally aired on 02/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011033000 +0000" stop="20241011043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Mischievous Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a shady private investigator and his pawn die mysteriously, the woman who may have been his intended target is charged with their murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011043500 +0000" stop="20241011050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Come Wander With Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A singer searches for an authentic folk song.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011050500 +0000" stop="20241011060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Body In The Barn  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>With the intention of marrying another woman, a man uses a badly decomposed body to frame his wife for his murder. When the newly betrothed woman's mother learns of the scheme, however, she fears that she may be her son-in-law's next target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011060500 +0000" stop="20241011070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellen Gray hires Mannix because she believes she has been stalked by a Vietnamese man ever since the death of her husband in Hong Kong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011070500 +0000" stop="20241011080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Investigator</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is called in to investigate police corruption by the mayor of a Midwestern town."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011080500 +0000" stop="20241011090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Renegade's Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby's search for a 6-year-old boy leads him to the boy's father - a vagrant who deals in illegal arms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011090000 +0000" stop="20241011093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>With a man-hunting gunman on the loose, Dan Mathews springs a manhunt of his own</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011093000 +0000" stop="20241011100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011100000 +0000" stop="20241011103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 75: Have A Nice Weekend</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers investigate robberies, attempted arson and a violent argument."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011103000 +0000" stop="20241011110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 105 -- Elegy For A Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Malloy pays tribute to Officer Tom Porter, who has recently fallen in the line of duty. Malloy recounts the close friendship they developed while training at the academy, as well as the moments where they crossed paths on duty, including the night of the officer's unfortunate demise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011110000 +0000" stop="20241011120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Cosplay Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony run into a few almost identical faces at a cartoon curation fan convention."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011120000 +0000" stop="20241011123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Plays Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver find themselves tardy for the third time this week and decide to skip altogether. However, they quickly find themselves caught when they accidentally walk on the set of a live TV show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011123000 +0000" stop="20241011130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Garage Painters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lazy weekend leads Ward to direct Wally and Beaver to read a book, Tom Sawyer. The book influences them so much that they take on the job of painting the garage doors. However, they soon find the job to be awfully boring and messy. Chaos erupts when neighbor Bengie Bellamy stops by wanting to help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011130000 +0000" stop="20241011140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Petulant Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret was a much younger woman on the make who entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011140000 +0000" stop="20241011150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Heiress  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a troubled young woman is accused of murder, her late father's former business partner hires Matlock to prove her innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011150000 +0000" stop="20241011160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Family Matters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's dream of a better relationship with his Aunt Ruda and her son is shattered when his cousin takes part in a string of burglaries that result in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011160000 +0000" stop="20241011170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Flight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob meets a boy who is on his way to join the Air Corps, but the boy never actually leaves</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011170000 +0000" stop="20241011180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Kiowa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt must rescue a teenage girl from indians and bring her back to her family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011180000 +0000" stop="20241011190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Mountain Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Raised in the hills by her reclusive grandfather, Trudy is left in Joe's care when he dies. Honoring a promise to the girl's late grandfather, Joe is determined to transform the hoydenish Trudy into a "lady."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011190000 +0000" stop="20241011193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Baranca</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When an outlaw leader lures Marshal Torrance out of town, Lucas is the only one who can stop him from lynching a local man who killed one of the members of his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011193000 +0000" stop="20241011200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Martinet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A former army captain comes to North Fork to kill the man who shot down his son in a gunfight—Lucas McCain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011200000 +0000" stop="20241011210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Trial For Murder: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When the deceased's wife arrives, the people on the wagon train learn that the murdered man has a dark past, and this could be a case of Cain and Abel—or perhaps someone in the dead-man's past came home-to-roost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011210000 +0000" stop="20241011220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Brushfire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Station 51 is called to fight a wildfire. John and Roy rescue an elderly woman and her sister, treat an injured fireman, deliver a baby, catch a looter and find a boy's lost dog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011220000 +0000" stop="20241011223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye Get Your Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After 24 hours of surgery, Hawkeye and Potter venture off to a Korean hospital to lend a hand. Hawkeye is appalled to learn that he must carry a gun. After helping the Koreans, they are shelled on the way back. They scramble from the jeep before it is shelled, and Potter urges Hawkeye to shoot in self-defense, against Hawkeye's will, and he does—into the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011223000 +0000" stop="20241011230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Colonel Potter goes to Tokyo on R&amp;R, his horse develops colic. Klinger becomes chronically depressed, and Hot Lips gets appendicitis. The horse is flushed out with a hose, Hawkeye and B.J. perform an appendectomy on Hot Lips, and all are well when Potter returns, except Klinger. Potter offers Klinger a discharge for severe depression, and Klinger gets very excited, which loses him the discharge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011230000 +0000" stop="20241011233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Exorcism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Potter orders Radar to move a Korean spirit post believed to ward off evil spirits, things mysteriously begin to go wrong. When an old Korean man is brought into camp for medical attention, he refuses surgery unless the spirits in the camp are exorcised. A priestess is brought in, who exhibits her dance and her bells and chants. All is well, and Radar returns the spirit post to its original position.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241011233000 +0000" stop="20241012000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawk's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hawkeye bemoans the young age of the wounded, he appears to develop problems. Sleepwalking and bad dreams, according to Sidney Freedman, are taking Hawkeye back to a simple time, but the horrors of war continue to intrude. After Sidney's assurances that he is as sane as can be, Hawkeye's life once again seems to settle down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012000000 +0000" stop="20241012003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes suspicious when a record promoter comes to town to gather material for a folk music album.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012003000 +0000" stop="20241012010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Barney's Morale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's overzealous policing enrages the people of Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012010000 +0000" stop="20241012013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Something For The Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts, Drysdale and Jane are heading to their castle in England. Their plane ride isn’t the easiest, especially for Drysdale and another passenger. Jethro smuggles Elly’s turkey, buzzard, on board, and Drysdale is attacked by it in the bathroom, as well as another man who has the misfortune of being seated near the clan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012013000 +0000" stop="20241012020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Never Trust A Little Old Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>It's tomato planting season and Oliver needs some useful weather information. Hooterville relies on WPIXL-TV's Mildred, a little old lady who prances out of her dollhouse, or Walter, the singing weatherman. Both are constantly wrong so Oliver contacts the Weather Bureau which predicts warm days and nights. With the plants in the ground, Hooterville suffers the coldest night of the year. Incredibly, it's Lisa's crepe suzettes that save the crop from the cold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012020000 +0000" stop="20241012023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Tanks For The Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to photograph and destroy a model for a radio-controlled tank that is being tested at camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012023000 +0000" stop="20241012030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Adolf Please Stand Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>With camp security raised, Hogan and his men are desperate to smuggle top-secret German fortifications information to the Allies. The solution? Make liberal use of Carter's remarkable impersonation of Adolf Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012030000 +0000" stop="20241012033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Pat Carroll, Tim Conway, And Karen Wyman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Pat Carroll, Tim Conway, and Karen Wyman. Originally aired on 03/01/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012033000 +0000" stop="20241012043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Laughing Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman being held in prison pending her trial sees the woman whom she believes committed the crime with which she has been charged on a televised gala.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012043500 +0000" stop="20241012050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Two people in a remote cabin find signs of an extraterrestrial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012050500 +0000" stop="20241012060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Verge Likens  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A country farmer plans vengeance on his father's murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012060500 +0000" stop="20241012070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Round Trip To Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix uncovers a mysterious world that surrounded the late husband of his client, Amanda Hewitt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012070500 +0000" stop="20241012080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady On The Run</sub-title>
    <desc>"After witnessing a murder, a woman flees to a sanitarium where she was once a patient. It's up to Cannon to find her and keep her safe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012080500 +0000" stop="20241012090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fraternity Of Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of amateur thieves attempt to cover up the death of their cohort during a holdup - at the risk of the diamonds they've stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012090000 +0000" stop="20241012093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Joe Retires</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Lazy Uncle Joe, who fancies himself a human dynamo, announces his retirement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012093000 +0000" stop="20241012100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Organ Fund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Hooterville folks are faced with a larcenous fundraiser when they try to find enough money to buy the church a new organ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012100000 +0000" stop="20241012103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Man For Elly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is glued to the television set the Clampetts received for Christmas, especially because of one TV Western star, Quirt Manly. She really wants to meet him, and Drysdale arranges for it to happen. And Granny already has him set up for Elly May, because she knows he is probably the only who can tame the vine-swinging girl. However, when he arrives at the mansion, the Clampetts see he isn’t who they thought he was. Quirt Manly is actually a short actor with a high-pitched voice who doesn’t do any of his own stunts or riding.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012103000 +0000" stop="20241012110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Giant Jackrabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>At the mansion, the clan is in need of food because the hunting in Beverly Hills is horrible. They call a catering company, but get mean-mouthed. At the bank, Drysdale gets a call and learns that he got a kangaroo from a friend and it is at his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012110000 +0000" stop="20241012113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Morning, Noon And Night Club, Crystal Brawl, The Jeep</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye temporarily drops his nautical air to become a night club dancer, all for Olive's sake., When Bluto takes Olive to the fair, Popeye disguises himself as a fortune teller to get her attention., Popeye and the Jeep, his magical pet, visit Olive and learn Swee'pea has crawled out of his crib and disappeared."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012113000 +0000" stop="20241012120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Purr-chance To Dream, The Prospecting Bear, Smitten Kitten</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom isn't sleeping well and keeps having nightmares about getting beat up by a bulldog., Barney Bear goes prospecting for gold with a donkey to help him out., Jerry has flashbacks when he sees Tom interested in a female cat."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012120000 +0000" stop="20241012130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ace In The Hole, Chilly And Looney Gooney, Unlucky Potluck, Seal On The Loose, Pixie Picnic, Scrappy Birthday, Wet Blanket Policy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody Woodpecker is a stable boy who longs to fly a plane. But the bulldog sergeant on the airfield stands in his way., Chilly and Gooney the "Gooney Bird" Albatross work together to avoid the hunter Colonel Pot Shot., After he discovers a loose floorboard in the front steps, Charlie tells Junior to fix and paint the steps. Junior paints the back steps as well, thinking it will please Charlie…, Woody tries to hide a pet seal from Miss Meany in her "no pets allowed" boarding house., A group of forest pixies have a picnic., Andy buys a hound to catch a fox and make a fox fur coat for his girlfriend's birthday present., Buzz Buzzard tries to collect on Woody Woodpecker's life insurance policy by any means necessary!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012130000 +0000" stop="20241012140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbit Transit, Beep Prepared, Peck Up Your Troubles, The Iceman Ducketh, Cat Feud, Feather Bluster, Rabbit Romeo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and Cecil Turtle decide to have their own "tortoise and the hare" race. , Wile E. Coyote chases the Road runner in this classic., Sylvester tries everything he can to catch a woodpecker. , At a trading post in the Klondike, Daffy Duck overhears that they are paying big bucks for furs. He heads north to trap Bugs Bunny and cash in. , Marc Anthony, the ferocious guard dog, falls for a cute cuddly little kitty. An evil cat tries to swipe the kitty and it’s up to Marc Anthony to protect the kitty. , Foghorn and the farm dog have reached old age and are far past their fighting phase, instead they prefer to sit around and play chess. Seeing their kids fight brings them memories of their past that they reminisce of. , Elmer's uncle, Judd, promises him $500 if he will watch his lovesick rabbit, Millicent. When Elmer gets Bugs to come over and keep Millie company, crazy things start happening."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012140000 +0000" stop="20241012150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Ready-made Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Agents West and Gordon are assigned to guard foreign dictator Colonel Pellargo, but they are foiled by a clever assassin, who also turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012150000 +0000" stop="20241012160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Amos Gibbon Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After an argument with Major Adams, Flint leaves the wagon train and cozies up to a bar at a nearby town. What he doesn't know is the locals are shanghaiing strangers for slave labor in a mine and no one on the train knows where he went.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012160000 +0000" stop="20241012170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Boots With My Father's Name</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria starts brooding about how Tom could truly love her if he was unfaithful and fathered a bastard child. She journeys to Heath’s hometown to try to find the truth about Tom’s relationship with Heath’s mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012170000 +0000" stop="20241012180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Celia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Newly's is the victim of a con game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012180000 +0000" stop="20241012190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Miracle Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Susan Blanchard is injured in a wagon crash. Though there is nothing physically wrong with her, Susan is psychosomatically incapable of leaving her bed. Enter faith healer Garth, who promises to make Susan walk again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012190000 +0000" stop="20241012193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Milly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A new store owner upsets the town by demanding that all credit accounts be paid off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012193000 +0000" stop="20241012200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Cold Cash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The widow of a bandit killed by Lucas plots a grotesque revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012200000 +0000" stop="20241012210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Gallows Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In Cottonwood, at the Pair-A-Dice Saloon, Qunice gets into a fight with Major Courtney. Jim swears he'll kill him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012210000 +0000" stop="20241012213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Gold And Brimstone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin finds a sick old man and his son trying to protect their mine from claim jumpers. The old man is delirious and thinks that Paladin is the devil and has only offered to help in exchange for their souls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012213000 +0000" stop="20241012220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>When phony wanted posters put a price on the head of a retired Confederate officer, Colonel Sykes summons Josh Randall to help keep the bounty hunters at bay while also uncovering the person behind the bogus posters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241012220000 +0000" stop="20241013000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Hula-la-la, Self Made Maids, Studio Stoops, Three Arabian Nuts, Quiz Whizz, Slap Happy Sleuths</sub-title>
    <desc>"The boys run into trouble with the local witch doctor who wants to add their heads to his collection., The Stooges are artists who want to marry their models; "Moella", "Larraine", and "Shempetta".  The girls' father doesn't approve, so the Stooges tickle him into submission. , The Stooges are investigators for the Onion Oil Company.  The company's service stations are being robbed by a gang of crooks, so the boys pose as gas station attendants to capture the bad guys. , The Stooges are hired by a movie studio as publicity men.  Their first assignment is to get publicity for Dolly Devore, a pretty starlet.  They fake a kidnapping, but the cops won't believe their story.  Then the girl is really kidnapped and the Stooges must come to the rescue.  Shemp winds up hanging out a tenth story window on an extending telephone. , The Stooges find themselves in the crosshairs of thieves who want a magic lamp., Joe wins a contest and is promptly fleeced out of his winnings by some con men.  When the Stooges go to recover his money, the bad guys convince them that they can get rich by posing as children and becoming the wards of a millionaire.  The boys go along with the plan, not realizing that the "millionaire" and his pretty niece are in on the scam and are planning to knock them off.  The Stooges foil the plan and recover Joe's money. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013000000 +0000" stop="20241013023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost And Mr. Chicken</sub-title>
    <desc>"A timid typesetter who longs to be a reporter hopes to land a big story by spending a night in a haunted house."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013023000 +0000" stop="20241013050000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Fiend Without A Face</sub-title>
    <desc>"Invisible atomic monsters attack a U.S. Armed Forces base and the local residents."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013050000 +0000" stop="20241013060000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie Uncrypted</title>
    <sub-title>Svengoolie Uncrypted</sub-title>
    <desc>"After 43 years in his warm and cozy dungeon, master horror host, Svengoolie leaves on an epic journey filled with celebrity encounters; long lost archives; a search for lost memorabilia and a celebration that could only take place in Berwyn, Illinois."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013060000 +0000" stop="20241013063000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare At 20,000 Feet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While aboard a commercial aircraft, a man believes he is seeing a gremlin on its wing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013063000 +0000" stop="20241013070000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Living Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is displeased when his wife buys an expensive doll for his step-daughter. He becomes even more displeased when the doll tells him it doesn't like him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013070000 +0000" stop="20241013073000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Shelter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nuclear attack appears imminent, several suburban friends and neighbors fight over control of a single bomb shelter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013073000 +0000" stop="20241013080000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Monsters Are Due On Maple Street</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Paranoia strikes the residents of Maple Street when they believe human-looking aliens have invaded the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013080000 +0000" stop="20241013083000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Eye Of The Beholder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A bandaged young woman awaits the outcome of an experimental treatment that has been administered to her in a last-ditch effort to make her appear normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013083000 +0000" stop="20241013090000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The After Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is shocked to learn that the floor of a department store on which she bought a gold thimble doesn't exist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013090000 +0000" stop="20241013093000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely old woman refuses to leave her apartment for fear of meeting "Mr. Death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013093000 +0000" stop="20241013100000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>To Serve Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kanamits, nine-foot-tall aliens, arrive on Earth with one lofty goal: To Serve Man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013100000 +0000" stop="20241013110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>The Racer's Edge</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt develops a new power and is tasked with protecting a diplomat's daughter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013110000 +0000" stop="20241013113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Will   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A favorite graduate dies and leaves $10,000 in his will to Bayside, creating a battle of the sexes at the school as both feel they deserve the endowment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013113000 +0000" stop="20241013120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>No Hope With Dope   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A famous film star comes to Bayside to shoot an anti-drug PSA. The gang is enamored with him but then they discover that he uses drugs himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013120000 +0000" stop="20241013123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Detention   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>If Zack can just get out of detention, he has a chance at winning a trip to Hawaii. Doing their best to get him off the hook, the gang ends up in detention, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013123000 +0000" stop="20241013130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Isn't It Romantic   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On Valentine's Day, the gang flashes back to the romantic adventures they've had in the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013130000 +0000" stop="20241013133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Wrestling With The Future   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Slater and his father fight over where he should attend college and Zack tries to fix it. Meanwhile, Jessie becomes a cheerleader and worries about college acceptances.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013133000 +0000" stop="20241013140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Class Rings   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack buys class rings for all the seniors at Bayside, he's embarrassed to find out he's been had when the rings turn out to be phonies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013140000 +0000" stop="20241013143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Popularity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan competes in a popularity contest at school. With Peter as her campaign manager and the rest of the family pitching in, she's got a great chance of winning - if she can stop making promises to her classmates that she can't possibly keep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013143000 +0000" stop="20241013150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Kelly's Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The Brady's friends, the Kellys, adopt three boys, all of different ethnic backgrounds, and soon find themselves dealing with racist neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013150000 +0000" stop="20241013153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Ah, Wilderness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys and their girls go on a camping trip for their spring vacation. Under Richie's leadership, however, everything seems to go wrong and nobody has a good time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013153000 +0000" stop="20241013160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Day Blind Dates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley unwittingly double-date with two criminals intent on robbing the bank next to the Pizza Bowl, the girls find themselves being held as hostages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013160000 +0000" stop="20241013163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Gentleman Crook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An infamous con artist, held temporarily in Mayberry, manages to enchant everyone except Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013163000 +0000" stop="20241013170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Train Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy gets mixed up with a jewel thief on a cross-country rail trip that marks the end of the series' Hollywood sojourn. That's not the only reason it's a bumpy ride—Lucy keeps pulling the emergency-brake cord!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013170000 +0000" stop="20241013173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver learns he has to go to the dentist and that's when his friends tell him some horror stories about the drill the dentist is going to use. This prompts Beaver to become downright scared of going to the dentist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013173000 +0000" stop="20241013180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Gets Adopted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally wins a trophy at school and Beaver accidentally breaks it. This leads Ward to accuse Beaver of being jealous of Wally and that he broke it on purpose. Upset, Beaver decides to get new parents and heads to an adoption agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013180000 +0000" stop="20241013183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick arrives with his daughter, Essiebelle. He found love letters Jethro wrote to his daughter, a beauty contest winner. He plans to get Jethro and Essiebelle married so he can get his paws in the Clampett fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013183000 +0000" stop="20241013190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Lingers On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick returns to the Clampett mansion looking to get rich off Jed's money. He tries to get a job at the bank guarding Jed's money, only to get a few million dollars. But Granny has her doubts about the freeloader, though he seems to be proving her wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013190000 +0000" stop="20241013193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs.???</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A radio bulletin states that the minister who married the Howell's was a fraud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013193000 +0000" stop="20241013200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Meet The Meteor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A huge meteor lands on the island, causing everything nearby to age very rapidly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013200000 +0000" stop="20241013203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Harper Versus Harper  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Naomi's feud with Mama lands the two in court when Mama breaks Naomi's vacuum cleaner. The judge has an impossible time keeping order and holds both parties in contempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013203000 +0000" stop="20241013210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama's Birthday  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The family can't understand why Mama dislikes celebrating her birthday. Helping her clean out the attic later that day, Buzz finally pries the story out of her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013210000 +0000" stop="20241013220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Eyes Of Love / Masquerade / Hollywood Royalty (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Part 1. Thieves eye a honeymooning actress's gems; a man encounters his blind childhood love; a wife meets her spouse's mistress."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013220000 +0000" stop="20241013223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to help Barney express his lovestruck feelings for Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013223000 +0000" stop="20241013230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Masks- Rudy Munis</sub-title>
    <desc>"Classic Halloween mask collector Rudy Munis has one of the most pristine mask collections known.  Costume expert Mark Short value's Rudy's collection and brings a master mask mold to offer in trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013230000 +0000" stop="20241013233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Trick Or Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Halloween at the 4077th, and the staff dons costumes and trades ghost stories. Father Mulcahy discovers a soldier alive that had been pronounced dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241013233000 +0000" stop="20241014000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Unforgettable Characters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets accepted into the "Famous Las Vegas Writers School," and begins to write his impressions of the camp. It happens to be Frank's birthday, so Hawkeye and B.J. stage a fight with each other to make Frank happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014000000 +0000" stop="20241014003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Unemployment Story (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's self-esteem takes a beating when he loses his job on the loading dock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014003000 +0000" stop="20241014010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Unemployment Story (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A college grad threatens to commit suicide after he loses a jaintor's job to Archie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014010000 +0000" stop="20241014013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Operation (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's trip to the hospital is an ethnic nightmare. He's admitted by a Puerto Rican receptionist, treated by a Jewish physician, and is forced to accept a blood transfusion from a black doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014013000 +0000" stop="20241014020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Operation (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie recuperates in record time after he's called back to work-with a raise and a promotion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014020000 +0000" stop="20241014023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Shani Wallis And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Shani Wallis and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 04/29/68."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014023000 +0000" stop="20241014030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol suspects her sister is pregnant and tries to figure out who the father is. Then, in George and Zelda, Carol sabotages a poker game on a riverboat. Finally, in Salute to Horror Movies, the gang parodies classic films, including "The Mummy", "The Wolf Man", and "The Bride of Frankenstein".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014030000 +0000" stop="20241014033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>It May Look Like A Walnut!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob falls asleep with a sci-fi movie on and gets visited by an alien from another planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014033000 +0000" stop="20241014040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Ghost Of A Chantz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob, Laura, Buddy and Sally spend the night in a seemingly haunted cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014040000 +0000" stop="20241014043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph cuts a record to sweet talk Alice after insulting her mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014043000 +0000" stop="20241014050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Bewitchin' Pool</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Two unhappy children find a happy escape in a swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014050000 +0000" stop="20241014060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Address  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A couple moves into an isolated seaside residence in a last-ditch effort to save their unstable marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014060000 +0000" stop="20241014070000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Fatso</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After getting into a car accident in a rural Kentucky town, Kimble lands in jail by the redneck sheriff who hates outsiders. But Kimble manages to escape with his cellmate Davey "Fatso" Lambert. Hiding out at the Lambert ranch, Kimble sees that Davey's fa</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014070000 +0000" stop="20241014080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Illusion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Skarbeck and Lom are rivals for the vacant post of chief of secret police in the East European Peoples Republic. As they are both hardliners, the IMF must eliminate both of them and make sure Paul Trock becomes the new chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014080000 +0000" stop="20241014083000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Dust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Matthews searches for a laboratory worker who exposed himself to radioactive isotopes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014083000 +0000" stop="20241014090000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014090000 +0000" stop="20241014093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014093000 +0000" stop="20241014100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-21</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pot-detecting pooch joins the police to stop marijuana smuggling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014100000 +0000" stop="20241014103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 25 -- Indians</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed hunt down a suspect who has been bombing downtown storefronts. Then they report to a scuffle between two native americans at a bar that the bartender thinks may be a prelude to something a lot more serious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014103000 +0000" stop="20241014110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 135 -- Arson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In what would prove to be a very busy shift, Malloy and Reed search for a serial arsonist who spawns a copycat, settle a domestic dispute that results from a love triangle, rescue a man who wandered onto the ledge of a high rise and deal with a mentally ill man who is holding his wife at knife-point.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014110000 +0000" stop="20241014120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Stretching A Buck</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony learn tips and tricks to help them save more money without compromising on the fun."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014120000 +0000" stop="20241014123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus Ride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward allow Wally to escort Beaver on a bus headed to a friend's house in Crystal Falls. However, on one of the stops, Beaver inadvertently gets on the wrong bus, a bus that takes him back to Mayfield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014123000 +0000" stop="20241014130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Gilbert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The Cleavers have new neighbors in the Gates family and Beaver befriends their son, Gilbert Gates (changed to "Bates" in later episodes). However, Ward, June and Wally quickly realize the obvious when Beaver comes home with all kinds of wild stories that Gilbert has told and that Beaver is convinced are true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014130000 +0000" stop="20241014140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dangerous Dowager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Matilda Benson is a tough old broad who rules her children with an iron hand and the promises in her will. When Benson and her brood become involved in a gambling scandal and the death of a nightclub owner, Mason looks into the matriarch's matter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014140000 +0000" stop="20241014150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lemon  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's new neighbor, Les "Ace" Calhoun (Don Knotts), is charged with murdering the used car salesman who sold him a lemon, Matlock takes the case to prove that more than one person had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014150000 +0000" stop="20241014160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie receives word that a former Spartan is wanted for the murder of a socialite in Houston. But a ruthless bounty hunter, sent by the victim's jealous husband is already in Sparta and sees the man's sister as a means to locate his quarry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014160000 +0000" stop="20241014170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Milestone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia becomes emotional (menopausal symptoms) and runs away from home to visit a relative</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014170000 +0000" stop="20241014180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Morgan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E23</episode-num>
    <desc>With Matt out helping the Army deliver a gold shipment, Dodge is wide open for Morgan and his men to come in with a Gatlin gun and take over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014180000 +0000" stop="20241014190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The First Born</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man comes to town claiming to be Marie's son, Joe is not sure what to think. Could this be his brother, or is it all just a big lie?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014190000 +0000" stop="20241014193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Schoolmaster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and his friend become trapped in an old mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014193000 +0000" stop="20241014200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Promoter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark attempt to reform a con man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014200000 +0000" stop="20241014210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Countess Baranof Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Baranof is desperate to get to Alaska to claim her family fortune, and with no horses she applies her considerable charms on Flint. But she's not the one Flint should worry about, as her bodyguard has a more sinister agenda.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014210000 +0000" stop="20241014220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dealer's Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy talks down a boy in a plane after the pilot (his father) has a heart attack. The paramedics respond to an attempted suicide, an overturned truck and a teenage overdose victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014220000 +0000" stop="20241014223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014223000 +0000" stop="20241014230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014230000 +0000" stop="20241014233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241014233000 +0000" stop="20241015000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015000000 +0000" stop="20241015003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Housekeepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie go to great lengths to show Aunt Bee what a mess they'd be without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015003000 +0000" stop="20241015010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a handsome new doctor arrives in town, his friendship with Ellie arouses suspicion in Aunt Bee and Barney and jealousy in Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015010000 +0000" stop="20241015013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Cabin In Beverly Hills</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed puts up the cabin for Granny's birthday, which Mrs. Drysdale is not happy about. During the celebrating, a sociology student stops by and sees the Clampetts. She thinks they are Drysdale's servants and works to liberate them from what she believes to be a life of servitude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015013000 +0000" stop="20241015020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>School Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver spends a lot of time in the principal's office when Lisa enrolls at Hooterville High. In school primarily for a cooking course, she also disrupts history class with her own version of Hungary's past, destroys the womens' showers and explodes a chemistry lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015020000 +0000" stop="20241015023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015023000 +0000" stop="20241015030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hold That Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The POWs smuggle a tiger tank, about which Klink has been boasting, into camp in order to photograph and study it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015030000 +0000" stop="20241015033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Mike Douglas And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Mike Douglas and Bernadette Peters. Originally aired on 03/08/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015033000 +0000" stop="20241015043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fatal Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fortune teller gives a series of accurate predictions regarding a woman's future. But something goes wrong when she's charged with murdering her new husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015043500 +0000" stop="20241015050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Where Is Everybody?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds himself in a town strangely devoid of people. What's more, he can't recall his own identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015050500 +0000" stop="20241015060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Water's Edge  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An ex-convict is determined to find burglary loot stashed by his previous cellmate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015060500 +0000" stop="20241015070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>What Happened To Sunday?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix can't recall the events of the past 24 hours—other than a haunting memory of a little girl falling from a balcony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015070500 +0000" stop="20241015080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former convict gets Cannon to help him find the man who sent him to jail for no reason."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015080500 +0000" stop="20241015090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sister Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A nun is accused of taking her terminally ill sister off life support.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015090000 +0000" stop="20241015093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Witness Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man witnesses the disposal of a body and finds himself in danger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015093000 +0000" stop="20241015100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Administrative Vice - Dr-29</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's problem: is his temporary partner an aide—or an adversary?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015100000 +0000" stop="20241015103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 85 -- Sign Of The Twins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed start the shift with a call to a liquor store robbery, where a fellow officer was shot but the owner of the store appears to be lying. Further investigation pushes the owner to admit one of the thieves was his brother and he was trying to protect him. In the meantime, they have a zoning issue with an elderly astrology reader followed by the report of a young boy asking a pharmacist questions about Seconal pills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015103000 +0000" stop="20241015110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 175 -- Con Artists</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy respond to a car rollover where a good samaritan makes matters worse. Afterward, they respond to several victims of a well-known family of seasonal home improvement con artists before finally catching them in the act. In the meantime, they search for a disgruntled ex-employee who is trying to sabotage his former workplace, and take a drunk driver off the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015110000 +0000" stop="20241015120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Diners, Drive-ins &amp; Drive-thrus</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony cook up the idea to open their own restaurant while exploring the tasty past of diners, drive-ins, and drive-thrus."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015120000 +0000" stop="20241015123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Fame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying after school cleaning the chalkboards, Larry convinces Beaver that Mrs. Rayburn keeps a spanking machine in her office closet. Later, a curious Beaver sneaks a peek but soon finds himself locked in the principal's office. Beaver's fame doesn't go over well with his family, but Beaver has another problem on his hands: he's just gotten his head stuck in an iron fence in the park.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015123000 +0000" stop="20241015130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Horse Named Nick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally get jobs at the circus cleaning the animals and a promise to each be paid $10 dollars at the end of the week. However, the end of the week comes and there is no money in sight; instead, Beaver and Wally become the proud owners of a horse named Nicholas, which they hide in the garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015130000 +0000" stop="20241015140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Toy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Selkirk is a major league rotter who wants Claire Allison in the worst way, even though she's dating Dirk Benedict. Selkirk has Dirk's jaw broken and begins sending Claire threatening mail. Then Selkirk is murdered in his beach house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015140000 +0000" stop="20241015150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ambassador: Part 1  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Anthony Stewart is charged with murdering Michael Russell, the husband of the woman with whom he has been sleeping. Although Stewart, a visiting British ambassador, has diplomatic immunity, he refuses to use it and wants to clean his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015150000 +0000" stop="20241015160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Shine On Sparta Moon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A bottle of spiked moonshine leads to an accident that claims the life of one teen and blinds another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015160000 +0000" stop="20241015170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Celebration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Waltons have one remaining payment on their mortgage</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015170000 +0000" stop="20241015180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam takes a special interest in Eric Tabray, who is running around in a gang committing crimes in Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015180000 +0000" stop="20241015190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Quest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to prove his independence and break out of the shadows of his Pa and older brothers, Little Joe sets out to win a lucrative timber contract for the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015190000 +0000" stop="20241015193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Illustrator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas encourages a drunken artist charged with murder to use his talents to identify the true killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015193000 +0000" stop="20241015200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Knife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark try to persuade a persecuted young mute to return stolen money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015200000 +0000" stop="20241015210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Jarvis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy hurt in a crippling accident and his domineering mother meet a runaway boy, who she feels is making her son do things outside his capabilities. Another accident reveals something unexpected because it may pit two friends against each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015210000 +0000" stop="20241015220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nurses Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A store owner shoots an armed robber and is filled with remorse. Sparks fly between Johnny and a nurse. Dr. Early treats an alcoholic. A dog delays the rescue of an unconscious woman. Dr. Morton assumes an unconscious hippie is on drugs. The firemen rescue a man trapped at a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015220000 +0000" stop="20241015223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015223000 +0000" stop="20241015230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015230000 +0000" stop="20241015233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241015233000 +0000" stop="20241016000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016000000 +0000" stop="20241016003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Plaque For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Pike (Dick Elliott) and the townspeople are shocked to discover that the last living descendant of Revolutionary War hero Nathan Tibbs is Mayberry's town drunk, Otis Campbell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016003000 +0000" stop="20241016010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Inspector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A by-the-book courthouse inspector condemns Andy and Barney's lack of proper procedure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016010000 +0000" stop="20241016013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Foils A Home Wrecker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale tries to save the cabin for the Clampetts, but his wife calls a professional home wrecker to tear down the mountain shack. Meanwhile, Ginny Jennings and her sociology professor come back to visit the Clampetts and see that they are still occupying the cabin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016013000 +0000" stop="20241016020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>His Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver misunderstands when the Hooterville bigwigs ask him to be a judge. He thinks he's being appointed an appellate judge but they just want him to judge apples at the county fair. The Douglases travel to New York so Oliver can get some judging advice while Lisa shops for a robe and wig for His Honor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016020000 +0000" stop="20241016023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Forget To Write</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink fails a physical and gets combat duty at the Russian front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016023000 +0000" stop="20241016030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Rocket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to detour the German bombers that normally attack London to a nearby Allied airbase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016030000 +0000" stop="20241016033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, And David Frost (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, and David Frost. Originally aired on 03/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016033000 +0000" stop="20241016043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Candy Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Claire Armstrong has built a candy empire, but things go sour when her cousin is almost killed by poisoned candy and a man is found dead in his office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016043500 +0000" stop="20241016050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A street salesman cleverly eludes Death. But if he lives, a little girl must die in his place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016050500 +0000" stop="20241016060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Life Work Of Juan Diaz  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A dying Mexican frenetically looks for a way to provide for his poor family after his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016060500 +0000" stop="20241016070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Judas Touch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A missing police officer leads Chief Carl Yaring in search of the cop, a former ex-con who was suspected of robbery and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016070500 +0000" stop="20241016080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Ends At Noon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a Cuban exile to investigate the death of the man's brother at the hands of law enforcement officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016080500 +0000" stop="20241016090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Charade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty falls for a playboy who's planning a murder to gain an inheritance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016090000 +0000" stop="20241016093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A hunting accident leads Dan Matthews to investigate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016093000 +0000" stop="20241016100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Joy Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A 15-year-old car thief is given a tour of the jail in an attempt to show him the consequences for choosing crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016100000 +0000" stop="20241016103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 115 -- Gang War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Reed loses a robbery suspect while in foot pursuit. Afterward, he and Malloy try to help a priest prevent bloodshed between rival hispanic gangs, and then respond to a battered wife whose husband is very familiar to the officers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016103000 +0000" stop="20241016110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 26 -- Lemras</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed drive up on a convenience store robbery in progress, which results in the suspects taking hostages. Later, they pull over a reckless driver who has just committed a heinous crime, learn about a new computer system designed to help them be more productive and finally thwart a group of serial burglars who use motorcycles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016110000 +0000" stop="20241016120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Frontier</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony and Bill head north to Alaska, the land of bald eagles, northern lights, and... outhouse races?!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016120000 +0000" stop="20241016123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver discovers that Ward was in WWII and brags to his classmates that Ward was a war hero. As usual, his classmates don't believe him and Beaver promises to bring in some momentos to prove it. However, at home, Beaver discovers that Ward was an engineer in the war and didn't actually fight in combat, thus leaving Beaver to take drastic measures so as not to look like a fool in front of his classmates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016123000 +0000" stop="20241016130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Says Good-bye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward makes an offer on a house located in a neighboring town and Beaver believes moving is going to be a sure thing. This leads him to tell all his classmates that he's moving, but when the deal falls through Beaver must tell his class that he won't be moving after all—after they've just thrown him a goodbye party and shoved a handful of presents in his face!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016130000 +0000" stop="20241016140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spanish Cross</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Jimmy Morrow can't seem to catch a break. Already on probation for car theft, he's charged with stealing a valuable Spanish cross and killing its owner. Mason feels sorry for the kid and decides to take the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016140000 +0000" stop="20241016150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Ambassador, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Anthony Stewart is nearly killed in a hit and run, Matlock realises that the only way to clear him is to find Shelby Russell, the supposed witness whose claim put Stewart in the hot seat in the first place. He tracks her down via her mother, and tells her that if she doesn't take the stand, her lover will go down for Michael Russell's murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016150000 +0000" stop="20241016160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Execution Of Trust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A psychiatrist tells Gillespie that one of her patients has confessed to a crime that another man is about to be executed for, but she refuses to divulge his identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016160000 +0000" stop="20241016170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Rumor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Members of Flossie Brimmer's family visit the mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016170000 +0000" stop="20241016180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hackett</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S15E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict wants revenge against the partner that ran out on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016180000 +0000" stop="20241016190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Artist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Wallowing in self-pity after having gone blind, Matthew Raine begins coming out of his self-imposed exile after befriending Ben's housekeeper, Ann Loring. However, there is someone who doesn't want Matthew to extricate himself from his miserable state.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016190000 +0000" stop="20241016193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bertie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A lively old lady arrives in town hot on the trail of a notorious bandit—and the reward money for capturing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016193000 +0000" stop="20241016200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Six Years And A Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A doctor seeks revenge on the man he blames for ruining his practice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016200000 +0000" stop="20241016210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dr. Swift Cloud Story</sub-title>
    <desc>"The wagon train runs into their old pal Swift Cloud who's on his way back to his Native American village after studying medicine in China. However, the aspiring physician faces resentment from both whites and his own people."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016210000 +0000" stop="20241016220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Publicity Hound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John is envious of the publicity given to another paramedic. After Roy and John rescue a man trapped in ship's rigging, John gets seasick. Dr. Brackett clashes with a tycoon over a diagnosis. The paramedics rescue a horse from a ditch and a child stuck in a well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016220000 +0000" stop="20241016223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016223000 +0000" stop="20241016230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016230000 +0000" stop="20241016233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241016233000 +0000" stop="20241017000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017000000 +0000" stop="20241017003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Saves A Female</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie encourages and helps a female farmhand to express her femininity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017003000 +0000" stop="20241017010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Forecloses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Grumpy businessman Ben Weaver insists that Andy foreclose on a down-on-his-luck neighbor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017010000 +0000" stop="20241017013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny Goes To Hooterville</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Right after the Clampett's return from London, Granny gets a letter saying she is needed in Hooterville. The problem is that nobody knows where it is. Granny tries to find out, but doesn’t have much luck. Jethro, who isn't getting fed because Granny is focusing on Hooterville, is desperate for food and accidentally eats Elly's grits and rocks for her critters. Granny has to “doctor” him back to health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017013000 +0000" stop="20241017020000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>It's So Peaceful In The Country</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Oliver's mother needs bed rest so what better place than her son's farm. All she has to do is ignore Alf and Ralph's drilling, Haney's tour group, a group of dancing Sioux Indians and their chief who thinks she's a looker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017020000 +0000" stop="20241017023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Information Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After detecting an information leak in the area of Stalag 13, the Germans replace Klink with a more efficient officer, who Hogan sets up to take the fall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017023000 +0000" stop="20241017030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Art For Hogan's Sake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a French painting from ending up in Goering's art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017030000 +0000" stop="20241017033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, And David Frost (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Eileen Farrell, Marilyn Horne, and David Frost. Originally aired on 03/22/71."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017033000 +0000" stop="20241017043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cheating Chancellor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason returns to his college alma mater to receive an award, but there's no rest for the weary when he's called upon to defend Van Fowler for the murder of a professor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017043500 +0000" stop="20241017050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Denton On Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A has-been, drunk gunslinger finds his fast-draw abilities magically restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017050500 +0000" stop="20241017060500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>See The Monkey Dance  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A youthful London man heading for a weekend with his married mistress encounters a gentleman with oddly similar plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017060500 +0000" stop="20241017070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>With Intent To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When attempts are made on the life of Detective Ira Deegan, who is in hot pursuit of a robber, his wife hires Mannix to keep an eye on her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017070500 +0000" stop="20241017080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Search And Destroy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon tries to find a girl who went missing after witnessing a murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017080500 +0000" stop="20241017090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Testament Of Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The executors of a millionaire's estate attempt to get rid of a new will putting them out of their jobs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241017090000 +0000" stop="20241017093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Convicted Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is exonerated for murder, he goes after the witness who identified him.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
