<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315090000 +0000" stop="20260315100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Storm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a hurricane mysterious avoids a church building, David investigates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315100000 +0000" stop="20260315110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams recalls the tale of how he met Nakoma when he was a new "Greenhorn" to the ways of the wilderness. How Nakoma helped him learn survival and also the tribal ceremony that bonded their friendship as Blood Brothers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315110000 +0000" stop="20260315113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Falcon</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit the mountain prairies of Wyoming where falcons, eagles and hawks rule the air."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315113000 +0000" stop="20260315120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bears Of The High Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim follow a pair of black bear cubs in Yellowstone National Park; track a large black bear to tag for future reference."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315120000 +0000" stop="20260315123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bundu Rescue</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go on a thrilling adventure in South Africa to catch lions, hippos and elephants for scientific and conservation purposes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315123000 +0000" stop="20260315130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Raccoon Valley</sub-title>
    <desc>"With Marlin and Jim you follow the raccoon family in their adventures in a remote valley amid the scenic splendor of southern Utah."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315130000 +0000" stop="20260315133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Crocodile Is King</sub-title>
    <desc>"To Marlin and Jim, Africa’s waters mean the chance to film the most exciting dramas and most unusual animals ever captured by the camera.  Crocodiles are among the largest reptiles in the world and the most feared!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315133000 +0000" stop="20260315140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>El Tigre</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the hostile mountains and deserts of Mexico roams one of the world’s most beautiful and dangerous cats…El Tigre the jaguar. Marlin and Jim track this predator through miles of inhospitable terrain."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315140000 +0000" stop="20260315143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Love And The Older Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia falls for Dr. Vogel, the family's new dentist. When he asks Mike if Marcia would be interested in doing some babysitting for his kids, she's mistakenly under the impression that he's asking her out on a date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315143000 +0000" stop="20260315150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Locket, Found Locket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan receives a mysterious locket in the mail. Pretty soon a manhunt begins to find the sender, the only clue being the typewriter used to address the envelope drops its ‘y.’ When the locket mysteriously vanishes, Peter suggests they re-enact exactly what they were doing the night it disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315150000 +0000" stop="20260315153000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Giant Jackrabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>At the mansion, the clan is in need of food because the hunting in Beverly Hills is horrible. They call a catering company, but get mean-mouthed. At the bank, Drysdale gets a call and learns that he got a kangaroo from a friend and it is at his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315153000 +0000" stop="20260315160000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly Comes Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly shows Granny an article about an old school mate getting engaged after having a coming out party. Granny tells Jed about this, and the clan decides to give Elly May a coming out party. Drysdale isn’t happy about hearing this, especially the spare-no-expense part and seeing the Clampetts’ country decorations. Drysdale decides to get someone to help with the task so the Clampetts don’t embarrass themselves, getting his wife to tend to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315160000 +0000" stop="20260315163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie For Council</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie's decision to run for town council sparks a battle of the sexes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315163000 +0000" stop="20260315170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Does A Tv Commercial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Desperate to be in Ricky's new television commercial, Lucy makes every attempt to get her way, which eventually pays off. But her one-and-only chance flops when she is forced to test the sponsor's product over and over, a vitamin syrup called Vitametavegimin, which is 23% alcohol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315170000 +0000" stop="20260315173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>June's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June's birthday has Wally and Beaver fighting over what to buy with the $5 dollars that Ward gave them. Wally buys her a wallet while Beaver buys an ugly blouse that June kindly thanks him for, but she has a hard time bringing herself to wear it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315173000 +0000" stop="20260315180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>No Time For Baby Sitters</sub-title>
    <desc>"June, Ward and Wally are going out for the evening and not wanting to worry about Beaver, June calls a babysitter, despite Beaver's pleas against the idea."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315180000 +0000" stop="20260315190000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Angels On Wheels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Jill gears up as a roller derby star to solve a murder of the champ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315190000 +0000" stop="20260315200000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Color Jennifer Dead</sub-title>
    <desc>"An up and coming artist's premature death exposes a collectors scheme to increase the value of his own collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315200000 +0000" stop="20260315210000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Bowling / Command Performance</sub-title>
    <desc>"A retired circus owner gathers her old acts together for 5-year reunion, dangerously aware that one of the performers wants her dead on Fantasy Island. An amateur bowler fulfills his dream of competing with the world's best professional bowlers on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315210000 +0000" stop="20260315220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>How Do I Love Thee? / No More Alimony / Authoress! Authoress!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A man bound by alimony wants to make sure his ex goes through with her marriage; Julie's Aunt Sylvia and her pal Betsy try to interest a publisher in Betsy's memoirs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315220000 +0000" stop="20260315223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Medicine Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, saddened by the death of a friend, is feeling old and tired. She stumbles across a medicine man's presentation and is intrigued by his bottle of elixir, which she believes to add pep to her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315223000 +0000" stop="20260315230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Props/costumes- Jennifer Klein</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jennifer Klein grew up in LA with a dad who worked in Hollywood, and her screen used Props &amp; Costumes collection from TV shows like "CHIPs" and films like "Back To The Future" is stunning.  Expert and longtime costume dealer Marcia Tysseling appraises Jen's collection and has brought some classic TV costumes to offer in trade."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315230000 +0000" stop="20260315233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger saves Winchester's life when an explosion rocks the operating room; and B.J. is reluctant to reveal the extent of his injuries after the blast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260315233000 +0000" stop="20260316000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Sweat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret develops a case of prickly heat, Charles does his tax returns and Klinger takes the P.A. apart—just some of the events that occur during another unendurably hot night at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316000000 +0000" stop="20260316003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of Stephanie's Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Stephanie's father, Floyd, finally arrives with a devastating proposition for the Bunkers: They can keep Stephanie if they agree to pay him $1000 cash!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316003000 +0000" stop="20260316010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Too Good Edith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>On Archie's St. Patrick's Day Party at the tavern, he discovers that Edith is terribly ill after doing a lot of cooking for him. Sidney comes to the rescue and is able to save Edith before it's too late and he also tells Archie that he knew about her illness before and so did Edith. Sidney mentions that he did tell Edith to stay off her feet, but obviously, with the cooking for Archie, she didn't listen to his instruction. Archie visits Edith upstairs and is disappointed that she didn't get rest instead of doing something for his party. Instead of leaving to host it, Archie falls asleep in the arms of his lover, Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316010000 +0000" stop="20260316013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Meet The Bunkers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Edith and Archie Bunker's 22nd wedding anniversary and their daughter Gloria and her husband Mike are planning a surprise Sunday brunch. Edith is pleasantly surprised, however, Archie's "no big deal" attitude leads to a huge argument with his son-in-law on topics ranging from Archie's prejudices, problems with the nation's government and Mike's atheism.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316013000 +0000" stop="20260316020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Writing The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike writes a letter to President Nixon protesting everything that's wrong with America, including the state of the environment and the nation's involvement in Vietnam. Archie finds out, and to refute his son-in-law's claims, he decides he also will write a letter to Tricky Dick, praising the nation's chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316020000 +0000" stop="20260316023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond's pleasantly surprised with the laughs he gets at Debra's expense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316023000 +0000" stop="20260316030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Visit, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Debra's mother comes to visit, she wishes her mom were more like Marie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316030000 +0000" stop="20260316033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ray Murdock's X-ray</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob describes Laura as a nut on TV...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316033000 +0000" stop="20260316040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>I Was A Teenage Head Writer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recalls how he became head writer and how Buddy and Sally really were.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316040000 +0000" stop="20260316043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Safety Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph has an accident on his way to receiving his Safest Bus Driver Award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316043000 +0000" stop="20260316050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Probe 7 - Over And Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The lone survivors of two annihilated worlds find themselves stranded together on a distant and uninhabited planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316050000 +0000" stop="20260316060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Owl  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A man blackmails a couple by threatening to tell their adopted daughter the truth about her birth parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316060000 +0000" stop="20260316070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Break!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate man Dutch Krebbs controls a large gambling operation. After an undercover IMF agent with a camera-watch disappears, presumably with recorded evidence against Krebbs, the IMF must find the agent's body and the watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316070000 +0000" stop="20260316080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Chariot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble happens to watch a TV debate in which a once-renowned attorney, named G. Stanley Lazer, claims that he could reverse Kimble's criminal conviction if the case went back to trial. Lazer once a respected lawyer, had his license revoked after getting i</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316080000 +0000" stop="20260316090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Double Jeopardy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry O takes on an unusual client when he tries to protect a murder suspect from syndicate killers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316090000 +0000" stop="20260316093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316093000 +0000" stop="20260316100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Parolee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon retrace a 14-year-old investigation to determine whether charges can be brought against a man up for parole.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316100000 +0000" stop="20260316103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Harry Nobody</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed's investigation of a fatal shooting in a hotel room hinges on the eyewitness account of a hopeless wino named Harry who is desperate to make a name for himself. Meanwhile, they investigate a report of a peeping tom at the home of an exotic dancer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316103000 +0000" stop="20260316110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Malloy's birthday, but he's consumed with anger over the thought his colleagues might have a plan to throw him a surprise party. On a busy patrol, he and Reed make an ironic traffic stop while responding to a burglary call at an antique store, deal with an extremely embarrassed theft victim at a lingerie store, investigate suspicious activity at a service station, use a creative approach to apprehend a serial jewelry store burglar and engage in a shootout inside the police station's parking garage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316110000 +0000" stop="20260316120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toony's Talent Showcase</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony hosts his very own talent showcase."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316120000 +0000" stop="20260316123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo Magic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward make Wally and Beaver promise that they won't go see a scary movie. However, Wally and Beaver are talked into seeing it, thanks to Wally's so-called best friend, Eddie Haskell. The movie has quite an influence on Beaver, who makes a voodoo doll, names it Eddie Haskell and sticks it with pins.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316123000 +0000" stop="20260316130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Paper Route</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Beaver want to get brand-new bikes so they ask Ward for some money; however, he suggests that they earn the money. This leads Wally and Beaver to get a job delivering papers. Later, while trying to help the boys out, Ward and June inadvertently almost get Wally and Beaver fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316130000 +0000" stop="20260316140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lurid Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A young widowed high school English teacher in a small town is accused via letter of making passes and more towards some of her male students. But a small town is a small town and it seems that all the key figures are involved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316140000 +0000" stop="20260316150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Reporter (aka The Widow)  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A reporter asks for Matlock's help in clearing a newlywed (Caryn Richman) charged with the murder of her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316150000 +0000" stop="20260316160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese computer research company executive is recognized by a veteran as his former captor in a Philippine prison camp in World War II.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316160000 +0000" stop="20260316170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen finds a ring in a purse she got. Belongs to a neighbor. Loses it at a dance</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316170000 +0000" stop="20260316180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Champion Of The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Bull Bannock (Alan Hale), retired heavyweight champion of the world, attempts to make a home for himself in Dodge City, and tries to buy Miss Kitty's Longbranch Saloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316180000 +0000" stop="20260316190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Way Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam finds shelter overnight at a stagecoach way station. There he meets others ranging from a beautiful girl to a dangerous outlaw on the run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316190000 +0000" stop="20260316193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Conscience</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>No one's more surprised than Micah when newcomer Leota Carraway claims he's her long-lost husband and the father of her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316193000 +0000" stop="20260316200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Reckoning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is torn by conflicting emotions when he meets the town's new preacher—a former outlaw whom he vowed to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316200000 +0000" stop="20260316210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Millie Davis Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Millie Davis reluctantly takes in an orphaned baby girl. Eight years later the girl's grandmother arrives to retrieve her. But Millie doesn't want to give up the child, so she claims that she and Flint are the parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316210000 +0000" stop="20260316220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen plan to celebrate the imminent retirement of a martinet captain with a party, under the guise of throwing a farewell dinner. A model in a bear suit suffers from heat stroke during a promotion stunt. A bizarre family believes their sleeping mother is dead. The firemen rescue CHP officers from a helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316220000 +0000" stop="20260316223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Depressing News</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger's army newspaper reports on Hawkeye's monument to military stupidity; a giant tower made from a half million erroneously shipped tongue depressors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316223000 +0000" stop="20260316230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>No Laughing Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye wagers that he can go a full day without a wisecrack, and Winchester finally confronts the major who exiled him to the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316230000 +0000" stop="20260316233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Oh, How We Danced</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester is sent to inspect sanitary conditions on the frontlines, while the rest of the camp plans a surprise anniversary party for B.J.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260316233000 +0000" stop="20260317000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottoms Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Margaret's nurses tries to hide her severe drinking problem, and Hawkeye is scorned after a practical joke he plays on Winchester backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317000000 +0000" stop="20260317003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rivals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his first crush, who ignores him. Barney steps in and tries to give him advice about women, which leads to Opie developing a crush on Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317003000 +0000" stop="20260317010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Wife For Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy should be getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317010000 +0000" stop="20260317013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Halloween Candy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray decides to make the drastic move of "cutting the wires."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317013000 +0000" stop="20260317020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert finally musters up the courage to move out on his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317020000 +0000" stop="20260317023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>The Engagement (pilot)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The pilot centers on Blanche who has fallen in love, raising the possibility that her boarders will have to move out in the event of a marriage. When the wedding is called off Blanche finds comfort and love from her dearest friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317023000 +0000" stop="20260317030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Guess Who's Coming To The Wedding?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy's daughter, Kate, comes to Miami with an announcement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317030000 +0000" stop="20260317033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Joanne Woodward</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice reunites with an old friend who's now a carefree divorcee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317033000 +0000" stop="20260317043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lame Canary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ruth Prescott wants to divorce Walter Prescott so she can be with her true love, Jimmy MacLaine. After a brush with death, Ruth becomes convinced that Walter is trying to kill her, but then Walter turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317043500 +0000" stop="20260317050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The 7th Is Made Up Of Phantoms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Three National Guardsmen explore the site of Custer's Last Stand and begin hearing strange noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317050500 +0000" stop="20260317053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Safe Conduct</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Suspense and romance fill the travel of an American reporter returning after a visit to an Iron Curtain nation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317053500 +0000" stop="20260317060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Place Of Shadows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A man looking for revenge goes undercover in a monastery but things do not turn out the way he planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317060500 +0000" stop="20260317070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Search For Darrell Andrews</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix suspects foul play when colleague Wes Tully is discovered floating dead in his swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317070500 +0000" stop="20260317080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Lady On The Run</sub-title>
    <desc>"After witnessing a murder, a woman flees to a sanitarium where she was once a patient. It's up to Cannon to find her and keep her safe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317080500 +0000" stop="20260317090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Mercenaries, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>J.R. is asked to find a man who hasn't been heard from since he became a mercenary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317090000 +0000" stop="20260317093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317093000 +0000" stop="20260317100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Bunco - $9,000</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The search is on for a swindler who conned an old vaudevillian out of $9,000 he found on a sidewalk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317100000 +0000" stop="20260317103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed suspect that a well-armed immigrant tailor who claims to be defending his establishment from burglars is actually plotting a murder. In the meantime, they deal with a drunken traveling businessman who passes out in a bar girl's car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317103000 +0000" stop="20260317110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate an interstate bounty hunter who has an invalid gun permit and questionable tactics. Meanwhile, they deal with an elderly man who strongly dislikes hippies, and a frustrated wife who desperately wants to receive a traffic ticket.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317110000 +0000" stop="20260317120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>St. Paddy's Day Hooray!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony travel to the Emerald Isle to celebrate St. Patrick's Day like the Irish."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317120000 +0000" stop="20260317123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Party Invitation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is invited to Linda Dennison's birthday party and quickly discovers that he is the only boy that she invited. Fearing for his reputation, Beaver tries his best to get out of attending but June and Ward are insistent, not aware of the situation Beaver's in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317123000 +0000" stop="20260317130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy Rutherford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The local bully, Lumpy Rutherford, has been picking on Beaver and Wally and, thanks to a story Ward tells them, the boys decide to play a joke on Lumpy. However, their ploy catches the wrong person: Lumpy's father and Ward's co-worker, Fred Rutherford, is caught in the trap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317130000 +0000" stop="20260317140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fickle Filly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After her father's death, a young woman finds herself penniless and alone. Then a present from her father—for which he paid $50,000—drops on her lap. However, it turns out to be worthless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317140000 +0000" stop="20260317150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Doctors  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an abhorred doctor meets his end, four of his former medical students are considered likely suspects. Matlock, however, is tasked with defending the prime suspect, the man seen fleeing the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317150000 +0000" stop="20260317160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Late John Louisiana</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The hit man sent to kill the witness to a two-year-old murder instead falls in love with her. McGarrett and the team must lead the search to find her before duty overtakes love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317160000 +0000" stop="20260317170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The System</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy tutors another person on a scholarship</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317170000 +0000" stop="20260317180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E15</episode-num>
    <desc>To Marshal Matt Dillon and his deputies falls their grimmest task in many years—the hanging of a ruthless gunman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317180000 +0000" stop="20260317190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Hoss And The Leprechauns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss goes leprechaun hunting, hoping to find gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317190000 +0000" stop="20260317193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Town Slept</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The town of North Fork becomes a haven for outlaws when suave Ben Judson smooth-talks his way into the marshal's job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317193000 +0000" stop="20260317200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Milly's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran returns with tales of heroism and the fate of Milly's brother in the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317200000 +0000" stop="20260317210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sakae Ito Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The major comes upon two Japanese men, attacked by Indians and heading towards California. He learns one of the men plans on committing hara kiri while others on the train have designs on a black box they suspect may contain precious gems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317210000 +0000" stop="20260317220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Computer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The computer fouls up and Gage gets a check for thousands instead of for hundreds. A transient is injured in a car at a junkyard. A victim’s dog causes problems. Two workers are trapped on a scaffold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317220000 +0000" stop="20260317223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Red/white Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter nearly blows his stack when his well-intentioned colleagues mollycoddle him in order to lower his blood pressure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317223000 +0000" stop="20260317230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bless You, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye can't stop a sneezing fit that has no apparent cause, psychiatrist Sidney Freedman digs into the surgeon's past for a clue to this unusual malady.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317230000 +0000" stop="20260317233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is overcome by the devotion of a terminally ill G.I., who has leukemia, for his critically wounded buddy, but he has trouble coming to terms with the fact that he can't cure the man. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is worried about the impending visit of a Cardinal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260317233000 +0000" stop="20260318000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Foresight Saga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is given a gift of fresh-grown vegetables by a grateful Korean; and Potter questions the veracity of an upbeat letter from Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318000000 +0000" stop="20260318003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dogs, Dogs, Dogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Visiting officials take pause when they visit Mayberry and find that the courthouse is full of dogs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318003000 +0000" stop="20260318010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mountain Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney visit the Darlings to rid them of Ernest T. Bass, who has his mind set on marrying daughter Charlene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318010000 +0000" stop="20260318013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Article, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is devastated, when his friend Andy, sells a piece to Sports Illustrated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318013000 +0000" stop="20260318020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Lone Barone, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond laments to his brother that marriage is like a prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318020000 +0000" stop="20260318023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Rose The Prude</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Having not dated since her husband died, Rose reluctantly agrees to go on a blind date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318023000 +0000" stop="20260318030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Transplant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche's sister, Virginia, comes to Miami for a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318030000 +0000" stop="20260318033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Dick Van Dyke And Tony Randall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Death of a Salesman, Dick Van Dyke tries to sell encyclopedias, only he keeps getting hurt by Carol. Then, in Root of All Evil, Tony and Dick get into a squabble about money after one loses five dollars and the other burns a ten dollar bill. Finally, in Warning Signals, a couple uses hand signals with each other in an attempt to get rid of their house guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318033000 +0000" stop="20260318043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Spurious Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Chapman returns home early from a business trip to find that his wife, Marie, wants a divorce. Chapman is shocked at this turn of events because he thought his wife had recently been strangled to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318043500 +0000" stop="20260318050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ninety Years Without Slumbering</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>An old man fears that he will die if his grandfather clock stops running.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318050500 +0000" stop="20260318053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Back For Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A man plans to get rid of his nagging wife — permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318053500 +0000" stop="20260318060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Two twisted brothers scheme to speed up their inheritance by killing their aunt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318060500 +0000" stop="20260318070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix sets out to prove the innocence of a young woman accused of shooting a businessman. A track leads Mannix to journalist Hackett, who was interviewing the victim moments before the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318070500 +0000" stop="20260318080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <desc>"A former convict gets Cannon to help him find the man who sent him to jail for no reason."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318080500 +0000" stop="20260318090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Wife Beater, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates a vicious husband who beats his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318090000 +0000" stop="20260318093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318093000 +0000" stop="20260318100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318100000 +0000" stop="20260318103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Spell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>On an unseasonably hot day, Malloy and Reed suspect that an elusive bicyclist who overreacts to having his air pump stolen in a park is actually a drug pusher. Meanwhile, their investigation of a two-month-long yard sale leads to an armed fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318103000 +0000" stop="20260318110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gifts And Long Letters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin today's patrol by investigating a deluded and reclusive parolee whose troubled girlfriend in the apartment next door has just attempted suicide for the second time. In the meantime, they provide vital information to a detective's search for an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318110000 +0000" stop="20260318120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Pillow Talk</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer starts a pillow company. Bill and Toony have loads of fun with the overstock."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318120000 +0000" stop="20260318123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Child Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After Ward's bragging about Wally and Beaver being responsible, Herb and Janet Wilson assume that it would be alright to leave their four-year-old daughter in Wally and Beaver's care while they go out to a party with Ward and June. However, the trouble begins when the youngster locks herself in the bathroom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318123000 +0000" stop="20260318130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Account</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward tries to teach Wally and Beaver the importance of saving by giving them a piggy bank. The boys quickly save up a handful of change and are all ready to spend it on some baseball equipment. However, unknown to their parents, they change their minds and decide to spend the money on a most unselfish gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318130000 +0000" stop="20260318140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Polka-dot Pony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy woman is confronted by two girls who claim to be the daughters she was forced to abandon 20 years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318140000 +0000" stop="20260318150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 1  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318150000 +0000" stop="20260318160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Eden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Five-O search for the criminals who set up Hawaiian singer and ecologist Jimmy Nuanu as the fall guy for a sewage plant bombing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318160000 +0000" stop="20260318170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoilers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A mountain man moves his family back to Walton's Mountain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318170000 +0000" stop="20260318180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Saturday Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A vengeful prisoner poses a continual threat to the life of Marshal Matt Dillon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318180000 +0000" stop="20260318190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Gallagher's Sons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss helps out two young girls, whose father has just died, by taking them on a journey to their Aunt's place. Unbeknownst to Hoss, one of the girls carries a stolen bag of money and he soon finds out that there are others who are interested in both the money and the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318190000 +0000" stop="20260318193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A head wound wipes out Lucas' memory, leaving him with only one clue: he's wearing an outlaw's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318193000 +0000" stop="20260318200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Executioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A former neighbor of the McCain's is released from jail after serving his sentence for stage coach robbery, but the money was never found. Lucas agrees to let the man work for him, but the new work hand holds a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318200000 +0000" stop="20260318210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tent City Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a member of the train is placed in chains after breaking indian law by killing a buffalo, Major Adams quarrels with Flint, who quits and takes a job at nearby Tent City. White Eagle discovers the dead buffalo and demands justice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318210000 +0000" stop="20260318220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Santa Rosa County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John try to go fishing in Santa Rosa County, but end up rescuing climbers from a cliff face and fishermen whose boat blew up. They also help the sheriff come up with ideas for implementing emergency medical services in his county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318220000 +0000" stop="20260318223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Life You Save</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles is nearly felled by a sniper's bullet, he develops a philosophical obsession with death. Meanwhile, the officers have all been assigned new responsibilities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318223000 +0000" stop="20260318230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318230000 +0000" stop="20260318233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That's Show Biz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A touring USO show brings an unexpected touch of vaudeville to the 4077th when the star showgirl requires an emergency operation. And wouldn't you know, the comedian is Klinger's hero!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260318233000 +0000" stop="20260319000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Identity Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy counsels a GI who is plagued by guilt because he has swapped tags with a dead colleague. Meanwhile, B.J. and Charles consider ways of keeping a soldier-salesman quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319000000 +0000" stop="20260319003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Big House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When the state police leave two captured bank robbers in the custody of the Mayberry police department overnight, Barney is determined to show the prisoners that the Mayberry jail is as good as any other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319003000 +0000" stop="20260319010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie The Birdman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie accidentally kills a mother bird with his new slingshot and takes it upon himself to raise the orphaned baby birds. After adopting them, Opie faces the difficult task of setting them free.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319010000 +0000" stop="20260319013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>No Fat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra, Ray and the kids make plans to spend the holiday at Frank and Marie's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319013000 +0000" stop="20260319020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Apartment, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Everywhere Ray looks  women are coming out to stop by and say "hi" to Robert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319020000 +0000" stop="20260319023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Triangle, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Dorothy is dating Dr. Elliot Clayton. Dr. Clayton makes a pass at Blanche.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319023000 +0000" stop="20260319030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>On Golden Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche's 14-year old grandson comes to Miami for a visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319030000 +0000" stop="20260319033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jack Klugman</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Small Office, accountants systematically cram into the smallest office to get work done. Then, in The Clairvoyant. a department store salesman tells a writer his bleak future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319033000 +0000" stop="20260319043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Watery Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lorna Thomas is a has-been actress who once gave up her baby for adoption and lived to regret it. George Clark discovers that his wife might be Lorna's long-lost daughter and begins to see dollar signs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319043500 +0000" stop="20260319050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Ring-a-ding Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A movie star receives a ring from her home town fan club. In it she sees the faces of people she knows telling her she's needed there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319050500 +0000" stop="20260319053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>There Was An Old Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An old and eccentric woman is targeted by a crooked couple who think she has a lot of money stashed away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319053500 +0000" stop="20260319060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Whodunit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur comes back from the afterlife to find out the identity of his murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319060500 +0000" stop="20260319070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is involved in a war of nerves when he deals with blackmailers threatening an entire town with nerve gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319070500 +0000" stop="20260319080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Ends At Noon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a Cuban exile to investigate the death of the man's brother at the hands of law enforcement officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319080500 +0000" stop="20260319090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Yesterdays Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman with a shady past plots the murder of her blackmailer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319090000 +0000" stop="20260319093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319093000 +0000" stop="20260319100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319100000 +0000" stop="20260319103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed starts a flu epidemic that decimates the city's police force, forcing him and Malloy to work a double shift. During day watch, he and Malloy encounter a bookmaker being held at gunpoint, mediate a dispute over a cantaloupe, investigate a possible robbery in progress, engage in a foot chase with an athletic young man and pull over a motorist who turns out to be a VIP.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319103000 +0000" stop="20260319110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly appointed Police Commissioner Edna Dixon accompanies Malloy and Reed on night watch, where they deal with a naked elderly wino at a bar, try to diffuse a possible riot situation following a gang-related stabbing and pursue a deaf teenager in a stolen car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319110000 +0000" stop="20260319120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Women's History - Going Undercover</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate women who were spies!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319120000 +0000" stop="20260319123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lonesome Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally goes away on a trip with the Boy Scout troop that he belongs to, leaving a lonesome Beaver behind. Finding his friends to be busy, Beaver takes up other means to make the time go by.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319123000 +0000" stop="20260319130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward becomes a bit jealous when Wally and Beaver begin spending time playing basketball at Willie Dennison's house after Willie's dad put up a backboard and a basket. This prompts Ward to do the same thing but it just seems like things are working against him in his quest to be the perfect father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319130000 +0000" stop="20260319140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Shoplifter's Shoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason digs into a dead man's past in search of evidence to clear an accused murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319140000 +0000" stop="20260319150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Billionaire: Part 2  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock flies to England to represent Eric Gordon, a man accused of murdering his wealthy businessman father. While his sister is convinced of his innocence, his brother isn't so sure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319150000 +0000" stop="20260319160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Over Fifty? Steal!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett and company must match wits against a veteran thief and robber who leaves Monopoly money at the scene of his crimes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319160000 +0000" stop="20260319170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Marathon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy participates in a dance marathon with Daisy</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319170000 +0000" stop="20260319180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus Haggen is mistaken for a hired gunman and offered $300 to fight and run out of town the three sons of a man his cousin is accused of killing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319180000 +0000" stop="20260319190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is seriously injured on a cattle drive and Ben takes him to a nearby town in search of a doctor. To his dismay, Ben finds out that the only doctor available is in jail, waiting to be hung for murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319190000 +0000" stop="20260319193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319193000 +0000" stop="20260319200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319200000 +0000" stop="20260319210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Jamison Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint, at a grave, sees a man stabbed in the back with a note saying, "Deliver to Beauty Jamison." As that is the daughter of the man interred he pays a visit and sees a woman trying to continue a legacy with the locals trying to break her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319210000 +0000" stop="20260319220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Paperwork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Chet and Marco are drafted to sort out a filing dilemma caused by computer error. A kid falls in a storm drain and nearly drowns. The paramedics experience problems with a new supply nurse. A janitor drinks samples of an archeologist's Mesopotamian wine. The firemen respond to a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319220000 +0000" stop="20260319223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rumor At The Top</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The latest scuttlebutt affects everyone's behavior when a visiting Army rep is rumored to be recruiting for a new M*A*S*H unit. The gang fears that the 4077th will be split up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319223000 +0000" stop="20260319230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give 'em Hell, Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes a heartfelt letter to President Harry Truman to protest at the continued fighting in Korea. Meanwhile, Colonel Ditka has promised a much-needed water heater if the 4077th beautifies the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319230000 +0000" stop="20260319233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Wheelers And Dealers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>On the eve of a big poker game, B.J.'s pride is bruised when he finds out his wife is working as a waitress. And Potter takes driving lessons from Klinger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260319233000 +0000" stop="20260320000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Breakdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester infuriates the camp when he hoards his stateside newspapers, and Hawkeye reunites two Korean brothers who have been fighting on opposite sides of the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320000000 +0000" stop="20260320003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Haunted House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Opie and his friend, Arnold, hit a baseball into the window of an old, abandoned house, they hear noises and run for help. Barney and Gomer go to investigate—and hear noises, too!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320003000 +0000" stop="20260320010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ernest T. Bass Joins The Army</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. wants to join the Army to impress a girl with the uniform. When he is refused induction, he goes on a window-breaking rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320010000 +0000" stop="20260320013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Toaster, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is overjoyed by the reaction he is getting from gifting a toaster to his family and friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320013000 +0000" stop="20260320020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray challenges Frank to a winner take all ping pong match.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320020000 +0000" stop="20260320023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Competition, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In a bowling competition, it's Dorothy and Blanche verses Rose and Sophia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320023000 +0000" stop="20260320030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Break-in, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After a Madonna concert, the girls arrive home, one evening, to discover their house has been broken into.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320030000 +0000" stop="20260320033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Digs, The</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice is furious when her vacation gets canceled. Then, in The Digs, a married couple decides to tell each other the truth about what really bugs them about the other person, and it doesn't end well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320033000 +0000" stop="20260320043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Garrulous Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry Benton is a hard-luck guy. He gets in an argument in a poker game and knocks Mike Granger out cold. Then he is informed him that Granger is dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320043500 +0000" stop="20260320050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>You Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving home one rainy evening, a man accidentally hits a boy on a bicycle. Determined to hide his guilt, the man flees the scene—but his car has other ideas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320050500 +0000" stop="20260320053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Help Wanted</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man desperate for money takes on a strange job offer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320053500 +0000" stop="20260320060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of Jocelyn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A man finds his disappeared wife in a painting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320060500 +0000" stop="20260320070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon A Saturday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After a string of strange accidents, a carnival-troupe boss employs Mannix to investigate the mishaps.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320070500 +0000" stop="20260320080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Search And Destroy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon tries to find a girl who went missing after witnessing a murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320080500 +0000" stop="20260320090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Damocles Gun, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The victim of a hit-and-run disappears as the sole witness calls an ambulance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320090000 +0000" stop="20260320093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>A.i.d. - The Weekend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon confront a phony magazine salesperson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320093000 +0000" stop="20260320100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Pill Maker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>It's a job half done when police nab a narcotics manufacturer: they still need his backer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320100000 +0000" stop="20260320103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>O'brien's Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy's headstrong and elderly apartment manager stages a protest at the station after she's victimized by a serial purse snatcher, and Malloy suggests a stakeout will be their only chance to apprehend the suspect. On patrol, he and Reed chase a suspicious vehicle into a lumber yard, and investigate the murder of a young man at his parents' home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320103000 +0000" stop="20260320110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest - 484</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspected child stealer who has escaped custody with the baby after being arrested for shoplifting baby formula. Meanwhile, Reed has to think quickly when he is held at gunpoint while responding to a burglary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320110000 +0000" stop="20260320120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Boxing Bill</sub-title>
    <desc>"How many rounds will Bill go in the ring?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320120000 +0000" stop="20260320123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Cleaning Up Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally begins to outgrow his "sloppy" phase and becomes much neater. This is noticed by Ward and June who try to encourage Beaver to undergo the same transformation. However, Beaver changing like that just seems too extraordinary of a task.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320123000 +0000" stop="20260320130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The State Vs. Beaver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward helps Beaver and Wally build a miniature race car powered by the lawn mower motor, and Ward makes the boys promise not to use it without his supervision. Later, Larry talks Beaver into taking it for a spin, resulting in the boys being pulled over by a traffic officer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320130000 +0000" stop="20260320140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bluffing Blast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl searching for the father she has never seen seeks Mason's help when she's charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320140000 +0000" stop="20260320150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Justice  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Michelle defends college chum Andrea Morrow after she is accused of murdering her abusive lover, Clay Graham. Matlock soon becomes convinced that the murderer was Clay's blind friend, Arthur Hampton, but has a devil of a time proving how a blind man managed to carry off a near-perfect murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320150000 +0000" stop="20260320160000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Beautiful Screamer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Williams' fiancee is murdered by a strangler who writes poetry in lipstick on his victims' legs. Danno resolves to catch the culprit who has other murderous plans to carry out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320160000 +0000" stop="20260320170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy gets his book of short stories published</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320170000 +0000" stop="20260320180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Muley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A young gunman (Zalman King) falls for one of Kitty's saloon girls (Lane Bradbury) while waiting to kill Marshal Matt Dillon and rob the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320180000 +0000" stop="20260320190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Song In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>When a guitar-strumming "traveling troubadour" is hired on at the Ponderosa, it is up to Adam to prove the minstrel's guilt or innocence when he is accused of a murder, before which a witness overheard singing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320190000 +0000" stop="20260320193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Lou Mallory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Mallory has arrived in North Fork and quickly purchases land, which includes the hotel and Milly Scott's store. She pays higher prices than the sellers feel their properties are worth. Everyone is happy until they find out that Lou really is an astute businesswoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320193000 +0000" stop="20260320200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320200000 +0000" stop="20260320210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dick Richardson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When the wagon horses start to die of a disease, Adams is forced to send two feuding men to buy new horses with his emergency money. Two horses return, but with only one man, leading Adams to wonder whether he made a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320210000 +0000" stop="20260320220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Ends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny tries to win a ticket-selling contest. Dr. Backett blames himself when he is involved in a car accident that leaves the other driver dead and The driver's daughter refuses to speak. While repairing the squad, the paramedics find themselves in the middle of a shootout and treat a policeman with heart trouble. A boxcar full of ammonia complicates a fire on a pier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320220000 +0000" stop="20260320223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Judgment: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The military police think they've solved a rash of thefts at the 4077th when they apprehend Klinger with Hawkeye's stolen camera.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320223000 +0000" stop="20260320230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snappier Judgment: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. and Hawkeye resolve to clear Klinger's name after he chooses Winchester to defend him at his military court-martial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320230000 +0000" stop="20260320233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260320233000 +0000" stop="20260321000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Follies Of The Living - Concerns Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While suffering a fever, Klinger communicates with the spirit of a dead soldier, Private Weston, who stays on to witness his own last rites.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321000000 +0000" stop="20260321003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon For Today</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting preacher gives a sermon about taking time to relax. In trying to create an atmosphere of relaxation on a Sunday afternoon, the townsfolk all end up running themselves ragged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321003000 +0000" stop="20260321010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Briscoe Declares For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Briscoe Darling becomes obsessed with Aunt Bee after hearing her recite a poem, going as far as to kidnap her and bring her back to his shack in the hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321010000 +0000" stop="20260321013000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Pants On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Marie is hurt and disappointed after finding that beloved Ray lied to her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321013000 +0000" stop="20260321020000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's entire demeanor changes when he starts clubbing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321020000 +0000" stop="20260321023000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Blanche And The Younger Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Blanche goes all out to try to look good for her latest beau.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321023000 +0000" stop="20260321030000 +0000">
    <title>The Golden Girls</title>
    <sub-title>Heart Attack, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a dinner party, Sophia suffers an apparent heart attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321030000 +0000" stop="20260321033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Butler And The Maid, The / Mrs. Wiggins</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Butler and the Maid, a married couple channels their frustration for each other through their butler and maid. Then, in Mrs. Wiggins, Mr. Tudball tries to teach Mrs. Wiggins how to use the intercom again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321033000 +0000" stop="20260321043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blushing Pearls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mitsuo Kamuri has been seeing a great deal of Grover Nichols, son of wealthy businessman Hudson Nichols. Nichols doesn't approve of his son's relationship and when Mitsuo is "caught" with a string of valuable pearls belonging to Mrs. Nichols, he agrees to absolve her if she stops seeing his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321043500 +0000" stop="20260321050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Morrow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Before leaving on a 40-year mission, an astronaut meets a woman and they fall in love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321050500 +0000" stop="20260321053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Orderly World Of Appleby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lawrence Appleby will do anything to keep his antiques shop, even murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321053500 +0000" stop="20260321060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Never Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Karen has a problem with alcohol, one that leaves her wondering what happened the previous night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321060500 +0000" stop="20260321070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Ticket To The Eclipse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A member of Mannix's Korean War Army unit is out for revenge for a wrong done to him in the past. But the man's odd confessions lead Mannix to believe he is suffering from combat fatigue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321070500 +0000" stop="20260321080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon receives a confession from a dying hitman who says he was responsible for the murder of his wife and daughter 14 years ago."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321080500 +0000" stop="20260321090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Gang War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang kidnaps J.R. and demands that he find out who killed the leader.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321090000 +0000" stop="20260321093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Cannonball, Inc.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After a derailment, Hooterville residents take over operation of the Cannonball from Homer Bedloe, and demand so many changes that the train's crew decides to quit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321093000 +0000" stop="20260321100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Kate Grounds Selma Plout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate Bradley tangles with Selma Plout when Selma tries to lure pilot Steve Elliott into marriage with her daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321100000 +0000" stop="20260321103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett General Hospital</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale wakes up to find she is no longer in the hospital but in her one hell—the Clampett mansion. After hearing she’s missing, her husband wants to sue the hospital. But when Jed and Jethro visit to return the mattress Mrs. Drysdale was on when they brought her home, the mystery of what happened is solved.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321103000 +0000" stop="20260321110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>An authority on American history finds evidence that Jed's ancestors preceded the Mayflower to America.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321110000 +0000" stop="20260321113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>The Man On The Flying Trapeze, Big Bad Sindbad, A Date To Skate</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye learns his girl friend Olive Oyl has gone away with a "young man on a flying trapeze.", Popeye tells his nephews about the time he bested Sinbad., It's Olive's first visit to a skating rink, and Popeye accidentally crashes into the pillar to which she is clinging. Popeye manages to rescue Olive in an amusing climax."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321113000 +0000" stop="20260321120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bodyguard, The Flying Bear, The Invisible Mouse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry uses a whistle given to him by a grateful bulldog to stop Tom from chasing him., Barney Bear is in the Army Air Corp as a mechanic but he decides to take a small plane out for a ride and ends up having some trouble with other flyers., Jerry turns invisible after diving into a bottle of invisible ink and then gets back at Tom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321120000 +0000" stop="20260321130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Woody Woodpecker Polka, The Big Snooze, Three Lazy Mice, Lonesome Ranger, The Bongo Punch, Rough And Tumbleweed, Tumble Weed Greed</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody disguises himself as a lovely lady to woo Wally Walrus and get into the dance for free., Chilly disturbs the hibernation of the bears at Grizzly National Park, and the park ranger tries to stop him., Three lazy mice try to get out of working by claiming to be blind., Woody makes a forest ranger's job difficult., Pepito the Rooster only wants to play the bongos, even though his dad wants him to be a champion fighter., Inspector Willoughby pursues a Wild West outlaw., Woody wins a cash prize and goes on vacation with it, but Buzz Buzzard wants to steal the cash."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321130000 +0000" stop="20260321140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Compressed Hare, I Taw A Putty Tat, Patient Porky, Barbary-coast Bunny, Wild Over You, Daffy Duck &amp; Egghead, A Witch's Tangled Hare</sub-title>
    <desc>"Wile E. Coyote becomes Bugs' new neighbor. While the Coyote pretends to be his friend, his real interests are in cooking the rabbit. , Sylvester has eaten every bird that his master gets until she gets Tweety., Porky enters a hospital with a stomach ache and contends with a crazy cat patient posing as a doctor. , Bugs runs into a giant gold boulder, which makes him rich. Unfortunately, Nasty Canasta uses a phony bank to steal Bug's fortune. , A female wildcat paints a white stripe on herself to scare a zookeeper and escape from the zoo at the Paris Exposition. Pepe LePew pursues his love, but any time he showers her with hugs and kisses the claws come out and she attacks., In an episode done in a very Elmer Fudd and Bugs fashion, Daffy and Egghead struggle with each other. , In search of poetic inspiration, William Shakespeare comes across the castle of Macbeth and finds Witch Hazel chasing Bugs Bunny therein. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321140000 +0000" stop="20260321150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Flying Pie Plate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>West gets involved in a bizarre scheme: a green girl emerges from a fallen spaceship claiming she needs gold for fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321150000 +0000" stop="20260321160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Kitty Angel Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty Angel finds herself not welcome on the wagon train because of her past. When Flint returns to the train toting a sick indian baby, she has everyone's prejudices to deal with as well as the baby's life-threatening illness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321160000 +0000" stop="20260321170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>A Noose Is Waiting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Two men are found hung, and a note left by each of them claims a third person will die: Victoria Barkley.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321170000 +0000" stop="20260321180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Drop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy (Eddie Hodges) comes to Dodge City in search of his father, only to learn that he is a wanted criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321180000 +0000" stop="20260321190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Ben Cartwright's old war buddies, who claims to be a business tycoon developing a new territory, woos a wealthy Virginia City widow and jeopardizes a Ponderosa land deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321190000 +0000" stop="20260321193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321193000 +0000" stop="20260321200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321200000 +0000" stop="20260321210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Ride A Crooked Mile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed intervenes when a card player refuses to surrender the Arabian stallion he lost in a poker game.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321210000 +0000" stop="20260321213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballad Of Oscar Wilde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin is hired to protect Oscar Wilde. Another 3 men apply for the job, but after Paladin upstages them they kidnap Wilde for ransom. Paladin takes care of them, his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321213000 +0000" stop="20260321220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Surprise Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh captures a notorious killer but no one wants to testify against him, until a surprise witness comes forward, his mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260321220000 +0000" stop="20260322000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Pests In A Mess, All Gummed Up, Squareheads Of The Round Table, Listen, Judge, They Stooge To Conga, Vagabond Loafers</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are three inventors trying to a get a patent on their preposterous fly catching invention.  When they learn they'll have to catch 100,000 flies to earn enough to get a patent, some crooks overhear and think the boys are the $100,000 sweepstakes winners.  When the crooks give chase, the Stooges hide in a sporting goods store where Curly shoots a dummy, which they mistake for a real person.  The boys decide to bury the "body" in a pet cemetery, but the cemetery owner arrives from a costume party with his partners, all dressed as spooks, and they proceed to scare the devil out of the Stooges. , The Stooges run a drug store and are about to have their lease taken away by the Flint, the mean old man who owns the place.  When Flint kicks his wife out for being old, the Stooges try to help her by inventing a formula that makes old people young.  Their concoction turns the wife into a beautiful young woman, and Flint offers the boys the store for free if they'll transform him as well.  They agree, but after he swallows the stuff he turns into an infant, and the boys leave on the run. , The Stooges are plumbers who are called out to a fancy mansion where a high society party is being thrown., Set in Elizabethan times, the Stooges decide to help their friend Cedric the Blacksmith win the hand of the fair princess Elaine.  At night the group sneaks into the castle to serenade Elaine, but pick the wrong window and are caught by the King.  Tossed in the dungeon, the boys escape with Cedric's help and manage to foil the plans of the Black Prince who was plotting against the King.  All turns out well when the grateful King allows Cedric to marry Elaine. , The Stooges becomes servants for the judge that they ran away from., The Stooges are repairmen who get a job fixing the doorbell in large house, which is the secret headquarters of some Nazi spies.  They manage to ruin most of the house while working on the wiring and then subdue the spies and sink an enemy submarine by remote control. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322000000 +0000" stop="20260322020000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Mummy's Hand</sub-title>
    <desc>"An American archaeological expedition meets with disaster when they ignore warnings not to desecrate an Egyptian tomb."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322020000 +0000" stop="20260322023000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Sandman Cometh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Catwoman teams with the Sandman to lure a rich insomniac.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322023000 +0000" stop="20260322030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Catwoman Goeth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman races to save Robin, stop the Sandman from marrying a millionaire and find his missing Batmobile. Meanwhile, the Sandman plans to double-cross Catwoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322030000 +0000" stop="20260322040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Who Mourns For Adonais?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise encounters an alien who claims to be the Greek god Apollo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322040000 +0000" stop="20260322043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois Lane is vacationing in Canada when she is kidnapped by gunmen. Jimmy tries to help her, but gets captured as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322043000 +0000" stop="20260322050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl is kidnapped by counterfeiters when she mistakenly receives a phone call meant for them, telling the time and location of a meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322050000 +0000" stop="20260322060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>A Visit To Hades</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After a harp unlocks a passageway to another world, Dr. Smith believes he has ended up in Hell and met the devil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322060000 +0000" stop="20260322070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Fires Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson and his men battle to stop an aged alchemist who's endangering the whole southern hemisphere to obtain an elixir of youth from an exploding volcano.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322070000 +0000" stop="20260322080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A giant scientist and his assistant hunt the Earthlings using a sound detector from which there is no escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260322080000 +0000" stop="20260322090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In an Iron Curtain country, Tony and Doug pose as scientists to investigate a primitive enemy time-tunnel in 1956.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
