<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224160000 +0000" stop="20241224170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Leftover Man: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A white supremacist politician plans to have his wife's lover murdered and blame it on black radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224170000 +0000" stop="20241224180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Children's Carol - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas approaches, Mary Ellen and the baby leave to be near Curt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224180000 +0000" stop="20241224190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Tatum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E10</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-gunfighter is dying. He must reconcile with the daughters he abandoned, and find a way to be buried next to his wife, who is buried in a town that hates him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224190000 +0000" stop="20241224200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Saga Of Muley Jones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Bruce Yarnell makes his first appearance as the Cartwrights' cousin, Muley, from Missouri. "Blessed" with a singing voice that can literally shatter glass, Muley manages to make life difficult for his rich relations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224200000 +0000" stop="20241224203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224203000 +0000" stop="20241224210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224210000 +0000" stop="20241224220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Ellen Thomas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Ellen is an orphan traveling west to join family; members of the train reject her due to her surly disposition. Her only friend is Sally Mayhew, another girl traveling west with her family dying of consumption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224220000 +0000" stop="20241224230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Fix It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's husband is trapped under their house, where a natural oil well has erupted. John tries to fix a boy's bike. A boy who wants to become a doctor is admitted to Rampart. The firemen rescue a child stuck in a pipe. Roy and John remove a ring from a young man’s finger. Roy and Capt. Stanley struggle with a shutoff valve at a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224230000 +0000" stop="20241224233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Mildred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Potter's anniversary. While Potter writes home, Frank and Hot Lips have a wood carving made for him, and Radar rescues a horse and makes him a present of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241224233000 +0000" stop="20241225000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th plays host to kids bombed out of their orphanage, and at the same time has to deliver a baby and care for battle casualties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225000000 +0000" stop="20241225003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Death Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester fulfills a family Christmas tradition but has trouble maintaining the anonymity required to keep it a truly charitable act. Even Klinger lends a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225003000 +0000" stop="20241225010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225010000 +0000" stop="20241225013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225013000 +0000" stop="20241225020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225020000 +0000" stop="20241225023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Possum Day Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny is preparing for her Possum Queen campaign, and also wondering why Mrs. Drysdale hasn’t fought back yet. When Jed asks Drysdale about this, he starts her campaign with a false radio interview and continues to try to get a Possum festival going. Granny continues with her campaign, and Mrs. Drysdale realizes that she has been campaigning without even knowing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225023000 +0000" stop="20241225030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Hail To The Fire Chief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Scheming to get Oliver to pay his way to a convention, Fire Chief Joe Carson appoints him as his assistant. Instead, Oliver finds the Hooterville Fire Department to be inept and ill-prepared. Oliver's call for improvements results in Uncle Joe being voted out and him being named the new chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225030000 +0000" stop="20241225033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to think he is about to capture a POW escape ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225033000 +0000" stop="20241225040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Cuisine A La Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau decides to escape leaving the camp without a chef.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225040000 +0000" stop="20241225043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Wiggins / Harry's Mirage And Grill</sub-title>
    <desc>Mrs. Wiggins, just before Christmas, Mr. Tudball conducts a fire drill to keep the insurance company appeased. Then, in Harry's Mirage and Grill, Harvey and Tim find a desert oasis with a beautiful woman -- or is it just a mirage?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225043000 +0000" stop="20241225053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The One-eyed Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Della and Mason's dinner at a fancy French restaurant is interrupted by a phone call and an envelope containing $500 from a mysterious woman named Marian Fargo. She wants him to make an exchange: the money for some documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225053500 +0000" stop="20241225060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Meek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After a derelict Santa Claus is fired on Christmas Eve, he finds a bottomless sack of gifts. With this bag he sets out to fulfill his one wish—to see the less fortunate inherit the bounties of Christmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225060500 +0000" stop="20241225080500 +0000">
    <title>Holiday Special</title>
    <sub-title>An American Christmas Carol</sub-title>
    <desc>"In an American town, an old bitter miser is given a ghostly chance at redemption on Christmas Eve."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225080500 +0000" stop="20241225090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Torch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a man who is charged with arson and murder by burning down his textile company which killed his wife who was trapped inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225090500 +0000" stop="20241225100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Echo Of A Distant Battle (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tangles with violent veterans of the Vietnam war as he attempts to clear the name of an Army deserter who's still missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225100000 +0000" stop="20241225103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Mathews and Sergeant Corey spend Christmas Eve searching for a lost girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225103000 +0000" stop="20241225110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A statue of the child Jesus was stolen from a church. Joe and Bill have to get it back by Christmas. They have less than 48 hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225110000 +0000" stop="20241225113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>During their Christmas Eve Patrol, Malloy and Reed contemplate using their patrol car to deliver a Christmas tree to the residents of a soon-to-be-closed retirement home. Meanwhile, an elderly man's bagpipe playing is considered a public nuisance, a couple of teenagers steal a delivery truck containing radioactive material, a nervous man is desperate to cover up the smell of perfume on his clothing and an armed robbery suspect becomes intent on committing suicide-by-cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225113000 +0000" stop="20241225120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lady's Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>On today's patrol, Malloy and Reed try to corral cattle that are wandering into the downtown area, pull over a speeding bicyclist, chase down a man with a stolen guitar and break up a bar fight. After their shift is over, Reed and his wife witness a gas station holdup on their way to dinner with Malloy and his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225120000 +0000" stop="20241225130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Merry Christmas To All!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate Chrsitmas and warm up with a holiday beverage!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225130000 +0000" stop="20241225133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Night In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends are all psyched to go on a camping trip with Gilbert's father as an escort. However, when Gilbert's father suddenly has to work, Wally agrees to take them. Meanwhile, Eddie and Lumpy decide to secretly tag along and scare the boys with animal noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225133000 +0000" stop="20241225140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Long Distance Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends decide to make a call to California to talk to Don Drysdale and they agree to chip in on the cost of the call, assuming that it's only going to be a couple dollars. However, when they're put on hold, the cost quickly jumps up to $9.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225140000 +0000" stop="20241225150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Difficult Detour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Contactor Pete Mallory is charged with the murder of a vacation resort developer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225150000 +0000" stop="20241225160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 1  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225160000 +0000" stop="20241225170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A son (Edward Albert) is opposed to his father's plan to give land to slave descendants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225170000 +0000" stop="20241225180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Children's Carol - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>As Christmas approaches, Mary Ellen and the baby leave to be near Curt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225180000 +0000" stop="20241225190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Sodbusters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt has trouble getting a fight about water rights under control when things escalate to violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225190000 +0000" stop="20241225200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Roper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Army soldiers and an outlaw gang have a shootout at the Ponderosa while Will is home alone. To make matters worse, Will realizes that the money in Ben's safe is in jeopardy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225200000 +0000" stop="20241225203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225203000 +0000" stop="20241225210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225210000 +0000" stop="20241225220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dr. Denker Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The wagon train takes in a terrified young boy who has just seen his father murdered by a bandit gang. While Bill and Flint try to help him recover, embittered Civil War vet Ed Beaufort tells the boy that taking vengeance is the best medicine. Soon a traveling musician, Dr. Denker, joins the wagon train and he and Billy hit it off, but it becomes evident that Billy and the doctor had a prior connection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225220000 +0000" stop="20241225230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Gossip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy encourages John to represent the station in the Fireman's Olympics track events. An armored car sideswipes a motorist and Station 51 must break into the van. A nurse spreads the rumor that Dr. Morton is having financial problems. Doctors treat a child with cyanide poisoning from peach pits. Dr. Brackett treats a bigamist with a skull fracture. The firemen rescue an electrocution victim hanging in mid-air and a man trapped in a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225230000 +0000" stop="20241225233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Quo Vadis, Captain Chandler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Intelligence officer Colonel Flagg and psychiatrist Sidney Freedman grapple over the fate of a wounded officer, Captain Chandler, who claims to be Jesus Christ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241225233000 +0000" stop="20241226000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Peggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. writes home to his wife, Peg, reporting Klinger's escape attempts, the visit of a formidable chaplain and one of Frank's goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226000000 +0000" stop="20241226003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Of Moose And Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tangles with a tough Army colonel, Colonel Spiker; B.J. helps Zale, who's received a Dear John letter; and Frank looks endlessly for Korean saboteurs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226003000 +0000" stop="20241226010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Soldier Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has a fever and makes a will, leaving all his money to his wife and all his clothes to Hot Lips.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226010000 +0000" stop="20241226013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226013000 +0000" stop="20241226020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226020000 +0000" stop="20241226023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Brewster's Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After Drysdale stops the clan from going back home to deliver a baby, the Clampetts try to help the Brewsters with their baby, while Jethro unsuccessfully tries to open his own version of the Kitty Kat Club. Of course, the Brewsters don't need the help because they are adopting, though after hearing the explanation given, the Clampetts believe they really need help and advice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226023000 +0000" stop="20241226030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Eb's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Eb announces his engagement to Loreli Appleby, a girl he met the day before. In an attempt to impress his future father-in-law, Eb succeeds in destroying the farmer's cabbage crop. To get back in the man's good graces, Eb pawns Oliver's cow Eleanor so he can make the Appleby's mortgage payment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226030000 +0000" stop="20241226033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Experts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan saves a German radio expert whom the Nazis want to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226033000 +0000" stop="20241226040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Masterpiece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that the kommandant is a great painter so the prisoners can meet an underground contact at an art gallery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226040000 +0000" stop="20241226043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Carol And Sis / Back Alley</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol has the Hong Kong Flu, and Harvey is terrified he'll get it. Then, in Back Alley, a parody of "Back Street", Harvey finds himself married every time he falls in love with Carol.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226043000 +0000" stop="20241226053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Robert Crane is charged with the murder of his sister's estranged husband, Mason needs the testimony of sister Helen Reed to clear him of the charge. Unfortunately for all concerned, Helen suffers from multiple personality disorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226053500 +0000" stop="20241226060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Martian Please Stand Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Troopers follow the tracks from a frozen pond into a diner. Inside they find a soda jerk, a bus driver and his seven passengers. The bus driver is certain only six people boarded his bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226060500 +0000" stop="20241226063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Crackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Two newlyweds stay at the same hotel as a man with whom they got into a scuffle with earlier that day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226063500 +0000" stop="20241226070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare In 4-d</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband has a vague memory of helping a woman get rid of a corpse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226070500 +0000" stop="20241226080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Carol Lockwood, Past Tense</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix seeks to prove that the death of one of his former gal-pals was not an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226080500 +0000" stop="20241226090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Cain's Mark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is hired when a young brother of a gun manufacturer and collector vanishes from sight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226090500 +0000" stop="20241226100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dance With Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When a friend of a disco dancer is found murdered, she believes she's a killer's real target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226100000 +0000" stop="20241226103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Prospector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>A poor prospector arouses suspicion when he suddenly begins paying off long-standing debts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226103000 +0000" stop="20241226110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226110000 +0000" stop="20241226113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen With A Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Officer Wells appears to have met his match with a new partner who always insists on doing things his own way. Today's shift features a hot-headed husband who's decided he needs a gun to protect his home, and a neglected girl who causes a scare while playing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226113000 +0000" stop="20241226120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Follow Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he's got a great deal lined up on a used boat, but Malloy's convinced there's something fishy going on. While on patrol, they search for a man who sold a stolen horse to a riding academy, use an informant's tip to investigate a suspicious restaurant parking lot attendant and face an accusation of stealing a socialite's diamond ring during a burglary investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226120000 +0000" stop="20241226130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Old News</sub-title>
    <desc>"Breaking News! Bill and Toony become newscasters and profile legendary news anchor, Bill Kurtis."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226130000 +0000" stop="20241226133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Stocks And Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally become interested in the stock market and Ward decides that they should try their hand at it. However, Wally and Beaver have different ideas about what to invest in compared to Ward who wants them to play it safe and invest in Mayfield Power and Electric, while they want to invest in a more risky venture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226133000 +0000" stop="20241226140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Untogetherness</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Cleavers are all excited about their annual summer vacation up to the cabin, that is except Wally. Wanting to be close to his latest girl, Wally wants to stay behind and gets permission to stay at Eddie's house during the two weeks the Cleavers are on vacation, but June and Ward are a bit unsure of Wally's plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226140000 +0000" stop="20241226150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cowardly Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hilde Fursten and Tony Osgood work at the San Diego Zoo. When a baby monkey goes missing, Fursten is blamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226150000 +0000" stop="20241226160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret: Part 2  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a gambler is accused of killing his bookie, Matlock agrees to take the case, believing that someone from the bookie's past is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226160000 +0000" stop="20241226170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Even Nice People: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Corrupt developers set their sights on Lana's farm. When she refuses to sell they enlist the services of an arsonist to force her out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226170000 +0000" stop="20241226180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Violated</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier is sending his wife mail, but getting no replies</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226180000 +0000" stop="20241226190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After killer Jay Wrecken is shot dead, man's brother begins methodically murdering everyone connected to the incident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226190000 +0000" stop="20241226200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Pink Cloud Comes From Old Cathay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A headstrong Chinese girl (Marlo Thomas) visiting the Cartwrights incites labor unrest among local workers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226200000 +0000" stop="20241226203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226203000 +0000" stop="20241226210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226210000 +0000" stop="20241226220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jeff Hartfield Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Jeff Hartfield becomes concerned when his sister Jenny begins dating Dallas who threatens him with an orphanage at journey's end. Jeff takes off but Dallas follows with deadly intent, believing Jeff knows the location of $30,000."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226220000 +0000" stop="20241226230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nagging Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy picks winning horses from the newspaper and Johnny wants to know how he does it. The paramedics rescue a woman who has fallen into a lion’s cage, a dancer in a bar and an adult skateboarder who landed in a cactus patch. They also save a bleeding policeman from a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226230000 +0000" stop="20241226233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241226233000 +0000" stop="20241227000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227000000 +0000" stop="20241227003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227003000 +0000" stop="20241227010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Ma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes home to his mother, as Hawkeye conducts the camp foot inspection, and Colonel Potter gets some shrapnel in his backside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227010000 +0000" stop="20241227013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227013000 +0000" stop="20241227020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober Takes A Car Apart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy needs someone to answer the phone at the courthouse while he is in Mt. Pilot at a sheriff's conference and Barney is on vacation. Against his better judgement, Andy agrees to let Goober man the fort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227020000 +0000" stop="20241227023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Frog Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny thinks Jethro has turned into a frog after he went swimming and takes him to Dr. Klinger in the bank building. Jethro stops by the bank and takes the frog home. Granny sees him at home and thinks he is cured. Jed decides to learn to be a frogman too, but when he tells Jethro, Granny jumps on him to stop him. Jethro takes Granny to her room, and Granny begs someone to end her suffering.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227023000 +0000" stop="20241227030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>The Candidate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Fed up with the lousy condition of the Hooterville highway, Oliver launches an attack on their beloved state district representative, Ben Hanks. The folksy, duck-calling, guitar-playing politician proves too wily for Oliver, even when caught padding the state payroll with relatives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227030000 +0000" stop="20241227033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An English traitor, who could pass for Colonel Crittendon's twin brother, parachutes into camp with information for Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227033000 +0000" stop="20241227040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Chitterly's Lover: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hogan becomes convinced that Crittendon can't fool Hitler, things get complicated when Chitterly escapes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227040000 +0000" stop="20241227043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Ruth Buzzi And Richard Crenna</sub-title>
    <desc>In Salute to Bad Girls, Carol and the gang pay homage to classic films and their scheming starlets, including "The Graduate", "All About Eve", "Born to Be Bad",</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227043000 +0000" stop="20241227053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Empty Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Doris Hocksley is shown a personal ad in a Los Angeles newspaper for locating the daughter of Adam Hocksley and providing proof of same. A friend, John Lowell, suggests she pursue the idea to prove she is the rightful heir to the Adam Hocksley estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227053500 +0000" stop="20241227060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsolete Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a future state where religion and books have been banned, a librarian is judged obsolete and sentenced to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227060500 +0000" stop="20241227063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother, Richard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A man kills his brother’s opponent for the governor’s office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227063500 +0000" stop="20241227070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Manacled</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal offers $50,000 to a detective in exchange for his freedom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227070500 +0000" stop="20241227080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Cage A Sea Gull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The site of a helicopter accident uncovers the body of a member of the Nazi party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227080500 +0000" stop="20241227090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Moonlight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A young convict is being harassed by a prisoner who is running a gambling operation inside of the lock up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227090500 +0000" stop="20241227100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Protectors, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An assault on a businessman leads Barnaby to work with a firm that specializes in preventing terrorist kidnappings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227100000 +0000" stop="20241227103000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Several law-abiding citizens unknowingly help a charming murderer escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227103000 +0000" stop="20241227110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227110000 +0000" stop="20241227113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suicide</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a traveling business man driving a green pinto, who called his wife in Nebraska and told her he was going to commit suicide at 2 PM. Meanwhile, they search for a woman who abandoned her newborn baby in a garbage can, and get a tip from an elderly woman about a group of car strippers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227113000 +0000" stop="20241227120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Action</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>On his way to an auto mechanic, Malloy is ambushed and kidnapped by a group of drug runners who plan to use him to secure the release of one of their associates.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227120000 +0000" stop="20241227130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>An Idol Mind</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill tries to transform himself into a teen idol of yesteryear."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227130000 +0000" stop="20241227133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Dinner Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has been constantly spending his time at Julie Foster's house and June suggests that he's old enough to take her out on a dinner date. Julie suggests a new expensive restaurant called The White Fox. However, during the meal Wally discovers that he forgot his wallet at home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227133000 +0000" stop="20241227140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Football Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is scheduled to receive a football award at a father-son dinner being held in the school gym. While talking with his friends, Beaver learns that none of them are planning on wearing a jacket and a tie so when June and Ward insist that he wear one, he adamantly refuses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227140000 +0000" stop="20241227150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Torrid Tapestry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Having served a six-year prison sentence for a fire he didn't start, Claude Demay has devised a plan to expose the real criminal, Leonard Voss, who tried to burn down a warehouse containing a valuable art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227150000 +0000" stop="20241227160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a plastic surgeon is found dead after an argument with his partner about dissolving the business, the business partner is the immediate suspect, until Matlock meets the man's twin brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227160000 +0000" stop="20241227170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Lake Winahatchee: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill discovers the motivation behind a crime syndicates attempt to muscle in on Sparta and the reason they are determined to get Lana's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227170000 +0000" stop="20241227180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver Wings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim-Bob delivers a package to a woman whose husband is in the war</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227180000 +0000" stop="20241227190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw gang leader Jude Bonner will stop at nothing to persuade Matt to stay his brother's execution, going so far as to kidnap Kitty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227190000 +0000" stop="20241227200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Enter Thomas Bowers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After a triumphant tour in Europe, a famous African-American singer encounters racial prejudice in Virginia City when he arrives to perform a concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227200000 +0000" stop="20241227203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Town character Brett Conway blackmails Lucas with the knowledge that a young couple Lucas rescued are suffering from yellow fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227203000 +0000" stop="20241227210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Ordeal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When their wagon breaks down, Mark and an injured Lucas are stranded in the desert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227210000 +0000" stop="20241227220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Daniel Clay Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>"Judge Clay and his family join the wagon train. He has a reputation for cleaning up frontier towns, but his fanatical attention to the law sees him ostracized as often as he is praised. He must face this when his son must be tried by him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227220000 +0000" stop="20241227230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Gaffe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and Joanne go on a TV quiz show. Roy and John respond to a holdup where both a policeman and a suspect have been shot, and another officer gives them a hard time over treating the suspect. A woman brings in her abused son for treatment. A man inhales too much nitrous oxide. The paramedics treat a boy suffering an allergic reaction to a bee sting. A pickup carrying kerosene collides with a station wagon and starts a brushfire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227230000 +0000" stop="20241227233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Der Tag</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter decides Frank would be less of a pain if the others were friendlier to him; they oblige, with some startling results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241227233000 +0000" stop="20241228000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is injured in a jeep accident and, aware he has a concussion, babbles to a Korean family to keep himself awake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228000000 +0000" stop="20241228003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Some 38th Parallels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank tries to distinguish himself by selling the camp garbage, but it's Hawkeye who finds a use for it: he dumps it on a troublesome Colonel Coner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228003000 +0000" stop="20241228010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Novocaine Mutiny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has Hawkeye up on charges of mutiny for usurping his authority when Potter was away on leave and Frank was the commanding officer. B.J., Potter and Radar are in attendance of the preliminary hearing, at which they hear conflicting versions of what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228010000 +0000" stop="20241228013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rehabilitation Of Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to use psychology to reform Otis of his drinking habit but this eventually leads Otis to "take his business" elsewhere—the jail in Mt. Pilot!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228013000 +0000" stop="20241228020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Lucky Letter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney receives a chain letter, but Andy goads him into throwing it away. Suddenly things begin going wrong for Barney and he's convinced he'll soon be out of a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228020000 +0000" stop="20241228023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Jethro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed and Granny decide Jethro needs a job. They send him down to the bank to try to get work. While he is there, he runs into a magician, Marvo the Magnificent. After Marvo learns of his uncle’s many, many millions, he agrees to go home with Jethro. Marvo puts on a show for the Clampetts, and afterwards Jethro decides to become a magician.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228023000 +0000" stop="20241228030000 +0000">
    <title>Green Acres</title>
    <sub-title>Handy Lessons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting to be a bigger help to Oliver, Lisa decides to learn carpentry. She buys overalls and begins to study the craft from the inept Monroe brothers. Lisa's talents result in destruction in Monroes' workshop and earns Oliver a punch in the nose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228030000 +0000" stop="20241228033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gestapo Takeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo takes over Stalag 13, planning to send Klink and Schultz to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228033000 +0000" stop="20241228040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Schultz lets his new power as camp kommandant go to his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228040000 +0000" stop="20241228043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Anthony Newley And Dick Martin</sub-title>
    <desc>In Singles Bar, an obnoxious and prying Carol sabotages Vicki's chance with a guy. Then, in Salute to Detective Movies, the gang parodies classic films, including "Sherlock Holmes", "The Maltese Falcon", "Sam Spade", and "Miss Marple".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228043000 +0000" stop="20241228053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Half-wakened Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Lawton goes to visit old friend Scott Shelby and ends up being charged with his muder. Fortunately for Lawton, Mason is another old friend of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228053500 +0000" stop="20241228060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and a woman, on opposite sides of a future war, encounter each other in a deserted town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228060500 +0000" stop="20241228063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>A Bottle Of Wine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A judge tries to prove that his wife’s lover is a coward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228063500 +0000" stop="20241228070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Malice Domestic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Carl, a newlywed, suspects his wife is trying to poison him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228070500 +0000" stop="20241228080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Search For A Whisper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A political candidate hires Mannix to dig up dirt, but not on an opponent. He wants the gumshoe to dig up dirt on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228080500 +0000" stop="20241228090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Cats And Sudden Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Public prosecutor Mike Arnold needs Cannon's help. He is suspected of the murder of his wife. His problem: Dubious friends want him to finish a corruption investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228090500 +0000" stop="20241228100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Overture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband and wife are framed for the death of the husband's ex-lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228100000 +0000" stop="20241228103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>But I've Never Been In Erie, Pa</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An industrialist registers at the Shady Rest and offers Uncle Joe a chance to make a fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228103000 +0000" stop="20241228110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>How To Arrange A Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobbie Jo keeps giving blatant hints to Billie Jo's new boyfriend, hoping to talk him into marrying Billie Jo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228110000 +0000" stop="20241228113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Meet Mrs. Drysdale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mr. Drysdale describes Mrs. Drysdale as being a hypochondriac, the Clampetts assume she must be a drunk. With his wife coming home, Drysdale and Jane try to prevent her from meeting the family before they can shape the hillbillies up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228113000 +0000" stop="20241228120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mrs. Drysdale's Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale's father comes to Beverly Hills to visit. When he learns of the Clampetts, he decides he wants to meet them. He visits and ends up playing poker and pool with Jed. But Farquhar loses all his money because his tricks backfire and the Clampetts are better at the games then he could even imagine. In the end, Jed suggests they give up the gambling and just play a friendly game of pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228120000 +0000" stop="20241228123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Never Sock A Baby, Leave Well Enough Alone, Hello, How Am I?, Stealin Aint Honest</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Popeye punishes Swee'pea, the little guy runs away., Popeye, saddened by the sight of dogs in a pet shop, buys them and releases them into the streets., Popeye meets himself walking down the street toward Olive's house, where he has been invited to a hamburger feast., Popeye and Olive Oyl sail off to find the whereabouts of Olive's gold mine."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228123000 +0000" stop="20241228130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Bad Day At Cat Rock, Peace On Earth, Cat And The Mermouse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry pulls numerous pranks on Tom while he is having a bad day., Two squirrel children get a story from the grandfather on Christmas Eve how mankind ended in violence., Tom drowns in a lake, and goes to the bottom. There, he finds a mermouse, and then tries to capture it and eat it. The mermouse doesn't give in so easily, though."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228130000 +0000" stop="20241228140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Red Riding Hoodlum, Teeny Weeny Meany, Nutty Pine Cabin, After The Ball, Case Of The Red-eyed Ruby, Pied Piper Of Basin Street, Calling All Cuckoos</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody sends Knothead and Splinter to deliver a basket to their grandmother's house. They encounter a wolf, and it seems like the story will follow Little Red Ridinghood's plot. Instead, grandmother falls in love with the wolf and marries him., Smedley stops Chilly from stealing all of the captain's fish., Andy is trying to build a cabin, but a group of beavers steal all his lumber for a dam., After his tree home is turned into a bowling ball, Woody Woodpecker refuses to leave, despite Pierre Bear., Inspector Willoughby returns a stolen red-eyed ruby to an Egyptian tomb, only to have Yeggs Benedict try to steal it again., A trombone player plays swing to rid a town of rats, but when the mayor refused to pay his promised fee, the musician has a trick up his sleeve., Herr Spring, a German clockmaker, tries to capture woody for his cuckoo clock."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228140000 +0000" stop="20241228150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>False Hare, Hairied And Hurried, Little Boy Boo, The Million Hare, Street Cat Named Sylvester, A (1953), The Unbearable Bear, Dumb Patrol</sub-title>
    <desc>"The big bad Wolf and his cousin setup a rabbit club as a front for a rabbit trap. Bugs plays along with their club just to cause more trouble for the Wolves. , Wile E. Coyote sends in a mail-order to ACME for a snow machine and then he sets up signs for "Chains Required" and then gives away chains at another stop. He intends to use a portable electro-magnet to catch the Road Runner but it fails. , Foghorn Leghorn is cold in his shack and decides to befriend the Widow Hen so he can live in her warm house. , A television show is having a contest to see who can get to the television station first, Bugs or Daffy. , Tweety is freezing in the winter cold and seeks warmth in Granny's home where Sylvester and Hector are also. , A burglar fox breaks into the Bear home, but Mr. Bear comes home and realizes there is an intruder., Bugs Bunny and Porky Pig are World War I pilots that are trying to rid the skies of Yosemite Sam who is Baron Sam Von Schamm. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228150000 +0000" stop="20241228160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Deadly Bubble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On the trail of the source of mysterious tidal waves, the guys finds a fanatical marine environmentalist at the heart of the mystery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228160000 +0000" stop="20241228170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Lieutenant Burton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>"A young lieutenant on his first assignment must face an overbearing, murderous sergeant who is determined to kill two deserters in cold blood. The sergeant wounds Chris thinking he is one of them and into a feud with Flint at the train."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228170000 +0000" stop="20241228180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Guilt Of Matt Bentell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barkleys learn that the man they have hired to run their logging operations was the commandant of a notorious Civil War prisoner camp, in which Heath was held prisoner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228180000 +0000" stop="20241228190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Jubilee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A man neglects his family in favor of raising his prize possession: a race horse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228190000 +0000" stop="20241228200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Dark Past</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The men of the Ponderosa cannot understand why bounty hunter Dev Farnum (Dennis Hopper) is so unfriendly and secretive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228200000 +0000" stop="20241228203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spiked Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is kidnapped as he and Lucas try to protect Banker Hamilton's gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228203000 +0000" stop="20241228210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas makes a life-or-death decision when Micah is held hostage and the kidnappers demand the release of a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228210000 +0000" stop="20241228220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Red Wind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Favor tells Rowdy to let Lou Bowdart drive the herd up the San Marcos trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228220000 +0000" stop="20241228223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellsworth believes he has had an old tiger curse put on him and that a tiger is coming to kill him. He hires Paladin to protect him from the tiger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228223000 +0000" stop="20241228230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Ricochet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh sets out to help a heartbroken wife locate her missing husband, but his mission of mercy meets with a resistant and tight-lipped townspeople. The mission becomes desperate when Josh discovers another man is also seeking the missing husband, but with murder in mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241228230000 +0000" stop="20241229010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Maniacs, Restless Knights, Grips, Grunts And Groans, Crime On Their Hands, Scrambled Brains, Pardon My Backfire</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges arrive in Hollywood hoping to make it in the movie business. , Set in Medieval times, the Stooges learn they are of royal blood and vow to save the kingdom.   , The Stooges are auto mechanics who need money so they can marry their girls.  When some escaped convicts pull into their garage, the boys manage to capture them and use the reward money to marry their sweethearts. , The Stooges become trainers of "Bustoff", a champion wrestler.  The big boss has a lot of money bet on Bustoff and orders the boys to take good care of him.  Instead they accidentally knock him out and Curly must disguises himself as Bustoff and wrestle in his place.  The match doesn't go very well until Curly smells "Wild Hyacinth" perfume on a lady fan at ringside.  This drives him crazy and he knocks out his opponent and half the people in the stadium. , The Stooges are janitors working in a newspaper office.  When an anonymous caller phones in a tip about the theft a famous diamond, the boys decide to become reporters and go after the crooks.  They find the crooks, but Shemp accidentally swallows the diamond, which was hidden in a bowl of candy.  The crooks want to cut the diamond out, but the boys foil them with the help of a friendly gorilla. , Shemp is a sick man, suffering from hallucinations.  His worst vision is that his ugly nurse Nora is actually beautiful.  When Moe and Larry come to take him home from the sanitarium, they discover he's become engaged to Nora.  On the way to Nora's apartment for the wedding, the boys get in a fight with a stranger who promises to get even with them if he ever sees them again.  They arrive to finding Nora waiting for her father, who, when he arrives, turns out to be the man they just fought with. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229010000 +0000" stop="20241229033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Of Dracula</sub-title>
    <desc>"In a girl's boarding school, science teacher, Miss Branding, tests her theory that there is power within the human potential that is beyond that of the atom. Using hypnosis and a special amulet, a new and troubled student, Nancy Perkins, becomes the subject of her experiments which result in a series of full-moon murders."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229033000 +0000" stop="20241229040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Goes To School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Joker attempts to recruit high school dropouts for his gang, it's up to Batman and Dick Grayson to teach the students to make better choices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229040000 +0000" stop="20241229050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Spectre Of The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When visiting a xenophobic, isolationist planet, Captain Kirk and his landing party are punished for trespassing. They are sentenced to death in a surreal recreation of the Gunfight at the OK Corral.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229050000 +0000" stop="20241229060000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Vampire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An overlooked victim of the Las Vegas vampire makes her way to Los Angeles and begins killing anew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229060000 +0000" stop="20241229070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Condemned Of Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After quickly leaving the planet they are on and rescuing the robot, which was swept overboard, the Robinson's discover a prison ship filled with cryogenically preserved prisoners.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229070000 +0000" stop="20241229080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Human Computer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview set out with Commander Crane, supposedly the only human being aboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229080000 +0000" stop="20241229090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Doomsday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A rival power plots to destroy the nearby city, and the Earthlings are forced to help Inspector Kobick.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229090000 +0000" stop="20241229100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Secret Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In an Iron Curtain country, Tony and Doug pose as scientists to investigate a primitive enemy time-tunnel in 1956.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229100000 +0000" stop="20241229110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Pit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A professor diagnosed with delusions tells Vincent aliens are experimenting with dreams.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229110000 +0000" stop="20241229120000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Daredevil</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Matthew's friend decides to become a stuntman, Star has to intervene with his powers to protect him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229120000 +0000" stop="20241229123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Game   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack bets Carosi that if his team wins a volley ball game, Carosi will sell his car to him. But Zack's team becomes a bit short handed when the star player is injured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229123000 +0000" stop="20241229130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fourth Of July   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the annual Fourth of July beauty pageant and Zack is one of the judges. Carosi wants Zack to choose Stacey no matter what it takes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229130000 +0000" stop="20241229133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Boss Lady   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Stacey is left in charge when her father is away. Everyone is pitching in to help her, but disaster strikes when someone accidentally booked two parties at the same time and then the chefs decide to quit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229133000 +0000" stop="20241229140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>My Boyfriend's Back   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the annual ATV race. Zack and the gang enter it, but Zack feels inferior when Stacey's ex-boyfriend shows up at the beach resort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229140000 +0000" stop="20241229143000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Weekend   (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's the last day at the beach resort and Zack and Stacy are hoping to spend it together. Carosi, however, doesn't approve of their romance. Meanwhile, a secret admirer is sending Slater love letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229143000 +0000" stop="20241229150000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Best Summer Of My Life   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack stays home on the first day of school, and looks back on the time he's spent at Malibu Sands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229150000 +0000" stop="20241229153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Tiger, Tiger!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby briefly leaves Tiger unattended and returns to find him missing. Soon there's a citywide search to track him down. Meanwhile, a string of burglaries in the neighborhood has worried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229153000 +0000" stop="20241229160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby bets Greg that he can't do twice as many chin-ups as him. Greg is a tad too confident and sees no need to train, a decision that comes back to bite him. Meanwhile, Mike prepares for his high school reunion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229160000 +0000" stop="20241229163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Football Frolics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Needing money to get tickets to a big football game, Richie, Potsie and Ralph decide to babysit 15 children on the night of Mardi Gras.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229163000 +0000" stop="20241229170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Some Enchanted Earring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne accidentally loses one of her mother's diamond earrings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229170000 +0000" stop="20241229173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goober And The Art Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney try to set the perpetually unlucky-in-love Goober up with a woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229173000 +0000" stop="20241229180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Raises Chickens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The Mertzes find a way to stay with the Ricardos: chicken farming. But the scheme puts Lucy over her head in chickens when she and Ethel bring home 500 baby chicks before the hen house is ready.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229180000 +0000" stop="20241229183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's License</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Now that Wally is 17, he feels it's about time that he get his drivers license. However, June and Ward are a bit apprehensive about the idea of Wally driving, but Wally is persistant and finally gets his parents to agree to let him take a drivers class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229183000 +0000" stop="20241229190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his heart set on taking a swing at being a paper boy again but another kid beats him to it. This leads Beaver to think about using sabatoge to get the new paper boy fired. However, the boy may just do that himself when the service becomes terrible leading Beaver to confront him only to discover he is a she.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229190000 +0000" stop="20241229193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Farquhar Stays On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has taken interest in Mrs. Drysdale’s father, Mr. Farquhar. And Farquhar is trying to get someone to go to Las Vegas with him, first asking Drysdale, who turns him down. He asks Granny to accompany him, and Granny believes this is a marriage proposal. Farquhar tells Drysdale about this, who is against it, and Drysdale tells Jed, who is all for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229193000 +0000" stop="20241229200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Military School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro finally decides on his life’s calling again. He decides on being a five-star general. Jethro is hoping to attend West Point, but Drysdale talks him into going to Haven Hurst. Granny is against him joining because he might get hurt, and Drysdale is having trouble getting him in because this military academy is for boys.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229200000 +0000" stop="20241229203000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Take A Dare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A radio contestant must survive on the island for a week if he wants to collect the $10,000 prize. But since he must do it without any help, he resists the castaways' pleas to help get them rescued.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229203000 +0000" stop="20241229210000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Court-martial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways hear on the radio that the Maritime Board of Inquiry has blamed the Skipper for the S.S. Minnow crash.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229210000 +0000" stop="20241229213000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Desperately Seeking Anyone  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>The date whom Mama and Naomi find for Iola is more interested in Mama.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229213000 +0000" stop="20241229220000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Porn Again  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mama finds a dirty magazine under Bubba's bed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229220000 +0000" stop="20241229230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Triangle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A married old flame pursues Stubing; a model pretends to be wed; a science-fiction buff thinks a librarian is an alien.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229230000 +0000" stop="20241229233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Runs For Sheriff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers taking an out-of-town job, and with the election nearing, no one has yet filed to run for Sheriff. Barney throws his hat in the ring, and then Andy's job prospect takes a turn.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241229233000 +0000" stop="20241230000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Cher- Robyn Fisher</sub-title>
    <desc>"From her childhood, watching The Sonny and Cher Show, Robyn Fisher blossomed into a superfan, with a sprawling collection of memorabilia that covers the diva’s entire career. Joining Robyn is her daughter Marina, who’s grown up alongside the collection, and show-business appraiser Marcia Tysseling, who once handled consignment items for Cher herself (and in fact sold Robyn many items in her collection). Marcia now sets a total value on everything Robyn’s collected – including such treasures as the iconic mermaid tail from Mermaids and a pair of dazzling concert-worn earrings by legendary designer Bob Mackie. Marcia then tries to tempt Robyn into a three-for-one trade for a Sonny and Cher Show rarity that makes her long to sing, “I’ve Got You, Babe.”"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230000000 +0000" stop="20241230003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Smilin' Jack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th turns up a sick helicopter pilot, 'Smilin' Jack, who doesn't want to quit, and a twice-wounded GI who does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230003000 +0000" stop="20241230010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The More I See You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is reunited with a woman he thought was out of his life forever, but who never altogether leaves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230010000 +0000" stop="20241230013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Eats And Runs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home for a nice dinner that Edith has prepared: beef and mushroom stew. Later, when Mike comes to the table for dinner, he finds Archie has completely finished his meal and then breaks the news that there has been a recall at the supermarkets of a certain brand of mushroom. Convinced that he has food poisoning, Archie rushes down to the hospital for treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230013000 +0000" stop="20241230020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria Sings The Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria comes home from work one evening in a total apathetic mood. When Archie tries to find out what's wrong with her, she snaps at him and storms off. Later, Edith gets to the bottom of Gloria's mood when she confides in Edith that she thinks that she has temporarily fallen out of love with Mike (something that Edith confesses happened to her and her feelings for Archie). Meanwhile, Archie and Mike prepare for a fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230020000 +0000" stop="20241230023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike And Gloria Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The family relives Mike and Gloria's blind date where they first insulted each other and ended up having sex in the kitchen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230023000 +0000" stop="20241230030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Commercial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is chosen to appear in a tv commericial but finds herself unable to lie when she begins to doubt the quality of the sponsor's detergent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230030000 +0000" stop="20241230033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Glen Campbell</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Guinea Pig, Carol searches for a cure for Swine Flu before her lover turns into a pig. Then, in A Star is Born, Carol and the gang parody the classic film. Next, in The Other Woman, Carol distracts her friend so she won't see her husband is cheating. Finally, in Take a Letter, Carol tries to take dictation from her boss, but the company's faulty products keep getting in the way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230033000 +0000" stop="20241230040000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Monkey Man, Tim is bitten by a chimp and acts like a monkey in front of his fiance's father. Then, in The Ad Men, Tim's old boss tries to woo him back to his old job, angering his current boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230040000 +0000" stop="20241230043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Plots Thicken</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura's families fight over where Laura will be buried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230043000 +0000" stop="20241230050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Scratch My Car And Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura panics when she gets a big scratch on Rob's new car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230050000 +0000" stop="20241230053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Pardon My Glove</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Alice is getting the apartment re-decorated for free but Ralph thinks she's two-timing him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230053000 +0000" stop="20241230060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A plane lands safely, but all its passengers, pilot and crew are missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230060000 +0000" stop="20241230070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Annabel  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A disturbed chemist refuses to accept his ex-girlfriend's marriage to a co-worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230070000 +0000" stop="20241230080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Rat In A Corner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Herbie Grant, a second rate hoodlum, is shot in the leg while trying to rob a liquor store that Kimble works at. Herbie later takes Kimble hostage where Herbie claims that although he tried to rob the store, he is innocent of two other liquor store robber</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230080000 +0000" stop="20241230090000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Mastermind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Merrick has gathered blackmail evidence on ranking U.S. government officials and plans to turn it over to the Syndicate. The evidence is being held by Jonas Stone, Merrick's chief. The IMF must destroy Merrick and the blackmail file.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230090000 +0000" stop="20241230093000 +0000">
    <title>Highway Patrol</title>
    <sub-title>Kidnap Copter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Highway Patrol races to the rescue when a kidnapped victim is injured in the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230093000 +0000" stop="20241230100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230100000 +0000" stop="20241230103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230103000 +0000" stop="20241230110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230110000 +0000" stop="20241230113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Gus Corbin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy is asked to fill in for Sgt. MacDonald, leaving Reed to partner with a young probationary officer who lets his judgment be clouded by his constant need to prove himself. On patrol, they search for a purse snatcher inside a church, encounter a burglary in progress at a closed pharmaceutical company and search for an armed robbery suspect in a lumber yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230113000 +0000" stop="20241230120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Dana Hall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy continues his fill-in assignment for Sgt. MacDonald, Reed is paired with the department's first female officer, which presents both of them with a series of unique challenges. On patrol, they detain an underage drunk driver with a dismissive mother, search a parking garage for car strippers and help round up a large group of young people causing trouble outside a rock concert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230120000 +0000" stop="20241230130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Zoot Yourself</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill slips on a zoot suit and learns to jitterbug as he revisits the swing craze!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230130000 +0000" stop="20241230133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Double Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's new girlfriend, Carolyn, can't go out to the movies on Saturday night because she has to watch her little sister, Susan. Carolyn suggests that Beaver take Susan out to the movies and that they all double date. Not wanting to let Wally down, Beaver decides to go along, despite being nervous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230133000 +0000" stop="20241230140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie, The Businessman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie get jobs at the Mayfield Dairy thanks to Ward pulling some strings. They soon unknowingly find themselves involved in a plot started by the foreman and his assistant, who are secretly stealing the merchandise. When Ward learns of the plot, he warns Wally who in turn tries to warn Eddie, but Eddie doesn't buy it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230140000 +0000" stop="20241230150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Violent Vest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Advertising executive Herman Albright is in the wrong place at the wrong time wearing the wrong clothes. These mistakes cost poor Herman his life in a case of mistaken identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230150000 +0000" stop="20241230160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cover Girl  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock meets Conrad's new girlfriend, Carla Royce. When Carla's boss is murdered and she is suspected, Matlock defends her against the charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230160000 +0000" stop="20241230170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Correct Settling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Eugene hopes a well-known minister can save his father from Death Row. But someone runs the Reverend off the road on his way into town and the Sparta police try to protect him and track down his assailant. Meanwhile Harriet struggles with what her part in her ex-husbands appeal should be and is even more unsettled when Eugene demands that she break up with Bill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230170000 +0000" stop="20241230180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Wager</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A run (on foot) and ride (on horse) race is being held. Mary Ellen and Erin bet two guys that they will win</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230180000 +0000" stop="20241230190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Arizona Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S18E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A midget arrives in Dodge City claiming he will turn into an elephant at the stroke of midnight. Arizona begins asking for someone to care for him along with three bales of hay. Everyone finds the story a bit far fetched.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230190000 +0000" stop="20241230200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Pressure Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura Dayton's Aunt Lil comes to visit and quickly decides it's time she help the hesitant Adam propose to her favorite niece. Her plan is to make Adam jealous by using his cousin, Will, but it doesn't go exactly as planned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230200000 +0000" stop="20241230203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to do a good deed for the old town drunk but it backfires when the drunk's son believes he inherited Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230203000 +0000" stop="20241230210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance hall singer asks Lucas to care for her daughter in an effort to hide the baby from her self-righteous, bigoted father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230210000 +0000" stop="20241230220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charley Shutup Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>"The wagon master encounters opposition when he calls a halt to the train due to weather. One group needs to push on due to an inheritance in California. Chris and Duke take them but Duke injures his foot forcing him to stay in a cabin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230220000 +0000" stop="20241230230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is thrown from a motorcycle into a cactus patch. A surprise birthday party is planned for Dixie, who breaks her ankle while shopping, and the ER falls apart without her. Gage and DeSoto rescue two workers trapped on the side of a building next to a 1,000-pound sign. A man is trapped in his new sauna. When an old woman refuses to leave her apartment during a gas leak, the building explodes with John inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230230000 +0000" stop="20241230233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deluge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A sudden deluge of wounded at the 4077th is followed by a fire and a rainstorm, which makes matters difficult for the staff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241230233000 +0000" stop="20241231000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Interview</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Clete Roberts has arrived in Korea to interview the staff of the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital because of its high 97% efficiency rating. In Roberts' interviews with Hawkeye, B.J., Frank, Radar, Klinger, Mulcahy and Potter, they talk about how they cope with their situation, what they miss about home, how they feel about who they work with and whether they see any good in coming from war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231000000 +0000" stop="20241231003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A rumor that there's going to be a practice bug-out causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in to bug out, and the rumor suddenly comes to life! Meanwhile, Hawkeye begins surgery on a patient with a spinal injury. The bug-out proceeds without him, Hot Lips and Radar, and they quickly learn after the unit departs that they're in the midst of the front. When Potter, Mulcahy, BJ, Frank and the others arrive at the buildings which had been scouted by helicopter, they find the house full of "business girls," and Potter gives them Klinger's dresses to persuade them to leave the house. A helicopter comes to evacuate the spinal injury patient, and just as the three get ready to go to the new location, they find the 4077 is already returning, and eventually everyone reunites back at the camp, what with the Chinese being repulsed.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231003000 +0000" stop="20241231010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bug Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A rumor that there's going to be a camp relocation causes anxiety. When Potter assembles the unit in an attempt to squelch the rumor, the call comes in that the rumor is indeed fact!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231010000 +0000" stop="20241231013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>If I Had A Quarter-million</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When Barney finds $250,000 stolen in a bank heist, he goes undercover to find the thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231013000 +0000" stop="20241231020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tv Or Not Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Thieves pretend to be Hollywood producers in order to rob the Mayberry Bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231020000 +0000" stop="20241231023000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Shorty To The Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has come up with a new way to split Elly and Mark up and has called Shorty Kellems to help her do so. When Shorty arrives, she tells Mark that Shorty used to be Elly’s fiancé and wants revenge on Mark, but her story fails. At this time, Drysdale is trying to tell Jed that oceanography is a bad idea, but doesn’t succeed and ends up saying Miss Jane said it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231023000 +0000" stop="20241231030000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Overcomes The Obstacle Course</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer tries to pass an obstacle course to earn the respect of Sgt. Carter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231030000 +0000" stop="20241231033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Eight O'clock And All Is Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan finds that a new prisoner is a German spy right after he tells the man all about their secret operations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231033000 +0000" stop="20241231040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sergeant Schultz Meets Mata Hari</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo gets a female to pry information out of Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231040000 +0000" stop="20241231043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Paul Sand</sub-title>
    <desc>In After the Wedding, Carol's husband becomes jealous when she kisses another man goodbye. Then, in Energy Crisis Blackouts, everyone's life is complicated when the electricity stops. Finally, in Wedding Plans, divorcees discuss their future wedding plans, only to discover they may still love their old spouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231043000 +0000" stop="20241231053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Desperate Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Stefan Riker has come from Germany seeking the woman posing as Lisa Bannister. Attempting to help her stepmother, Doris Bannister pretends to be romantically interested in Stefan Riker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231053500 +0000" stop="20241231060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Shelter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nuclear attack appears imminent, several suburban friends and neighbors fight over control of a single bomb shelter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231060500 +0000" stop="20241231063500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Number Twenty-two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A petty crook clashes with a hardened criminal in a jail cell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231063500 +0000" stop="20241231070500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The End Of Indian Summer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman is investigation by her insurance company when she plans to get married for a third time, her previous husbands having died mysteriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231070500 +0000" stop="20241231080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Quote A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A vagrant becomes the target of killers whenever he wears a patchwork coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231080500 +0000" stop="20241231090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Sky Above, Death Below</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A trade union boss dies in the mountains of Colorado. His daughter believes it was murder and hires Cannon to investigate. While the detective is inspecting of the scene someone pursues him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231090500 +0000" stop="20241231100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Master Of Deception</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A man marries many women involved in electronics projects to steal their industrial secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20241231100000 +0000" stop="20241231103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
