<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129070500 +0000" stop="20260129080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Way To Dusty Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix ruffles some feathers in a small town when he arrives in search of a missing youth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129080500 +0000" stop="20260129090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By The Numbers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After a model ends up dead, the man last seen with her hires Cannon. He insists the girl was alive when he left her, so Cannon starts to dig - and turns up quite a collection of motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129090500 +0000" stop="20260129100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man abducts Betty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129100000 +0000" stop="20260129103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man has been found in a locked room, along with a gun that could not have been the murder weapon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129103000 +0000" stop="20260129110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Grenade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A surly teenager throws acid on the back of another student and later crashes a party armed with a live hand grenade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129110000 +0000" stop="20260129113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 124 -- Airport</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are rendered powerless when a drunken man with no flight experience decides to take a solo flight in a stolen airplane at a busy airport. Later, they try to locate a 17-year-old runaway living in a condemned home with a much older man, engage in a shootout with a convenience store robber and search for a booby-trapped bank safe that has been stolen with a tow truck.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129113000 +0000" stop="20260129120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 94 -- Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy fears that a boxer who has just been paroled after serving a murder sentence is going to seek revenge against him. Out on patrol, they try to save a man who has been crushed while working under a stolen car, apprehend a liquor store robber who swears revenge against reed, change a flat tire on their patrol car, locate a four-year-old child who locked himself in a refrigerator and become the targets of an ambush.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129120000 +0000" stop="20260129130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toon In With Moi</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129130000 +0000" stop="20260129133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Electric Trains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>June runs across Beaver's old electric trains while cleaning and because he hasn't played with them in years, finds someone who will take them, with Beaver's consent. However, Beaver quickly re-discovers the fun of playing with the trains and wants to withdraw from the arrangement, even though the new owners-to-be are expecting them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129133000 +0000" stop="20260129140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Long Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has Gilbert over to spend the night but after they watch a gangster movie things get out of hand. A suspicious car has just pulled up to the front of the house with two strange characters sitting inside, and they just happen to be Lumpy and Bill, dressed for a masquerade party. Not knowing this, Beaver calls the police and Lumpy and Bill are arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129140000 +0000" stop="20260129150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Traveling Treasure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>His fishing trip ruined, Mason is on the case when a deep-sea fisherman aboard a rented boat is found dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129150000 +0000" stop="20260129160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Accused of murdering his uncle in a drunken rage, Matlock takes the case of Drew Carey, a spoiled, self-centered young man who refuses to listen to his lawyer's council.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129160000 +0000" stop="20260129170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Six Kilos</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>As Chin Ho and Dan Williams are tracking a safecracker, Danno is forced to shoot him when the suspect draws his weapon. McGarrett takes on the identity of the safecracker, Harry Brown, in order to infiltrate a sophisticated gang of international thieves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129170000 +0000" stop="20260129180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Easter Story. An</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>When Olivia is stricken with polio, John-Boy refuses to accept the doctor's prognosis that she may never walk again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129180000 +0000" stop="20260129190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Bounty Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A bounty hunter comes out of retirement to find the man who murdered a rich rancher's son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129190000 +0000" stop="20260129200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonely House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded bank robber holes up in a widow's house, keeping an eye on both her and Little Joe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129200000 +0000" stop="20260129203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a young stablehand kills a notorious gunslinger, he is baffled by the hostility of the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129203000 +0000" stop="20260129210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Traders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a horse dealer transporting a prize stallion stops in North Fork, two saddle tramps try to use trickery to obtain it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129210000 +0000" stop="20260129220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Darro Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A couple on the train try to keep the husband's past from their son, but a tramp threatens to expose the secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129220000 +0000" stop="20260129230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Mouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly man is trapped in his burning house. Chet becomes obsessed with ridding the station of an uninvited guest. Paramedics and doctors treat a man who suffers repeated cardiac arrests. Dixie comforts the husband of an elderly patient. Roy and John help break up a fight. Several crises occur at an apartment house hit by a jet fighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129230000 +0000" stop="20260129233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Aid Station</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye, Houlihan and Klinger go to an aid station at the front. Working closely together under heavy fire and unsanitary medical conditions, the three return to camp with new found respect for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260129233000 +0000" stop="20260130000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love And Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper prevent a GI from marrying a call girl who has TB, while trying to help a Korean soldier join his pregnant wife. Radar, of course, provides his usual invaluable help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130000000 +0000" stop="20260130003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Big Mac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp prepares for a visit from General MacArthur. Klinger dresses as the Statue of Liberty as the General's jeep drives through the camp. MacArthur is so impressed, he salutes!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130003000 +0000" stop="20260130010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Payday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On payday, Frank buys two sets of pearls, a cheap imitation one for Margaret and a real one for his wife. After some talk, Radar gets Hawkeye $3,000 in lost earnings, Hawkeye gives it to Mulcahy for the orphans, but then the army wants the money back. Trapper wins big at poker after using Hawkeye's watch as a stake, so Hawkeye takes his winnings and gives them to the army to avoid a stay in the honeymoon suite of The Stockade Hilton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130010000 +0000" stop="20260130013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Trader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ignoring his own advice to Opie, Andy plays fast and loose with the facts when trying to sell the old town cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130013000 +0000" stop="20260130020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Those Gossipin' Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Andy teases the fairer sex about gossiping, Aunt Bee pulls a prank to prove that men are gossips, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130020000 +0000" stop="20260130023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Lateness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray decides to teach Debra a lesson in lateness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130023000 +0000" stop="20260130030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Party Dress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray takes Ally dress shopping.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130030000 +0000" stop="20260130033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Information Please</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After detecting an information leak in the area of Stalag 13, the Germans replace Klink with a more efficient officer, who Hogan sets up to take the fall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130033000 +0000" stop="20260130040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Art For Hogan's Sake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a French painting from ending up in Goering's art collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130040000 +0000" stop="20260130043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Joan Rivers And Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Alice Portnoy, Carol plays a Fireside girl scout who blackmails a best-selling author. Then, in The Ham Actor, the understudies rebel against the players in order to perform. Finally, in The Walnuts, Carol and the gang parody the hit TV show "The Waltons".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130043000 +0000" stop="20260130053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Black-eyed Blonde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>A visit from an attractive blonde sporting a black eye segues into a case concerning a wealthy man's long-lost grandson and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130053500 +0000" stop="20260130060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Before he died, notorious gunslinger Pinto Sykes put a curse on hired gun Conny Miller. When Miller returns to town, he is challenged to visit Sykes' grave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130060500 +0000" stop="20260130070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Life Work Of Juan Diaz  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A dying Mexican frenetically looks for a way to provide for his poor family after his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130070500 +0000" stop="20260130080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Only Giants Can Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A petty crook dies strangely. It's not so much the man as the motive that tickles Mannix in his head. Or is it the fact that it might be related to the political aspirations of someone he doesn't like very much?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130080500 +0000" stop="20260130090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Valley Of The Damned</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When a counterfeiting suspect escapes custody, rumors fly that Jim Farragut, the cop in charge of him, succumbed to either greed or cowardice. Jim's an old friend, so Cannon agrees to find a witness Jim claims can prove that he neither took a bribe nor experienced a failure of courage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130090500 +0000" stop="20260130100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Vendetta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A former gangster goes into hiding to finish an indictment he'd been writing about the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130100000 +0000" stop="20260130103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Shooting Board</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday lands in hot water after a thief he attempted to apprehend, and in the process shot at, turns up dead and SID can't find evidence that the man fired at Friday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130103000 +0000" stop="20260130110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Three con artists have been swindling businessmen from out of town by posing as a prostitute and two policemen. The detectives set a trap as Gannon pretends to be a manufacturer from Lincoln, Nebraska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130110000 +0000" stop="20260130113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 104 -- The Bomb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspect who frames an employee of a manufacturing plant for theft and then plants a powerful bomb on the premises. They also apprehend two criminals after questioning a suspicious man who is carrying heavy bags down the street, and protect an innocent motorist from a street race that still ends in tragedy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130113000 +0000" stop="20260130120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 74 -- Light Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed spend a night shift on desk duty after Malloy breaks his wrist and another office worker calls in sick. With the assistance of a new female recruit, they deal with a homesick elderly woman who refuses to identify herself, help a lenient father bail out his son and become suspicious of a man who walks in looking for a wanted fugitive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130120000 +0000" stop="20260130130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Coldest Winter Ever</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130130000 +0000" stop="20260130133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Jacket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Richard has just gotten, as Beaver describes it, a "keen" new jacket and this prompts Beaver to ask his parents for one exactly like it. June and Ward are hesitant after learning the price but decide to give in. However, when Richard loses his jacket, he coerces Beaver into a plot to trick his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130133000 +0000" stop="20260130140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Loves Me</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes convinced that he's ugly and unwanted after constantly being reminded how cute he used to be and from being yelled at by his parents for how messy he is currently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130140000 +0000" stop="20260130150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Posthumous Painter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Artist Jack Culross fakes his own suicide and sees the sales of his paintings go through the roof. His only oversight was forgetting to inform his wife of the scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130150000 +0000" stop="20260130160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Getaway  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An ex-convict is arrested for robbing the same bank he robbed years earlier. Matlock knows he didn't do it and has a star witness, who won't talk unless Matlock gets his father out of prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130160000 +0000" stop="20260130170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kahuna</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Sam Kalakua, a distant uncle of Kono, is being frightened into an early grave by a fake apparition of the Hawaiian goddess of volcanoes and fire, Pele. His nephew and niece want to drive him insane so that they can sell his property to a real-estate mogul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130170000 +0000" stop="20260130180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly neighbor reinforces John-Boy's feelings that despite hard times he is lucky to be surrounded by a loving family</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130180000 +0000" stop="20260130190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Reward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A convicted gold-mine swindler gets out of prison to resume mining—with money he's accused of stealing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130190000 +0000" stop="20260130200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Smiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The brother of a man Hoss killed in self-defense says he understands but secretly plans revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130200000 +0000" stop="20260130203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoiler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple moves to North Fork under an assumed name to hide the fact that they are the parents of a vicious killer. The plan backfires when the son shows up at their home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130203000 +0000" stop="20260130210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After foiling a girl's attempt to rob the general store, Lucas finds that she and her brother are plotting the murder of their abusive stepfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130210000 +0000" stop="20260130220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charles Avery Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint suspects that an Army officer has an ulterior motive while accompanying him to deliver a peace treaty to a once hostile Native American chief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130220000 +0000" stop="20260130230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Back-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A young OD victim is brought into the ER. A man fakes back pain to get a free ride to the hospital. John gets peeved at all the frivolous calls the squad goes on while real emergency victims need help. A man is shocked after kicking in his TV screen. The ambulance carrying the paramedics and a heart attack victim is involved in a traffic accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130230000 +0000" stop="20260130233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>White Gold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Flagg blows into camp trying to obtain penicillin to barter for information. But Flagg comes down with appendicitis, and the only penicillin he gets is in the keister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260130233000 +0000" stop="20260131000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Abyssinia, Henry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry finally gets his discharge. While he is tying things up, Burns prepares for his new command. Henry bids a tearful adieu, but not before Klinger turns up in an outrageous tropical outfit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131000000 +0000" stop="20260131003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp. On the way back, BJ is introduced to the Korean War.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131003000 +0000" stop="20260131010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper is shipped home while Hawkeye is on R&amp;R. Hawkeye speeds to Kimpo with Radar to catch Trapper's plane, but they just miss him. While they are there, they pick up BJ Hunnicut and take him back to camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131010000 +0000" stop="20260131013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy is chosen to be the sole judge of a local beauty pageant. The entrants include Floyd's niece, the mayor's daughter and Ellie Walker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131013000 +0000" stop="20260131020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol And Old Lace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney, on a spree of destroying illegal stills, are surprised when a trail leads them to two spinster sisters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131020000 +0000" stop="20260131023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Security</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert gets caught in the middle when Marie and Amy argue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131023000 +0000" stop="20260131030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ingrate, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray feels guilty when he doesn't mention Debra in his speech.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131030000 +0000" stop="20260131033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The General Swap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan captures a German general to trade for an American general who dislikes Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131033000 +0000" stop="20260131040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Brinksmeyer Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan robs a bank to help pay for a map to German rocket installations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131040000 +0000" stop="20260131043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Beniha-Ha, a bus boy takes center stage as a chef. Then, in The Witness, Carol and Harvey can't agree to the facts surrounding a car accident they witnessed. Finally, in The Other Secretary, Carol finds out her boss has been "cheating" on her by using another secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131043000 +0000" stop="20260131053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Terrified Typist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>While a woman is searching the office of the South African Diamond Company, George Baxter enters to meet Walter Lumis and Duane Jefferson. He notices things in disarray and tries to question the woman, but she makes her escape and seeks out Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131053500 +0000" stop="20260131060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>It's A Good Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The residents of a small town are terrorized by a young boy who has the ability to read minds and make anything he wishes a reality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131060500 +0000" stop="20260131070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>See The Monkey Dance  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A youthful London man heading for a weekend with his married mistress encounters a gentleman with oddly similar plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131070500 +0000" stop="20260131080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of A Man (aka Kill Joy)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Nils Sanderson tries to kill Mannix, but won't explain why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131080500 +0000" stop="20260131090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Well Remembered Terror</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mobsters kidnap Judge Hayes's daughter, on the orders of their boss who is on trial in Hayes's courtroom. Cannon must find and rescue her before the judge is forced to preside over a miscarriage of justice."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131090500 +0000" stop="20260131100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of Guilt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks for a member of Chicano street-gang who is the only witness to a millionaire's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131100000 +0000" stop="20260131103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Windfall</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>On an excursion to Pixley (ostensibly to look for a job), Uncle Joe stumbles on a fortune in buried money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131103000 +0000" stop="20260131110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Second Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe's constant photography and meddling threatens the 10-year marriage of a couple who have returned to the Shady Rest for a second honeymoon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131110000 +0000" stop="20260131113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Another Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Countess Maria comes to Beverly Hills, making Mrs. Drysdale very excited. But she wants to keep the countess away from the hillbillies. However, it's spring tonic time, and Granny passes it around the neighborhood, including at Countess Maria's house. She falls in love with the brew and visits the Clampetts. They become friends instantly. She starts falling for Jed, and has plans to marry her 6th husband, hoping it is an American.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131113000 +0000" stop="20260131120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Raising</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed gets invited to the opening of Drysdale’s new Commerce Bank building. Granny thinks that he will actually be building the bank. Jed attends the party and meets two of Drysdale friends, who think he is a market wizard. When Jed is told he is helping to build the bank, he heads home to get tools and pick up Elly and Granny to help out. When they get there, they cause a bit of a disturbance and misunderstand what is going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131120000 +0000" stop="20260131123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Shuteye Popeye, More Pep, Never Sock A Baby, Nearlyweds</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye's snoring is keeping his resident mouse awake., Max draws Betty and Pudgy out of the inkwell., After Popeye punishes Swee'pea, the little guy runs away., Popeye and Bluto both plan to marry Olive Oyl."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131123000 +0000" stop="20260131130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Neapolitan Mouse, The Field Mouse, Duck Doctor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom and Jerry are touring through Naples and they encounter an Italian mouse., A lazy field mouse proves his worth to his grandfather by rescuing him from a thresher., Hunting in the woods, Tom wounds a duckling, little Quacker, who is doctored by Jerry."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131130000 +0000" stop="20260131140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Gooney Is Born, Andy Panda's Victory Garden, The Hams That Couldn't Be Cured, Careless Caretaker, Dog Tax Dodgers, Tricky Trout, Janie Get Your Gun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Captain Sure Shot shoots at the gooney birds threatening to damage his planes. A mother gooney bird leaves her egg for protection in Chilly's igloo., Andy Panda and his dog Balmer plant a victory garden, while a pesky rooster eats their plants. Andy wants to plant a new garden, but another pest named Charlie the Chicken spoils the garden., A wolf is about to be hanged for taking the lives of the three little pigs, but it turns out it was the pigs who wrecked his home playing jive music., Smedley is a caretaker of the trees in a park, and gets angry when Woody starts pecking at the eldest tree. Woody tries to convince Smedley that he tree is sick., Wally Walrus tries to force Andy to pay a $3 tax for his dog., Chilly tries to steal trout from a trout hatchery run by Wally Walrus., An outlaw pastes Woody's face over his on his wanted poster. Calamity Jane goes after Woody, but then falls in love with the real outlaw when she sees what he really looks like."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131140000 +0000" stop="20260131150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Wackiki Wabbit, Fish Tales, The Hep Cat, Hare-trimmed, Moby Duck, Lickety-splat, Rabbitson Crusoe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Two castaways are starving on a raft. They come upon an island inhabited by Bugs Bunny, who looks like a tasty meal. , While fishing out in the open sea, Porky bites into a donut which turns out to be bait from a huge fish. The huge fish grabs Porky and takes him home to eat. , A dog tries to lure a cat in with a sexy-cat puppet. The cat, struck with love, breaks out in a variety of songs. , Yosemite Sam hears that Granny has inherited fifty million dollars. Good guy Bugs tries to save Granny from Sam's clutches. , Speedy and Daffy are shipwrecked on a desert island with only one can of food between them. , The Coyote tries to catch the Road Runner but never gets a chance because all his pranks to catch the Road Runner end up hurting him. , Bugs travels to an island where he’s hunted by Sam Crusoe. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131150000 +0000" stop="20260131160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Inferno</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim is set up as a renegade as a cover for him and Artie to sneak into Texas and track down General Juan Manolo, who is trying to take over the region.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131160000 +0000" stop="20260131170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Mary Halstead Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Halstead joins the wagon train to search for the son she deserted years before. Could a wounded young man picked up by the train be him?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131170000 +0000" stop="20260131180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Victoria and a reluctant Simon Carter are the only protection three Yaqui indian women have from a group of bounty-seeking scalp hunters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131180000 +0000" stop="20260131190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Malachi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Town drunk Malachi Harper poses as marshal just to impress his brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131190000 +0000" stop="20260131200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Countess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Unsettling events that could spell financial ruin for the Ponderosa mysteriously coincide with the arrival of a wealthy countess who seems determined to win the love of Ben Cartwright, the man she spurned 20 years before in New Orleans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131200000 +0000" stop="20260131203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A condemned killer being transported by train murders a marshal and takes Mark hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131203000 +0000" stop="20260131210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark discovers that the new preacher and his wife are impostors planning a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131210000 +0000" stop="20260131220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Order</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy's ex-commanding officer, Jeff McKeever, is part of a band of Confederates not willing to admit the war has ended. They have stolen $50,000, but during the holdup Wish shot one of the men, Decker. Decker stumbles into Favor's camp with the strongbox and dies. McKeever, posing as a deputy sheriff, comes for the money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131220000 +0000" stop="20260131223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Duel At Florence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin receives a letter with a bank draft for $82.17 from Ernie Teller asking for help with a matrimonial problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131223000 +0000" stop="20260131230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Pay-off At Pinto</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Having been robbed, the Bank of Pinto hires Josh to go to Santa Fe to replenish the funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260131230000 +0000" stop="20260201010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Disorder In The Court, Grips, Blunder Boys, Back From The Front, Scotched In Scotland, Space Ship Sappy, Grunts And Groans</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are witnesses at a trial where their friend, a dancer at a nightclub where they are musicians, is accused of murder.   , The Stooges become trainers of "Bustoff", a champion wrestler.  The big boss has a lot of money bet on Bustoff and orders the boys to take good care of him.  Instead they accidentally knock him out and Curly must disguises himself as Bustoff and wrestle in his place.  The match doesn't go very well until Curly smells "Wild Hyacinth" perfume on a lady fan at ringside.  This drives him crazy and he knocks out his opponent and half the people in the stadium. , A parody of the television series Dragnet. , Moe, Larry and Curly become sailors and go to sea.  And the Three Stooges as sailors are really something to see  - and laugh about.  When their ship is sunk by a nazi cruiser the boys are taken aboard by the enemy and in their own wild and zany way they end up  - after some pretty funny and weird happenings, in capturing the entire ship. , Would be detectives, the Stooges get a job guarding a Scotch castle while the owner is away.  The servants are crooks intent on robbing the castle of its valuables.  Though they do their best to frighten the boys off, the Stooges prevail and expose the crooked goings-on. , An eccentric scientist tricks the stooges into joining himself and his daughter on an expedition to Venus."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201010000 +0000" stop="20260201033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>War Of The Colossal Beast</sub-title>
    <desc>"A mysterious series of food truck robberies makes government officials doubt that the 60-foot tall Colossal Man is dead. He is discovered in a desolate mountain range in Mexico, insane and horribly disfigured. The military drugs him and transports him back to America where he promptly escapes and wreaks havoc on a city."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201033000 +0000" stop="20260201040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker's Provokers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman saves Robin from a wax machine and confronts the Joker and his new time machine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201040000 +0000" stop="20260201050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Devil In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk investigates a series of grisly murders on a mining planet that are the work of a seemingly hostile alien creature.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201050000 +0000" stop="20260201053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Forget</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois and Jimmy try to use an anti-memory vapor to go after a criminal. The crook captures them and gets the vapor to use for holdups. Clark reveals his identity to save his friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201053000 +0000" stop="20260201060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentle Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A kind professor's robot is stolen by racketeers, who use it to their advantage. The robot's power unit uses Kryptonite.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201060000 +0000" stop="20260201070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Space Circus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinsons go through a food crisis when their plant purifier breaks down. Will and Dr. Smith discover a traveling show of circus people, and Will is later tricked in to agreeing to join.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201070000 +0000" stop="20260201080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Shadowman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview is ensnared by a hostile enemy mass from a foreign galaxy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201080000 +0000" stop="20260201090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Crash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Spindrift is drawn through a space warp and crashes on a planet where everything is twelve times larger than Earth. They must quickly learn to deal with a hostile environment while becoming the target of giant scientists who want to capture and study them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201090000 +0000" stop="20260201100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Sky Fell In</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At Pearl Harbor on December 6, 1941, Tony and Doug find Tony's father, reported missing after the attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201100000 +0000" stop="20260201110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A reclusive town has David wondering what secrets are hidden there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201110000 +0000" stop="20260201120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Littlest Greenhorn</sub-title>
    <desc>"A new creature's in the forest,scaring the animals. Mad Jack's seen it and tells Adams it's a giant gorilla. Skeptical,Adams decides to investigate this tall tale and finds more and less than expected."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201120000 +0000" stop="20260201123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Vanishing With The Wilderness</sub-title>
    <desc>"What happens to the creatures living in the wilderness when their natural habitat is destroyed? Some die out…others move to a new home, and some like the coyote and opossum have journeyed far beyond their original range.  Others move in, attracted by food or by the elimination of their natural enemies.  Camped in a wilderness area on the fringe of civilization, Marlin Perkins explores the why and hows of this cross-migration."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201123000 +0000" stop="20260201130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of Quaking Earth</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the southeastern coastal plain of the United States in Georgia, there exists one of the world’s truly unique jingle swamps named by the Indians OKEEFENOKEE (land of floating islands).  Here in this intricate maze of river-ways with its ferns, grasses and cane growths, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore a fairytale jungle that is one of the last strongholds of the alligator.  The jungle suddenly becomes marshland, also called wet prairies, with water 1 to 4 feet deep.  Here in profusion fly hundreds of American egrets, the swamp fisherman.  Jim uses the Indian soap plant to wash his hands, and Marlin tries to balance on one of the floating hammocks or floating islands of “quaking earth.”  We witness the lassoing, from a boat, of a bear that has moved in too close to civilization.  After being caged, he is moved into the interior on an island that can support him, and we follow his encounters with an alligator, a skunk, and an alligator snapping turtle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201130000 +0000" stop="20260201133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Trailing The Midnight Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Winter is night, summer is day, and you need your wits to survive in the forbidding land north of the Arctic Circle.  In this story you go by walrus skin boat, dogsled, airplane and helicopter.  You hunt seal with Eskimos, find polar bear and beluga whale.  You round up a large herd of reindeer and tag them for conservation officials. And you watch Jim Fowler discover a far-north version of a popular rodeo event:  bulldogging moose from a helicopter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201133000 +0000" stop="20260201140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Cattail Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin visits the Grand Teton Mountains in the U.S. and the wilderness north of Canada to show us the territorial fight, the rescue of a baby moose and to see the sandhill cranes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201140000 +0000" stop="20260201143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the Kalahari region of southern Africa, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler study the life and habits of the graceful and cunning leopard by establishing a camp near a hidden leopard den."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201143000 +0000" stop="20260201150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Spotted Ghost Of The Desert Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim continue their investigation into the home life of the leopard."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201150000 +0000" stop="20260201153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Hustler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Brady family tries to figure out who would send them a pool table and later learn that Mike's boss, Mr. Matthews is the one. Meanwhile, Bobby becomes obsessed about the game and begins betting everyone including Mr. Matthews.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201153000 +0000" stop="20260201160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>And Now, A Word From Our Sponsor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial producer discovers the Brady family while they are grocery shopping and asks them to be in a laundry soap commercial. The dilemma facing the Bradys is whether to do the commercial because they don't use the product.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201160000 +0000" stop="20260201163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Crawdad Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>There is excitement going on at the hillbilly’s mansion when a package from home arrives. They get everything they can’t get in Beverly Hills, including crawdads. Meanwhile, at the bank, Lucas and Pendleton are trying to find out what crawdad is. They overhear Jane on the phone with Jed saying that he will share his stock of crawdad with Drysdale. The Clampetts are trying to figure out how many crawdads they have and learn of how the government put three men on the task of finding moon(shine).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201163000 +0000" stop="20260201170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Dress Shop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Drysdale buys the Clampetts a dress store using their money, and the clan decides to check it out. When they arrive at The House of Renee, they are mistaken for poor and Renee tries to help them. She thinks they need jobs. However, the Clampetts think Renee and her models are poor and starving. Renee gives the Clampetts money for food, and they think it is for them to buy food for Renee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201170000 +0000" stop="20260201173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy, The Marriage Counselor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy counsels a Mayberry couple who are constantly bickering with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201173000 +0000" stop="20260201180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Plays Cupid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Lewis, the Ricardo's elderly neighbor, requests Lucy's assistance in getting the attention of Mr. Ritter, the elderly grocery man whom she is sweet on. Lucy readily agrees to give Mr. Ritter a dinner invitation for Miss Lewis. The first complication arises when Lucy shares the news with Ricky, who spanks Lucy for interfering and makes her promise to give the note back to Miss Lewis. But, when Lucy proceeds to give Mr. Ritter the note anyway, he misunderstands and thinks the invitation is from Lucy herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201180000 +0000" stop="20260201183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is rounding up some guys to go to an amusement park and he's one short from getting a discount so he settles on Beaver. However, Beaver begins having second thoughts when he hears stories about one of the roller coasters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201183000 +0000" stop="20260201190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Three Boys And A Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Gilbert and Richard find a burro for sale in Mayfield and they each decide to go in $10 for it. After getting their parent's permission, Richard and Gilbert fight over who gets to keep the burro, which they name Pepe. However, once they get a load of just how destructive a burro can be, they dump the problem of room and board on Beaver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201190000 +0000" stop="20260201200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Target: Angels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>In separate incidents, an unknown assassin tries to kill Angels Jill, Kelly and Sabrina. The pressure intensifies forcing the girls to take to the only sure safety they know: the compound where Charlie lives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201200000 +0000" stop="20260201210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>You Made Me Kill You</sub-title>
    <desc>"A Hart Industries employee's infatuation with Jonathan endangers Jennifer's life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201210000 +0000" stop="20260201220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Hunt / Beauty Contest</sub-title>
    <desc>"When greed becomes the issue in "Treasure Hunt," Stu decides friendship and the love for his wife is worth more than all the jewels in the world on Fantasy Island. Sheltered Sally Quinn loses the "Beauty Pageant," but wins her father's respect and love on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201220000 +0000" stop="20260201230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Isaac Gets Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The company doctor eyes Isaac; a mother and daughter want the same man; a man tries to pawn off his boring fiancee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201230000 +0000" stop="20260201233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry On Record</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes suspicious when a record promoter comes to town to gather material for a folk music album.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260201233000 +0000" stop="20260202000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Meet Scott Hamilton</sub-title>
    <desc>"Scott Hamilton is a four-time world champion figure skater, best known for winning the 1984 Olympic gold medal during the Winter Games in Sarajevo. He’s also a world-class memorabilia collector. But while he does keep a few items from his notable figure skating career, including the costume he wore in the 1984 Olympics, his collection isn’t dominated by items from his career. Instead, Scott primarily collects vintage pinball machines and guitars autographed by rock and roll’s most famous personalities, including the Eagles and Bruce Springsteen. Most of these items were purchased to benefit a variety of charities, including his own Scott Hamilton CARES Foundation. Scott is joined by his wife, Tracie, who shares his dedication to charitable organizations and love for music. And Lisa has brought back certified appraiser Judy Martin, who has something quite unique from the music world to offer as a trade item."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202000000 +0000" stop="20260202003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Of Command</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank settles in as commanding officer, only to have a new one appointed over his head, one that, to his chagrin, fits in very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202003000 +0000" stop="20260202010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>It Happened One Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>It happened one night: freezing cold, an artillery barrage that's coming too close, a patient going downhill and Frank's searching Hot Lips' tent for his letters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202010000 +0000" stop="20260202013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Stivics Go West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunker house is the scene of many tearful good-byes when Mike and Gloria finally leave for California.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202013000 +0000" stop="20260202020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Little Miss Bunker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith's cousin Floyd abandons his nine-year-old daughter, Stephanie, on the Bunkers' doorstep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202020000 +0000" stop="20260202023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>End In Sight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie spends a night wallowing in self-pity when an insurance physical reveals an ominous spot on his liver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202023000 +0000" stop="20260202030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>George And Archie Make A Deal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>George Jefferson seeks Archie's help when he runs for local political office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202030000 +0000" stop="20260202033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Crazy Chin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Amy's parents point out a strange habit of Robert's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202033000 +0000" stop="20260202040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Nice Talk, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The MacDougalls and Barones attempt to bond over a 500-piece puzzle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202040000 +0000" stop="20260202043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>My Husband Is Not A Drunk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob is accidently hypnotized and acts drunk every time a bell rings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202043000 +0000" stop="20260202050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>What's In A Middle Name?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob and Laura tell Richie how he got the middle name "Rosebud".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202050000 +0000" stop="20260202053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Ralph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, after making a suggestion at work, is laid off. Alice decides to take a job as a secretary, but tells her boss that Ralph is her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202053000 +0000" stop="20260202060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Deaths-head Revisited</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A former Nazi SS captain returns to the ruins of Dachau and begins reminiscing on the power he enjoyed there, until he finds himself on trial by those who died at his hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202060000 +0000" stop="20260202070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Lonely Place  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Dread stalks a ranch occupied by a farmer, his wife and a strange hired hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202070000 +0000" stop="20260202080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Image</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Emil Gadsen has controlled the Syndicate's vice operation in the Northeast U.S. Now he plans to flee the country to avoid an indictment, leading his underling, Thor Coffin, in charge. Gadsen has a list of officials he pays off that he'll be taking with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202080000 +0000" stop="20260202090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>This'll Kill You</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble finds work at a Laundromat owned by Charlie Paris, a former stand-up comic and mob bookie who hopes to go straight. But Kimble doesn't know that that the underworld has put a hit contract on Charlie for testifying against some of their business "as</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202090000 +0000" stop="20260202100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Accounts Balanced</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell probes the mystery of an accountant leading a double life--as a paid killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202100000 +0000" stop="20260202103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Jobs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A nervy bank robber uses innocent women to help commit his crimes. Friday and Gannon are nearly sidetracked when one of the victims lies about her involvement and later proves to have a criminal record of her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202103000 +0000" stop="20260202110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill invites Joe to dinner and a football game at his home in Eagle Rock. The only problem: Gannon's neighbors keep interrupting the visit with petty and then not-so-petty problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202110000 +0000" stop="20260202113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 114 -- The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed witness a young hispanic man save a trapped watchman from a burning warehouse, but become suspicious when he resists numerous attempts of private and public commendation. They also try to prevent a drunken man from falling out a window, and resuscitate a man with a heart condition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202113000 +0000" stop="20260202120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 134 -- Child Stealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed has to deal with the consequences of forgetting to roll up the window on the patrol car before he left it. Back on patrol, Malloy and Reed search for an estranged husband who kidnaps his own child, deal with an elderly man who tries to pay for a meal with trading stamps, engage in a shootout with an escaped prisoner caught napping on a city bus and pull over a hijacked delivery van full of booze.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202120000 +0000" stop="20260202130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Black History - Harlem Rennaissance</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202130000 +0000" stop="20260202133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie Quits School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie pompously announces that he's dropping out of school to get a high paying job at a gas station. However, all is not as it seems when Wally and Lumpy get a glance at Eddie's new free spending life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202133000 +0000" stop="20260202140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Stays At Lumpy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A communication gap ensues when Wally wants to spend the night at Lumpy's and Beaver wants to have Gilbert spend the night. Beaver asks June and she tells him he can sometime when Wally spends the night somewhere and Wally asks Ward, who tells him he can sometime when Beaver has someone spend the night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202140000 +0000" stop="20260202150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Injured Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After a test driver deliberately crashes a race car equipped with an experimental engine, claims the collision paralyzed him and then ends up murdered, Mason defends the investor behind the engine's creation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202150000 +0000" stop="20260202160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Talk Show  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When talk show host Dan Galloway is murdered after publicly humiliating three woman on the air and firing his executive producer, Matlock has no shortage of suspects as he looks for clues in the death of the despised man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202160000 +0000" stop="20260202170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>A Thousand Pardons -- You're Dead!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An army sergeant and a municipal worker run a scam in which they use local bar women to claim G.I. widow benefits. Sgt. Simms then kills the women, motivated by both the cash and his desire to avenge his brother killed in Vietnam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202170000 +0000" stop="20260202180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy seeks some solitude to write his stories, but finds a life-altering situation</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202180000 +0000" stop="20260202190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Pretender</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Dano brothers return home from prison to a dying mother and a bitter father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202190000 +0000" stop="20260202200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Friendship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe befriends and takes responsibility for an ex-convict named Danny. Danny loves horses and is not used to people's ways on the outside of jail. Will his rough jailhouse upbringing mar any hopes of friendship?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202200000 +0000" stop="20260202203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance get into trouble with the Army when they try to help a wounded young soldier who deserted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202203000 +0000" stop="20260202210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mark contracts typhoid fever and has a vision of his dead mother, he no longer seems interested in getting well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202210000 +0000" stop="20260202220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Zeke Thomas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Zeke Thomas and his second wife are headed West with the train when he's confronted with a huge problem. During a stopover, Zeke sees his first wife—who he thought had died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202220000 +0000" stop="20260202230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>905-wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny and Roy answer a pre-dawn call at a small grocery store for a man down, bleeding. Searching the back of the store, Johnny is confronted with a Bengal tiger. A big brush fire threatens a suburban canyon area with lots of domesticated animals and things get dicey all around for the fire department and the Animal Control guys. Rampart becomes a veterinary surgical center for a while.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202230000 +0000" stop="20260202233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Captain Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hawkeye's father is notified that he's dead, he finds it's no easy matter either to get word to him or to establish otherwise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260202233000 +0000" stop="20260203000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Doc</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Its quid pro quo at the 4077th: two bottles of Scotch for secret surgery, and a tank to scare off snipers for an unauthorized shot of penicillin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203000000 +0000" stop="20260203003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Bus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Driving back from a medical conference, Radar, Hawkeye, B.J., Sherman and Frank find themselves lost. When they decide to turn around, the bus does not want to start. And when Radar goes off in the middle of the night for the latrine, he does not immediately return.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203003000 +0000" stop="20260203010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Mildred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Potter's anniversary. While Potter writes home, Frank and Hot Lips have a wood carving made for him, and Radar rescues a horse and makes him a present of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203010000 +0000" stop="20260203013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Saves Barney's Morale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's overzealous policing enrages the people of Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203013000 +0000" stop="20260203020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And The Gentleman Crook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>An infamous con artist, held temporarily in Mayberry, manages to enchant everyone except Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203020000 +0000" stop="20260203023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Blabbermouths</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert informs Ray that Amy filled him in on some juicy gossip about him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203023000 +0000" stop="20260203030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Model, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is convinced to pose for head shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203030000 +0000" stop="20260203033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Praise The Fuhrer And Pass The Ammunition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men create chaos during staged war games that a ruthless Nazi colonel has scheduled near Stalag 13, replacing the exercise's fake explosives with live ammunition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203033000 +0000" stop="20260203040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan And The Lady Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan resents having a lady scientist in charge of a mission to destroy a lab.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203040000 +0000" stop="20260203043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest William Conrad</sub-title>
    <desc>In Twitches, Carol develops a twitch as Harvey describes an old flame. Then, in The Family, Eunice double dates with Mama.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203043000 +0000" stop="20260203053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Rolling Bones</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When Daniel Reed finds himself being blackmailed by an old business partner from his time in Alaska, Mason must first save him from the insane asylum and then the gas chamber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203053500 +0000" stop="20260203060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Midnight Sun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earth's orbit has been changed, drawing ever closer to the sun and promising imminent destruction.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203060500 +0000" stop="20260203070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Mcgregor Affair  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Dopey McGregor makes his living carrying boxes to a medical college, unaware that they contain the remains of murder victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203070500 +0000" stop="20260203080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Climb A Deadly Mountain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Forced to crash land a plane, Mannix gets rescued by an escaped convict who's being pursued by corrupt law enforcement officers out to silence him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203080500 +0000" stop="20260203090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Arena Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Socialite Doris Hawthorne's fiance disappears. Only then does she learn he was actually married to a Swiss woman, and also a blackmailing extortionist with a long list of enemies, many of whom want his files.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203090500 +0000" stop="20260203100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Due to circumstantial evidence, Betty's old flame is a prime suspect in a restaurant tycoon's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203100000 +0000" stop="20260203103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Frustration</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carl Maxwell, a frustrated fellow detective, goes AWOL; Friday and Gannon have three days to track him down before Maxwell loses his badge for good.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203103000 +0000" stop="20260203110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Senior Citizen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of daring daylight house burglaries are taking place perpetrated by an octogenarian who uses the wedding and obituary notices in the paper to select his victims.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203110000 +0000" stop="20260203113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 144 -- Bank Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are in for a rude awakening when they report to the home of a former professional wrestler on a domestic abuse call. Later, they become suspicious of an apartment burglary victim after they find one of the suspects dead, deal with a man who discovers car parts that were stolen from him installed on another car and become involved in a shootout responding to a bank robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203113000 +0000" stop="20260203120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 44 -- Attempted Bribery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A wealthy businessman openly offers malloy and reed security jobs at three times their current salaries if reed agrees to withhold damaging testimony against his troubled son. In the meantime, they have to deal with an elderly man who has strangled his ch</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203120000 +0000" stop="20260203130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Novelty Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203130000 +0000" stop="20260203133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Laundry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver agrees to help Richard cart his family's clothes down to the laundromat; however, half way there they discover that Richard has lost the three dollars his mother gave him. This leads him to ask Beaver if he could use the Cleaver washer. They soon find themselves in another jam when the washing machine overflows after Beaver put in too much soap and starch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203133000 +0000" stop="20260203140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Car Trouble</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows his car to be driven by Lumpy, who must get Eddie, Wally and Beaver to a sporting event in a neighboring town. However, on the way back, Lumpy disobeys Ward's orders and takes a shortcut home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203140000 +0000" stop="20260203150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Left-handed Liar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Health club instructor Ward Nichols wants to marry the daughter of his employer, but his estranged wife is pressuring him for money and claiming to be pregnant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203150000 +0000" stop="20260203160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Victim  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to prove that someone other than his client had a motive in a murder case. His best bet? The victim's paraplegic husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203160000 +0000" stop="20260203170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Feet High And It Kills!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A tsunami warning is called and a geneticist is evacuated from a conference. He is then kidnapped under the orders of Wo Fat, but he uses his diabetic medical condition as a ploy to stop Wo Fat from carrying out the plan to return him to China.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203170000 +0000" stop="20260203180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Separation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A misunderstanding and plain stubborn pride causes a rift between the Walton grandparents</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203180000 +0000" stop="20260203190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>South Wind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy goes into hiding after witnessing his father's murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203190000 +0000" stop="20260203200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Springtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A friend of Ben's arrives at the Ponderosa right as the Cartwright boys are fighting in mud. Mr. Milbank, who is injured by a flying log during the fight, gives an assignment to each of the three boys. Can they fulfill the assignments, or has springtime gotten to them all?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203200000 +0000" stop="20260203203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Lucas's returns to town in the company of a shady gambler and is accused of cheating at cards.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203203000 +0000" stop="20260203210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men are vying for a rancher's daughter's affections. When she is found dead, one of them becomes the prime suspect in her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203210000 +0000" stop="20260203220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Riley Gratton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Major Adams sets out to recover passengers' money that was taken by con man Riley Gratton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203220000 +0000" stop="20260203230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Stewardess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John falls for a stewardess and shows his stuff when a passenger has a heart attack; later, he tries to date her. The firefighters respond to a motorcycle accident and a chemical fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203230000 +0000" stop="20260203233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th plays host to kids bombed out of their orphanage, and at the same time has to deliver a baby and care for battle casualties.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260203233000 +0000" stop="20260204000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Quo Vadis, Captain Chandler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Intelligence officer Colonel Flagg and psychiatrist Sidney Freedman grapple over the fate of a wounded officer, Captain Chandler, who claims to be Jesus Christ.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204000000 +0000" stop="20260204003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Peggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. writes home to his wife, Peg, reporting Klinger's escape attempts, the visit of a formidable chaplain and one of Frank's goof-ups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204003000 +0000" stop="20260204010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Of Moose And Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tangles with a tough Army colonel, Colonel Spiker; B.J. helps Zale, who's received a Dear John letter; and Frank looks endlessly for Korean saboteurs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204010000 +0000" stop="20260204013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cyrano Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy tries to help Barney express his lovestruck feelings for Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204013000 +0000" stop="20260204020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Opie, Housekeepers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Opie go to great lengths to show Aunt Bee what a mess they'd be without her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204020000 +0000" stop="20260204023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Mentor, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man, Sam Gilula, arrives at Frank and Marie's.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204023000 +0000" stop="20260204030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Golf For It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Ray  decide not to help Marie with a home project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204030000 +0000" stop="20260204033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Swing Shift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk gets drafted into the German army while working on Hogan's plan to sabotage a ammunition factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204033000 +0000" stop="20260204040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Heil Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is hiding a defecting German officer, and convinces Klink that the latter, who looks like Schultz, is really Hitler in disguise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204040000 +0000" stop="20260204043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Rock Hudson</sub-title>
    <desc>In When My Baby Laughs at Me, a vaudeville sketch, Rock leaves Carol behind in order to pursue fame in New York.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204043000 +0000" stop="20260204053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Corresponding Corpse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason receives a telephone call from George Beaumont, a man who supposedly died in a plane crash nearly three years earlier. In reality, Beaumont missed the plane and after hearing about the accident decided to disappear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204053500 +0000" stop="20260204060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Still Valley</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A Confederate soldier wanders into a town and finds a group of Union soldiers frozen in time. An old man with a black book implores the soldier to use the book's powers to win the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204060500 +0000" stop="20260204070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Misadventure  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An outsider forms a wobbly coalition with an insatiable woman bent on murdering her rich husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204070500 +0000" stop="20260204080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Little Girl Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to help a girl who witnessed her father's murder and was driven over the edge mentally by the event.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204080500 +0000" stop="20260204090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Photo Finish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank agrees to look into a murder, convinced the Indian suspect did not commit the crime. His investigation unearths dozens of missing Indians and a drug smuggling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204090500 +0000" stop="20260204100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dangerous Gambit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigation a fatal automobile accident, Barnaby uncovers a complex scheme to defraud a bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204100000 +0000" stop="20260204103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly businessman concerned about the welfare of his grandchild informs Friday and Gannon that his daughter and son-in-law are using marijuana regularly. The young couple make no apologies for their lifestyle, which inevitably leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204103000 +0000" stop="20260204110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204110000 +0000" stop="20260204113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 173 -- Shoplift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed track down a young shoplifter who escapes custody and hides at the lair of an eccentric spiritualist whom she worships.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204113000 +0000" stop="20260204120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 174 -- Loan Sharks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating the severe beating of a factory worker, Reed and Malloy uncover an extensive loansharking operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204120000 +0000" stop="20260204130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' Old Dominion</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204130000 +0000" stop="20260204133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Baby-sitter</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Wally has a previous engagement and is unable to babysit, Beaver fills in and quickly finds himself the object of a 10-year old's affection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204133000 +0000" stop="20260204140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Younger Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to join the basketball team but finds himself trying to live up to Wally's performance. However, after not making the team, Beaver allows his family to believe that he did.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204140000 +0000" stop="20260204150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Brazen Bequest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles Cromwell, the president-elect of Euclid College, worries that some less than stellar moments from his past will be exposed when Maisie Freitag arrives at the college.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204150000 +0000" stop="20260204160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapper  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock is kidnapped, Michelle and Conrad go through Matlock's old cases to try to figure out who is holding him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204160000 +0000" stop="20260204170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Just Lucky, I Guess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A middle-aged mainland hardware salesman uses a prostitute, and then witnesses her murder by a mobster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204170000 +0000" stop="20260204180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Theft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The disappearance of some valuable silver pieces throws suspicion on one of the Waltons</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204180000 +0000" stop="20260204190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Four convicts take Matt hostage on their way to Mexico.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204190000 +0000" stop="20260204200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Breaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While working at the Ponderosa, wrangler Johnny Lightly suffers an accident that costs him the use of both legs. Though Dr. Kay theorizes that the injuries may not last, Johnny has given up the will to live.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204200000 +0000" stop="20260204203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Shotgun man John Beaumont, who Lucas sent to prison, returns with vengeance on his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204203000 +0000" stop="20260204210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting a man in self-defense, Andy Moon turns to Lucas for protection from his vengeful brothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204210000 +0000" stop="20260204220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clara Beauchamp Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A cavalry colonel's wife tries to foment a war with Native Americans as part of a convoluted scheme to get her husband promoted and transferred back east.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204220000 +0000" stop="20260204230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Old Engine Cram</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A fireman is injured in a practice drill. Roy and John think they have a buyer for the old fire engine. A man suffers a back injury while riding a motorcycle. A mother pressures Dr. Morton to give her son a prescription. A man having a heart attack walks into the station. DeSoto and Gage rescue a man who has fallen off a cliff on Catalina Island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204230000 +0000" stop="20260204233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Soldier Of The Month</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank has a fever and makes a will, leaving all his money to his wife and all his clothes to Hot Lips.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260204233000 +0000" stop="20260205000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded colonel's gun, a showpiece, disappears, and Hawkeye and B.J. play a hunch and bluff Frank, who has it, into returning it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205000000 +0000" stop="20260205003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mail brings a letter to Frank saying his wife is divorcing him, and one to Potter telling him he's going to be a grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205003000 +0000" stop="20260205010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price Of Tomato Juice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets the help of Hawkeye and B.J. to procure something Colonel Potter says he's fond of, but that's hard to come by—tomato juice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205010000 +0000" stop="20260205013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a handsome new doctor arrives in town, his friendship with Ellie arouses suspicion in Aunt Bee and Barney and jealousy in Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205013000 +0000" stop="20260205020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Plaque For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayor Pike (Dick Elliott) and the townspeople are shocked to discover that the last living descendant of Revolutionary War hero Nathan Tibbs is Mayberry's town drunk, Otis Campbell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205020000 +0000" stop="20260205023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Home, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank and Marie have decided to buy a condo in New Jersey.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205023000 +0000" stop="20260205030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Not So Fast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert's anxiety gets the best of him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205030000 +0000" stop="20260205033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Everyone Has A Brother-in-law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan's plot to destroy an ammunition train is foiled by Burkhalter's brother-in-law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205033000 +0000" stop="20260205040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses an incredibly original ruse to get Schultz a weeklong furlough in Heidelberg. While there, Schultz is to deliver needed radio parts to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205040000 +0000" stop="20260205043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And The Pointer Sisters</sub-title>
    <desc>In Stella Toddler, Carol plays an accident-prone woman on a game show "Up Your Income". Then, in Nora Desmond, Carol plays a has-been actress who searches for a replacement for her butler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205043000 +0000" stop="20260205053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lucky Loser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason has all kinds of trouble when a murder brings him into the tangled financial and personal affairs of the wealthy Balfour family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205053500 +0000" stop="20260205060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jungle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a business man plans to build a dam in Africa, a witch doctor puts a curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205060500 +0000" stop="20260205070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Triumph  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When two missionaries arrive at a remote medical mission in the Indian jungle, jealousy leads to murder and a coverup.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205070500 +0000" stop="20260205080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>End Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A member of Mannix's old combat unit, brought up on charges and court-martialed, wants revenge on Mannix and the only other survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205080500 +0000" stop="20260205090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Duel In The Desert</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Years earlier, Mel Danvers organized a successful hijacking and walked away with a cool million. But there is a witness: a stewardess. Danvers engineers a campaign of terror to keep her mum, until Cannon puts a stop to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205090500 +0000" stop="20260205100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Wipeout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the death of a girl who was a supposedly skilled surfer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260205100000 +0000" stop="20260205103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
