<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510103000 +0000" stop="20250510110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Tag-team Match</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the day after Granny beat up the Boston Strong Girl, making her the new champ, and the Clampetts are celebrating Granny’s great victory. But not all is well. The woman who plays the Boston Strong Girl is in trouble for getting beat up. The woman who plays Rebecca of Donnybrook Farm, a former topless waitress, has learned the truth, getting an invitation from Granny to visit. Their manager, Gene Booth, sees this as an opportunity to get Granny to fight, after hearing the huge ratings the fight got.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510110000 +0000" stop="20250510113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>The Twisker Pitcher, Adventures Of Popeye, Safari So Good</sub-title>
    <desc>"An exciting baseball game pits Popeye against Bluto as captains of opposing teams., In this combination of photography and cartoons, a little boy is bullied for reading POPEYE books., Popeye and Olive Oyl are on safari when they run into a Tarzan-like Bluto."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510113000 +0000" stop="20250510120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Jerry And The Lion, Duck Doctor, Early Bird And The Worm</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom and Jerry hear on the radio that a lion is loose in the area., Hunting in the woods, Tom wounds a duckling, little Quacker, who is doctored by Jerry., A young bird tries to get the jump on his worm neighbor by getting up early but the worm proves to be too elusive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510120000 +0000" stop="20250510130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Pantry Panic, Andy Panda's Victory Garden, Wicket Wacky, Polar Fright, Tumble Weed Greed, Guest Who?, Woodpecker From Mars</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody fails to go South for the winter, leaving him vulnerable to a starving cat., Andy Panda and his dog Balmer plant a victory garden, while a pesky rooster eats their plants. Andy wants to plant a new garden, but another pest named Charlie the Chicken spoils the garden., Woody plays a game of croquet and disturbs the underground parlor of a gopher., Chilly helps Maxie escape an Inuit hunting for polar bears., Woody wins a cash prize and goes on vacation with it, but Buzz Buzzard wants to steal the cash., Junior wins a monkey as a dance contest prize and tries to hide it from his family., Woody gets mistaken for a Martian on earth, only to be sent to Mars by the human authorities and perceived as an alien by the martians when he lands."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510130000 +0000" stop="20250510140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbit Punch, War And Pieces, Porky's Duck Hunt, Ballot Box Bunny, Ain't She Tweet, Super Rabbit</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs heckles the champ so much while at the World Champion fight that the fighter brings him into the ring for a beating., The Road Runner runs from the Coyote! , Porky decides to go duck hunting with his dog but has considerable trouble when he meets Daffy. , Bugs runs against Yosemite Sam in this political comic farce. Bugs opting for "speak softly and carry a big stick" and Sam opting for "speak louder and carry a bigger stick." , Tweety gets bought by Granny and Sylvester tries all sorts of devices to defeat the dogs guarding Tweety in the house. , A spoof of Superman with Bugs Bunny as Super Rabbit. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510140000 +0000" stop="20250510150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Turncoat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The stress of secret service work appears to be finally getting to Jim as his temper flares and he makes mistakes. As West is being recruited by some member of the underworld who seeks to capitalize on his misfortune, Artemus and Colonel Richmond struggle to find out exactly who, for what, and why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510150000 +0000" stop="20250510160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Wilbot Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Tensions are running high in the train between Northerners and Southerners traveling west. As trouble escalates one passenger with a noticeable limp, John Wilbot, is accused of being John Wilkes Booth, who many believe to still be alive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510160000 +0000" stop="20250510170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Legend Of A General: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Barkleys offer sanctuary to a Mexican general who has fled false arrest. Heath is jailed in Mexico, and the Barkley ranch is invaded by men trying to seize the general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510170000 +0000" stop="20250510173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Innocent Broad</sub-title>
    <desc>"Linda Bell comes to Dodge to meet her fiance Lou Paxon. Lou makes Linda take a job at the Long Branch. Matt is suspicious of Lou and Joe Bassett."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510173000 +0000" stop="20250510180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Con</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Shaneway wants Mr. Pap at the bank to loan him $20,000 for a poker bet. Doc gets kidnapped."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510180000 +0000" stop="20250510190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Sure Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Trudy Loughlin loves her horse, a wild stallion. But her father has plans of his own, and they are likely to leave the girl heartbroken.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510190000 +0000" stop="20250510193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Queue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A Chinese man and his son fight prejudice as they try to open a laundry in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510193000 +0000" stop="20250510200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vaqueros</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While Lucas and Mark are traveling across the Mexican desert they encounter a trio of Mexican bandits. They demand payment from Lucas for crossing "their" desert. Lucas refuses. In retaliation, the three slam Lucas in the throat with his rifle, strip him of all his possessions (including Mark), tie him to a tree and leave him to die of thirst and exposure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510200000 +0000" stop="20250510210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of The Swindler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An old "friend" of Wish's tells him he is a wanted man for a murder in New Orleans 13 years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510210000 +0000" stop="20250510213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Lady With A Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After she attempts to shoot Rudy Rossback and fails, Eve McIntosh offers Paladin $1,000 to kill him. After Paladin turns her down she hires another gunman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510213000 +0000" stop="20250510220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Crossroads</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Pursuing killer Joe Collins into the Superstition Mountains, Josh is shadowed by a man who believes Collins could be his long-lost son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250510220000 +0000" stop="20250511000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Little Beers, Dizzy Doctors, Studio Stoops, Pardon My Backfire, Beer Barrel Polecats, Tassels In The Air</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are inept deliverymen at a brewery.   , Larry, Curly and Moe make a grand mess of things when they mistake the medicine they're selling for auto polish.  , Moe pretends to be trendy interior designer. , The Stooges are hired by a movie studio as publicity men.  Their first assignment is to get publicity for Dolly Devore, a pretty starlet.  They fake a kidnapping, but the cops won't believe their story.  Then the girl is really kidnapped and the Stooges must come to the rescue.  Shemp winds up hanging out a tenth story window on an extending telephone. , The Stooges are auto mechanics who need money so they can marry their girls.  When some escaped convicts pull into their garage, the boys manage to capture them and use the reward money to marry their sweethearts. , The Stooges make a whole batch of homemade beer, but get tossed in jail when Curly sells some to a cop.  Their minor indiscretion turns into a forty-year sentence when a keg of beer Curly has hidden under his coat explodes while the boys are being photographed.  In prison the Stooges get into more trouble with the warden and wind on the rockpile when they try to escape.  Released as old men with long gray beards, the first thing Curly wants is a bottle of beer. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511000000 +0000" stop="20250511023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Kingdom Of The Spiders</sub-title>
    <desc>"In rural Arizona, countless killer tarantulas are migrating through a farm town, killing every living thing in their path. The town's veterinarian will do everything in his power to survive the onslaught."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511023000 +0000" stop="20250511030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Hi Diddle Riddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler stages a scene in order to sue Batman for false arrest. Now the Caped Crusader must uncover the plot before he's forced to reveal his true identity in court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511030000 +0000" stop="20250511040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Cloud Minders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk must resolve a mining dispute on a the cloud city of Stratos to acquire the resources to cure a space plague.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511040000 +0000" stop="20250511050000 +0000">
    <title>Kolchak: The Night Stalker</title>
    <sub-title>The Youth Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Helen of Troy returns to drain the youth out of unsuspecting perfect victims, sacrifices for the goddess Hecate, in her quest for immortality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511050000 +0000" stop="20250511060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Fugitives In Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Smith comes across an alien prison escapee, the alien makes Dr. Smith change jackets with him and then runs off. Soon, Dr. Smith and Don are arrested for aiding the escaped prisoner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511060000 +0000" stop="20250511070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Peacemaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Nelson battles a fanatic scientist in possession of a bomb that will destroy the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511070000 +0000" stop="20250511080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Bounty Hunter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The giants step up their efforts to find the Earthlings, and Barry befriends a giant girl who can help them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511080000 +0000" stop="20250511090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Town Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are propelled into the future (1978) to fight invaders siphoning off the Earth's oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511090000 +0000" stop="20250511100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Betrayed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>David's personal life threatens his mission when aliens resort to foul play to recover a computer tape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511100000 +0000" stop="20250511110000 +0000">
    <title>The Powers of Matthew Star</title>
    <sub-title>Powers Of Matthew Star</sub-title>
    <desc>"After developing powers, a teenager realizes he's not from Earth."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511110000 +0000" stop="20250511113000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Senior Prom   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>It's up to the gang to raise the funds needed for the senior prom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511113000 +0000" stop="20250511120000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Graduation   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>On graduation day, Zack discovers that he is one credit short of getting his diploma, and the only way he can earn it is by doing the unbelievable—BALLET!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511120000 +0000" stop="20250511123000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>The Time Capsule   (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Mr. Belding and the class of 2003 find a video time capsule from the class of 1993. The video shows the funny and the touching moments Zack and the gang shared with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511123000 +0000" stop="20250511130000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>King Of The Hill   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Zack starts high school ready to woo longtime crush Kelly, but A.C. Slater stands in his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511130000 +0000" stop="20250511133000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Distraction   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After Zack spies on Kelly, trying to hear who'll she'll take to the dance, she sets up a prank to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511133000 +0000" stop="20250511140000 +0000">
    <title>Saved by the Bell</title>
    <sub-title>Screech's Woman   (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Trying to cheer Screech up so he'll complete their science project, Zack pretends to know a girl who is interested in him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511140000 +0000" stop="20250511143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Getting Greg's Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After he and his teammates swipe a rival school's mascot in retaliation for theirs being stolen first, Greg is tasked with watching Raquel, a goat. Things get out of control when Raquel proves to be hard to handle, easy to feed and not easy to catch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511143000 +0000" stop="20250511150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Marcia Gets Creamed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia's got a new job at an ice cream parlor. With both school and work, Marcia has little time for her boyfriend who, fed up, comes into the parlor with another girl. And how will Marcia handle her own brother goofing off on the job?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511150000 +0000" stop="20250511153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>A Sight For Sore Eyes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie fears that his famous cool will be compromised if he wears the reading glasses prescribed to cure his headaches.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511153000 +0000" stop="20250511160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Playing Hooky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley call in sick so they can have a day of fun, they meet a couple of fellows who may not be what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511160000 +0000" stop="20250511163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Virgil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to help out his visiting cousin, Virgil. When Virgil makes one too many mistakes, Barney rails against him and storms out. Leave it to Andy to put things right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511163000 +0000" stop="20250511170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ricky Thinks He Is Going Bald</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ricky fears he's going bald, so Lucy steps in to help."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511170000 +0000" stop="20250511173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Sweatshirt Monsters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver, Richard, Whitey and Alan each buy sweatshirts that have monster faces on the front of them. They like them so much they each decide to wear them to school the next day. However, each one finds that their parents forbid them from wearing such hideous sweatshirts to school. However, Beaver manages to sneak out of the house with his on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511173000 +0000" stop="20250511180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>A Night In The Woods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends are all psyched to go on a camping trip with Gilbert's father as an escort. However, when Gilbert's father suddenly has to work, Wally agrees to take them. Meanwhile, Eddie and Lumpy decide to secretly tag along and scare the boys with animal noises.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511180000 +0000" stop="20250511183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jethro Proposes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has heard that Miss Jane has never been proposed to and wants to help out. She tries to get Jed to propose, but has no luck with that plan. Granny then settles to have Jethro propose to her. Jethro asks Miss Jane out, and she accepts. While at the bank, Jethro also meets the gorgeous new night guard, Ilse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511183000 +0000" stop="20250511190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Sheik</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After entering an oil deal with Jed and O.K. Oil, the Sheik befriends the Clampetts, giving Jed four of his dancing girls for wives and tries to get the beautiful Elly May as one of his wives. Jed tries to give the girls back, while Jethro tries to enjoy some of the Sheik's life, mainly the company of his beautiful dancing girls, after selling his cousin.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511190000 +0000" stop="20250511193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds Are An Ape's Best Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A gorilla kidnaps Mrs. Howell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511193000 +0000" stop="20250511200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>How To Be A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The castaways attempt to make Gilligan feel like a hero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511200000 +0000" stop="20250511203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Naomi's Identity Crisis  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Naomi loses her memory, Mama takes advantage of her condition by molding her into the perfect housewife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511203000 +0000" stop="20250511210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Pomp And Circumstance  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A disappointed Bubba refuses to go to his graduation when he learns his parents will not be there. And Mama, the valedictorian and speaker for the commencement, refuses to go without him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511210000 +0000" stop="20250511220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Third Wheel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Gopher unintentionally hurts his father. Meanwhile, a woman whose children are grown learns she is pregnant, while another woman wins her stepdaughters' love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511220000 +0000" stop="20250511223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Rich Girlfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy has begun seeing Peggy McMillan and he discovers she is from a wealthy family. The differences in their upbringings and education unsettle Andy, and he begins to doubt the ability of the relationship to endure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511223000 +0000" stop="20250511230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Joe Salg- Cyndi Lauper</sub-title>
    <desc>"When a teenage Joe Salg heard Cyndi Lauper’s single “Time After Time,” he was hooked. She represented what he had been seeking as a young gay man: Outside acceptance of one’s true colors, whatever they might be. He began buying albums and any other memorabilia he could find. Then he went on a quest: to gain bragging rights to the most unique items ever related to the pop icon. Years later, he had so many prized possessions that friends and family urged him to open a museum dedicated to the singer. Today, he is the proud owner of The Cyndi Lauper Museum, which is acknowledged and admired by the music legend herself. Joe walks Lisa through some of the most iconic items, including the first microphone Cyndi ever used as an emerging star and everything from a quirky corset used for a famed photo shoot to a glamorous dress worn to the 50th anniversary of the Grammys. Later, Liam will propose a trade: one of his most treasured items, personally signed by the singer, for Joe’s rare relic of ‘80s pop culture itself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511230000 +0000" stop="20250511233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bananas, Crackers And Nuts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Henry goes for some R&amp;R, Hawkeye pretends to crack up so that Frank will let him and Trapper go on some R&amp;R.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250511233000 +0000" stop="20250512000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cowboy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>John Hodges, a chopper pilot referred to as The Cowboy, has been hit in the shoulder, and arrives at the 4077th. He is expecting a letter—he's worried that his wife, Jean, is leaving him for another man. He wants to go home, but Henry refuses, stating Cowboy's wound isn't serious enough to merit a stateside ticket. Bad luck then follows Henry Blake like the seat of his pants!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512000000 +0000" stop="20250512003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria And The Riddle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria has become friends with a girl named Tammy and they have been organizing a Women's Fair. Male chauvinism is put to the test when Gloria poses a riddle to Mike and Archie who are stumped when they can't come up with the answer. Archie even goes to his drinking buddies for help, but to no avail. However, it is Edith who suddenly comes up with the answer (an answer that Archie doesn't want to hear).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512003000 +0000" stop="20250512010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Lionel Steps Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's niece has been visiting the Bunkers and having a great time. She's even made friends with Lionel and loves going out on the town with him. However, a picture taken of the two of them becomes the thing that clues Archie in on their blossoming relationship and he hits the roof, citing that people should stick to their own race.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512010000 +0000" stop="20250512013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith Flips Her Wig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith comes home from shopping in a terrible state; it seems she had been arrested for shoplifting. Apparently, she had walked out of a store, wearing a wig, while trying to give bus directions to a woman. Edith becomes convinced that she has become a kleptomaniac, after finding that she also "stole" a necklace. Edith begins to obsess and Mike suggests that she see a psychiatrist, however, Edith has something in mind herself; she visits a priest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512013000 +0000" stop="20250512020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Bunkers And The Swingers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith finds a magazine on the subway and reads an ad in the "swap" section. Not realizing what is actually being asked for, Edith assumes the couple is looking for friendship. Mike and Gloria, in a rush, try to explain what they really want. However, it isn't until the couple is actually standing in the Bunker's living room that Edith realizes, with a little help from Louise, that they are "swingers" and they want to swap with Archie and Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512020000 +0000" stop="20250512023000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Dick Van Dyke And Tony Randall</sub-title>
    <desc>In Death of a Salesman, Dick Van Dyke tries to sell encyclopedias, only he keeps getting hurt by Carol. Then, in Root of All Evil, Tony and Dick get into a squabble about money after one loses five dollars and the other burns a ten dollar bill. Finally, in Warning Signals, a couple uses hand signals with each other in an attempt to get rid of their house guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512023000 +0000" stop="20250512030000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Washington Wacko / D.m.v., The / I'll Do The Talking</sub-title>
    <desc>In Washington Wacko, Carol goes bananas just before her husband meets the President. Then, in The D.M.V., Harvey's license plate gets mixed up with a confusing employee. Finally, in I'll Do the Talking, Carol and Tim talk to each other and over each other, oblivious to what they other is saying.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512030000 +0000" stop="20250512033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>One Hundred Terrible Hours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recalls how he became the head writer of "The Alan Brady Show".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512033000 +0000" stop="20250512040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Br-rooom, Br-rooom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Laura doesn't like Rob's new motorcycle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512040000 +0000" stop="20250512043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512043000 +0000" stop="20250512050000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Back There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While discussing time travel among friends in 1961, a man suddenly finds himself in 1865—on the date of Lincoln's assassination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512050000 +0000" stop="20250512060000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>An Out For Oscar  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Weighed down by an adulterous partner and her money-mad lover, a shy bank teller schemes to free himself via the "perfect crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512060000 +0000" stop="20250512070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When Jim returns to his hometown of Norville to donate family property to the community, he finds it plagued by a serial killer. Jim secretly brings in Barney to help investigate. A disturbed Vietnam vet is the suspected killer but Jim and Barney believe it could be someone else.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512070000 +0000" stop="20250512080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The Cage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While working as a handyman in the predominantly Hispanic fishing village of Puerto Viejo, Kimble becomes aware that the area is beset with a plague epidemic and he's forced to call the state health inspector to have the entire area quarantined. But he so</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512080000 +0000" stop="20250512090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Double Jeopardy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry O takes on an unusual client when he tries to protect a murder suspect from syndicate killers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512090000 +0000" stop="20250512093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shipment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Drugs are found aboard a plane that has crashed in the San Fernando Valley. The pilot is quickly traced, but in order to force him to name his connection, Friday and Gannon ask the press to sit on the story for a few hours.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512093000 +0000" stop="20250512100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When two small girls go missing, the mother is convinced that their estranged father kidnapped them. However, a preliminary investigation by Friday and Gannon determines that the man has no knowledge of his daughters' whereabouts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512100000 +0000" stop="20250512103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Jimmy Eisley's Dealing Smack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy spot TJ, an informant, who tells them about a possible drug house. They spot a woman and girl at the same bus stop an hour apart. When they stop to talk to her, she tries to run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512103000 +0000" stop="20250512110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 62 -- Grand Theft Horse?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have to put with a mystery noise in the car while handling grand theft horse, a naive girl and a robbery suspect who makes fake calls to distract the police</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512110000 +0000" stop="20250512120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Originators</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore the origins of popular phrases, movies, products and more!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512120000 +0000" stop="20250512123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Long Distance Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and his friends decide to make a call to California to talk to Don Drysdale and they agree to chip in on the cost of the call, assuming that it's only going to be a couple dollars. However, when they're put on hold, the cost quickly jumps up to $9.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512123000 +0000" stop="20250512130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Stocks And Bonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally become interested in the stock market and Ward decides that they should try their hand at it. However, Wally and Beaver have different ideas about what to invest in compared to Ward who wants them to play it safe and invest in Mayfield Power and Electric, while they want to invest in a more risky venture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512130000 +0000" stop="20250512140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Scandalous Sculptor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Scandal rocks the art world when a model is found dead, presumably murdered by the jealous wife of a sculptor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512140000 +0000" stop="20250512150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lemon  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's new neighbor, Les "Ace" Calhoun (Don Knotts), is charged with murdering the used car salesman who sold him a lemon, Matlock takes the case to prove that more than one person had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512150000 +0000" stop="20250512160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Turning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Althea thinks Virgil needs a new line of work after seeing the aftermath of a deadly shooting at a roadhouse. Virgil finds himself in danger when they arrest the man who committed the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512160000 +0000" stop="20250512170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>John Walton gets job in city because he wants an adventure</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512170000 +0000" stop="20250512173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Widow's Mite</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gambler Leach Fields marries Zach Morton's widow Ada thinking she knows where the money Zach stole is."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512173000 +0000" stop="20250512180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chester's Hanging</sub-title>
    <desc>"Someone keeps hanging people in Dodge and making it look like suicide."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512180000 +0000" stop="20250512190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown At Tahoe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A career robber claiming to be a lumber man plans to use Ben's new freight paddleboat to haul a $1-million-dollar currency shipment to San Francisco.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512190000 +0000" stop="20250512193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>First Wages</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to find out why Mark has taken a job as a stableboy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512193000 +0000" stop="20250512200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sheer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark and Milly are held prisoner in her general store when two gunmen attempt a daring robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512200000 +0000" stop="20250512210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Monty Britton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Low on water, Flint scouts for more. When three water holes are dry or poisoned, Fort Paiute seems their only hope but he has to make it back to the wagon train on foot and the only other man who knows the way is believed to be a deserter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512210000 +0000" stop="20250512220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Women</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman journalist covers the Squad's rescues. A man is trapped in a truck under live power lines. Doctors treat a boy poisoned by wild hemlock and a girl addicted to drugs. The paramedics rescue a man trapped in a sofa bed, a man whose arm is stuck in a garbage disposal and a man trapped in a bombed building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512220000 +0000" stop="20250512223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry, Please Come Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Col. Henry Blake is transferred to Tokyo and Frank starts imposing military discipline on the camp, the surgeons will do anything to get Henry back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512223000 +0000" stop="20250512230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>I Hate A Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A rash of thefts breaks out in the camp. Missing pieces include Frank's silver picture frame, Margaret's hair brush and Trapper's watch. The camp is searched and everything is found in Hawkeye's locker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512230000 +0000" stop="20250512233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Germ Warfare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye moves a wounded North Korean soldier into The Swamp, rather than let him be shipped out before he's stable. During the night he and Trapper play Dracula, and siphon off a pint of Frank's blood. The soldier then contracts hepatitis, so they have to test Frank without him knowing, and have to keep him away from Margaret and the patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250512233000 +0000" stop="20250513000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye writes home, describing Christmas in Korea: Radar ships a jeep home, a piece at a time; Henry gives the monthly lecture on sex, with the aid of figure A and figure B; Trapper helps deliver a calf; Klinger and Frank get into a fight, but Father Mulcahy smoothes things over; Hawkeye and Trapper sabotage Margaret's tent; Hawkeye flies to the front line dressed as Santa to help a wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513000000 +0000" stop="20250513003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Gets His Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped convict vows revenge on the man who sent him back to prison: none other than Deputy Barney Fife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513003000 +0000" stop="20250513010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sheriff Barney</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets an offer to become the sheriff of Greendale, and Andy tries to discourage him. Unsure how to handle matters, Andy gets the idea to let Barney be sheriff of Mayberry for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513010000 +0000" stop="20250513013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Elly In The Movies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly gets a job at Jed’s movie studio, though Granny and Jane are against it. Both are worried about Elly getting involved in the Hollywood scene. At the studio, Elly meets actor Dash Riprock. He goes for her straight off, unaware that this is the girl he will be starring with, having been told he’ll be opposite the studio owner’s daughter, Miss Clampett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513013000 +0000" stop="20250513020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Says "hey" To The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>In Washington, Gomer gets separated from his tour group and ends up entering the Oval Office and causes no small amount of grief for the Secret Service.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513020000 +0000" stop="20250513023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>German Bridge Is Falling Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The heroes plan to blow up a bridge near camp when a bomber raid fails.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513023000 +0000" stop="20250513030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Movies Are Your Best Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must discover what is contained within the documents of a visiting German general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513030000 +0000" stop="20250513033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Betty White</sub-title>
    <desc>In Pom Pom Girls, Carol and Betty reunite at their high school reunion and sing "Ready to Begin Again". Then, in Mrs. Wiggins, Carol plays a flighty secretary who learns to play blackjack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513033000 +0000" stop="20250513043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Grumbling Grandfather</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Young David Gideon has his head turned by a conniving woman. In his haste to protect her and her supposed good name, the source of her pain turns up dead—namely her estranged husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513043500 +0000" stop="20250513050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Invaders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman in an isolated farmhouse is troubled by the appearance of tiny aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513050500 +0000" stop="20250513053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Remains</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A man tries to hide the murder of his business partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513053500 +0000" stop="20250513060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Ten O'clock Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A seedy character comes up with an amazing formula and then puts it to good use.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513060500 +0000" stop="20250513070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Odds Against Donald Jordan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to find missing building contractor Donald Jordan. He gets poor help from the man's partner, wife and sister. Each offers a different reason for his disappearance. When Jordan reappears, he assures Mannix that he's fine and asks him to drop the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513070500 +0000" stop="20250513080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By The Numbers</sub-title>
    <desc>After a model ends up dead, the man last seen with her hires Cannon. He insists the girl was alive when he left her, so Cannon starts to dig - and turns up quite a collection of motives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513080500 +0000" stop="20250513090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Flight To Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby tracks a pair of heroin dealers who are using unsuspecting flight attendants as couriers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513090000 +0000" stop="20250513093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are convinced that "Brother" William Bentley's Temple of the Expanded Mind is just a sham—a front for Bentley to sell LSD to the students of a nearby elementary school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513093000 +0000" stop="20250513100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513100000 +0000" stop="20250513103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 33 -- It All Happened So Fast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In a behind-the-scenes look at police investigations into deadly force incidents, Reed endures a night of intensive questioning by the station's lieutenant after he kills a man in self-defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513103000 +0000" stop="20250513110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 112 -- You Blew It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The shift starts with the officers talking about another officer's judgment. Little do they realize they will be facing the same problem several times during the shift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513110000 +0000" stop="20250513120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Strange But True...</sub-title>
    <desc>"BIll and Toony discuss strange facts that are surprisingly true."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513120000 +0000" stop="20250513123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Untogetherness</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Cleavers are all excited about their annual summer vacation up to the cabin, that is except Wally. Wanting to be close to his latest girl, Wally wants to stay behind and gets permission to stay at Eddie's house during the two weeks the Cleavers are on vacation, but June and Ward are a bit unsure of Wally's plans."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513123000 +0000" stop="20250513130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Dinner Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally has been constantly spending his time at Julie Foster's house and June suggests that he's old enough to take her out on a dinner date. Julie suggests a new expensive restaurant called The White Fox. However, during the meal Wally discovers that he forgot his wallet at home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513130000 +0000" stop="20250513140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sleepy Slayer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is accused of killing his employer, who still owed him $50,000 for an accident years before, it's up to Mason to find the real killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513140000 +0000" stop="20250513150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cover Girl  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock meets Conrad's new girlfriend, Carla Royce. When Carla's boss is murdered and she is suspected, Matlock defends her against the charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513150000 +0000" stop="20250513160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Woman Much Admired</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie's old flame returns to Sparta to settle some business matters and see Bill. When she is murdered he travels to Gulfport and meets his daughter Lana for the first time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513160000 +0000" stop="20250513170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Visitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Former neighbor, an elderly man comes back to Walton's Mountain to live</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513170000 +0000" stop="20250513173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Carmen</sub-title>
    <desc>"A secret Army payroll is stolen and two soldiers killed. The Major threatens Matt with marshal law if the thieves aren't caught. Matt suspects Jenny Lane, a new girl at the Long Branch of being involved."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513173000 +0000" stop="20250513180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Overland Express</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt and Chester track Nation for a killing in Dodge. Nation kills their horses then gives himself up. They wind up having to take a stage back to Dodge. Nation recognizes a man on the stage and helps Matt prevent a robbery."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513180000 +0000" stop="20250513190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Six Black Horses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Ben's comes to Nevada with money to invest. Ben is initially delighted, but then discovers that his friend stole the money from corrupt New York politicians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513190000 +0000" stop="20250513193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Stand-in</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Two prison wagon drivers stop at the McCain ranch looking for whiskey. Lucas turns them down because they are escorting Rudy Croft, a murderer who is to be hanged in Yuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513193000 +0000" stop="20250513200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Journey Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark goes to work for Will Temple, a badly scarred and very mysterious rancher.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513200000 +0000" stop="20250513210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Sacramento Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>At the end of a long journey, lives were lost. Some made it with their dreams intact. Flint tries to help one of the passengers and almost bites off too much. Politics are involved as well as unsolicited trips to the Far East.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513210000 +0000" stop="20250513220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Dinner Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman almost hits a kid on a bike, who starts choking; she later has an epileptic fit. A man is shot by his father-in-law when he learns his daughter is married and pregnant. Roy tries to set John up with his wife's cousin. Three drug addicts are treated in the hospital: a woman with a gangrenous hand, a poison victim and a man showing signs of tetanus. In the field: an alcoholic, an obese man with a pacemaker, and a child whose arm is caught in a swimming pool drain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513220000 +0000" stop="20250513223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Edwina</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The nurses go to extreme lengths to find a date for Nurse Eddie—they won't go out with anyone until Eddie gets a date. The men draw straws, and Hawkeye is the big loser, especially after Eddie nearly kills him in a scene resembling teenage "mating" rituals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513223000 +0000" stop="20250513230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a Dear John recording from home. Hawkeye and Trapper try to set him up with a date, but fail. Radar is taken by a new nurse at the camp and she is into poetry and music, so they coach him. Margaret wants to stop the relationship, so Hawkeye and Trapper get between her and Frank until she relents. Radar's "Ahhhh, Bach!" and "That's highly significant" quotes win him the girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513230000 +0000" stop="20250513233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tuttle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye creates a fake doctor, Captain Jonathan S. Tuttle, to give supplies to the local orphans. Henry wants Tuttle to be officer of the day, so Hawkeye creates a fake personnel file, and all his back pay is given to the orphanage. When General Clayton wants to reward his generosity, Hawkeye is forced to invent a story about Tuttle jumping from a chopper without his parachute!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250513233000 +0000" stop="20250514000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Ringbanger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper operate on a famous Colonel - after discovering that he is particularly ruthless about sacrificing his men, they come up with a scheme to get him sent back to the states with a little unwitting help from Frank, Margaret, and a drunk Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514000000 +0000" stop="20250514003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Choir</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the awful sound coming from the Mayberry choir is narrowed down to Barney, the members decide they must get rid of him, but no one has the heart to do it. They devise a plan with an allegedly super-sensitive microphone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514003000 +0000" stop="20250514010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Convicts-at-large</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Floyd run out of gas while coming home from a fishing trip. While looking for a telephone they are captured by three female escaped convicts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514010000 +0000" stop="20250514013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Dash Riprock, You Cad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly is disappointed about losing Dash to Miss Jane, so Jed and Drysdale try to fix everything. And Granny is trying to figure out why Dash is going for the plain Miss Jane instead of her gorgeous granddaughter. Another actor, Biff Steel, is set up for Elly, but, once again, he sees Miss Jane and figures she is Miss Clampett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514013000 +0000" stop="20250514020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>And A Child Shall Lead Them</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer and Sgt. Carter try helping a Japanese boy who claims he's lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514020000 +0000" stop="20250514023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Go Light On The Heavy Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a heavy water supply by convincing Klink it is a youth potion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514023000 +0000" stop="20250514030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514030000 +0000" stop="20250514033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Alan King</sub-title>
    <desc>In Rich Lady, Broke Lady, Carol and the gang parody "Rich Man, Poor Man".  Then, in Salute to Warner Brothers, Carol and the gang parody classic movies, including The Fountainhead, They Died with Their Boots On, and Ceiling Zero.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514033000 +0000" stop="20250514043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Guilty Clients</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lola and Jeff Bronson are going through a divorce and can't wait to be rid of each other—until Bill Ryder sabotages Jeff's business and makes a play for Lola. When Ryder is found dead, Jeff and Lola are the two prime suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514043500 +0000" stop="20250514050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For Your Thoughts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gaining telepathic abilities when his coin lands on its edge, a mild-mannered bank clerk learns about the difference between other people's plans and fantasies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514050500 +0000" stop="20250514053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Kerry Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's love for his pet dog leads to disaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514053500 +0000" stop="20250514060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Matched Pearl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A successful jewelry shop owner sells a rare black pearl to a wealthy client.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514060500 +0000" stop="20250514070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Last Rites For Miss Emma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix suspects Floyd Brown of stealing 45 cases of morphine. That's bad news for Peggy because Floyd is her boyfriend. This case almost costs Joe his secretary, and Peggy her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514070500 +0000" stop="20250514080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Mad Man</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is hired to investigate when an Army researcher seems to have gone insane for no obvious reason. Another cry for help comes out of Cannon's past. A girl he once knew is concerned about her husband's -he's a research scientist- fits of irrational behavior. they touch on mind-boggling drugs here, a topical subject."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514080500 +0000" stop="20250514090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Double Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman plots her revenge on the two men who conned her deceased father out of his land rights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514090000 +0000" stop="20250514093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514093000 +0000" stop="20250514100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514100000 +0000" stop="20250514103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 51 -- A Jumper - Code Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have one of those nights where they either have no calls or minor issues they can do nothing about. But at the end of the shift, Malloy must cook up a dangerous solution to a suicide jumper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514103000 +0000" stop="20250514110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 73 -- I'm Still A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While Malloy is attending college, radicals learn he is a cop. They reject him and antagonize him on the job. After helping arrest demonstrators, his new car is vandalized. When a timer is found missing, he locates and disarms a bomb using it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514110000 +0000" stop="20250514120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Sunflower State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore the state of Kansas on their Trekkin' All 50 tour of the United States."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514120000 +0000" stop="20250514123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Football Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is scheduled to receive a football award at a father-son dinner being held in the school gym. While talking with his friends, Beaver learns that none of them are planning on wearing a jacket and a tie so when June and Ward insist that he wear one, he adamantly refuses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514123000 +0000" stop="20250514130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's License</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Now that Wally is 17, he feels it's about time that he get his drivers license. However, June and Ward are a bit apprehensive about the idea of Wally driving, but Wally is persistant and finally gets his parents to agree to let him take a drivers class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514130000 +0000" stop="20250514140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Betrayed Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A recently widowed women becomes tangled in a web of suspicion when she hastily remarries a fortune-hunting Frenchman. When the Frenchman's ex-wife comes looking for him, he turns up shot dead in a swimming pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514140000 +0000" stop="20250514150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cookie Monster  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a cookie mogul is found dead after announcing plans to take over a number of baking companies, Matlock works the defense for another cookie maker suspected in the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514150000 +0000" stop="20250514160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Baby For Sale</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Bubba's cousin adopts a baby her husband is blackmailed by the child's real parents - they want him to help them steal the payroll where he works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514160000 +0000" stop="20250514170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandpa has heart problems. Thinks he is going to die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514170000 +0000" stop="20250514173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Gentleman</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marcus France, a "Gentleman Gambler" comes to Dodge and falls in love with Bonnie Damon. Tiller Evans thinks Bonnie is his girl. Matt has to keep Tiller from killing France."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514173000 +0000" stop="20250514180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Matt For Murder</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt resigns as Marshall after Tom Samples accuses Matt of killing an innocent man. However Doc, Matt and Matt's old friend Wild Bill Hickock come up with a plan that might clear Matt of this erroneous charge of murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514180000 +0000" stop="20250514190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Check Rein</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>An injured rancher enlists the aid of the Cartwrights to buy back one of his horses after his farm is foreclosed. If that's not bad enough, the rancher must also avoid getting killed by his ruthless uncle, who will stop at nothing to gain full control of the ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514190000 +0000" stop="20250514193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Corey Hazlett insists he's innocent of murder, despite Lucas's eyewitness testimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514193000 +0000" stop="20250514200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Knight Errant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to dissuade a latter-day knight from rushing into battle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514200000 +0000" stop="20250514210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Around The Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Planning to sail to Boston, the Major, Hawks and Charlie are instead shanghaied to New Orleans where they meet a Captain who has different ideas on raising his child and running a ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514210000 +0000" stop="20250514220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Musical Mania</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Chet cracks a joke about John playing the squad horn, John takes up the bagpipes, trombone and guitar. Paramedics help a gardener suffering from tetanus. The father of a boy suffering from lead poisoning is reluctant to have it treated. The firemen rescue the driver of an ice cream truck. A schoolgirl dies from an overdose. A glider pilot crash lands. A man working under his house is trapped.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514220000 +0000" stop="20250514223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad, Again</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Once again, Hawkeye writes home to his father, telling him of the latest gossip: the camp gets a new surgeon, who turns out to be a fake; Hawkeye bets he can walk into the mess tent naked for lunch and no one will notice; and Radar cheats on his final exam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514223000 +0000" stop="20250514230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Long-john Flap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp suffers from the severe cold, except for Hawkeye who has received some long johns from his father. They get passed around from person to person as a gift, a gambling stake, a trade, a bribe, stolen and given up to Father Mulcahy, who ends up giving them away.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514230000 +0000" stop="20250514233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Army-navy Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp tunes into the Army/Navy football game, only to be shelled and have an unexploded bomb land in the middle of the compound. They ring around trying to identify the bomb, and the camp prepares for the worst. Hawkeye and Trapper are left the task of following instructions to disarm the bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250514233000 +0000" stop="20250515000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Frank argue over Frank's surgical ability. Hawkeye performs a difficult operation and the patient does not recover as he should. Hawkeye begins to doubt his ability and moves out of The Swamp. He decides to open up his patients again, and discovers a nick in the colon that even Frank admits anyone could have missed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515000000 +0000" stop="20250515003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to convince everyone of a lack of security at Mayberry Bank, and is furious that no one listens to him. Taking matters into his own hands, he ends up stuck in the bank vault.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515003000 +0000" stop="20250515010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's First Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney uses his life savings of $300 to buy a car, which almost immediately begins to break down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515010000 +0000" stop="20250515013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett A-go-go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing Elly May in a bathing suit, hippie Sheldon Epps crashes his car. When the Clampetts see this, they take him inside their house in case he is injured. He is healthy, but sticks around for Elly, driving Dash Riprock off.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515013000 +0000" stop="20250515020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Baby In The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee is thrilled to babysit her niece's infant, but the baby seems bothered by Aunt Bee—going ballistic every time she picks her up!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515020000 +0000" stop="20250515023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happiness Is A Warm Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Klink finds Sergeant Schultz drunk he gets a tough new replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515023000 +0000" stop="20250515030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Scientist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau pretends to be a famous French scientist who is visiting camp while Hogan smuggles the real one out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515030000 +0000" stop="20250515033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pickups, The /  Beauty And The Shrimp / Mrs. Wiggins</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Pickups, Harvey and Tim try to woo two wanna-be actresses. Then, in Beauty and the Stump, Tim complains about everything. Finally, in Mrs. Wiggins, Carol covers for her boss by lying to his wife, only she turns his night out with the boys into a night out with the girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515033000 +0000" stop="20250515043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Jealous Journalist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The drowning death of a newspaper executive during a fishing trip sets off all kinds of repercussions at the newspaper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515043500 +0000" stop="20250515050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flight 33</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A commercial aircraft mysteriously travels back through time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515050500 +0000" stop="20250515053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Most Likely To Succeed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Two old college friends meet again after a long separation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515053500 +0000" stop="20250515060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Victim Four</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband searches desperately for his wife in a neighborhood where numerous murders have been committed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515060500 +0000" stop="20250515070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Solid Gold Web</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaper publisher John Randolph asks Mannix to learn why his daughter is acting so strangely. Mannix discovers she may have killed a mobster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515070500 +0000" stop="20250515080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A private detective investigates the murder of his ex-girlfriend's husband and gets entangled in small-town corruption."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515080500 +0000" stop="20250515090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must vindicate a doctor accused of murder by a girl subject to hallucinations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515090000 +0000" stop="20250515093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515093000 +0000" stop="20250515100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515100000 +0000" stop="20250515103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 102 -- We Can't Just Walk Away From It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to a call about a drug overdose and track the drugs to a 17-year-old who has barricaded himself in his room with a gun and threatens kill himself. They contend with a distraught mother and an overbearing father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515103000 +0000" stop="20250515110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 152 -- A Dead Cop Can't Help Anyone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to shield an impressionable Reed from Officer Ed Wells, a shoot-first-ask-questions-later style officer. Wells' reckless philosophy endangers his own safety when he responds to a sniper, forcing them to come to his rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515110000 +0000" stop="20250515120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Stuntman Bill</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515120000 +0000" stop="20250515123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his heart set on taking a swing at being a paper boy again but another kid beats him to it. This leads Beaver to think about using sabatoge to get the new paper boy fired. However, the boy may just do that himself when the service becomes terrible leading Beaver to confront him only to discover he is a she.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515123000 +0000" stop="20250515130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Double Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's new girlfriend, Carolyn, can't go out to the movies on Saturday night because she has to watch her little sister, Susan. Carolyn suggests that Beaver take Susan out to the movies and that they all double date. Not wanting to let Wally down, Beaver decides to go along, despite being nervous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515130000 +0000" stop="20250515140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Nautical Knot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is summoned when Harvey Scott's efforts to retain temporary control of the family mining company lead to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515140000 +0000" stop="20250515150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Brothers  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a plastic surgeon is found dead after an argument with his partner about dissolving the business, the business partner is the immediate suspect, until Matlock meets the man's twin brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515150000 +0000" stop="20250515160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Obsession</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A flirtatious schoolteacher is stalked by a madman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515160000 +0000" stop="20250515170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Lie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben secretly borrows John Boy's car and gets both into trouble</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515170000 +0000" stop="20250515173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <desc>"After a young man is shot in the back, people think it was young Fly Hoyt. Holly Fanshaw was the only person who saw the murder happen and she tells Matt that Fly Hoyt committed the murder The Older Brother (Joe Thorp)vows revenge for the murder of his Brother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515173000 +0000" stop="20250515180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Gunsmuggler</sub-title>
    <desc>"When renegade Pawnee Indians attack some local ranchers, Matt and Major Evans think that white gunrunners supplied the Renegades the rifles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515180000 +0000" stop="20250515190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Justice Deferred</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An anguished Hoss discovers that his testimony helped hang an innocent man accused of murder. As he struggles to bring the real killer to justice, Hoss must also combat the cowardice of another witness and the jury foreman, an influential banker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515190000 +0000" stop="20250515193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Honest Abe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Able Lincoln's claim that he's the Great Emancipator himself amuses everyone except Matt Yorty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515193000 +0000" stop="20250515200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Long Goodbye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Stubborn Grandpa Fogarty is Lucas's main roadblock as he tries to get young Woody Fogarty to attend school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515200000 +0000" stop="20250515210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Juan Ortega Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Juan awakens to the sound of three men hanging his beloved father. Joining the wagon train, he comes across one of the three, tortured by Indians. He nurses him back to health but only under the guise of looking for the other two killers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515210000 +0000" stop="20250515220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Helpful</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy has an argument with his wife and Johnny tries to help. The firemen rescue a man from precarious auto wreck. A brilliant doctor's erratic behavior causes concern at the hospital. Doctors diagnose a woman's heart condition. Paramedics rescue a dog from a roof and two children lost in a rapidly flooding storm drain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515220000 +0000" stop="20250515223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Fred C. Dobbs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's normal drone of verbal abuse upsets Ginger, so Hawkeye puts his arm in a cast while he is asleep. Frank puts in for a transfer, and after Franks tells Margaret he's leaving, she decides to leave as well. As a result, Col. Blake puts both Hawk and Trap on double post-op duty until he finds replacements for Majs. Burns and Houlihan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515223000 +0000" stop="20250515230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Cease-fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>General Clayton calls to say that a ceasefire is to be declared. The camp celebrates, Klinger gives away his dresses and locals start to take pieces of the camp. But Trapper does not believe it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515230000 +0000" stop="20250515233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Showtime</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Kaplan is to be shipped home, but becomes paranoid that something will happen to him before he leaves. He takes the wheel of the jeep to drive to Kimpo himself, but crashes and ends up in plaster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250515233000 +0000" stop="20250516000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Divided We Stand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Brought on by Frank and Margaret's negative reports, General Clayton assigns a psychiatrist, Captain Hildebrand, to examine the 4077th M*A*S*H unit to see if it should be disbanded. Henry tells them to be on their best behavior, or else they will be split up. But the 4077th soon begins to act in their traditional, insane way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516000000 +0000" stop="20250516003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Big House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When the state police leave two captured bank robbers in the custody of the Mayberry police department overnight, Barney is determined to show the prisoners that the Mayberry jail is as good as any other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516003000 +0000" stop="20250516010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Black Day For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are to protect a shipment of gold passing through Mayberry. It's critical that they keep it a secret, but Barney spills the beans immediately and soon all the town knows.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516010000 +0000" stop="20250516013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Granny's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale sets Granny up with an older man on the Board of Directors, a playboy who dates young, attractive women. Mr. Cavanaugh meets Granny and is not pleased with what he sees. And Cavanaugh’s original date for the night, who is described as his "dear, sweet old aunt" is set up with Jed. Of course, this “Aunt Phyllis” is no older woman; she's a young, glamorous girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516013000 +0000" stop="20250516020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Better Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Ann's father comes to town along with her ex-fiancé, and they both set about trying to persuade her to give up on Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516020000 +0000" stop="20250516023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Hofbrau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan visits a local Hofbrau to get the plans to a German army division that is camping out nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516023000 +0000" stop="20250516030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Oil For The Lamps Of Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that there is oil underneath the camp in order to discourage the Germans from building a synthetic fuel plant there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516030000 +0000" stop="20250516033000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Oldest Man, the only person to help fight an airport epidemic is the Oldest Man. Then, in The Guardians, Carol and Steve fake an argument so they won't be named the guardians of their friends' kids.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516033000 +0000" stop="20250516043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impatient Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Paint manufacturer Amory Fallon suspects that his partner, Ned Thompson, is behind a mysterious fire and explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516043500 +0000" stop="20250516050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Dingle, The Strong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Martians give Luther Dingle the strength of 300 men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516050500 +0000" stop="20250516053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Golden Opportunity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to leave his wife takes a turn he didn't foresee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516053500 +0000" stop="20250516060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Twelve Hour Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A meek clerk plots with his companions to rob the investment firm for which he works.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516060500 +0000" stop="20250516070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Merry Go Round For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>The demolition of a boarding school reveals old evil: a corpse linked to a missing quarter of a million dollars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516070500 +0000" stop="20250516080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A private detective investigates the murder of his ex-girlfriend's husband and gets entangled in small-town corruption."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516080500 +0000" stop="20250516090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Beware The Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog is the prime suspect in the fatal mauling of a man whose stepson is the dog's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516090000 +0000" stop="20250516093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516093000 +0000" stop="20250516100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516100000 +0000" stop="20250516103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 12: He – He Was Trying To Kill Me</sub-title>
    <desc>"Malloy and Reed investigate a case of child neglect."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516103000 +0000" stop="20250516110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 172 -- Boy...the Things You Do For The Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After Malloy gives a gorgeous wealthy blonde a traffic ticket, she stalks him, affecting him and the police force. Although uninterested in her, Malloy is forced to "take one" for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516110000 +0000" stop="20250516120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Flashback To 2005</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516120000 +0000" stop="20250516123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie, The Businessman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and Eddie get jobs at the Mayfield Dairy thanks to Ward pulling some strings. They soon unknowingly find themselves involved in a plot started by the foreman and his assistant, who are secretly stealing the merchandise. When Ward learns of the plot, he warns Wally who in turn tries to warn Eddie, but Eddie doesn't buy it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516123000 +0000" stop="20250516130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It To Ella</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After coming home late on a school night, Ward and June punish Beaver by not allowing him to go anywhere on school nights. Beaver feels the punishment is unfair, so Eddie suggests Beaver write to an advice column.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516130000 +0000" stop="20250516140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Bullied Bowler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After a struggling bowling alley is shut down at the insistence of a domineering townswoman, a doctor involved in the closure is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516140000 +0000" stop="20250516150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Accident  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When one of two partners at a law firm is murdered after he is unable to keep a promise to a client, the other attorney is suspected.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516150000 +0000" stop="20250516160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Liar's Poker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A game of high stakes poker ends in murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516160000 +0000" stop="20250516170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Matchmakers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Cora Beth joins the series and marries Ike</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516170000 +0000" stop="20250516173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Monopoly</sub-title>
    <desc>"A stranger by the name of Ivy comes to Dodge and proceeds to buy up all the local freight lines. Old Joe Trimble refuses to sell and soon afterwards his home is set on fire. Trimble's wife dies in the fire."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516173000 +0000" stop="20250516180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Matt is forced to serve an eviction notice on farmer Brandon Teek, Matt tries every way he can to help the farmer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516180000 +0000" stop="20250516190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Detector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss is sure there's gold in an old mine he wants to buy, and has the gold detector to prove it. However, things are not what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516190000 +0000" stop="20250516193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Shattered Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark meet Mark Twain and find out that he hides a sad secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516193000 +0000" stop="20250516200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Long Gun From Tucson</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to stop embittered John Holliver from venting his wrath on the people who expelled him from town years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516200000 +0000" stop="20250516210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jennifer Churchill Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jennifer Churchill, pampered all her life, runs away from a smothering lifestyle and pending marriage to join the wagon train. With bounty hunters on her heels, she finds Flint, a man who she wants but doesn't want her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516210000 +0000" stop="20250516220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Drivers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>John gets bugged by other people's bad driving habits. A college quarterback experiences back pain. Roy and John's former paramedic instructor dies, while Roy and John themselves teach a CPR class. A boy gets stuck inside a tree. A fire at a hotel is complicated by a cardiac victim on the third floor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516220000 +0000" stop="20250516223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>5 O'clock Charlie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>An inept North Korean pilot, known as 5 O'Clock Charlie, makes his daily attempt to bomb the ammo dump. Frank puts in a request for an anti-aircraft gun, which is granted when Charlie hits General Clayton's jeep. Frank takes charge of the gun, while Hawkeye and Trapper are determined to prevent him from using it, by getting rid of the ammo dump. Frank misses Charlie and destroys the dump.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516223000 +0000" stop="20250516230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Radar's Report</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar writes the weekly activity report: Hawkeye operates on a wounded prisoner who grabs a scalpel and attacks the doctors. Frank wants Klinger thrown out on a section 8, so Henry calls in a psychiatrist, Major Freedman. Hawkeye is attracted to a new nurse but thinks she is married. Trapper loses a patient who developed complications during the O.R. fracas with the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516230000 +0000" stop="20250516233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For The Good Of The Outfit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper want the army to admit responsibility for the accidental bombing of a local village. They fill out a report and Major Stoner arrives to investigate, and leaves with all the evidence. When the story is released it claims that the enemy bombed the village, and the army tries to gag the doctors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250516233000 +0000" stop="20250517000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Pierce And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye has been in non-stop surgery for three straight days without sleep, and the wounded keep coming. He decides to find out who started the war, and sends a telegram to Harry S Truman. After listening to some of Frank's rubbish about the North Koreans wanting better plumbing, he tries to send the officers' latrine to the North Koreans with an offer of peace.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517000000 +0000" stop="20250517003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Sidecar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney comes back from a police auction with a motorcycle and sidecar. After he upsets the whole town with the conveyance, Andy has to find a way to convince Barney to give up the bike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517003000 +0000" stop="20250517010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Shoplifters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Weaver's Department store is being robbed, presumably by shoplifters. Barney poses as a mannequin to catch a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517010000 +0000" stop="20250517013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed's Temptation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>It is the day after Jed spent the night dancing with Phyllis, and he is stiff from all the dancing. Granny is throwing her “I told you sos” at him. And when Phyllis invites him to the horse races, he accepts. When Drysdale and Jane learn of the type of woman she is, they warn Granny and drive her down to the racetrack to stop them. Meanwhile, at the racetrack, Jed and Phyllis are finding great success, because Jed can tell which horse will win.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517013000 +0000" stop="20250517020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>To Watch A Thief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter puts a down payment on a watch for Miss Bunny at the PX, but Gomer mistakenly thinks he has stolen it and returns the watch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517020000 +0000" stop="20250517023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reservations Are Required</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan tries to arrange the unscheduled escape of 20 men, his mission is complicated when a captured sergeant jumps the gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517023000 +0000" stop="20250517030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Anchors Aweigh, Men Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men are tasked with getting an escaped prisoner and smuggled German gun sight to England. To accomplish this Hogan convinces Klink that he is fatigued and should have an officer's club in which to relax.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517030000 +0000" stop="20250517033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Juliet Prowse And Martha Raye</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Juliet Prowse and Martha Raye. Originally aired on 11/20/67."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517033000 +0000" stop="20250517043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Moth-eaten Mink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Restaurateur Morey Allen, a friend of Mason and Della's, contacts Mason after his waitress, Dixie Dayton, is struck by a car while fleeing the restaurant after spotting a man stalking her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517043500 +0000" stop="20250517050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Prime Mover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man discovers that his business partner has the ability to control objects with his mind, the pair head to Vegas to win big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517050500 +0000" stop="20250517053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Children Of Alda Nuova</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A man disappears while visiting little-known tourist attractions in Italy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517053500 +0000" stop="20250517060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>First Class Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E34</episode-num>
    <desc>A man makes a deal with a friend to keep from having to pay his wife alimony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517060500 +0000" stop="20250517070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Rabbit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix accuses a man of murder, but the accused maintains that the death was an accident and that the dead man owed him money. The status of the victim's family complicates Mannix's investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517070500 +0000" stop="20250517080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Salinas Jackpot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon is called in to investigate a robbery and murder of six people at a rodeo. The police had come up with nothing after six weeks except for the knowledge that there was a film taken of the rodeo at the day of the crime. Cannon believes that there is a possibility that the rodeo clowns may have played a part in the crime and must now learn where the clown suit came from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517080500 +0000" stop="20250517090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Relations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to replace a detective who was murdered while looking for a woman's biological mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250517090000 +0000" stop="20250517093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Hooterville Flivverball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Jo plans to use Orville Miggs' Flivver to power his own railroad and bankrupt the Hooterville Cannonball.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
