<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906140000 +0000" stop="20250906150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Kraken</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating why fishing had been prohibited on local waters, agents James West and Artemus Gordon are attacked by a rough bunch of sailors. After the melee, Lt. Bartlett is killed, apparently the victim of some sort of tentacled sea creature. West joins a resolute fisherman on his boat and are attacked by a giant squid. But things are not what they appear as an even more insidious threat is revealed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906150000 +0000" stop="20250906170000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke II: The Last Apache</title>
    <desc>"Matt Dillon goes after a renegade Apache named Wolf (Joe Lara) who has taken his daughter captive. As a bargaining chip, Dillon helps two sons of Apache chief Geronimo out of the fort stockade and offers them in trade. Dillon is aided by an Army scout, Chalk Brighton"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906170000 +0000" stop="20250906180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Decision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Disturbed over being forced to kill a prisoner who was trying to save his life, Matt Dillion turns in his badge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906180000 +0000" stop="20250906190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Desperado</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A fugitive black man holds Hoss hostage—and has no problems killing a white man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906190000 +0000" stop="20250906193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906193000 +0000" stop="20250906200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906200000 +0000" stop="20250906210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserters' Patrol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When an indian tribe wants to trade six soldiers they hold in exchange for their chief, Favor is commissioned as a captain to make the trade.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906210000 +0000" stop="20250906213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The O'hare Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Hired to prevent the construction of a dam that would imperil a town's water supply, Paladin finds that he sympathizes more with the Irish engineer who's trying to build it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906213000 +0000" stop="20250906220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>No Trail Back</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe Hooker, after raiding a bank on behalf of his brother, Ben, is bitten by a dog with rabies. Upon learning this, the sheriff ends his pursuit. Josh, however, decides to go after Hooker anyway.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906220000 +0000" stop="20250907000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Heavenly Daze, Malice In The Palace, Fling In The Ring, Musty Musketeers, Gypped In The Penthouse, Three Hams On Rye</sub-title>
    <desc>"A divine comedy classic! Shemp goes to Heaven but isn't allowed through the Pearly Gates until he can reform bad boys Larry and Moe.  , "Set in a desert land where the stooges run a restaurant, the boys set out to recover the stolen Rootin Tootin diamond after they learn from the thieves that the Emir of Shmo has absconded with the contraband jewel. They journey to the stronghold of Shmo where they disguise as Santa Clauses and scare the ruler into giving them the diamond. 
" , The Stooges are stagehands who also have small parts in a big play.  They quickly get on the bad side of the producer.  First they fail to prevent a famous critic from sneaking into the audience.  Then Shemp accidentally adds a potholder into a cake they bake as a prop.  During the play the Stooges (as southern gentlemen) and the rest of the cast spit up feathers during what was supposed to be a serious scene.  The critic thinks it's a hilarious satire and the boys are redeemed , The Stooges are the trainers of "Chopper", a beefy boxer, and they bet their bankroll on Chopper to win his next fight.  When "Big Mike", their boss, tells them to have Chopper lose or they'll lose their lives, the boys try to soften up Chopper so he'll lose.  The fight gets canceled and the Stooges have to contend with an angry Big Mike and his goons. , Set in the middle ages, the Stooges wish to marry their sweethearts, but the King won't give his consent until Princess Alicia gets married.  The princess is abducted by Mergatroyd, an evil magician who plans to marry her and become ruler of the country.  The Stooges help the princess escape and then defeat the magician and his henchmen in a sword fight , Larry and Shemp reminisce about their experiences with Jean, a diamond crazy gold digger each of them was gypped by.  After telling their stories, they have a run in with Moe, who is now married to the same women.  When Jean shows up, they deliver some stooge-style revenge. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907000000 +0000" stop="20250907023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Creature Walks Among Us</sub-title>
    <desc>"This is the final installment in Universal's uneven "Gill Man trilogy," which began with Creature From the Black Lagoon and was followed by Revenge of the Creature, is the least interesting of the bunch. The story finds the prehistoric amphibian far from his Amazon home, kept under close scientific scrutiny in a special facility in Florida. After a laboratory fire severely damages the creature's gills, the head of the research team (Jeff Morrow) initiates an operation that will allow their subject to breathe through a set of latent lungs. After some attempts are made to acclimate the creature to life among human beings, Morrow's plans are destroyed by his own pettiness when one of his colleagues (Gregg Palmer) makes romantic overtures toward his wife, leading to a violent confrontation that leaves the creature badly injured. Alone in alien territory, the Gill Man resolutely shuffles off into the sea — presumably to commit suicide, since he no longer possesses the ability to breathe underwater. This disappointing conclusion to the series makes little use of the 3-D thrills that enlivened the original and forsakes the opportunity to present a literal fish-out-of-water story in favor of hackneyed melodrama. Champion diver Ricou Browning again portrays the creature in the underwater sequences, with Don Megowan donning the gill-less Gill Man suit on land. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907023000 +0000" stop="20250907030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Not Yet, He Ain't</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Batman and Robin turn the tables on the Penguin by faking their own deaths in order to foil his evil plot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907030000 +0000" stop="20250907040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Menagerie, The (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Spock kidnaps his former captain, the crippled Christopher Pike, and heads for a quarantined planet, putting his career and Kirk's life on the line."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907040000 +0000" stop="20250907043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Topsy Turvy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man invents a machine that gives people the illusion of being turned completely upside down. The device falls into the hands of a crook who uses it to rob a bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907043000 +0000" stop="20250907050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Jimmy The Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Clark gets evidence against a gang of phony investment operators who hire Jimmy Olsen's double for Jimmy to break into the Daily Planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907050000 +0000" stop="20250907060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>One Of Our Dogs Is Missing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While the men are out installing communications equipment, a creepy creature stalks the Robinson women; however, they think a small dog is to blame for raids on food and other mischief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907060000 +0000" stop="20250907070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Phantom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>The phantom returns from the dead in a renewed attempt to capture Commander Crane's body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907070000 +0000" stop="20250907080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Giants And All That Jazz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A down-and-put trumpet player is in trouble with crooks, and a sympathetic Dan offers him a way out by teaching him Earth-style jazz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907080000 +0000" stop="20250907090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Kill Two By Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are hunted by two officers on a Japanese-held island in 1945.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907090000 +0000" stop="20250907100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Labyrinth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent discovers an unconscious alien, but the invaders try to stop an X-ray from happening.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907100000 +0000" stop="20250907110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Unholy Beast</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jack sees an unfamiliar four legged beast and asks Adams's help to figure out what it is. Nakoma has also seen it but a member of his tribe wants to kill it,thinking it's an evil spirit."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907110000 +0000" stop="20250907113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bundu Rescue</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go on a thrilling adventure in South Africa to catch lions, hippos and elephants for scientific and conservation purposes."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907113000 +0000" stop="20250907120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Raccoon Valley</sub-title>
    <desc>"With Marlin and Jim you follow the raccoon family in their adventures in a remote valley amid the scenic splendor of southern Utah."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907120000 +0000" stop="20250907123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Where The Crocodile Is King</sub-title>
    <desc>"To Marlin and Jim, Africa’s waters mean the chance to film the most exciting dramas and most unusual animals ever captured by the camera.  Crocodiles are among the largest reptiles in the world and the most feared!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907123000 +0000" stop="20250907130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>El Tigre</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the hostile mountains and deserts of Mexico roams one of the world’s most beautiful and dangerous cats…El Tigre the jaguar. Marlin and Jim track this predator through miles of inhospitable terrain."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907130000 +0000" stop="20250907133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Survival Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to every corner of the globe to capture and tag wild animals to be studied and for conservation purposes.  Some are taken to restock old ranges, others moved to new ranges where they will have a better chance to survive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907133000 +0000" stop="20250907140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Expedition Geronimo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin, Jim and the crew of Marineland of the Pacific’s capture ship “Geronimo “ sail the seas in search of the strangest underwater creatures and Marlin battles a ten-foot octopus at the bottom of the Pacific Ocean."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907140000 +0000" stop="20250907143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Tiger, Tiger!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobby briefly leaves Tiger unattended and returns to find him missing. Soon there's a citywide search to track him down. Meanwhile, a string of burglaries in the neighborhood has worried.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907143000 +0000" stop="20250907150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Sprain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol is out of town visiting her sick aunt when Alice sprains her ankle, leaving Mike and the kids to fend for themselves. Meanwhile, Alice's boyfriend Sam wonders whether or not he should take someone else to the upcoming Meatcutters' Ball.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907150000 +0000" stop="20250907153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At The Circus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>In an attempt to get Ashley's young daughter, Heather, to warm up to him, Fonzie takes her to the circus. Meanwhile, K. C., Howard's niece, moves in with Howard and Marion while her parents look for a new boarding school. Marion asks Howard to consider letting her stay permanently.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907153000 +0000" stop="20250907160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Fire Show</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After putting out a fire at the apartment, one of the responding firemen falls for Laverne. Soon Shirley finds herself having a crush on the firefighter, and the girls' friendship is put to the test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907160000 +0000" stop="20250907163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's First Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney uses his life savings of $300 to buy a car, which almost immediately begins to break down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907163000 +0000" stop="20250907170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Visits Grauman's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>With only a week left in Hollywood, Lucy weeps about her lack of souvenirs. Her collection already includes a tin can run over by Cary Grant's rear tire, a napkin boasting Lana Turner's lip-prints and a few other goodies. But when Lucy discovers that John Wayne's cement footprints at Grauman's Chinese Theater are loose, she and Ethel scheme to pry them out of the ground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907170000 +0000" stop="20250907173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Cat Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange cat appears at the Cleaver's door and Beaver takes it in and feeds it. However, when the owner is found, and the cat is returned, Beaver finds himself with a dilemma: The cat keeps coming back!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907173000 +0000" stop="20250907180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Weekend Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets a job at the ice cream parlor leaving a gaggle of girls swooning and Eddie and Lumpy feeling neglected. So to get back at him, Eddie and Lumpy concoct a plan of revenge that involves Mary Ellen Roger's slumber party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907180000 +0000" stop="20250907183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Shorty To The Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny has come up with a new way to split Elly and Mark up and has called Shorty Kellems to help her do so. When Shorty arrives, she tells Mark that Shorty used to be Elly’s fiancé and wants revenge on Mark, but her story fails. At this time, Drysdale is trying to tell Jed that oceanography is a bad idea, but doesn’t succeed and ends up saying Miss Jane said it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907183000 +0000" stop="20250907190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To The Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny still believes Mark can turn people into water critters and turned Shorty into a seal. She gets the frogman to turn him back and continues to try to break up Elly May and Mark by having Elly cook for Mark. Meanwhile, Drysdale tries to keep Jed from withdrawing his money from the bank for oceanography research, this time dressing up as Napoleon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907190000 +0000" stop="20250907193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Erika Tiffany Smith To The Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Erika Tiffany Smith lands on the island looking for a place to start a new resort, and find a new husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907193000 +0000" stop="20250907200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Not Guilty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A crate containing coconuts is wrapped in an old Honolulu newspaper that says one of the castaways is being sought in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907200000 +0000" stop="20250907203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>And Mama Makes Three  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Naomi and Vint decide to adopt a child. But when they—and Mama—meet with an adoption counselor, they are rejected by the adoption agency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907203000 +0000" stop="20250907210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama's Medicine Show  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Hoping to raise money now that a baby is on the way, Naomi and Vint begin selling Mama's homemade tonic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907210000 +0000" stop="20250907220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Doc Takes The Fifth / Safety Last / A Business Affair</sub-title>
    <desc>"Doc arrives back from holidays and introduces his new wife of a couple of hours to the crew. Don Adams is a Safety Investigator on holidays but finds danger around every corner on board the ship. The president of a financial group comes aboard to talk his female VP out of resigning due to untrue rumors about them having an affair."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907220000 +0000" stop="20250907223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Rivals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie has his first crush, who ignores him. Barney steps in and tries to give him advice about women, which leads to Opie developing a crush on Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907223000 +0000" stop="20250907230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Pingel- Charlie's Angels</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the city of angels, writer, actor, and publicist Mike Pingel has immersed himself in the world of Charlie’s Angels. When the show made its debut in 1976, it was an instant smash hit, and a young Mike was among the legions of fans. So much so that he started collecting magazines, toys, and other memorabilia, a collection that now consists of more than 2,000 items. He then moved to Los Angeles and created a newsletter called Angelic Heaven. He was determined to meet the Angels, and he did. Mike later launched charliesangels.com, took part in Farrah Fawcett’s reality series Chasing Farrah, and served as her personal assistant from 2005-2007. He walks our pop culture expert and art historian Jennifer Klein through his heavenly collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907230000 +0000" stop="20250907233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fallen Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar wants to become a man so Hawkeye recommends he goes to Seoul. On his way there he is hit by a mine. Hawkeye performs surgery on him. After surgery, Hawkeye goes to the Officers Club where he gets hammered. The next day he goes to surgery severely hung over. Radar tells Hawkeye he is disappointed in him. Hawkeye explodes and is then yelled at by Major Houlihan, Colonel Potter and Father Mulcahy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250907233000 +0000" stop="20250908000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Last Laugh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Madness strikes as B.J. and his old friend, Bardonaro, play a series of practical jokes on each other, just as Bardonaro is about to leave Korea. Hawkeye gets the last laugh. He sends Bardonaro off without his traveling papers, and in a jeep with too little gas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908000000 +0000" stop="20250908003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie And The Quiz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie feels the weight of his own mortality after a magazine quiz on life expectancy gives him another seven years - tops.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908003000 +0000" stop="20250908010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is reunited with her childhood sweetheart when she returns to her hometown for a wedding</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908010000 +0000" stop="20250908013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>No Smoking</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunker house is locked in a battle of wills after Mike vows he can go without food longer than Archie can abstain from smoking.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908013000 +0000" stop="20250908020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mike Makes His Move</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After a fruitless seach for new lodgings, Mike and Gloria agree to rent George Jefferson's old house-even though it means living next door to Archie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908020000 +0000" stop="20250908023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Garry Moore And Durward Kirby</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Garry Moore and Durward Kirby. Originally aired on 12/15/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908023000 +0000" stop="20250908030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nancy Wilson And Donald O'connor</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nancy Wilson and Donald O'Connor. Originally aired on 12/29/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908030000 +0000" stop="20250908033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Gunslinger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>While Rob is under anesthesia, he dreams of being in a Western.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908033000 +0000" stop="20250908040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Last Chapter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob finally finishes the manuscript for his book, and his publisher hates it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908040000 +0000" stop="20250908043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Better Living Through Televison</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton go on T.V. to sell a kitchen utensil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908043000 +0000" stop="20250908053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>On Thursday We Leave For Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man named Benteen leads a colony of Americans stranded on a desert planet for 30 years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908053000 +0000" stop="20250908060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Not The Running Type</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A man has an interesting way of making a small fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908060000 +0000" stop="20250908070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Catafalque</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>In one of the IMF team's most audacious plans yet, they blatantly frame their victim and attempt to snatch the body of a deceased leader literally from under the noses of the honor guards. It's all part of Jim's plan to infuriate an official into revealing a sensitive document the U.S. government wants to get its hands on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908070000 +0000" stop="20250908080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Runner In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman calls the police after she recognizes Kimble's picture on a TV quiz show and in the ensuing manhunt, Kimble hides out in a home for the blind. Kimble becomes acquainted with some of the residents, including the attractive Claire Whittaker, whom he</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908080000 +0000" stop="20250908090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Mister Five And Dime</sub-title>
    <desc>"When young criminologist Lester Hodges gets a frantic telephone call from a female classmate who has been arrested for passing counterfeit money, he recruits his friend Harry Orwell to help him solve the case."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908090000 +0000" stop="20250908093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908093000 +0000" stop="20250908100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908100000 +0000" stop="20250908103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 61: The Runaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Walters and Brinkman are on a roll lately and like to brag, much to the irritation of Reed. He and Malloy help them out by finishing one of their calls, then rescue a sick teenage girl and arrest the young man who took her in. Back on patrol, they meet an informant who gives them a tip on a big drug buy scheduled for 11 PM. They give the info to Sgt. Miller who asks them to help in the bust.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908103000 +0000" stop="20250908110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 122 Christmas: The Yellow Dump Truck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>On Christmas Eve, Reed and Malloy make rounds distributing police department donation packages to needy families, and pull many heartstrings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908110000 +0000" stop="20250908120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Septembers Of Our Past</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony reflect on nostalgic memories of the transitional month."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908120000 +0000" stop="20250908123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Drive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Beaver and Gilbert are pretending to go for a drive in Ward's car, Beaver accidentally releases the parking brake, causing the car to roll down the driveway and into the street, backing up traffic. Wally steps in and drives the car back in the driveway and clears up the traffic mess, but he soon finds himself being issued a citation for driving without a license.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908123000 +0000" stop="20250908130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Big Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's school is having an exchange dance and Wally and Eddie must take girls from a rival school that they chose out of a hat. Eddie asks to trade with Wally and he agrees, like a shot, after seeing the picture of Eddie's intended in a yearbook. Suspicious, Wally soon quickly discovers why Eddie wanted to trade; the girl is a few inches taller than Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908130000 +0000" stop="20250908140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Daring Decoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Daniel Conway is involved in a vicious proxy war with Warner Griffith for control of an oil company. Conway's secretary, Rose Calvert, is spying for Griffith. When Rose is found dead, Conway fears he's being framed for murder and approaches Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908140000 +0000" stop="20250908150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Victim  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock tries to prove that someone other than his client had a motive in a murder case. His best bet? The victim's paraplegic husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908150000 +0000" stop="20250908160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Trip Upstate</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>In this thought provoking episode. Gillespie is surprised when a man he arrested asks to see him on the eve of his execution. He must confront his feelings about the death penalty when the prisoner asks him to witness his death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908160000 +0000" stop="20250908170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Return - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to Walton's Mountain to write about the failing economy and lack of jobs</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908170000 +0000" stop="20250908180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Gallows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt is certain that the convicted murderer he's taking to the gallows is innocent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908180000 +0000" stop="20250908190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Reluctant American</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the property of an English holding group shows little profit, the owners come from England to Nevada to see exactly why.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908190000 +0000" stop="20250908193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908193000 +0000" stop="20250908200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Assailants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An assassination plot unfolds as four gunmen disguised as cavalrymen enter North Fork. Their target: Sen. Jim Borden. Their weapon: a Gatling gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908200000 +0000" stop="20250908210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Nancy Palmer Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A married couple use the wife's innocent face and winning way with children to gain the trust of their companions on the wagon train so that they won't be suspected when the husband pulls off a bank robbery nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908210000 +0000" stop="20250908220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Captain Hook</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The firemen plan to celebrate the imminent retirement of a martinet captain with a party, under the guise of throwing a farewell dinner. A model in a bear suit suffers from heat stroke during a promotion stunt. A bizarre family believes their sleeping mother is dead. The firemen rescue CHP officers from a helicopter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908220000 +0000" stop="20250908223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>War Of Nerves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th, caught up in tension and nerves, creates a bonfire to release their pressure. Meanwhile, Sidney Freedman is depressed over a young soldier who blames him for his injuries, because Freedman had sent him back into combat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908223000 +0000" stop="20250908230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Winchester Tapes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye tries unsuccessfully to get to Seoul, to see Nurse Gilmore for the weekend. Meanwhile, Winchester has taped a letter home, asking for his influential parents to help get him back to the States. To get even, Hawkeye and B.J. switch Winchester's clothes, causing Winchester to alter his eating patterns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908230000 +0000" stop="20250908233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Light That Failed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>With supplies low, the 4077th gets a truckload of ice cream churns and salt tablets. But what it needs are light bulbs, and in the dimly lit post-op Charles makes an error for which he draws the ultimate wrath of his two surgeon bunkmates. Meanwhile, B.J. receives a mystery novel that everyone in camp reads in turn. The last page is missing and the solution to the mystery is undiscovered until B.J. calls the author by long distance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250908233000 +0000" stop="20250909000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>In Love And War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye falls in love with Kyong Soon, a Korean woman who is caring for her sick mother and orphaned children. But all hope is lost as Kyong takes her possessions and the children to the south after her mother has died.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909000000 +0000" stop="20250909003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Wife For Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney believes that Andy should be getting married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909003000 +0000" stop="20250909010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Dogs, Dogs, Dogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Visiting officials take pause when they visit Mayberry and find that the courthouse is full of dogs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909010000 +0000" stop="20250909013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Greetings From The President</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Just as the Clampetts are preparing to go home to the hills, Jethro receives a draft notice from the President. The women go ahead without them, and Jethro gets a few uniforms from the movie studio, one of a Prussian Field Marshall and one for General Patton. Jethro buys a tank and hopes for a crew, employing Drysdale and outfitting him with a Prussian Field Marshall uniform.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909013000 +0000" stop="20250909020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Supply Sergeants Never Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter, who says that Supply Sgt. Singer has the easiest job, wagers that any knucklehead could handle it—even Gomer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909020000 +0000" stop="20250909023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Go Light On The Heavy Water</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to destroy a heavy water supply by convincing Klink it is a youth potion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909023000 +0000" stop="20250909030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Traitor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send information to London by using a German radio propaganda program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909030000 +0000" stop="20250909033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Kaye Stevens And Audrey Meadows</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Kaye Stevens and Audrey Meadows. Originally aired on 01/05/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909033000 +0000" stop="20250909043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Antic Angel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is flabbergasted after seeing his wife—who died five years earlier! After he contacts her and she denies her identity, she soon ends up dead, and her husband is charged with the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909043500 +0000" stop="20250909050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>One More Pallbearer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric millionaire invites three people to visit him in his bomb shelter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909050500 +0000" stop="20250909053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Day Of The Bullet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When a friend is killed, a man reminisces about an incident in their past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909053500 +0000" stop="20250909060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Hitch Hike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman has second thoughts about having picked up a hitchhiker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909060500 +0000" stop="20250909070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Upside Down Penny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix works a case involving a child's missing stamp album. It appears as though someone is more than willing to kill for it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909070500 +0000" stop="20250909080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Couldn't Forget</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is in a full blown jam when he gets mistaken for the assassin of a bishop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909080500 +0000" stop="20250909090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Love, Child Of Vengeance (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby's probing of a lawyer's murder leads him to a religious cult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909090000 +0000" stop="20250909093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909093000 +0000" stop="20250909100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909100000 +0000" stop="20250909103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 81: The Long Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After roll call, Reed and Malloy provide backup at a robbery, help a lost man return home, handle a call about a prowler and respond to a silent alarm. Malloy demonstrates for Reed the importance of "officer presence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909103000 +0000" stop="20250909110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Jimmy Eisley's Dealing Smack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy spot TJ, an informant, who tells them about a possible drug house. They spot a woman and girl at the same bus stop an hour apart. When they stop to talk to her, she tries to run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909110000 +0000" stop="20250909120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Quizby</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Mr. Quizzer strikes it rich, he throws a 1925-themed party like The Great Gatsby."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909120000 +0000" stop="20250909123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Ice Skates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a new pair of expensive ice skates and asks Ward to borrow $13. Wanting to pick them out himself, he goes to the store and is conned by a salesman who sells him skates that are three sizes too big.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909123000 +0000" stop="20250909130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Weekend Invitation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally and a bunch of other guys are invited to spend the weekend at Scott's cottage on the lake. However, Scott doesn't mention to Wally that there will be no parent supervision.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909130000 +0000" stop="20250909140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hesitant Hostess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Albert Sanders is charged with the murder of Kim Lane, Mason offers to defend him free of charge because he knows Sanders is still devastated over the accidental death of his wife and children eight years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909140000 +0000" stop="20250909150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapper  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock is kidnapped, Michelle and Conrad go through Matlock's old cases to try to figure out who is holding him hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909150000 +0000" stop="20250909160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Aka Kelly Kay</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The past comes back to haunt JoAnn in the form of an escaped convict.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909160000 +0000" stop="20250909170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Revelation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy proposes to Daisy and she says yes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909170000 +0000" stop="20250909180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Caleb</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Having grown tired of farming, Caleb Marr comes to Dodge in search of adventure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909180000 +0000" stop="20250909190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben discovers that an Army general whom he supports as the next governor is all for killing Indians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909190000 +0000" stop="20250909193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mark's Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharpshooter Marty Blair tries to persuade Lucas to buy Mark a rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909193000 +0000" stop="20250909200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Amazing Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Fast-draw artist Wade Randall is less than anxious to display his prowess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909200000 +0000" stop="20250909210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Christopher Hale Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"Flint meets Chris Hale alone on the prairie. Hale has just found his entire family massacred by Indians, and Flint asks him to join the wagon train. However, the company that owns the wagon train has hired a new wagonmaster, Jud Benedict. Benedict is a ruthless and brutal tyrant who puts time above all other considerations, and does not care how many people are left behind or even die in the process of heading to the final destination as soon as possible. He has also hired unscrupulous gunmen to enforce this goal by brutalizing slower people, or anyone who stands up ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909210000 +0000" stop="20250909220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Computer Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The computer fouls up and Gage gets a check for thousands instead of for hundreds. A transient is injured in a car at a junkyard. A victim’s dog causes problems. Two workers are trapped on a scaffold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909220000 +0000" stop="20250909223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Change Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles plans a scheme to get rich when he discovers that blue scrip is going to be exchanged for red. Hawkeye and B.J. outsmart him, and he is left holding the worthless scrip. Klinger tries to get into West Point so that he can get out of Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909223000 +0000" stop="20250909230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Images</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar notices a number of tattoos on one of the wounded, and convinces himself that with a tattoo he will be irresistible to women. Everyone tries to discourage him, and he admits to having received a tattoo that will wash off. Meanwhile, Margaret is frustrated with a new nurse who keeps getting upset at the sight of combat injuries.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909230000 +0000" stop="20250909233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The M*a*s*h Olympics</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter, deciding that the camp is out of shape, enforces a calisthenics course. When nobody is enjoying it, he makes it fun by splitting the camp into two teams. These teams compete for three day R&amp;R passes. Klinger tries to get out of the army by getting fat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250909233000 +0000" stop="20250910000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Grim Reaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Victor Bloodworth predicts that 280 wounded will arrive at the 4077th. Hawkeye is antagonized by Bloodworth and shoves him against a wall. Bloodworth presses for a court martial until he becomes one of the wounded and watches Hawkeye saving a soldier's life. Realizing Hawkeye is value as a doctor, Bloodworth drops all charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910000000 +0000" stop="20250910003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mountain Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney visit the Darlings to rid them of Ernest T. Bass, who has his mind set on marrying daughter Charlene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910003000 +0000" stop="20250910010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Big House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When the state police leave two captured bank robbers in the custody of the Mayberry police department overnight, Barney is determined to show the prisoners that the Mayberry jail is as good as any other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910010000 +0000" stop="20250910013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Army Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Elly arrive back home just as Jethro is going to head to the Army. Granny decides to give Jethro his physical examination so the Army doctors don’t touch him. Though, Granny’s medical tools consist of a hammer to test reflexes and a burning candle to examine his throat. She splints his busted knee and puts corks in his ear to keep the draft out of them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910013000 +0000" stop="20250910020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Cat Overboard</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When the platoon goes on sea duty, Gomer sneaks a stray cat on board the ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910020000 +0000" stop="20250910023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happiness Is A Warm Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Klink finds Sergeant Schultz drunk he gets a tough new replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910023000 +0000" stop="20250910030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Scientist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau pretends to be a famous French scientist who is visiting camp while Hogan smuggles the real one out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910030000 +0000" stop="20250910033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Flip Wilson And Vikki Carr</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Flip Wilson and Vikki Carr. Originally aired on 01/19/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910033000 +0000" stop="20250910043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wayward Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Sutton is listed as the author of a best-selling book describing his experiences in a Korean POW camp. When the real author is released from an Army hospital, Sutton is slain before he can tell the truth and his widow is arrested for the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910043500 +0000" stop="20250910050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Man's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A vagrant steps into a murdered gangster's expensive shoes and is taken over by the dead man's ghost, who vows to remain on Earth to seek revenge against his killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910050500 +0000" stop="20250910053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Across The Threshold</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An overly possessive mother takes charge of her bachelor son's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910053500 +0000" stop="20250910060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Craig's Will</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's desire to marry into a rich family gets her into more trouble than she can handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910060500 +0000" stop="20250910070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>One Step To Midnight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix tries to protect the granddaughter of an exiled mobster. It seems as though she's being stalked by hoods who want to get to her grandfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910070500 +0000" stop="20250910080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Sounds Of Silence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon stirs up a hornet's nest worth of trouble after re-opening the case of an old shooting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910080500 +0000" stop="20250910090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Love, Child Of Vengeance (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A member of the cult that Barnaby has encountered may be the key to solving the murder of a lawyer the detective's been investigating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910090000 +0000" stop="20250910093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer is shot while making a routine check on a pair of paroled convicts parked near a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910093000 +0000" stop="20250910100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit And Run Driver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon use newspapers, radio and TV to publicize their clues to the identity of a hit-and-run driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910100000 +0000" stop="20250910103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 62 -- Grand Theft Horse?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have to put with a mystery noise in the car while handling grand theft horse, a naive girl and a robbery suspect who makes fake calls to distract the police</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910103000 +0000" stop="20250910110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 33 -- It All Happened So Fast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In a behind-the-scenes look at police investigations into deadly force incidents, Reed endures a night of intensive questioning by the station's lieutenant after he kills a man in self-defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910110000 +0000" stop="20250910120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Reunited...so Good!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill prepares for his high school reunion."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910120000 +0000" stop="20250910123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's English Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has been having trouble in English and Ward persuades Wally to tutor him. Wally has Beaver look over an old exam that he once took. To Beaver's surprise, the next day his teacher gives him the exact same test, which, of course, he aces. However, Beaver is left with a guilty conscience.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910123000 +0000" stop="20250910130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Chauffeur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally plans on going to a big dance with Evelyn Boothby and they plan on getting there cramped with six other people in Lumpy's car. When June and Ward refuse to allow that, Wally and Evelyn must find another way to get there. However, what Evelyn has in mind doesn't go over well with Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910130000 +0000" stop="20250910140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Screaming Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Gossip columnist Mary K. Davis is found murdered and it seems there is no shortage of suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910140000 +0000" stop="20250910150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Priest  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends when a mobster is accused of murdering a priest. It doesn't take long before Matlock suspects that the Church is covering something up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910150000 +0000" stop="20250910160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>These Things Take Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage mother from an impoverished family is arrested for murder after her infant is found dead, but Virgil believes there is more to the case than meets the eye. Meanwhile Althea believes the situation could have been prevented if the school had offered sex education classes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910160000 +0000" stop="20250910170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma Comes Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma returns from the hospital but the family does not let her do anything</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910170000 +0000" stop="20250910180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Sam Mctavish, M.d.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S16E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of the first woman doctor in Dodge City, Dr. Sam McTavish, riles Doc Adams. However, she soon wins his confidence and that of his patients, and the two physicians make a startling medical discovery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910180000 +0000" stop="20250910190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Killer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When an influenza epidemic hits the Ponderosa, the wife of a doctor feels she knows what to do. But Doc Martin insists that the doctor is merely a fraud.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910190000 +0000" stop="20250910193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Squeeze Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A speculator will stop at nothing to grab Lucas's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910193000 +0000" stop="20250910200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark blames himself for a friend's accidental death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910200000 +0000" stop="20250910210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tiburcio Mendez Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"Bill Hawks is leading four wagons through to California when they are stopped by Tiburcio Mendez and his band of renegades, who demand they turn back. Mendez and his group claim that California is their land and that it was stolen by the later settlers. A judge traveling with Hawks' group believes that Mendez has a legitimate grievance which could be addressed by the legislature in Sacramento, and against Hawks' warning goes in to Mendez' camp to talk with him. When Hawks follows, both he and the judge are taken prisoner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910210000 +0000" stop="20250910220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome To Santa Rosa County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John try to go fishing in Santa Rosa County, but end up rescuing climbers from a cliff face and fishermen whose boat blew up. They also help the sheriff come up with ideas for implementing emergency medical services in his county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910220000 +0000" stop="20250910223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lost behind enemy lines, Hawkeye and Margaret form a personal truce and seek shelter in a roadside hut."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910223000 +0000" stop="20250910230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Comrades In Arms (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Margaret and Hawkeye seek solace from enemy fire in each other's arms and end up, briefly, as lovers.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910230000 +0000" stop="20250910233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After Charles hands B.J. $200, he begins to take advantage. Everyone gets together and persuades Charles to play poker. He has incredible beginner's luck until Radar discovers that Charles whistles loudly when he bluffs. They all win back their money and then some.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250910233000 +0000" stop="20250911000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Smell Of Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th has just ended a rough three-day ordeal with wounded soldiers. Charles plays a French horn and drives Hawkeye and B.J. crazy. They refuse to bathe until the French horn playing is stopped; the two are even forced to eat outside because of their unhygienic presences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911000000 +0000" stop="20250911003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie The Birdman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie accidentally kills a mother bird with his new slingshot and takes it upon himself to raise the orphaned baby birds. After adopting them, Opie faces the difficult task of setting them free.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911003000 +0000" stop="20250911010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ernest T. Bass Joins The Army</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. wants to join the Army to impress a girl with the uniform. When he is refused induction, he goes on a window-breaking rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911010000 +0000" stop="20250911013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Race For Queen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May enters a Beverly Hills beauty contest, Queen of Beverly Hills, and the Drysdales and Miss Jane try to make sure that she'll win. And when Granny hears it is a race, she is set on entering, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911013000 +0000" stop="20250911020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Captures A Submarine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The men are on a simple reconnaissance mission, but Gomer somehow seems destined to ruin it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911020000 +0000" stop="20250911023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Hofbrau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan visits a local Hofbrau to get the plans to a German army division that is camping out nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911023000 +0000" stop="20250911030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Oil For The Lamps Of Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that there is oil underneath the camp in order to discourage the Germans from building a synthetic fuel plant there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911030000 +0000" stop="20250911033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Soupy Sales And Mel Torme</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Soupy Sales and Mel Torme. Originally aired on 01/26/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911033000 +0000" stop="20250911043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Careless Kidnapper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After a fake kidnaping goes wrong, Dr. Gregory Pelham finds that his secret experiments in rehabilitating prominent alcoholics have resulted in a mess of blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911043500 +0000" stop="20250911050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Hunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After returning from a hunting trip, a man discovers that no one can see or hear him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911050500 +0000" stop="20250911053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Madame Mystery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A man creates a successful publicity campaign to advertise his new movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911053500 +0000" stop="20250911060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Little Man Who Was There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A little man comes into a mining town with surprising results.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911060500 +0000" stop="20250911070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harvest Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When two crop-dusting pilots disappear, Mannix is hired to find them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911070500 +0000" stop="20250911080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911080500 +0000" stop="20250911090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Target Of A Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An heiress doesn't know that the fortune hunter she's fallen for has murdered her benefactor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911090000 +0000" stop="20250911093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bookie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday goes undercover with the department's chaplain in order to bust a gambling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911093000 +0000" stop="20250911100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Subscription Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday learns about a scam artist with a novel twist: he uses an authentic Congressional Medal of Honor to solicit magazine subscriptions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911100000 +0000" stop="20250911103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 112 -- You Blew It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The shift starts with the officers talking about another officer's judgment. Little do they realize they will be facing the same problem several times during the shift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911103000 +0000" stop="20250911110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 51 -- A Jumper - Code Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have one of those nights where they either have no calls or minor issues they can do nothing about. But at the end of the shift, Malloy must cook up a dangerous solution to a suicide jumper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911110000 +0000" stop="20250911120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 2002</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony reminisce on the year 2002."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911120000 +0000" stop="20250911123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's First Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A party is being thrown at the dancing school where Beaver and Wally once took lessons and they're both invited. This prompts Beaver to ask one particular girl who caught his eye, Betsy Patterson, if he could escort her to the dance. However, once at the dance, he finds that Betsy has promised other boys that she would dance with them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911123000 +0000" stop="20250911130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Golf Clubs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>During a particularly awful golf game, Ward happens to break his driver and decides it's not worth repairing it, so he just puts it in the closet. Later, Gilbert talks Beaver into hitting around some golf balls with Ward's clubs and one hit with the broken driver has Beaver thinking he broke it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911130000 +0000" stop="20250911140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fiery Fingers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When wealthy Louise Gordon is poisoned to death her nurse is charged with the crime. Mason does some digging and discovers that the first wife of the victim's husband also died of poisoning. Is the husband really the culprit or could it be someone else?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911140000 +0000" stop="20250911150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer: Part 1  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Sam Chandler is found murdered, his lawyer, David O'Malley, is the prime suspect—in part because Sam was sleeping with David's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911150000 +0000" stop="20250911160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Intruders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The police search for a burglar who preys on elderly women. And the prime suspect is the son of a city councilwoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911160000 +0000" stop="20250911170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Nest - Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandpa Zeb  has died and everyone is mourning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911170000 +0000" stop="20250911180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Seven Hours To Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A treacherous gang of outlaws takes over Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911180000 +0000" stop="20250911190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Terror At 2:00</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Three men, posing as newspaper reporters, plan on shooting down the whole town with a Gatling gun stolen from the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911190000 +0000" stop="20250911193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Anvil Chorus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nils Swenson, North Fork's blacksmith, volunteers to take the marshal's place for a few days while Micah attends a wedding in another town. To help maintain peace, Nils institutes a policy that anyone coming into town must turn in their weapons, getting them back when they leave. This plan backfires on Nils when some dishonest men come to town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911193000 +0000" stop="20250911200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas's self-confidence begins to slip away when he misses an easy shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911200000 +0000" stop="20250911210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Nellie Jefferson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>"When actress Nellie Jefferson joins the wagon train, her incessant demands for special treatment come to grate on Hale and Hawks, but Wooster is totally smitten with her. Meanwhile a fanatical man from her past is following her, talking about how she will meet her fate like the biblical Jezebel."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911210000 +0000" stop="20250911220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Paperwork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Chet and Marco are drafted to sort out a filing dilemma caused by computer error. A kid falls in a storm drain and nearly drowns. The paramedics experience problems with a new supply nurse. A janitor drinks samples of an archeologist's Mesopotamian wine. The firemen respond to a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911220000 +0000" stop="20250911223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Patient 4077</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In need of a special surgical clamp, Hawkeye and B.J. hire Mr. Shin, a local jewelry dealer, to make it. Days later the clamp is used to save the leg of a wounded soldier. Mr. Shin goes into the surgical supply business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911223000 +0000" stop="20250911230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Tea And Empathy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>With British and American casualties heavy, the 4077th's supply of penicillin has been stolen. Father Mulcahy discovers, from Corporal Bryant, the location of some penicillin, and he and Klinger go out in search of it. They are shot at, but safely return with the drug and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911230000 +0000" stop="20250911233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250911233000 +0000" stop="20250912000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912000000 +0000" stop="20250912003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon For Today</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting preacher gives a sermon about taking time to relax. In trying to create an atmosphere of relaxation on a Sunday afternoon, the townsfolk all end up running themselves ragged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912003000 +0000" stop="20250912010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Briscoe Declares For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Briscoe Darling becomes obsessed with Aunt Bee after hearing her recite a poem, going as far as to kidnap her and bring her back to his shack in the hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912010000 +0000" stop="20250912013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>A Plot For Granny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>For Granny’s birthday, the Clampetts plan to surprise her with some land in the country. Jed calls a number Jethro saw an ad for. However, the Clampetts do not know they are calling a cemetery. After a misunderstanding, the men from the cemetery begin believing the Clampetts are cold-blooded killers, having killed an entire family named Green, Granny and Mrs. Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912013000 +0000" stop="20250912020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Grudge Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter, perhaps overestimating his skill set, challenges the fleet's retired boxing champion to a fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912020000 +0000" stop="20250912023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reservations Are Required</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan tries to arrange the unscheduled escape of 20 men, his mission is complicated when a captured sergeant jumps the gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912023000 +0000" stop="20250912030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Anchors Aweigh, Men Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men are tasked with getting an escaped prisoner and smuggled German gun sight to England. To accomplish this Hogan convinces Klink that he is fatigued and should have an officer's club in which to relax.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912030000 +0000" stop="20250912033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Barbara Feldon And Joan Rivers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Barbara Feldon and Joan Rivers. Originally aired on 02/02/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912033000 +0000" stop="20250912043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drifting Dropout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason defends a mixed-up man accused of killing his former boss. The young man's uncle had been a business partner of the deceased and was quite a crook. Scandal and intrigue run deep and it's up to Mason to dredge up the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912043500 +0000" stop="20250912050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown With Rance Mcgrew</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While filming a scene in which Jesse James shoots him in the back, the star of a Western TV series suddenly finds himself in a real Old West saloon—with the real Jesse James.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912050500 +0000" stop="20250912053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Mother, May I Go To Swim?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man tries desperately to free himself from the women who would control his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912053500 +0000" stop="20250912060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cuckoo Clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped mental patient terrorizes a woman left alone in a remote cottage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912060500 +0000" stop="20250912070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A Puzzle For One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a fellow private eye assumes room temperature, Mannix investigates his death and tries to solve the deceased's final case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912070500 +0000" stop="20250912080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Daddy's Little Girl</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon helps fake the murder of a mobster in order to allow the man to testify against his boss."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912080500 +0000" stop="20250912090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Temptation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>As a police lieutenant ends up falling for the ex-girlfriend of a murderer in trying to make her a witness to have the murderer convicted, he's framed for the murder of a second witness, so Barnaby and J.R. try to clear him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912090000 +0000" stop="20250912093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A Japanese widow is senselessly murdered, leaving her small daughter an orphan. Friday has a hard time controlling his emotions while seeking the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912093000 +0000" stop="20250912100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Kids</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A gang of juvenile thieves have been stealing petty items in order to gain membership into an exclusive club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912100000 +0000" stop="20250912103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 73 -- I'm Still A Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While Malloy is attending college, radicals learn he is a cop. They reject him and antagonize him on the job. After helping arrest demonstrators, his new car is vandalized. When a timer is found missing, he locates and disarms a bomb using it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912103000 +0000" stop="20250912110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 102 -- We Can't Just Walk Away From It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed respond to a call about a drug overdose and track the drugs to a 17-year-old who has barricaded himself in his room with a gun and threatens kill himself. They contend with a distraught mother and an overbearing father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912110000 +0000" stop="20250912120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Go, Fight, Win!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill enters the dynamic world of cheerleading!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912120000 +0000" stop="20250912123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Farewell To Penny</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Penny learns that she will be moving away and Beaver deals with mixed feelings for the girl with whom he shares a mutual dislike. However, after a farewell party at school, Beaver and Penny openly show their true feelings for one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912123000 +0000" stop="20250912130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Bunny</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver is cast as a rabbit for a school play and June has his costume all ready, complete with floppy ears and puffy tail. On the night of the play, Beaver needs to be at the school early and gets a ride with Lumpy and Wally in full costume, however, Lumpy's car breaks down and Beaver must walk the few blocks to the school to get there in time."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912130000 +0000" stop="20250912140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Substitute Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della are traveling on a cruise ship returning to Los Angeles from Vancouver. Carl Houser jumps overboard and is presumed drowned. Houser later turns up on shore but with a bullet wound in his body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912140000 +0000" stop="20250912150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer: Part 2  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Sam Chandler is found murdered, his lawyer, David O'Malley, is the prime suspect—in part because Sam was sleeping with David's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912150000 +0000" stop="20250912160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Creek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The investigation of a possible assault brings back nightmarish and confusing childhood memories for Virgil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912160000 +0000" stop="20250912170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Empty Nest - Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandpa Zeb  has died and everyone is mourning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912170000 +0000" stop="20250912180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>With A Smile</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A powerful rancher's spoiled son gets violent when a pretty girl rebuffs his affections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912180000 +0000" stop="20250912190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Stillness Within</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Having been blinded in an explosion, an inconsolable Joe encounters a woman who tries to teach him how to survive without sight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912190000 +0000" stop="20250912193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Line Shack Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad gang boss John Gangling kills one of his crew to rob him of his savings. To cover his tracks, Gangling puts the blame on Johnny Wing, an Apache worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912193000 +0000" stop="20250912200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>On the road Lucas and Mark come upon Winslow Quince, a peddler whose wagon has broken down, and help him get his wagon into North Fork for repair. While in North Fork Quince barters several items that implicate him in a series of murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912200000 +0000" stop="20250912210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Saul Bevins Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>"Saul Bevins, a blind doctor traveling with his son, his sister, and his dog, asks to join the wagon train. Many others on the train object that he will slow them down, but Hale agrees to let him ride at least until the next settlement, at which time the entire wagon train will vote on whether he should continue. On the way Bevins is forced to overcome many obstacles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912210000 +0000" stop="20250912220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Loose Ends</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny tries to win a ticket-selling contest. Dr. Backett blames himself when he is involved in a car accident that leaves the other driver dead and The driver's daughter refuses to speak. While repairing the squad, the paramedics find themselves in the middle of a shootout and treat a policeman with heart trouble. A boxcar full of ammonia complicates a fire on a pier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912220000 +0000" stop="20250912223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912223000 +0000" stop="20250912230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912230000 +0000" stop="20250912233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250912233000 +0000" stop="20250913000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913000000 +0000" stop="20250913003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy takes Gomer in after Wally fires him for not doing his job right. Gomer proceeds to drive Andy, Aunt Bee and Opie crazy with all of the noise he makes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913003000 +0000" stop="20250913010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Black Day For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are to protect a shipment of gold passing through Mayberry. It's critical that they keep it a secret, but Barney spills the beans immediately and soon all the town knows.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913010000 +0000" stop="20250913013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Social Climbers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a letter from home, from Adeline Ashley, a hillbilly socialite. Miss Ashley says she going to stop by while visiting friends. However, she arrives early. And through her whole visit, she sets her sights on marrying Jed. Jed isn’t at all interested, but hopes that Miss Ashley could meet Mrs. Drysdale and arranges it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913013000 +0000" stop="20250913020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer, Star Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer witnesses a car accident involving Sgt. Carter, who is at fault. Rather than have Gomer testify against him, the sergeant schemes for Gomer to be out of town on the court date.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913020000 +0000" stop="20250913023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Adolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys plan to destroy a gun emplacement so the Allies can attack on Hitler's birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913023000 +0000" stop="20250913030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Rush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>French gold has been stolen by the Nazis. Hogan convinces Klink to have it brought to Stalag 13 so the prisoners can steal it back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913030000 +0000" stop="20250913033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Sketch Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Family Sketch Show. Originally aired on 02/16/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913033000 +0000" stop="20250913043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tandem Target</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E29</episode-num>
    <desc>After a hated businessman is killed in a sabotaged automobile, his future son-in-law—who the businessman despised—is arrested for the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913043500 +0000" stop="20250913050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Kick The Can</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The senior residents of Sunnyvale decide that the secret to youth is acting young, and in particular playing a childhood game called "kick-the-can."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913050500 +0000" stop="20250913053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Detectives Later</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's search for his wife's murderer leads to a small hotel room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913053500 +0000" stop="20250913060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Two men meet aboard a ship at sea, and one of them is sure he knows the other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913060500 +0000" stop="20250913070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Lost Sunday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The death of a factory foreman is ruled accidental, but his sister believes that it was murder and hires Mannix.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913070500 +0000" stop="20250913080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Conspirators</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon travels to a small town in Texas to investigate a young girl's suspicious death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913080500 +0000" stop="20250913090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Man On Fire</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby works with a claims adjuster in an arson-and-murder case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250913090000 +0000" stop="20250913093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Shady Rest Hotel Corporation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Uncle Joe plans to pay for a new water heater by selling stock in a corporation that represents the Shady Rest.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
