<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830093000 +0000" stop="20250830100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Modern Merchandising</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A new supermarket in Pixley finds Sam Drucker's losing all of his customers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830100000 +0000" stop="20250830103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Mark Templeton Arrives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly comes running to Granny with distressing news, sickness! Fairchild, Elly’s bear, is sick. Meanwhile, at the bank, Miss Jane has a visitor, Lieutenant Mark Templeton of the US Navy. He is Matthew Templeton’s brother. Drysdale kicks the two out, and Jane takes Mark to the Clampetts to meet the beautiful Elly. At this time, Granny made medicine for Elly May’s bear, but Jethro ate it. Elly tries to remake it, but fails, and ends up looking a mess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830103000 +0000" stop="20250830110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Come Back, Little Herby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After the Clampetts don’t have success with the gorilla they took out of the zoo, they decide to get Herby back. They contact Drysdale who tells Mr. Kelly, but he refuses to do it. Mr. Kelly tells Drysdale he’ll return on his own terms and has Drysdale buy him designer clothes and expensive food. Herby returns to the mansion and starts living the life of luxury, dancing and dining with Elly by the pool.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830110000 +0000" stop="20250830113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>It’s The Natural Thing To Do, Olive Oyl And Water Don’t Mix, I Yam Love Sick</sub-title>
    <desc>"Persuaded by Olive Oyl that the public might like them in a different role, Popeye and Bluto attempt to be sophisticated men-about-town., No sooner do Popeye and his sea-going sidekick, Bluto, agree that "wimmin is bad luck," that Olive gallops up the gangplank of the battleship the boys are on., Popeye plays sick to win Olive's attention."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830113000 +0000" stop="20250830120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Switchin' Kitten, Sheep Wrecked, Bowling Alley Cat</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom and Jerry enter an old castle on a dark and stormy night which is owned by a mad scientist., Droopy is a sheepherder that has to protect his flock from a wolf., Tom and Jerry are at the bowling alley as mayhem ensues."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830120000 +0000" stop="20250830130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Woody's Clip Joint, A Horses Tale, Bee Bopped, Home Sweet Homewrecker, Swiss Mis-fit, Eggnapper, Knock Knock</sub-title>
    <desc>"A lion escapes from the circus and forces Woody to hide him in a barber shop. Desiring the reward money for the lion's return, Woody instead traps the lion to hand over to the ringmaster., Sugarfoot finds a new job as a stunt double after a misunderstanding gets him kicked off the farm., Windy the bee tries to teach his son the "right" way to steal honey from a beehive. He mostly gets hurt along the way., Woody and Bucky Beaver attempt to destroy each other's homes., A rescue dog tries to prove himself by saving Chilly, but only ends up in trouble himself., When tourist season is over and the park ranger leaves the bears to fend for themselves in winter, Fatso disguishes himself as a female chicken to raid a nearby henhouse., Andy and Papa try to stop Woody from pecking on their roof."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830130000 +0000" stop="20250830140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Corny Concerto, Run, Run Sweet Road Runner (1965), Trip For Tat, People Are Bunny, Crockett-doodle-do, Good Noose, Rabbit Hood</sub-title>
    <desc>"A parody of Disney's Fantasia set in "Corny-Gee Hall". We watch Elmer Fudd, and Bugs Bunny act out a play from "A Tale of Vienna Woods". , Wile E. Coyote attempts numerous ways to catch the Road Runner. , When Granny goes on a world tour with Tweety, Sylvester joins them as a stowaway. It becomes a chase around the world for the little bird. , Daffy hears that a television station is giving away a prize to the first person who can bring in a rabbit. Daffy chases Bugs and traps him in a telephone booth., Foghorn tries to teach the brainy chicken, Egghead Jr., about the great outdoors., Daffy is found as a stowaway aboard large ship. In an effort to avoid being thrown off board he tries entertaining the captain with amateur magic tricks. , While stealing a carrot in Sherwood Forest on the king's property, Bugs gets caught by the sheriff. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830140000 +0000" stop="20250830150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Gruesome Games</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While on the trail of a scientist who has stolen a vial of deadly germs, the agents are pulled into a night of deadly parlor games. West and Gordon must recover the vial before it bursts and releases a veritable plague while managing to live though the games of their host.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830150000 +0000" stop="20250830170000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke I: Return to Dodge</title>
    <desc>"Will Mannon is released from a frontier prison and promptly goes in search of the people who put him there some 12 years ago -- Matt Dillon and Kitty Russell."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830170000 +0000" stop="20250830180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Matt's Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S19E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded Matt Dillon suffers amnesia then falls in love with a widow. It's Matt's first TV kiss, not to Miss Kitty, but to guest star Michael Learned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830180000 +0000" stop="20250830190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Honest John</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamie befriends an old man known as Honest John, urging him to rebuild an old wagon so he can leave the Ponderosa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830190000 +0000" stop="20250830193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Tinhorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A professional card player, John Keeler, has set up business in North Fork, but local Jesse Phillips claims that this tinhorn is a cheat. Lucas starts playing poker with Keeler to draw him out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830193000 +0000" stop="20250830200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>None So Blind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark befriends singer-banjoist Lafayette Bly, a blind man with an acute sense of hearing—and a very strong grip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830200000 +0000" stop="20250830210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>A Man Called Mushy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mushy is swindled out of the wagons and the remuda. He is fired, kidnapped by gypsies and sold into slavery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830210000 +0000" stop="20250830213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Girl From Piccadilly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Learning of his son's death, a rich man hires Paladin to locate the daughter-in-law he's never met, but Paladin finds two women both claiming to be her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830213000 +0000" stop="20250830220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Twelve Hours To Crazy Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh delivers Dan Murdock, wanted for multiple murders in Mesa City. He learns that the local sheriff is the brother of Crazy Horse's deputy, one of the victims, and it's unlikely that Murdock will arrive safely. Josh goes along to make sure that he does.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250830220000 +0000" stop="20250831000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Woman Haters, Three Little Sew And Sews, Nutty But Nice, Fuelin' Around, Commotion On The Ocean, Of Cash And Hash</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges join the "Women Haters" club and vow to have nothing to do with the fair sex.  Larry marries a girl anyway and attempts to hide the fact from Moe and Curly as they take a train trip. , The Stooges are sailors working in a ships' tailor shop.  When they can't get passes to go ashore, they steal officers' uniforms and go to a party with Curly passing himself off as Admiral Taylor and Moe and Larry as his aides.  Two spies, one of them a beautiful woman, trick the Stooges into stealing a new submarine.  The boys turn the table on the spies and capture them.  When the real Admiral shows up, Curly's reenacts the capture and accidentally detonates a bomb, blowing them all to kingdom come. , The Stooges witness an armed robbery and are brought in by the cops as suspects.  After passing a lie detector test, the boys are freed and go back to their jobs in a Cafe.  When one of the robbers comes into the Cafe, the boys recognize him and along with their friend Gladys trail him to a spooky house in the country where the crooks are hiding out.  The bad guys abduct Gladys and the Stooges must rescue her.  [A remake of "Shivering Sherlocks".] , The Stooges are singing waiters who are enlisted by a doctor to try and cheer up a little girl.  It seems that the girl's father is a banker who was kidnapped with $300,000 worth of bonds.  Failing to cheer up the girl, the Stooges go out looking for the father and by a series of coincidences wind up in the bad guys hideout.  The villains return and after a wild fight the boys free the missing man. , The Stooges are carpet layers working in the home of a scientist, Professor Sneed, who has invented a super rocket fuel.  Larry is mistaken for the professor by foreign agents who kidnap the trio and take them to the country of Anemia where they are ordered to produce the rocket fuel or be executed.  The boys come up with a concoction they try to pass of as the real stuff, but are exposed when the real professor and his daughter are also kidnapped.  The Stooges help them escape, using their secret formula to fuel a jeep. , The Stooges are would-be reporters, who are tricked into becoming stowaways by "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that Borscht has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831000000 +0000" stop="20250831023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Of Night</sub-title>
    <desc>"Three horror stories about a vintage car that transports its driver back to 1926, the mistress of an old Victorian mansion who is scared of a vampire and a mother tormented by her dead son who she has brought back to life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831023000 +0000" stop="20250831030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Penguin Goes Straight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After recent heroic feats, the Penguin announces his Penguin Protection Agency, intended to protect the wealth of Gotham City's society crowd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831030000 +0000" stop="20250831040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Corbomite Maneuver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise encounters a vast alien ship that sets out to test them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831040000 +0000" stop="20250831043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Freeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A criminal mastermind freezes away Superman's powers and intimidates people from voting against his crooked candidate for Metropolis' mayor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831043000 +0000" stop="20250831050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Peril By Sea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Perry White discovers a formula that can extract uranium from seawater. Crooks discover it and torpedo his cottage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831050000 +0000" stop="20250831060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Raft</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinsons manage to construct a small space ship that they plan to use to return to Earth. Dr. Smith and Will launch the craft but wind up returning back on the original planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831060000 +0000" stop="20250831070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Mechanical Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A life-like robot uses the Seaview to seize control of the world.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831070000 +0000" stop="20250831080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>The Unsuspected</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While fleeing the giants, Steve is exposed to hallucinogenic mushroom spores and becomes a raving paranoid who makes an alliance with Inspector Kobick to turn in his fellow Earthlings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831080000 +0000" stop="20250831090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>The Revenge Of Robin Hood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>In 13th-century England, Tony and Doug join Robin Hood's revolt against evil King John.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831090000 +0000" stop="20250831100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Vincent close in on a supposed prophet who glows in a way similar to the aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831100000 +0000" stop="20250831110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Rivals</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jack finds a gold nugget while seeing Sumi (a female Indian) home and takes off to find more."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831110000 +0000" stop="20250831113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tigers Of Sariska</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin goes unarmed deep into the jungles of India to film the adventures of a full-grown Bengal tigress and her two young cubs."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831113000 +0000" stop="20250831120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Voyage To Raza</sub-title>
    <desc>"Travel with Marlin and his band of adventurers as they explore the Golf of California, the last great unexplored marine paradise in the Western hemisphere, lying between the Mexican main land and Baja, California."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831120000 +0000" stop="20250831123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chincoteaque Roundup</sub-title>
    <desc>"There’s a legend that during the 16th century, Spanish ponies from a sinking galleon swam ashore to the island of Assateague, Virginia.  Today, once a year, men from neighboring Chincoteague Island gather for one of the most unusual roundups."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831123000 +0000" stop="20250831130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lions Of Gir Forest</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin travels to Gir Forest in India in search of the king of beasts…the lion."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831130000 +0000" stop="20250831133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of The Falcon</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit the mountain prairies of Wyoming where falcons, eagles and hawks rule the air."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831133000 +0000" stop="20250831140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bears Of The High Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim follow a pair of black bear cubs in Yellowstone National Park; track a large black bear to tag for future reference."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831140000 +0000" stop="20250831143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>My Brother's Keeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Bobby pushes Peter out of the way of a falling ladder, Peter volunteers to be Bobby's slave for life, a situation Bobby takes advantage of. Meanwhile, the girls try to decide on a wallpaper for their room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831143000 +0000" stop="20250831150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Mike's Horror-scope</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The day after Carol reads Mike's horoscope, which states "a strange woman will enter your life tomorrow," a difficult and demanding female client begins to dominate Mike's time, keeping him away from home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831150000 +0000" stop="20250831153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Grandma Nussbaum</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie and Chachi's grandmother becomes very upset at them for suggesting that she move into a retirement home after they observe signs of senility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831153000 +0000" stop="20250831160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Perfidy In Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Feeling guilty for losing Laverne's favorite purse and then lying about it, Shirley dreams that her friend is trying to kill her to get even.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831160000 +0000" stop="20250831163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>One-punch Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie must learn to defend himself against a bully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831163000 +0000" stop="20250831170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Return Home From Europe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Lucy disguises a block of cheese as a baby in order to take it aboard a flight."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831170000 +0000" stop="20250831173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>In The Soup</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is throwing a party and is successful in getting Beaver out of the house, who is planning to spend the night at Whitey's. However, on the way to Whitey's house, he and Beaver get into an argument over a billboard that is advertising soup, leading Beaver to fall into the giant soup bowl mounted at the top of the billboard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831173000 +0000" stop="20250831180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Community Chest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver volunteers to go around the neighborhood and collect for the Community Chest in June's place after she decides to attend Wally's open house at his school. Beaver brings along Gilbert and thanks to Beaver's astronomical mistake of losing the collection can, chaos erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831180000 +0000" stop="20250831183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Doctor, Cure My Frog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny checks on Mark to make sure he is all human. When she sees that he is, she is ready for him to marry Elly May, giving hints. Elly and Mark sit in the parlor, trying to be alone, but keep getting interrupted by the family, mostly Granny and Jethro. Even when they think they are alone, Jethro is watching them, but Elly chases him out. Granny decides to head to the bank and, since she helped her out, brings Miss Jane a frog to kiss, only if she wants to.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831183000 +0000" stop="20250831190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at Clampett Castle, and meet Mr. Faversham, who they call Major Domo after a misunderstanding with his name, also mistaking his name for a greeting. Granny decides to check on Marcus, but doesn’t know that the dog of the house is sitting in his bed. She feels the dog through the curtain and thinks the staff and doctors have been neglecting him. Jethro is working on fulfilling his duty as a knight and decides to start hunting dragons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831190000 +0000" stop="20250831193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Gilligan Gets Bugged</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Gilligan thinks he is doomed after being bitten by a yellow and green bug. Soon, the other castaways also are bitten by the same bug.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831193000 +0000" stop="20250831200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Mine Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>While fishing, Gilligan pulls a WWII mine out of the lagoon. When the Professor is unable to deactivate the mine, Gilligan tows it back into the lagoon, where it harmlessly explodes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831200000 +0000" stop="20250831203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Hate Thy Neighbor  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Bubba announces that he’s going to marry the daughter of Mama's hated neighbor, Mama is forced to make peace. But when the engagement is broken, the feud starts anew.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831203000 +0000" stop="20250831210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Dependence Day  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Iola declares her independence from her mother... and moves in with Mama. Now, the family unites with a single purpose: get Iola out of the house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831210000 +0000" stop="20250831220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Take A Letter Vicky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman falls for a man's claim of a year of celibacy; a woman's bridge partners hinder her romance; Stubing makes Vicki his secretary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831220000 +0000" stop="20250831223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney And The Governor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney is goaded into ticketing the governor's car and mistakenly believes Andy is setting him up for a dressing-down by the governor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831223000 +0000" stop="20250831230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Shawn Peterson- Pez</sub-title>
    <desc>"They say to do what you love, and Shawn Peterson loves PEZ.  After years of collecting rare dispensers, candies, and other company artifacts, Shawn successfully pitched a PEZ Visitor Center at the company’s historic and still-functioning factory, where he now manages and shares his collection with 80,000 visitors a year.  He also shares his collection with Collector’s Call, taking Lisa, and PEZ Price Guide expert and appraiser, John LaSpina, on a ride through PEZ history, including: a 1940s PEZ Girl uniform, a rare Colonel Sanders prototype, and a giant edible candy tablet that you can only acquire if you’re invited to the headquarters factory in Germany.  John appraises Shawn’s collection and attempts a trade, offering an ultra rare set and display featured in a Montgomery Ward catalogue in exchange for a dispenser from the 1984 Winter Olympics.  Also, Shawn shows Lisa around the PEZ factory and takes her behind-the-scenes of the candy-making process."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831230000 +0000" stop="20250831233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Nurses</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hot Lips confines Nurse Baker to her quarters, little does she know that Baker's husband has arrived in the camp. Hawkeye and B.J. put them together in Hot Lips' tent, telling everyone that a quarantined patient has been placed there. When Hot Lips discovers what has happened, she breaks down and refuses to press charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250831233000 +0000" stop="20250901000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Abduction Of Margaret Houlihan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After hearing that North Korean prisoners have been released in the area, everyone is upset when Margaret disappears. Colonel Flagg is called in to investigate, and bungles things in his usual manner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901000000 +0000" stop="20250901003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Jefferson's Move Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers bid fond farewell to the Jeffersons when their neighbors abandon Queens for the nouveau-riche life in a Manhattan high rise.[This episode was the pilot for "The Jeffersons."]</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901003000 +0000" stop="20250901010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>All's Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria gives Edith a lesson in marriage assertiveness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901010000 +0000" stop="20250901013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Amelia's Divorce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is surprised to discover that her cousin Amelia's ideal marriage is rotten to the core.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901013000 +0000" stop="20250901020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Everybody Does It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie's steals a box of nails from work and finds himself at the center of a household debate on morality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901020000 +0000" stop="20250901023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence, Durward Kirby, And Julie Bond</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Steve Lawrence, Durward Kirby, and Julie Bond. Originally aired on 12/14/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901023000 +0000" stop="20250901030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Bing Crosby, Ella Fitzgerald, And Rowan &amp; Martin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Bing Crosby, Ella Fitzgerald, and Rowan &amp; Martin. Originally aired on 11/10/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901030000 +0000" stop="20250901033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>You Ought To Be In Pictures</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob is cast in a movie with all sorts of trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901033000 +0000" stop="20250901040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Love Thy Neighbor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The Helpers are jealous of the Petries' new neighbors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901040000 +0000" stop="20250901043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Sleepwalker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Norton is sleepwalking and Ralph gets stuck looking after him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901043000 +0000" stop="20250901053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Incredible World Of Horace Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A toy designer who longs for his idyllic childhood gets a bitter taste of reality when he finds himself transported to the past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901053000 +0000" stop="20250901060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Blessington Method</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A unique society has a different method for preparing for the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901060000 +0000" stop="20250901070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Blast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Gregory Tolan leads an underground cell specializing in bank robberies with the money going to finance an American revolution. His mysterious sponsor is Jonathan Brace, who runs other such cells throughout the U.S. The IMF must find out Brace's identity and stop his operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901070000 +0000" stop="20250901080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Masquerade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While traveling through a small Oklahoma town, Kimble is arrested because the police have mistaken him for Leonard Hull, a former numbers runner about to testify against a big-time racketeer. The racketeer has run away from a witness relocation program in</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901080000 +0000" stop="20250901090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Madonna Legacy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell looks for a clue of murder in the apparent suicide of an alcoholic ex-cop."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901090000 +0000" stop="20250901093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>I.a.d. - The Receipt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a complaint that two veteran officers stole funds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901093000 +0000" stop="20250901100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - The Harassing Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901100000 +0000" stop="20250901103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 141 -- The Color Tv Bandit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed learn of a serial home burglar stealing color TVs. They stumble upon the suspect's car with unusual results. Also, Reed must come to terms with his anger over a drug using mother that endangered her children to score dope.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901103000 +0000" stop="20250901110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 131 -- Reed, The Dicks Have Their Job And We Have Ours</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy teaches raw rookie Reed about the job that detectives play when a murder scene must be secured and turned over. Reed learns to be content with his role and responsibilities in a uniformed radio car when they arrest fleeing fugitives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901110000 +0000" stop="20250901120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Don't Get Scammed!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony avoid becoming the victims of a scam with the help of a special guest."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901120000 +0000" stop="20250901123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Junior Fire Chief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to run for junior fire chief and, to his surprise, wins. However, as soon as he's elected, he lets the responsibilities go to his head and begins issuing citations to not only his family but his neighbors as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901123000 +0000" stop="20250901130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Frogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a canoe and makes a deal with Ward: If Beaver can come up with half the money, Ward will pay for the other half. So Beaver, comes up with a way of making money by selling frogs. However, little does he know that the man who's going to buy the frogs, uses them for class dissections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901130000 +0000" stop="20250901140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The One-eyed Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Della and Mason's dinner at a fancy French restaurant is interrupted by a phone call and an envelope containing $500 from a mysterious woman named Marian Fargo. She wants him to make an exchange: the money for some documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901140000 +0000" stop="20250901150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thoroughbred  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the manager of a thoroughbred farm is murdered, her father begs Matlock to represent the mentally handicapped man accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901150000 +0000" stop="20250901160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Nights</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba is seduced by an alluring writer who has more on her mind than romance. Bill and Virgil worry that he is in over his head. Bubba tries to protect her from her estranged husband, but things get complicated after she shoots someone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901160000 +0000" stop="20250901170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Olivia celebrate their 25th wedding anniversary</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901170000 +0000" stop="20250901173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Matt Gets It</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dan Grat, a gunman hunted by Texas authorities, seeks refuge in Dodge City. Marshal Dillon goes into action against this outlaw who shoots before he talks."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901173000 +0000" stop="20250901180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Cabin</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt get caught in a blizzard then finds shelter in a cabin but finds more than he bargained for."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901180000 +0000" stop="20250901190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>For A Young Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E14</episode-num>
    <desc>The aunt and uncle of a young girl want to gain custody of her because they believe she holds the rights to a gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901190000 +0000" stop="20250901193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Jealous Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Fay Owens, old friends of Micah, are the McCain's new neighbors. Jake quickly develops an unreasoning jealousy of Lucas with Fay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901193000 +0000" stop="20250901200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Guilty Conscience</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E27</episode-num>
    <desc>No one's more surprised than Micah when newcomer Leota Carraway claims he's her long-lost husband and the father of her child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901200000 +0000" stop="20250901210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Prairie Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Here is the story of the women of the wagon train and the unforgiving prairie through which they pass. Who will endure, and who will give up? Who will live, and who will die?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901210000 +0000" stop="20250901220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Unlikely Heirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>After John and Roy rescue an elderly transient from a fire, Chet and Marco discover $80,000 in the man's mattress. A bride faints while walking down the aisle. Dixie administers a tetanus shot to a young boy. An elderly woman loses her cat. A plane crashes into a warehouse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901220000 +0000" stop="20250901223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sigmund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman, feeling depressed, visits the 4077th to observe how they fare under the pressures of war. He begins a letter to Sigmund Freud as a form of self-therapy, and releases his tension in the form of a practical joke with B.J., aimed at Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901223000 +0000" stop="20250901230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mulcahy's War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After Frank discovers that Danny Fitzsimmons has shot himself to get out of combat, Father Mulcahy is called in. Realizing his lack of understanding of the fighting, Mulcahy accompanies Radar to an aid station, where they encounter the real war at first hand. Mulcahy performs an emergency tracheotomy, guided by Hawkeye over the radio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901230000 +0000" stop="20250901233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Korean Surgeon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When Dr. Syn Paik, a North Korean surgeon, arrives with some wounded, he is passed off as a South Korean by Hawkeye and B.J., but to no avail. Hot Lips and Frank try to convince Potter that Paik is a spy. Paik, Hawkeye and B.J. agree that it would be in the interest of all for him to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250901233000 +0000" stop="20250902000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawkeye Get Your Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After 24 hours of surgery, Hawkeye and Potter venture off to a Korean hospital to lend a hand. Hawkeye is appalled to learn that he must carry a gun. After helping the Koreans, they are shelled on the way back. They scramble from the jeep before it is shelled, and Potter urges Hawkeye to shoot in self-defense, against Hawkeye's will, and he does—into the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902000000 +0000" stop="20250902003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In A Hurry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Big businessman Malcolm Tucker is stuck in Mayberry on a Sunday when his car breaks down outside the city limits. He's soon driven to frustration when he finds there is no way to get anything done until the following day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902003000 +0000" stop="20250902010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>High Noon In Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney gets hysterical when Andy receives a letter from a man he arrested and sent to prison. The convict is to be released soon and says in the letter that he is coming to settle the score with Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902010000 +0000" stop="20250902013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Inherits A Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jethro tells Jed that he has inherited a castle in England, after hearing the word from Drysdale. He gets costumes from Tudor times, thinking that Queen Elizabeth I is still reigning. Jethro even makes Granny wear an oaf costume, since she doesn’t have Clampett blood. Drysdale and Jane visit, and Jane tells the Clampetts that what Jethro is telling them is wrong. But after Drysdale paints a picture for Jane, the two convince the Clampetts to go, even providing an oaf for Jethro, Miss Jane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902013000 +0000" stop="20250902020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Pfc Gomer Pyle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter postpones his vacation until all his men pass their Private First Class exams. Gomer, unfortunately, is the only one to fail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902020000 +0000" stop="20250902023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Antique</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets Klink to open an antiques business selling "rare" cuckoo clocks, a business venture that is actually a ruse enabling the POWs to smuggle information out in the timepieces.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902023000 +0000" stop="20250902030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Rockets Or Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan becomes the partner of a beautiful underground agent when he and his men team up with the underground to destroy a guided missile battery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902030000 +0000" stop="20250902033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Andy Griffith</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guest Andy Griffith. Originally aired on 11/17/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902033000 +0000" stop="20250902043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Frightened Fisherman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the former boss and wife of a scientist attempt to prevent him from taking the credit for a new antibiotic, the wife turns up dead and her scientist husband has trouble clearing his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902043500 +0000" stop="20250902050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Jungle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a business man plans to build a dam in Africa, a witch doctor puts a curse on him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902050500 +0000" stop="20250902053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Weight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's plan to rid himself of a blackmailer backfires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902053500 +0000" stop="20250902060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Special Delivery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A little boy's hobby of growing mushrooms in his cellar turns into a nightmare.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902060500 +0000" stop="20250902070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Crimson Halo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>An attorney hires Mannix to discover who's trying to kill his client, a prominent surgeon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902070500 +0000" stop="20250902080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Kathy Ackers hires Cannon to find out why her father, a banker, committed suicide at a Caribbean resort. She thinks he was murdered, and wants Cannon to prove it. But the man was embezzling from his own bank, so maybe he did have a motive to kill himself...</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902080500 +0000" stop="20250902090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dance With Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When a friend of a disco dancer is found murdered, she believes she's a killer's real target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902090000 +0000" stop="20250902093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Baseball</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Police search for a safecracker who left his calling card at the scene of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902093000 +0000" stop="20250902100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - The Victims</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's cases range from purse snatching to homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902100000 +0000" stop="20250902103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 11 -- It's Just A Little Dent, Isn't It?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed dents the fender of the patrol car while putting gas in it and frets the entire shift about the impact of it on his career. Meanwhile they deal with a man who wants revenge against a woman who testified against his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902103000 +0000" stop="20250902110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 91 -- You're Not The First Guy's Had The Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's ability to focus on his job is put to the test when his close friend and fellow academy partner is critically wounded during a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902110000 +0000" stop="20250902120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Bluegrass State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony trek through Kentucky!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902120000 +0000" stop="20250902123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Goes In Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert begin a lawn mowing business and plan to go door to door in seach of lawns that need to be mowed. However, shortly after they venture out, Eddie gives the boys some advice that leads them into trouble and Gilbert to bail out of the business when their first client appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902123000 +0000" stop="20250902130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Kite Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An upcoming father-son kite day has Beaver getting all excited when Ward agrees to participate with him. They do a great job building a kite together but when Gilbert talks Beaver into testing it out, the kite crashes and falls apart. This leaves Beaver with the duty to tell Ward just what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902130000 +0000" stop="20250902140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Deadly Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When Robert Crane is charged with the murder of his sister's estranged husband, Mason needs the testimony of sister Helen Reed to clear him of the charge. Unfortunately for all concerned, Helen suffers from multiple personality disorder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902140000 +0000" stop="20250902150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Scrooge  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a scrooge of a store owner is accused of murdering his partner, Matlock defends the man and makes a strange request as part of his fee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902150000 +0000" stop="20250902160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Gunshot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil is forced to shoot a suspect in an armed robbery. He has trouble dealing with the consequences of his actions, after he realizes the person he shot was a teenaged girl - and no one can locate the gun he believed she was pointing at him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902160000 +0000" stop="20250902170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Family Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason helps Verdie research her family tree</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902170000 +0000" stop="20250902180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Perce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>An outlaw named Perce McCall helps Matt fend off three gunmen, much to everyone's surprise.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902180000 +0000" stop="20250902190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Single Pilgrim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hoss is accidentally shot, two settlers from Virginia argue over what to do with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902190000 +0000" stop="20250902193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Day Of Reckoning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is torn by conflicting emotions when he meets the town's new preacher—a former outlaw whom he vowed to kill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902193000 +0000" stop="20250902200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Day The Town Slept</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E29</episode-num>
    <desc>The town of North Fork becomes a haven for outlaws when suave Ben Judson smooth-talks his way into the marshal's job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902200000 +0000" stop="20250902210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Path Of The Serpent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>At a Rocky Mountains fort, a wounded soldier asks his old friend, Ruddy Blaine, to bring his daughter to him before he dies. With the Ute indians on the warpath, Blaine will have to take a dangerous route known only to him and the Shoshone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902210000 +0000" stop="20250902220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>That Time Of Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Everyone gives Roy advice on where to go on vacation. Roy gets dizzy during a fire at a singles club. An instructor is injured during a self-defense class. A man with stomach pains is brought into Rampart. The firemen rescue two hang glider pilots from the face of a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902220000 +0000" stop="20250902223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Colonel's Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>While Colonel Potter goes to Tokyo on R&amp;R, his horse develops colic. Klinger becomes chronically depressed, and Hot Lips gets appendicitis. The horse is flushed out with a hose, Hawkeye and B.J. perform an appendectomy on Hot Lips, and all are well when Potter returns, except Klinger. Potter offers Klinger a discharge for severe depression, and Klinger gets very excited, which loses him the discharge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902223000 +0000" stop="20250902230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Exorcism</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After Potter orders Radar to move a Korean spirit post believed to ward off evil spirits, things mysteriously begin to go wrong. When an old Korean man is brought into camp for medical attention, he refuses surgery unless the spirits in the camp are exorcised. A priestess is brought in, who exhibits her dance and her bells and chants. All is well, and Radar returns the spirit post to its original position.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902230000 +0000" stop="20250902233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hawk's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Hawkeye bemoans the young age of the wounded, he appears to develop problems. Sleepwalking and bad dreams, according to Sidney Freedman, are taking Hawkeye back to a simple time, but the horrors of war continue to intrude. After Sidney's assurances that he is as sane as can be, Hawkeye's life once again seems to settle down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250902233000 +0000" stop="20250903000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Unforgettable Characters</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets accepted into the "Famous Las Vegas Writers School," and begins to write his impressions of the camp. It happens to be Frank's birthday, so Hawkeye and B.J. stage a fight with each other to make Frank happy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903000000 +0000" stop="20250903003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Loaded Goat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An escaped goat eats a case of dynamite that was going to be used for blasting and puts Mayberry in danger—especially when Otis Campbell gets drunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903003000 +0000" stop="20250903010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Rafe Hollister Sings</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Rafe Hollister, a simple farmer with an incredible voice, is encouraged by Andy to enter the Mayberry singing contest, much to the dismay of the mayor and other officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903010000 +0000" stop="20250903013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts In London</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are on the plane to England, with Sir Jethro as their leader. But with this comes a detour. The Clampetts get off the plane in San Francisco, after Jethro believes it is England. They get back on the plane and do finally arrive in England and are told that Jed’s cousin, Marcus, is late, meaning deceased, but they think he means late because he is diseased. After they arrive, Granny runs into trouble at the customs inspector’s office and gets her medical supplies and her jug confiscated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903013000 +0000" stop="20250903020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Third Finger, Left Loaf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked to be the best man at his friend's wedding. The night before the ceremony, he loses the ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903020000 +0000" stop="20250903023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Informer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Carter enters the camp and Hogan discovers a spy among his men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903023000 +0000" stop="20250903030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hold That Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The POWs smuggle a tiger tank, about which Klink has been boasting, into camp in order to photograph and study it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903030000 +0000" stop="20250903033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball And George Carlin (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball and George Carlin. Originally aired on 11/24/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903033000 +0000" stop="20250903043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Arrogant Arsonist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a retired fire chief is accused by a reporter of burning down his own warehouse for insurance money, he threatens the reporter with a $1.5 million slander suit, demanding that he publicly retract his statement. The reporter doesn't quite comply and ends up dead, landing the fire chief in jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903043500 +0000" stop="20250903050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Once Upon A Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor living in the year 1890 accidentally activates a time traveling helmet, which transports him to 1962—and then promptly breaks down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903050500 +0000" stop="20250903053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Road Hog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman is responsible for a death when he refuses to allow a truck to pass him on a narrow road.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903053500 +0000" stop="20250903060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Specialty Of The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A restaurant is specialized in "serving" its costumers very well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903060500 +0000" stop="20250903070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Broken Mirror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is brought into the case of the kidnapping of a tycoon's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903070500 +0000" stop="20250903080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Private eyes so rarely get a vacation free of peril, and Cannon is no exception. He goes fishing, little knowing that someone from his police past is hunting him: a murderer determined on revenge for the time he spent in prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903080500 +0000" stop="20250903090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Protectors, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An assault on a businessman leads Barnaby to work with a firm that specializes in preventing terrorist kidnappings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903090000 +0000" stop="20250903093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903093000 +0000" stop="20250903100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A neo-Nazi psycho has planted a bomb somewhere in L.A. Friday and Gannon have to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903100000 +0000" stop="20250903103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 161 -- And You Want Me To Get Married!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After an evening at Jim's with his wife, Pete's girlfriend, Donna, is making marriage comments that has Pete running for cover. Mixed in with their calls is a domestic noise complaint Pete uses to support his bachelorhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903103000 +0000" stop="20250903110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 71 -- I Feel Like A Fool, Malloy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It is a shift of conflicts forcing Malloy and Reed to use their wits to keep control and make the right decisions end on a low note.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903110000 +0000" stop="20250903120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Caveman Days</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903120000 +0000" stop="20250903123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Doll Buggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a rundown mini-race car from Eddie and needs to find a set of wheels for it. Beaver decides to ask Penny Woods if he could have the wheels off her old doll buggy but finds himself in an awkward position: pushing a doll buggy down the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903123000 +0000" stop="20250903130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Substitute Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Before leaving on a business trip, Ward asks Wally to look after June and Beaver and Wally does indeed. However, when Miss Landers hears Beaver swear at a bully, Beaver turns to Wally to handle the situation and be a "substitute father."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903130000 +0000" stop="20250903140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Empty Tin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Doris Hocksley is shown a personal ad in a Los Angeles newspaper for locating the daughter of Adam Hocksley and providing proof of same. A friend, John Lowell, suggests she pursue the idea to prove she is the rightful heir to the Adam Hocksley estate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903140000 +0000" stop="20250903150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>With Matlock out of town, Michelle takes a murder case in which she suspects an old lawyer friend may be the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903150000 +0000" stop="20250903160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Country Mouse, City Mouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Virgil's visiting niece and Bubba's nephew team up in an effort to escape the boredom of small town life. But they get more excitement than they bargained for when they cross paths with a dangerous parolee.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903160000 +0000" stop="20250903170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903170000 +0000" stop="20250903180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Us Haggens</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt hunts down outlaw Black Jack Haggen, assisted by the killer's nephew, Festus, who has his own reasons for wanting to find his uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903180000 +0000" stop="20250903190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold-plated Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Jamie runs off after getting in trouble for breaking a special rifle that Ben told him never to touch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903190000 +0000" stop="20250903193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Milly's Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A veteran returns with tales of heroism and the fate of Milly's brother in the Civil War.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903193000 +0000" stop="20250903200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A head wound wipes out Lucas' memory, leaving him with only one clue: he's wearing an outlaw's gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903200000 +0000" stop="20250903210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Odyssey Of Flint Mccullough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Looking forward to some time off, Flint heads towards the town of Monument. However, his plans run afoul when he meets an old man and some kids whose parents were just massacred by Mescaleros. They're running low on supplies, especially milk for the baby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903210000 +0000" stop="20250903220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Fair Fight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The crew finds a droopy-eyed hound dog in the station; at an industrial fire, Gage and DeSoto check a secret room for victims; a "therapeutic" argument between a husband and wife keeps getting out of hand; while attempting to rescue two injured workers, Johnny is trapped in a tunnel cave-in.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903220000 +0000" stop="20250903223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>38 Across</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Befuddled by a crossword puzzle, Hawkeye persuades his old friend, Tippy Brooks, a whiz at puzzles, to come to camp. Tippy arrives with his commanding officer, Admiral Prescot, thinking it's a medical emergency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903223000 +0000" stop="20250903230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ping Pong</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Lieutenant Colonel Harold Beckett lies wounded in post-op waiting to get back to the front for five more days of combat duty to get his promotion. Meanwhile, Cho Lin, the Ping Pong champ, is engaged to Soony. He leaves to get her a ring, when the South Korean army conscripts him. He arrives at the 4077th as a wounded soldier, and after being patched up he is married at the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903230000 +0000" stop="20250903233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>End Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Billy Tyler, a young black sergeant, is brought into camp with a bullet wound in the leg. He is a football player, and when he discovers that his leg has been amputated, he wants to die. After talks with Radar, Billy agrees that he must live on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250903233000 +0000" stop="20250904000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hanky Panky</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Nurse Carrie Donovan receives a Dear Jane letter from her husband, and practically falls apart. B.J. consoles her, and they spend the night together. Feelings of guilt come over B.J. until he discusses them with Donovan and the air is cleared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904000000 +0000" stop="20250904003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Spoiled Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Arnold the spoiled kid moves to town, he thinks he can walk all over the townsfolk, including Andy and Barney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904003000 +0000" stop="20250904010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Filling Station Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is accused of being the mysterious crook who's been robbing Wally's filling station. Andy and Barney try to determine his guilt or innocence in a variety of methods.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904010000 +0000" stop="20250904013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett Castle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts finally arrive at Clampett Castle, and meet Mr. Faversham, who they call Major Domo after a misunderstanding with his name, also mistaking his name for a greeting. Granny decides to check on Marcus, but doesn’t know that the dog of the house is sitting in his bed. She feels the dog through the curtain and thinks the staff and doctors have been neglecting him. Jethro is working on fulfilling his duty as a knight and decides to start hunting dragons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904013000 +0000" stop="20250904020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>The Blind Date</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Carter sets Gomer up with a blind date who thinks he is an oil millionaire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904020000 +0000" stop="20250904023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Of The Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Stalag 13 is named one of the top 10 prison camps in Germany, but it's just a distraction for Hogan and his men to destroy a secret rocket bomb.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904023000 +0000" stop="20250904030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Late Inspector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting general upsets plans to blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904030000 +0000" stop="20250904033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Lucille Ball And George Carlin (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Lucille Ball and George Carlin. Originally aired on 11/24/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904033000 +0000" stop="20250904043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Garrulous Go-between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A naive young woman enlists the help of not only Paul and Mason but also a fortuneteller. After confiding in her loquacious landlord, he and his pet parrot end up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904043500 +0000" stop="20250904050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Five Characters In Search Of An Exit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A hobo, clown, bagpipe player, ballerina and military officer are trapped in a huge cylinder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904050500 +0000" stop="20250904053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>An Occurrence At Owl Creek</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A Southerner is about to be hanged for attempting to destroy a bridge vital to the Union's advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904053500 +0000" stop="20250904060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Graduating Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A teacher gets too involved in the life of one of her students.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904060500 +0000" stop="20250904070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of A Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix investigates the mysterious death of an Air Force pilot who died right before the presentation of an experimental aircraft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904070500 +0000" stop="20250904080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Avenger</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon takes on a missing person's case which leads to the death of a policeman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904080500 +0000" stop="20250904090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fatal Overture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband and wife are framed for the death of the husband's ex-lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904090000 +0000" stop="20250904093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapping</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon help an employee rescue her kidnapped boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904093000 +0000" stop="20250904100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904100000 +0000" stop="20250904103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 72 -- El Presidente</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy teases Reed about calculating the cost of a new house while their first baby is still six months away. In the meantime they settle a domestic dispute between arguing neighbors and help a taxi driver who was just robbed as well as a local man mistaken as the president by a group of rural Mexicans. Finally, they must arrest a psychotic shooter holed up in his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904103000 +0000" stop="20250904110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 101: Someone Stole My Lawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed wants an early dinner when his wife puts him on a low-cal diet. However, one after another events prevents them from going code 7 all night long. Events include the theft of a man's sod, stolen credit cards and a suspected car theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904110000 +0000" stop="20250904120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>1000th Episode</sub-title>
    <desc>"Yep, it's our 1000th episode! Quizzer takes Bill on a stroll down memory lane. Plus, five cartoon premieres!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904120000 +0000" stop="20250904123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Goes Steady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June find themselves in the dark when they hear through the grapevine that not only is Wally going steady with Evelyn Boothby but that wedding bells may be heard soon. Meanwhile, Wally gets a different picture of marital life through Evelyn's sister and her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904123000 +0000" stop="20250904130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>No Time For Baby Sitters</sub-title>
    <desc>"June, Ward and Wally are going out for the evening and not wanting to worry about Beaver, June calls a babysitter, despite Beaver's pleas against the idea."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904130000 +0000" stop="20250904140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Half-wakened Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Lawton goes to visit old friend Scott Shelby and ends up being charged with his muder. Fortunately for Lawton, Mason is another old friend of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904140000 +0000" stop="20250904150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Model  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock has finally had a breakthrough in the case he was struggling with, but after being hit by a car, he needs to put the case together from scratch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904150000 +0000" stop="20250904160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie suspects that JoAnn's new cook is connected to the murder of a young prostitute. But Virgil suspects the culprit maybe a local pimp who has been intimidating the women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904160000 +0000" stop="20250904170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ordeal - Part Ii</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth falls while standing on top of a wood pile and fractures her leg; Doctors doubt her ability to walk ever again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904170000 +0000" stop="20250904180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Quint Asper Comes Home</sub-title>
    <desc>"A half-Indian named Quint Asper vows revenge on all white men when a pair of drifters kill his father and threaten his mother."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904180000 +0000" stop="20250904190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Top Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A trail boss battle ensues when the Cartwrights pick Kelly, a former ranch hand on the Ponderosa, but Mr. Weatherby knows that Kelly was fired on a previous cattle drive for drinking.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904190000 +0000" stop="20250904193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Executioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A former neighbor of the McCain's is released from jail after serving his sentence for stage coach robbery, but the money was never found. Lucas agrees to let the man work for him, but the new work hand holds a secret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904193000 +0000" stop="20250904200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Lou Mallory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou Mallory has arrived in North Fork and quickly purchases land, which includes the hotel and Milly Scott's store. She pays higher prices than the sellers feel their properties are worth. Everyone is happy until they find out that Lou really is an astute businesswoman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904200000 +0000" stop="20250904210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Beth Pearson Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The leaders of the wagon train are taken aback when they see a woman asking to join the group who is the twin of Major Adams one and only love—who died in his arms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904210000 +0000" stop="20250904220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Rules Of Order</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A driver crashes into a pole, injuring two workers. John and Roy are asked to be on a paramedic advisory committee, but they have to put up with everyone's favorite paramedic, Brice. The firemen rescue a stunt climber from the side of a building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904220000 +0000" stop="20250904223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hepatitis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy comes down with infectious hepatitis, and Hawkeye has to give the whole camp antibiotics, while dealing with a psychosomatic back pain. Meanwhile, B.J. has to perform a very difficult operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904223000 +0000" stop="20250904230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General's Practitioner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of Hawkeye being considered, much to his distaste, for the position of a general's personal physician, Radar becomes a surrogate father to a Korean woman and her baby, until the baby's GI father returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904230000 +0000" stop="20250904233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Movie Tonight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>As a cure for the increased tension at the 4077th, Potter obtains a copy of his favorite film, "My Darling Clementine," and makes a social event out of it. As the film continues to break, tensions rise, until Mulcahy plays the piano, Radar does his impersonations and everyone acts out scenes from the film.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250904233000 +0000" stop="20250905000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Souvenirs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Korean children and American soldiers are often badly wounded when they hunt for souvenirs that the enemy have booby-trapped. Potter asks for it to stop, and Hawkeye and B.J. put a local junk dealer out of business.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905000000 +0000" stop="20250905003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy Discovers America</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie doesn't like his new teacher, "Old Lady Crump," because she gives too much homework. Andy comments on the teacher, words which Opie twists in his retelling to Ms. Crump, and she is furious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905003000 +0000" stop="20250905010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Medicine Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, saddened by the death of a friend, is feeling old and tired. She stumbles across a medicine man's presentation and is intrigued by his bottle of elixir, which she believes to add pep to her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905010000 +0000" stop="20250905013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl From Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick arrives with his daughter, Essiebelle. He found love letters Jethro wrote to his daughter, a beauty contest winner. He plans to get Jethro and Essiebelle married so he can get his paws in the Clampett fortune.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905013000 +0000" stop="20250905020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Home On The Range</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer helps out a family by finding them shelter in a shack, unaware that the shack is the target of impending war games.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905020000 +0000" stop="20250905023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flight Of The Valkyrie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Because of all the "funny business" going on, Klink brings in Colonel Crittendon to replace Hogan as officer in charge of POWs. His arrival louses up plans to help a German baroness escape to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905023000 +0000" stop="20250905030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner's Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A British commando gives Hogan the assignment he failed at: blow up an ammo dump. Once done, Hogan uses a German general to find out where he is planning to attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905030000 +0000" stop="20250905033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Trini Lopez And Nanette Fabray</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Trini Lopez and Nanette Fabray. Originally aired on 03/09/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905033000 +0000" stop="20250905043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Woeful Widower</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Certain that her employer is plotting to murder his wife, housekeeper Nellie Conway launches her counterattack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905043500 +0000" stop="20250905050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Quality Of Mercy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A soldier gets a new perspective on war when he is forced to experience it from his enemy's point of view.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905050500 +0000" stop="20250905053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Whodunit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur comes back from the afterlife to find out the identity of his murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905053500 +0000" stop="20250905060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Ikon Of Elijah</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A man's dream of wealth takes form when he learns of a treasure buried in the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905060500 +0000" stop="20250905070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Inside Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling to New Orleans, Mannix goes undercover in the Big Easy to protect an informer and avenge the death of a pal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905070500 +0000" stop="20250905080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Killing In The Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former prostitute aids Cannon in an investigation involving mobsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905080500 +0000" stop="20250905090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Master Of Deception</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A man marries many women involved in electronics projects to steal their industrial secrets.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905090000 +0000" stop="20250905093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905093000 +0000" stop="20250905100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905100000 +0000" stop="20250905103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 132 -- Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed tries to pawn off his new litter of puppies to co-workers, strangers and even victims. The officers work a silent alarm, rescue a boy with his head stuck in a fence and track down a prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905103000 +0000" stop="20250905110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 111: Snake In The Trunk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A ditzy young woman reports her 1958 Ford convertible stolen while she went into a liquor store. She left the keys in the car, has no paperwork, doesn't know the license number or other details but she needs it by 6 PM for a date. She finally tells the officers that her eight-foot boa constrictor is in the trunk as she was coming from the vet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905110000 +0000" stop="20250905120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Tiny Trends</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore tiny trends!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905120000 +0000" stop="20250905123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>For $25, Wally buys a car and signs a contract with the owner knowing full well what he's getting, a car that doesn't start. Wally quickly finds himself with more trouble then he bargained for when the lemon becomes a fixture in front of the Cleaver home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905123000 +0000" stop="20250905130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has told his parents that he doesn't want anything big for his birthday and they decide to respect his wishes and give him a gift of money. Beaver also gets quite a bit of money from other relatives and finds himself debating on whether or not to spend it or put in the bank, like his parents suggest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905130000 +0000" stop="20250905140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Desperate Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Stefan Riker has come from Germany seeking the woman posing as Lisa Bannister. Attempting to help her stepmother, Doris Bannister pretends to be romantically interested in Stefan Riker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905140000 +0000" stop="20250905150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Talk Show  (s4, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When talk show host Dan Galloway is murdered after publicly humiliating three woman on the air and firing his executive producer, Matlock has no shortage of suspects as he looks for clues in the death of the despised man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905150000 +0000" stop="20250905160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Tear Down The Walls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A minister who was integrating his church(by inviting Virgil and Althea to attend services)is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905160000 +0000" stop="20250905170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Return - Part I</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to Walton's Mountain to write about the failing economy and lack of jobs</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905170000 +0000" stop="20250905180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Pillagers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S13E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty and fellow traveling passenger Newly O'Brien are captured by Mexican outlaw Manez and his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905180000 +0000" stop="20250905190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Deck Of Aces</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S12E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Confusion ensues when Bradley Meredith, a Ben Cartwright look-a-like, accepts a land deal with the railroad as Ben.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905190000 +0000" stop="20250905193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Marshal Torrance is heading home from a cattle sale with Lucas and Mark when the old lawman mysteriously disappears. They trace him to a nearby Mexican ghost town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905193000 +0000" stop="20250905200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Waste: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Alphonso's wife gives birth, the bandits holding Marshal Torrance relax their guard, enabling Lucas and Mark to rescue the old man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905200000 +0000" stop="20250905210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jed Polke Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When Flint brings a stranded woman and boy to the train, her husband, who went off to find help, is also soon found. But his return to the train sets off tempers when four men recognize him and their only thought is murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905210000 +0000" stop="20250905220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Exam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>John and Roy worry about their recertification exams. A fireman's widow keeps calling the station for assistance in minor matters. A TV sports fan experiences shortness of breath. The daughter of the fireman’s widow suffers a serious fall. An accident on a movie set turns deadly.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905220000 +0000" stop="20250905223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Post Op</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In the midst of a deluge of patients and their individual medical histories, the 4077th is out of blood. Everyone in camp is donating at 48-hour intervals when a truckload of Turkish soldiers arrives to offer their blood and save the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905223000 +0000" stop="20250905230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Margaret's Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Prompted by pressure from Frank, Hot Lips sets a date for marriage with Lieutenant Colonel Donald Penobscott. When Donald arrives in camp for the wedding, a bridal shower and bachelor party are given. When he has passed out drunk, Hawkeye and B.J. place Donald in a body cast and convince him that he has broken his leg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905230000 +0000" stop="20250905233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 1  (s6, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250905233000 +0000" stop="20250906000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Fade Out, Fade In: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Radar gets a temporary replacement for Maj. Burns: a Major Charles Emerson Winchester III. Maj. Winchester arrives at the 4077th, only to painfully discover that he's the permanent replacement Frank Burns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906000000 +0000" stop="20250906003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darlings Are Coming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Mayberry is visited by an unusual family from the mountains.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906003000 +0000" stop="20250906010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's English Valet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A tourist from England has to do chores to pay off a fine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906010000 +0000" stop="20250906013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Lingers On</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Lafe Crick returns to the Clampett mansion looking to get rich off Jed's money. He tries to get a job at the bank guarding Jed's money, only to get a few million dollars. But Granny has her doubts about the freeloader, though he seems to be proving her wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906013000 +0000" stop="20250906020000 +0000">
    <title>Gomer Pyle, U.S.M.C.</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer Untrains A Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is chosen to look after a new sentry dog. Gomer being Gomer, however, he promptly turns the trained guard dog into a pet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906020000 +0000" stop="20250906023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>German Bridge Is Falling Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The heroes plan to blow up a bridge near camp when a bomber raid fails.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906023000 +0000" stop="20250906030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Movies Are Your Best Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must discover what is contained within the documents of a visiting German general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906030000 +0000" stop="20250906033000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Martha Raye And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Martha Raye and Tim Conway. Originally aired on 12/08/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906033000 +0000" stop="20250906043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Simple Simon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Actress Ramona Carver is confronted by a young man who claims to be her son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906043500 +0000" stop="20250906050500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nothing In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A lonely old woman refuses to leave her apartment for fear of meeting "Mr. Death."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906050500 +0000" stop="20250906053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A South American native helps his boss' wife when it's evident that she needs a shrink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906053500 +0000" stop="20250906060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Backward, Turn Backward</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man is murdered, suspicion falls on his daughter's suitor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906060500 +0000" stop="20250906070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to uncover the past life of an amnesia victim who is a Vietnam veteran.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906070500 +0000" stop="20250906080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flashpoint</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is on the case when a psychiatric patient is accused of rape and murder after falling in with some unsavory companions. CANNON attempts to clear a young man accused of rape-murder while the real villain's mother accuses her son of the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906080500 +0000" stop="20250906090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Short Happy Life, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty's cousin is unaware that she's carrying a locker key that the two men stalking her are willing to kill for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250906090000 +0000" stop="20250906093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Organ Fund</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Hooterville folks are faced with a larcenous fundraiser when they try to find enough money to buy the church a new organ.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
