<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118070000 +0000" stop="20260118080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Mermaid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Crane captures a mermaid who eventually leads the sub to an undersea nuclear bomb about to explode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118080000 +0000" stop="20260118090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Wild Journey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When human time travelers from the future arrive on the Land of the Giants for a research mission, Steve and Dan steal their time machine and try to return to the day of the Spindrift launch to prevent the fateful trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118090000 +0000" stop="20260118100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>One Way To The Moon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug materialize on the first manned flight to Mars, where their added weight forces a change in flight plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118100000 +0000" stop="20260118110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Genesis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>David Vincent discovers the aliens have taken over a sea lab for sinister purposes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118110000 +0000" stop="20260118120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Runaway</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams meets a runaway slave named Isaac and decides to help him by letting stay at the cabin. Mad Jack thinks this may lead to trouble should Isaac's master come looking for him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118120000 +0000" stop="20260118123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Miracle Of Flight</sub-title>
    <desc>"An analysis of the ‘miracle of flight’ from the soaring condors of the Andes to the backward-flying fairy terns of Midway."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118123000 +0000" stop="20260118130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Prairie Village</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the base of Devils Tower near Horse Heaven Pass in Wyoming, is a wilderness city populated by the ….prairie dog."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118130000 +0000" stop="20260118133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Monkey Shines</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim rate the I.Q.’s of the gorilla, chimpanzee, baboon, orangutan, gibbon and ring-tailed monkey."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118133000 +0000" stop="20260118140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Island Outposts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim go island-hopping around the world."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118140000 +0000" stop="20260118143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Puma Pass</sub-title>
    <desc>"A story of the community of wildlife living in a mountain valley, reigned over by a puma who lives at the head of the pass."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118143000 +0000" stop="20260118150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Fact Or Fallacy</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim set out to separate fact from fallacy among many popularly held ideas about the animal kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118150000 +0000" stop="20260118153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Brady Braves (part 3)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While trying to find their way back to camp, Bobby and Cindy encounter the Indian boy again, who leads them back to a worried Mike and Carol. However, Bobby and Cindy's wanting to help the Indian boy, Jimmy, in his quest of running away to become an astronaut gets them into more trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118153000 +0000" stop="20260118160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>The Wheeler-dealer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After passing his driver's exam, Greg buys a car for $100 from his friend Eddie. Greg's bought a lemon though, and has a tough time getting rid of it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118160000 +0000" stop="20260118163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is looking for a beau for his gorgeous daughter, so Drysdale and Jane set Elly up with Fred Penrod, a young accountant at the bank. However, no one can seem to get his name straight. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns to plant a paw-paw tree in the back yard, really to look for the Clampett fortune he still believes is buried in the back yard.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118163000 +0000" stop="20260118170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Son Of Lafe Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Elly May and her new beau, Fred Penron, are getting rather serious. Meanwhile, Lafe Crick returns, this time with his son, Dub. He plans to set Dub up with Elly, to once again try to get some of Jed's money. Jed and Jethro try to hide this from Granny because the Cricks really rile her up. She sees the Cricks, but Jed tries to convince her that she is having visions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118170000 +0000" stop="20260118173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Punch In The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>In going through some courthouse paperwork, Barney discovers an open case involving Floyd and Charlie Foley. He tries to close the books on the case, but ends up reopening the arguments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118173000 +0000" stop="20260118180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Bonus Bucks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A dollar bill takes a zany trip—with the Ricardos and Mertzes in hot pursuit. It's a winning bill (worth $300) in a newspaper contest. It belongs to Ricky, but he gallantly slips it into Lucy's purse. Gallant isn't necessarily smart: Lucy unthinkingly gives the bill to the grocery delivery boy, who gives it to Ethel in change.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118180000 +0000" stop="20260118183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Junior Fire Chief</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver decides to run for junior fire chief and, to his surprise, wins. However, as soon as he's elected, he lets the responsibilities go to his head and begins issuing citations to not only his family but his neighbors as well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118183000 +0000" stop="20260118190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Frogs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver wants a canoe and makes a deal with Ward: If Beaver can come up with half the money, Ward will pay for the other half. So Beaver, comes up with a way of making money by selling frogs. However, little does he know that the man who's going to buy the frogs, uses them for class dissections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118190000 +0000" stop="20260118200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Night Of The Strangler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A series of rag doll stranglings brings Charlie's Angels in to the case. Charlie counts on Kelly's resemblance to the first murdered girl to attract the killer. The wife of a well-known fashion designer is the next victim.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118200000 +0000" stop="20260118210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Jonathan Hart, Jr.</sub-title>
    <desc>"A small time crook pressures a former girlfriend to claim their young son is actually Jonathan's child."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118210000 +0000" stop="20260118220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Voodoo / Parent Trap</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ann and Tony Kellino's fantasy to reunite their parents comes true when they set a "Parent Trap" on Fantasy Island. Bill Jordan programs Jane Howell in her sleep to believe she is Marion Connors. Jane discovers her real identity through "Voodoo" on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118220000 +0000" stop="20260118230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Pride Of The Pacific / Viking's Son / Separate Vacations / Experiment / Getting To Know You (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ellen and Jesse are beginning to get annoyed with each other and to find the cruise monotonous. Having been beaten during the games in Vancouver, Merrill Stubing's competitive spirit kicks in and he becomes as tough as Gunner Norquist is, upsetting Vicki and relentlessly driving his crew to physical exertion. Harry Meachum romances Britta the masseuse, who tells him Gunner Norquist hired professional athletes to rig the games."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118230000 +0000" stop="20260118233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Newspaper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie and his friends decide to start a newspaper. The early issues don't sell well, so the boys begin eavesdropping and printing local gossip in the paper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260118233000 +0000" stop="20260119000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Theme Parks- Morgan Richardson</sub-title>
    <desc>"Collector Morgan Richardson not only designs theme parks, he collectes all things theme park related.  Disney and pop culture Expert Joel Magee joins Lisa to appraise Morgan's fantastic collection."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119000000 +0000" stop="20260119003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Kim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye operates on a five-year-old Korean boy, and Radar can't find his family. Henry plans to send him to the orphanage, and the camp enjoys his company while they can. Trapper decides to adopt him after consulting his wife, and has to rescue him after he wanders into the minefield.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119003000 +0000" stop="20260119010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>L.i.p.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Corporal Walker is being sent home, and he wants to marry his Korean girl so she and their baby can return with him. CID sends Lt Willis to investigate, but when he refuses Hawkeye and Trapper frame him. Hawkeye is upset that a nurse he was pursuing does not approve of the marriage between "a gook" and "one of us."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119010000 +0000" stop="20260119013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Commercial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith is chosen to appear in a tv commericial but finds herself unable to lie when she begins to doubt the quality of the sponsor's detergent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119013000 +0000" stop="20260119020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Iola's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie refuses to let Edith's elderly aunt move into their spare bedroom, even after she's been turned away by every other relative.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119020000 +0000" stop="20260119023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Love Comes To The Butcher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is jealous when a lonely butcher lavishes attention on Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119023000 +0000" stop="20260119030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Two's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike and Archie have a long talk after they find themself locked in the storeroom of Archie's Place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119030000 +0000" stop="20260119033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Meeting The Parents</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Amy's parents arrive unexpectedly at her apartment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119033000 +0000" stop="20260119040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Plan, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is put in charge of selecting his wedding invitations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119040000 +0000" stop="20260119043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Two Faces Of Rob</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob disguises his voice on the phone as a practical joke, but Laura decides to play along.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119043000 +0000" stop="20260119050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Attempted Marriage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob recounts his hectic wedding days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119050000 +0000" stop="20260119053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Young Man With A Horn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph tries to hit the high note on a civil service exam as well as his cornet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119053000 +0000" stop="20260119060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapped in a recurring nightmare, a man tries to persuade those who are sentencing him to death that the whole scenario is not real.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119060000 +0000" stop="20260119070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Ten Minutes From Now  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An apparently insane performer is suspected of making bomb threats to a local official.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119070000 +0000" stop="20260119080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe Corvin, a Syndicate money handler, ships millions through Swiss banks and the IMF must put him out of business. Corvin uses a courier that the IMF set up; Corvin has him killed and needs a new courier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119080000 +0000" stop="20260119090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Not With A Whimper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble arrives in the factory town of Hempstead Mills, West Virginia to assist Andrew McCallister, his longtime mentor whom is dying from lung cancer which he is confined to a wheelchair. McCallister's vigorous anti-smog campaign has earned him a reputati</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119090000 +0000" stop="20260119100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Forty Reasons To Kill (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell unearths a deadly power struggle when he investigates the murder of an old friend--and finds himself the prime suspect in a second killing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119100000 +0000" stop="20260119103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Lsd Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Joe Friday and his partner, Bill Gannon, encounter a freaked-out young LSD user. This is the famous "Blue Boy" episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119103000 +0000" stop="20260119110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Explosion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A neo-Nazi psycho has planted a bomb somewhere in L.A. Friday and Gannon have to find it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119110000 +0000" stop="20260119113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 153 -- Find Me A Needle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for the "Mulholland Mauler," who has raped six female hitchhikers and left them for dead. They quickly make an arrest of a likely suspect and take him to the location of an abandoned vehicle, after learning its owner never made it to her destination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119113000 +0000" stop="20260119120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 52 -- Good Cop: Handle With Care</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed see a man passed out in an alley and stop to lend assistance, deliver bad news to a young wife, apprehend a mentally ill man who then becomes uncontrollably violent in their patrol car, and respond to a robbery that needlessly becomes a tragedy. All along the way the officers have their every move second guessed by a pair of young, unethical freelance journalists who are determined to document police brutality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119120000 +0000" stop="20260119130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Sew Be It!</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119130000 +0000" stop="20260119133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Goes In Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert begin a lawn mowing business and plan to go door to door in seach of lawns that need to be mowed. However, shortly after they venture out, Eddie gives the boys some advice that leads them into trouble and Gilbert to bail out of the business when their first client appears.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119133000 +0000" stop="20260119140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Kite Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E37</episode-num>
    <desc>An upcoming father-son kite day has Beaver getting all excited when Ward agrees to participate with him. They do a great job building a kite together but when Gilbert talks Beaver into testing it out, the kite crashes and falls apart. This leaves Beaver with the duty to tell Ward just what happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119140000 +0000" stop="20260119150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Guilty Clients</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Lola and Jeff Bronson are going through a divorce and can't wait to be rid of each other—until Bill Ryder sabotages Jeff's business and makes a play for Lola. When Ryder is found dead, Jeff and Lola are the two prime suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119150000 +0000" stop="20260119160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ex  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Julie's in Baltimore defending a man accused of killing a newspaper editor who besmirched his name. Complicating matters is the prosecutor, who just happens to be Julie's ex-husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119160000 +0000" stop="20260119170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Up Tight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>After Danno fails to stop a woman from jumping to her death off a seaside cliff, McGarrett investigates David Stone, a drug-promoting professor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119170000 +0000" stop="20260119180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Love Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>John Boy falls in love with Jenny Pendelton.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119180000 +0000" stop="20260119190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Honey Pot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Newcomer Ben Stack makes a play for saloon girl Honey Dare.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119190000 +0000" stop="20260119200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Infernal Machine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A conniving city slicker vanishes with the funds collected from townsfolk to finance the manufacture of a horseless carriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119200000 +0000" stop="20260119203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Patsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of outlaws devise a plan to get rid of Lucas so they can take over the town of North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119203000 +0000" stop="20260119210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Bloodlines</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After Lucas kills a mountain man in a barroom brawl, his father arrives in North Fork determined to take revenge on Lucas and Marshal Torrance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119210000 +0000" stop="20260119220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Silver Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E25</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop tells Bill the story of the Earp brothers and the Silver Lady, a woman who was encased in a coffin of sliver coins that melted around her after the stagecoach she was riding on and guarded by Morgan Earp had an accident and burned."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119220000 +0000" stop="20260119230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Details</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While responding to a call, Roy and John witness a pedestrian being struck by a car. A woman is badly burnt in a fire. John thinks about settling down. A belly dancer overdoses on diet pills. A child bites a dog and the dog bites back. At a burning building, Roy and John must jump to safety.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119230000 +0000" stop="20260119233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Trial Of Henry Blake</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Majors Houlihan and Burns press charges against Colonel Blake to get him arrested and put Frank in charge. They also put Hawkeye and Trapper under arrest so that they can't help Henry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260119233000 +0000" stop="20260120000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Dad... Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Once more Hawkeye writes home to his father: the doctors operate on a soldier with a grenade shot into his body; Hawkeye and Trapper color the skin of a racist patient, who demanded the right color blood, while he is asleep; Henry gets a movie of his daughter's birthday from home; the officers hold the monthly staff meeting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120000000 +0000" stop="20260120003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Sniper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A lone sniper has the 4077th pinned down—including Radar and Henry in the shower. The poor boy thinks he's firing on McArthur's headquarters, and a chopper finally comes by and wounds him with gunfire from above, ending the siege. Hawkeye walks out to into the bush to tend to the wounded soldier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120003000 +0000" stop="20260120010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Carry On Hawkeye</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The camp succumbs to the Asian flu, except for Hawkeye and Margaret, who have to do everything themselves. As the others start to recover, Hawkeye falls ill but he still manages to operate when wounded arrive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120010000 +0000" stop="20260120013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Invisible Beau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee begins to feel that she is preventing Andy and Helen from pursuing their relationship. She then conjures up a beau for herself—trouble is it's the butter and egg man and he's already married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120013000 +0000" stop="20260120020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrest Of The Fun Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney arrest the "fun girls" for speeding. It turns out to be a big mistake because Helen and Thelma Lou become jealous.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120020000 +0000" stop="20260120023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sleepover At Peggy's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond is horrified when he thinks his "cookie nemesis" flirted with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120023000 +0000" stop="20260120030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Who's Next?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray seems pleased when Debra picks an attractive friend to replace her if she dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120030000 +0000" stop="20260120033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Flame Grows Higher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When a POW is caught at the processing location after Stalag 13, Hogan suspects there is a traitor in the underground. Newkirk and LeBeau help him find out who it is.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120033000 +0000" stop="20260120040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Request Permission To Escape</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>After receiving a "Dear John" letter, Carter asks Hogan if he can escape and get back to his girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120040000 +0000" stop="20260120043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol tries to hide that she's been drinking from her husband. Then, in Nora Desmond, Carol plays a has-been actress who's being roasted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120043000 +0000" stop="20260120053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hesitant Hostess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>When Albert Sanders is charged with the murder of Kim Lane, Mason offers to defend him free of charge because he knows Sanders is still devastated over the accidental death of his wife and children eight years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120053500 +0000" stop="20260120060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Mind And The Matter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A book on the power of thought enables an irritable man to re-create the world exactly as he wants it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120060500 +0000" stop="20260120070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Sign Of Satan  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>During the making of a horror film, a gruesome story unfolds as the lead begins to fear that a sect of devil worshipers may try to slay him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120070500 +0000" stop="20260120080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Edge Of The Knife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Surgeon Dr. Cameron McKenzie faces a difficult choice: he must let a patient die under his blade or face the death of his son, who's been kidnapped by the blackmailers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120080500 +0000" stop="20260120090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Murder By Proxy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A dead man hires Cannon! The man's will requires than an investigator look into his death, so Christopher Grant hires Cannon to see if any of the man's scheming relatives might have helped him to an early exit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120090500 +0000" stop="20260120100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Beware The Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A dog is the prime suspect in the fatal mauling of a man whose stepson is the dog's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120100000 +0000" stop="20260120103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Kidnapping</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon help an employee rescue her kidnapped boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120103000 +0000" stop="20260120110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Interrogation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A new officer has been arrested for robbing a liquor store while on an undercover assignment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120110000 +0000" stop="20260120113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 23: Pig Is A Three Letter Word</sub-title>
    <desc>"The officers are subjected to verbal abuse when they arrest armed robbers."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120113000 +0000" stop="20260120120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 83 -- A Different Thing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An older husband complains about his wife and friend's noisy karate practice. A hit and run traffic accident looks looks like a homicide. The officers use their investigative skills to locate the suspect and arrest him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120120000 +0000" stop="20260120130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>A Minor Misunderstanding</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony step into the courtroom!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120130000 +0000" stop="20260120133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Doll Buggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a rundown mini-race car from Eddie and needs to find a set of wheels for it. Beaver decides to ask Penny Woods if he could have the wheels off her old doll buggy but finds himself in an awkward position: pushing a doll buggy down the street.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120133000 +0000" stop="20260120140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Substitute Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Before leaving on a business trip, Ward asks Wally to look after June and Beaver and Wally does indeed. However, when Miss Landers hears Beaver swear at a bully, Beaver turns to Wally to handle the situation and be a "substitute father."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120140000 +0000" stop="20260120150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Jealous Journalist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The drowning death of a newspaper executive during a fishing trip sets off all kinds of repercussions at the newspaper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120150000 +0000" stop="20260120160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Clown  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend aging clown Homer Fleming after he's charged with the murder of his long-time partner. After asking Conrad to go undercover as a roustabout at the circus, Matlock learns that the deceased had many enemies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120160000 +0000" stop="20260120170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Face Of The Dragon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett must locate the source of an outbreak of bubonic plague on the Hawaiian islands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120170000 +0000" stop="20260120180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Courtship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>The family sets up their cousin Cody, a 64-year-old bachelor, on a date with Cordelia Hunnicutt</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120180000 +0000" stop="20260120190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The New Society</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E35</episode-num>
    <desc>A cowboy admires a buffalo hunter too much to admit that the man also is a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120190000 +0000" stop="20260120200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Secret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe is accused of murdering a girl. Her father and brothers want to hang Joe, but the Cartwrights are determined to prove his innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120200000 +0000" stop="20260120203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Blowout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly arrived gunslinger Al Walker throws a mammoth party at the saloon, keeping acting Marshal Ben Waller busy until Lucas is forced to intervene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120203000 +0000" stop="20260120210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Obituary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newspaperman Byron Claremont specializes in profiles of famous gunmen. One of his stories was responsible for an old-time marshal's death; and his next subject is Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120210000 +0000" stop="20260120220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jarbo Pierce Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E26</episode-num>
    <desc>"The series' final episode begins and ends with the two characters who stayed with it from beginning to end, as Charlie tells Hawks about his earlier days working for trading post operator Jarbo Pierce. Jarbo, once a wild, hard-drinking man, had become a minister, though he could still take on any man who tried to fight him. When his younger brother Adam arrived at the post Jarbo found himself at odds with him as Adam preferred the wilder ways of life and didn't understand Jarbo's concerns for the Indians he traded with, and began working with a man who wanted to use ..."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120220000 +0000" stop="20260120230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John finally restore their old fire engine to ride in the California Fire Fighters Parade. A man with heart problems causes an accident for which the other driver blames herself. Dr. Early treats a patient who has a seizure in the waiting room. A man on a date passes out and has difficulty breathing. A child's medical condition causes an argument between his divorced parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120230000 +0000" stop="20260120233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Incubator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and Trapper recover from an all night party. Henry gets a barbecue, and Hawkeye puts in a request for an incubator. The Quartermaster turns him down. They locate a Major with three incubators, but he won't let them have one.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260120233000 +0000" stop="20260121000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Deal Me Out</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sidney Freedman comes to the camp, and joins in the poker game at The Swamp. Radar hits a local with a jeep, although the local is famous for jumping in front of vehicles for the compensation. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on an intelligence officer against regulations, and Sidney helps talk a soldier out of his plan to kill Frank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121000000 +0000" stop="20260121003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Lips And Empty Arms</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret revaluates her life, deciding to leave Frank and ask for a transfer, which is granted. She gets drunk at her goodbye party, but is sobered up in the shower when wounded start arriving. She changes her mind when she realizes how loyal her friends are.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121003000 +0000" stop="20260121010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officers Only</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger pretends to be pregnant. Hawkeye and Trapper operate on General Mitchell's son, and the General gives them three days in Tokyo, and Henry keeps getting calls from Tokyo about what Hawkeye and Trapper are doing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121010000 +0000" stop="20260121013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Luck Of Newton Monroe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>An itinerant peddler comes to town (Don Rickles) and sells Barney, Floyd and Goober defective goods. After he disregards Andy's warning, he finds himself in the Mayberry jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121013000 +0000" stop="20260121020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Flunks Arithmetic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When Opie brings home a bad mark in arithmetic, Andy, fearing the boy will not get into college, puts too much pressure on him to study.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121020000 +0000" stop="20260121023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Shower, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gives a bridal shower for Amy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121023000 +0000" stop="20260121030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Bachelor Party, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra and Marie give Raymond a guilt trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121030000 +0000" stop="20260121033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Gives A Birthday Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hijacks a German bomber, and plans to use it to destroy an oil refinery and foil a German general who knows about the his operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121033000 +0000" stop="20260121040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Schultz Brigade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink and two other prison camp kommandants are arrested for conspiring against General Burkhalter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121040000 +0000" stop="20260121043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Telly Savalas</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Broken Merger, two business partners decide to separate, terminating their merger. Then, in TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody TV products, including Bolger's Coffee and Sineoff Tablets. Finally, in Poopi Le Moko, a bored criminal risks his life for a dangerous love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121043000 +0000" stop="20260121053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Screaming Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Gossip columnist Mary K. Davis is found murdered and it seems there is no shortage of suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121053500 +0000" stop="20260121060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Will The Real Martian Please Stand Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Troopers follow the tracks from a frozen pond into a diner. Inside they find a soda jerk, a bus driver and his seven passengers. The bus driver is certain only six people boarded his bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121060500 +0000" stop="20260121070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Who Needs An Enemy?  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>In this comedy-drama, dishonest Charlie Osgood hits upon an odd way to evade prosecution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121070500 +0000" stop="20260121080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Polka Dot Dress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix scoffs at a psychic's tale about a woman in danger. Then the prophecy comes true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121080500 +0000" stop="20260121090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Night Flight To Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A man hires Cannon to find out who is using trained dogs to kill the man he served with in Vietnam, and why. It might have something to do with the unit's commanding officer, permanently disabled, perhaps by his own men.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121090500 +0000" stop="20260121100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Relations</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to replace a detective who was murdered while looking for a woman's biological mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121100000 +0000" stop="20260121103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121103000 +0000" stop="20260121110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121110000 +0000" stop="20260121113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 103 -- A Sound Like Thunder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and his date join Reed and his expecting wife on a weekend trip to a ghost town, but soon they cross paths with a dangerous motorcycle gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121113000 +0000" stop="20260121120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 63 -- Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed's wife is in the hospital expecting their first child, and Reed soon regrets his decision to report for work as usual. Out on patrol, they encounter a drunken man directing traffic, chase down a robbery suspect, investigate the theft of money from washing machines and become involved in a minor traffic accident that results in a major delay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121120000 +0000" stop="20260121130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toon In's Wellness Wednesday: Fitness</sub-title>
    <desc>"Determined to meet his fitness goals, Bill learns easy, low-impact exercises to get healthy in 2026."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121130000 +0000" stop="20260121133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally Goes Steady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June find themselves in the dark when they hear through the grapevine that not only is Wally going steady with Evelyn Boothby but that wedding bells may be heard soon. Meanwhile, Wally gets a different picture of marital life through Evelyn's sister and her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121133000 +0000" stop="20260121140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>No Time For Baby Sitters</sub-title>
    <desc>"June, Ward and Wally are going out for the evening and not wanting to worry about Beaver, June calls a babysitter, despite Beaver's pleas against the idea."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121140000 +0000" stop="20260121150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Impatient Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Paint manufacturer Amory Fallon suspects that his partner, Ned Thompson, is behind a mysterious fire and explosion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121150000 +0000" stop="20260121160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Star  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an aging actress is found dead, stabbed with the prop knife that made her famous, suspicion lands on the horror film director who wanted her off his picture.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121160000 +0000" stop="20260121170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Box</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Big Chicken returns in a tense prison hostage drama when McGarrett has to give himself over to the criminals as a bargaining chip and use psychology to take control of the situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121170000 +0000" stop="20260121180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gypsies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A band of gypsies are traveling through Walton's Mountain when they become stranded</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121180000 +0000" stop="20260121190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Steals</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus goes after the bandits who robbed and assaulted Doc.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121190000 +0000" stop="20260121200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Elizabeth, My Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben recalls his days at sea and how he met his first wife, Elizabeth, when Adam falls gravely ill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121200000 +0000" stop="20260121203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Tension</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Gavin and Ezra Martin think that Lucas killed their son, Clemmie, while taking part in a train robbery. Lucas refuses to tell them what really happened.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121203000 +0000" stop="20260121210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>After the daughter of Lucas' friend arrives in North Fork, two strangers threaten her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121210000 +0000" stop="20260121220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Willy Moran Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Willy Moran, Adams' old Civil War commanding officer, is now a drunkard. Adams offers him a job on the wagon train, provided that he can stay sober.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121220000 +0000" stop="20260121230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Bash</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is trapped on a film set with a bear. When Roy and John rescue him, they are invited to a "thing" that the man is giving later that week. John talks Roy into getting overdressed for the event. Dr. Brackett treats a man suffering from trichinosis. A bomb blast injures two men. The paramedics resuscitate a musician at the party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121230000 +0000" stop="20260121233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Henry In Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Henry returns from a week in Tokyo, announcing that he is in love with a 20-year-old girl named Nancy Sue Parker. When she arrives for the weekend, it isn't long before she starts making advances on Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260121233000 +0000" stop="20260122000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>For Want Of A Boot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In this riotous episode, Hawkeye gets wrapped up in a convoluted scheme to procure a new pair of boots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122000000 +0000" stop="20260122003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Noselift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Private Baker, who is always going AWOL, is desperate for plastic surgery on his nose. Hawkeye gets an old friend, and plastic surgeon, to visit the camp, promising him a nurse called "The Barracuda." They put together an elaborate scheme to perform the operation without Frank or Margaret finding out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122003000 +0000" stop="20260122010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Chosen People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A Korean family sets up camp in the middle of the compound. A Korean woman with a baby comes looking for the father, and names Radar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122010000 +0000" stop="20260122013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie And The Carnival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie goes to the carnival and blows all his money on a game to win a birthday gift for Andy. The game, however, is rigged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122013000 +0000" stop="20260122020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Banjo-playing Deputy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When former carnival man Jerry Miller becomes deputy to Sheriff Taylor, he finds himself jeopardizing Mayberry, making him question his decision to become a lawman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122020000 +0000" stop="20260122023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Wedding Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Like their relationship, Robert and Amy's road to the altar is rocky.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122023000 +0000" stop="20260122030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Robert's Wedding Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert and Amy exchange vows in a wedding ceremony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122030000 +0000" stop="20260122033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds In The Rough</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A German officer threatens to expose Hogan unless he is paid a million dollars in diamonds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122033000 +0000" stop="20260122040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Briefcase</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to give a German general a briefcase containing a time bomb to assassinate Hitler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122040000 +0000" stop="20260122043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Eydie Gorme And Rich Little</sub-title>
    <desc>In Silent Night, Carol and Harvey pantomime a marital spat. Then, in Salute to Alfred Hitchcock, Carol and the gang parody classic films, including "North by Northwest" and "Psycho". Finally, in Remembrance of Edna, Harvey finds a woman who looks exactly like his deceased wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122043000 +0000" stop="20260122053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fiery Fingers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>When wealthy Louise Gordon is poisoned to death her nurse is charged with the crime. Mason does some digging and discovers that the first wife of the victim's husband also died of poisoning. Is the husband really the culprit or could it be someone else?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122053500 +0000" stop="20260122060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsolete Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>In a future state where religion and books have been banned, a librarian is judged obsolete and sentenced to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122060500 +0000" stop="20260122070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Bed Of Roses  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A date with his girlfriend turns into a nightmare for newly wed George Maxwell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122070500 +0000" stop="20260122080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>In Need Of A Friend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After discovering that a man he sent to prison for embezzlement may be innocent, Mannix works to find evidence that will clear him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122080500 +0000" stop="20260122090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Come Watch Me Die</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A mob killer murders Cannon's client. But the killer is someone Cannon will never suspect, and that leaves him unprepared when he is accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122090500 +0000" stop="20260122100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Taste For Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man's long-range plans clash with his girlfriend's personal ambition, leading them to commit murder out of greed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122100000 +0000" stop="20260122103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122103000 +0000" stop="20260122110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122110000 +0000" stop="20260122113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 93 -- Once A Junkie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former convict and informant who Malloy helped give a second chance is accused of assaulting a priest, dealing drugs and stealing a gun after being fired from his dish-washing job at Duke's Longhorn Café. Malloy and Reed set out to determine if his story, which is full of suspicious coincidences, is actually true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122113000 +0000" stop="20260122120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 123 -- Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed feels a strong sense of accomplishment when he stumbles upon a large stash of narcotics as he secures a residence after executing a traffic warrant with Malloy and Officer Ed Wells. He's in for a rude awakening at the trial, however, when he's cross examined by the defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122120000 +0000" stop="20260122130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Hunkiest Man Alive</sub-title>
    <desc>"A competition of hunks, but only one will be crowned the Hunkiest Man Alive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122130000 +0000" stop="20260122133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Car</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>For $25, Wally buys a car and signs a contract with the owner knowing full well what he's getting, a car that doesn't start. Wally quickly finds himself with more trouble then he bargained for when the lemon becomes a fixture in front of the Cleaver home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122133000 +0000" stop="20260122140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Birthday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has told his parents that he doesn't want anything big for his birthday and they decide to respect his wishes and give him a gift of money. Beaver also gets quite a bit of money from other relatives and finds himself debating on whether or not to spend it or put in the bank, like his parents suggest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122140000 +0000" stop="20260122150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners, until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret, a young woman on the make, entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122150000 +0000" stop="20260122160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Dare  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An eccentric millionaire tells Matlock that he wouldn't be able to solve the perfect murder if it were handed to him on a silver platter. To prove his point, he kills Matlock's friend and successfully frames another man for the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122160000 +0000" stop="20260122170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>When a girl is found murdered and numbered ‘one,' McGarrett suspects a serial killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122170000 +0000" stop="20260122180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Deed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The validity of the Waltons' claim to their land is questioned when they cannot produce a legal deed to the property.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122180000 +0000" stop="20260122190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Seven Hours To Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A treacherous gang of outlaws takes over Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122190000 +0000" stop="20260122200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Dream Riders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When an old friend of Ben's comes to town testing out hot air baloons, no one knows what he is really up to. Things get even more complicated and confusing when the Major's daughter arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122200000 +0000" stop="20260122203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Town character Brett Conway blackmails Lucas with the knowledge that a young couple Lucas rescued are suffering from yellow fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122203000 +0000" stop="20260122210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Ordeal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When their wagon breaks down, Mark and an injured Lucas are stranded in the desert.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122210000 +0000" stop="20260122220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jean Lebec Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A New Orleans aristocrat escorting a young lass to San Francisco arouses the fury of a tyrannical town boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122220000 +0000" stop="20260122230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Transition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school classmate of John’s is assigned as Squad 51's new paramedic trainee. The firemen rescue a man trapped in his kitchen after a hydrogen sulfide explosion. The paramedics help treat accident victims at the hospital and tend to child at an amusement park. When an intoxicated man turns out to be a snakebite victim, Roy is hit in the eyes with cobra venom. Back at the amusement park, a heart attack victim is trapped high in the air.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122230000 +0000" stop="20260122233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As You Were</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While there are no casualties, Hawkeye and Trapper crate up Frank while he sleeps and receive gorilla suits through the mail. Henry gets a tan and gives another sex orientation lecture. When the wounded start pouring in again, their own side shells the camp, hitting the generator, and Radar tries to get through to tell someone to stop the shelling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260122233000 +0000" stop="20260123000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Crisis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The supply lines to the camp are cut. Radar, the housing officer, starts doubling people up to save fuel and Klinger is thrown out of the nurse's tent. People start burning everything to stay warm while Frank wears his heated socks. The toilet paper supply is worst hit, and then wounded start arriving.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123000000 +0000" stop="20260123003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Burns tries to slap a dishonorable discharge on a decorated soldier who admits to being a homosexual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123003000 +0000" stop="20260123010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a new batch of mail leaves Trapper depressed, and thinking of desertion, despite Hawkeye's efforts to dissuade him. Meanwhile, Hawkeye learns that he has successfully tricked Frank into buying stocks in a fictitious company, Pioneer Aviation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123010000 +0000" stop="20260123013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The New Housekeeper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose, the former housekeeper, gets married and Opie is unhappy at her departure. Aunt Bee comes to live with Andy and Opie, and Opie is not exactly thrilled with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123013000 +0000" stop="20260123020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Manhunt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The state police arrogantly ask Andy and Barney to step aside while they search for an escaped convict in Mayberry, believing that the Mayberry sheriff's department is not capable of doing "real" police work.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123020000 +0000" stop="20260123023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Baggage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra wind up in a two-week standoff over a suitcase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123023000 +0000" stop="20260123030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Fun With Debra</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra admits to Ray that she's disappointed they no longer have fun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123030000 +0000" stop="20260123033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Battle Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Two German officers interfere with Hogan's operations when one tries to turn Stalag 13 into an officer's retirement home the other wants to use the facilities to interrogate the citizens of the local town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123033000 +0000" stop="20260123040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Rise And Fall Of Sergeant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is stymied in the rescue of a captured member of the underground until a potential diversion appears in the form of an old WWI buddy of Sgt. Schultz.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123040000 +0000" stop="20260123043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Alan King And Lena Zavaroni</sub-title>
    <desc>In Sidewalk Stars, two aging stars reunite on Hollywood Boulevard while they clean their star square. Then, in Fans, Carol finds love at a baseball game. Finally, in The Package, a school teacher discovers an unattended package and claims it as her own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123043000 +0000" stop="20260123053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Substitute Face</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della are traveling on a cruise ship returning to Los Angeles from Vancouver. Carl Houser jumps overboard and is presumed drowned. Houser later turns up on shore but with a bullet wound in his body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123053500 +0000" stop="20260123060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A man and a woman, on opposite sides of a future war, encounter each other in a deserted town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123060500 +0000" stop="20260123070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Second Verdict  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An attorney learns that his acquitted client is in fact a murderer and may kill for a second time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123070500 +0000" stop="20260123080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Night Out Of Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Cliff Ross, Jr. awakens in big trouble. A girl is dead, there's evidence he was in some kind of fight and he can't remember what actually happened. Unless Mannix can help him reconstruct events, he's likely to go to prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123080500 +0000" stop="20260123090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Perfect Alibi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon tries to extract reporter Peggy Angel from a clever frame. Who is the real murderer, and why frame this particular person?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123090500 +0000" stop="20260123100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Final Burial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman hires Barnaby to find her missing husband and the detective's investigation uncovers bigamy, blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123100000 +0000" stop="20260123103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123103000 +0000" stop="20260123110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123110000 +0000" stop="20260123113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 143 -- Cave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed begin their shift responding to a disgruntled tenant who is holding his landlord at knife point. Later, they investigate a rash of property theft from multiple homes in a quiet neighborhood, stake out an apparent bag of laundry left on the side of the road and search for a runaway boy who gets himself into a life-threatening situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123113000 +0000" stop="20260123120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 142 -- As High As You Are</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>As Malloy and Reed's patrol begins, an uneventful traffic stop becomes more interesting when something catches Malloy's eye. Later, they discover an unusual situation responding to a break-in at a hospital supply warehouse, which becomes even more odd when the warehouse owner and a group of revenge-seeking thugs show up at the scene. The shift ends in a fitting way when they are called to an apartment where a baby has been left unattended with a pet lion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123120000 +0000" stop="20260123130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Palmetto State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony journey across South Carolina on their latest stop trekkin' across every state in America."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123130000 +0000" stop="20260123133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Cat Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A strange cat appears at the Cleaver's door and Beaver takes it in and feeds it. However, when the owner is found, and the cat is returned, Beaver finds himself with a dilemma: The cat keeps coming back!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123133000 +0000" stop="20260123140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Weekend Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally gets a job at the ice cream parlor leaving a gaggle of girls swooning and Eddie and Lumpy feeling neglected. So to get back at him, Eddie and Lumpy concoct a plan of revenge that involves Mary Ellen Roger's slumber party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123140000 +0000" stop="20260123150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Malicious Mariner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>During a terrible storm at sea, First Officer Jerry Griffin dumps a million dollars worth of goods overboard to lessen the chances of his cargo freighter sinking. Once on shore, Jerry is hauled before a maritime court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123150000 +0000" stop="20260123160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Con Man  (s9, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a victim of a group of con men is charged with murdering one of them, Matlock takes the case while Michelle attempts to get close to the remaining con artists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123160000 +0000" stop="20260123170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Along Came Joey</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When the boxer son of a Maui policeman, Phil Kalama, is killed, he starts a personal vendetta. McGarrett must solve the initial crime and stop Kalama from committing another murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123170000 +0000" stop="20260123180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Scholar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When Verdie Grant learns her daughter is graduating from college, she feels embarrassed by the fact that she never learned to read or write.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123180000 +0000" stop="20260123190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Storm</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A buffalo hunter is sentenced to be hanged for a murder he didn't commit, the real culprits being the sons of Matt's old friend, Adam Benteen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123190000 +0000" stop="20260123200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Many Faces Of Gideon Flinch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Bullethead Burke is looking for a man he says cheated him out of $5,000 dollars. The man's niece tricks Little Joe and Hoss into helping her uncle out. A pickpocket escapes from jail and complicates matters even more.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123200000 +0000" stop="20260123203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Spiked Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark is kidnapped as he and Lucas try to protect Banker Hamilton's gold.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123203000 +0000" stop="20260123210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Letter Of The Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas makes a life-or-death decision when Micah is held hostage and the kidnappers demand the release of a notorious outlaw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123210000 +0000" stop="20260123220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The John Cameron Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The husband of a much younger woman grows jealous of her flirtatious ways.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123220000 +0000" stop="20260123230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Eater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A temporary captain from "the old school" doesn't feel Gage and DeSoto should be practicing "medicine." An elderly man sets his chair on fire. Dr. Early keeps coming up with oranges when all he wants is an apple. The paramedics struggle to save a heart attack victim. A boy with asthma gets trapped in a storm drain. Dr. Brackett uses an old-fashioned sedative on a biker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123230000 +0000" stop="20260123233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Smattering Of Intelligence</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A classic episode in which Colonel Flagg and another secret agent from another intelligence agency come to the 4077th to keep their eyes on the camp. Hawkeye and Trapper trick them both into thinking that Burns is a traitor—one thinks he's a fascist, the other thinks he's a communist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260123233000 +0000" stop="20260124000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The General Flipped At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>The MASH 4077th is visted by General Steele. He wishes to move the camp five miles down the road. Hawkeye and Henry are charged with mutiny. And Hawkeye also is charged with impersonating a reporter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124000000 +0000" stop="20260124003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rainbow Bridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>As Hawkeye and Trapper are planning to leave for Tokyo, an unusual offer to swap POW patients between the Chinese and the 4077th comes in. Henry, after much debate, agrees to send Hawkeye, Trapper, Frank, Radar and Klinger into enemy territory. Frank almost botches the swap when he brings a squirt gun to the exchange. Fortunately, the Chinese Dr. Lin Tam has a sense of humor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124003000 +0000" stop="20260124010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Officer Of The Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While Henry is away in Seoul, Burns and Houlihan are in charge, and Hawkeye is the officer of the day. His refusal to release a wounded Korean soldier, wanted by US Intelligence, leads to a confrontation with Colonel Flagg.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124010000 +0000" stop="20260124013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Guitar Player</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Lindsey is a young guitarist that lives in Mayberry. When the famous musician Bobby Fleet and his band arrive in Mayberry, Andy and Barney scheme to arrest Bobby and his band so that Jim can get an audition.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124013000 +0000" stop="20260124020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie Walker, the local pharmacist's niece, comes to Mayberry to replace him on a temporary basis. Her "new" approach to dispensing medicine shakes things up in Mayberry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124020000 +0000" stop="20260124023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Thank You Notes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra convinces Amy to join forces against Marie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124023000 +0000" stop="20260124030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Home From School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray decides the tough love approach is the way to go with Michael.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124030000 +0000" stop="20260124033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan Springs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses a broken water main under the camp to aid the escape of captured resistance fighters by creating a health spa.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124033000 +0000" stop="20260124040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>A Klink, A Bomb And A Short Fuse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>General Burkhalter wants Hogan to defuse a bomb that has landed in camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124040000 +0000" stop="20260124043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Helen Reddy And John Byner</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Eunice plays "Sorry!" with her grumpy family. Then, in The Pick-Ups, Harvey and John try to pick up girls at the bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124043000 +0000" stop="20260124053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Long-legged Models</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Racketeer George Castle kills Las Vegas hotel owner Glenn Faulkner over a gambling debt and sets his sights on land inherited by Faulkner's daughter, Stephanie. When Castle turns up murdered as well, Stephanie finds herself the number one suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124053500 +0000" stop="20260124060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Arrival</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A plane lands safely, but all its passengers, pilot and crew are missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124060500 +0000" stop="20260124070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Isabel  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An ex-convict weds the woman whose evidence sent him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124070500 +0000" stop="20260124080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>A View Of Nowhere</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While on a helicopter flight, Mannix witnesses a murder. Or does he? No one can find a body, no one reports a missing person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124080500 +0000" stop="20260124090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Dead Lady's Tears</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a plane carrying three million in negotiable securities vanishes, the insurance carrier hires Cannon to find out what happened to it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124090500 +0000" stop="20260124100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Portrait Of Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An art collector's wife plots to steal one of his paintings, but her plan is complicated by her husband's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124100000 +0000" stop="20260124103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>It's Not The Principle, It's The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoping to win the business of a convention, Kate spruces up the Shady Rest. Meanwhile, peeved about a tax increase and scheming for its repeal, Uncle Joe does what he can to make the hotel appear run-down and shabby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124103000 +0000" stop="20260124110000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>War Of The Hotels</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Kate fights a no-holds-barred "hotel war" with Murdock Sneep, unscrupulous operator of the rival Pixley Hotel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124110000 +0000" stop="20260124113000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Fishing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale and Jane try to get the Clampetts interested in deep-sea fishing, but face an obstacle: Granny. She has a fear of water and refuses to go on a boat. So, Jane comes up with the idea of letting them visit Marineland. They decide to go right away and are impressed by the giant fishing holes. And Granny sees the fish of fishes, a giant whale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124113000 +0000" stop="20260124120000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Critter Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Duke is sick, and Elly calls the "critter doctor" from the zoo. When Jed finds out he is a "college boy," he thinks it is a possible beau for Elly May, not knowing he is a graduate and an older man. Granny is against this doctor coming, and she mistakes a young salesman who is selling bug repellents for the doctor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124120000 +0000" stop="20260124123000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Moving Aweigh, Barbecue For Two, Matinee Idol Popeye, Lunch With A Punch</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Shorty try to help Olive but stir up trouble with the police instead., Popeye's BBQ for two with  is interrupted by everyone else., Brutus is an egotistical French director making a film about Antony and Cleopatra, starring Popeye and Olive Oyl., Popeye uses a tale of how he defeated Bluto as a boy to convince his nephews to eat their spinach."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124123000 +0000" stop="20260124130000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Love That Pup, Barnyard Babies, Busy Buddies</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom accidentally grabs Tyke, Spike the bulldog's son, when he is trying to get to Jerry., A baby contest is going on in the barn where all the barnyard animals’ children compete in a talent contest but the rooster is left out because his baby is taking too much time to arrive so he tries to hurry the process along., Tom and Jerry are forced to take care of a baby because the babysitter is more interested in talking on the phone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124130000 +0000" stop="20260124140000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Hot Noon Or 12 O'clock For Sure, Mouse Trappers, Horse Play, Tin Can Concert, Gold Diggin' Woodpecker, Cool It Charlie, The Mad Hatter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody is a piano player in the Old West. When Buzz Buzzard comes into town to kill the sheriff, the sheriffs ask Woody to take over and catch him., Papa Panda unsuccessfully tries to catch a mouse in the house., Woody has a run-in with an indigineous man who doesn't like Woody's horse., Doc, a cat with musical talents, directs a symphony from the top of a grandfather clock. A mouse who lives in the grandfather clock is trying to sleep and tries to stop the music., Woody and his horse Sugarfoot discover gold in an abandoned mine and have to fight off another miner trying to claim jump., Charlie attempts to install an air conditioner himself to save money., Woody encounters difficulties acquiring a new top hat for his Hollywood screen test."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124140000 +0000" stop="20260124150000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare Brush, Mexican Mousepiece, Kiss Me Cat, Bugs Bunny And The Three Bears, The Music Mice-tro, Crockett-doodle-do, Hare-abian Nights</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs believes he’s a human and goes hunting for Elmer Fudd who believes he’s a rabbit. , Daffy is trying to send a care package overseas full of Mexican mice when Speedy stops the delivery. , Hearing that Pussyfoot has "got to do his job and catch mice or we'll just have to get another cat," Marc Antony, the bulldog, takes it upon himself to educate the kitten in the fundamentals of mouse-catching. , The three bears set a trap to catch Goldilocks, but their carrot soup attracts Bugs Bunny early on and he grows wise to their plans. , Daffy is on a vacation from Hollywood when Speedy and his Mexicali Mariachi band come to audition for him. , Foghorn tries to teach the brainy chicken, Egghead Jr., about the great outdoors., Bugs is forced to tell the Sultan some tales of his adventures or else face the croc-pit. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124150000 +0000" stop="20260124160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Tycoons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>West becomes involved with the Jupiter Corporation after the director of the board dies of an apparent heart attack and two others are killed. West discovers that they were all involved in a scheme to dump stock, cause a panic, and make tons of money off of the cheap stock. West's investigation leads him to an odd bar with a circus theme and animals who like to throw bombs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124160000 +0000" stop="20260124170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ruth Owens Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's brother kills a man who made a derogatory remark about her, only to discover later that the remark was true.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124170000 +0000" stop="20260124180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Joaquin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A newly hired ranch hand is suspected of being the famous outlaw Joaquin Murietta, supposedly killed in an ambush 10 years before.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124180000 +0000" stop="20260124190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Clayton Thaddeus Greenwood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Thad Greenwood trails the four tough guys who caused his father to have a fatal heart attack.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124190000 +0000" stop="20260124200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Burma Rarity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Widow Hawkins tricks a couple of con men who first try to swindle her with an emerald known as "The Burma Rarity."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124200000 +0000" stop="20260124203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Legacy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas tries to do a good deed for the old town drunk but it backfires when the drunk's son believes he inherited Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124203000 +0000" stop="20260124210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Baby Sitter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A dance hall singer asks Lucas to care for her daughter in an effort to hide the baby from her self-righteous, bigoted father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124210000 +0000" stop="20260124220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Empty Sleeve</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When the herd refuses to drink or cross a river, Favor sends for a vet and a one-armed man shows up wanting a drover job. Rowdy learns the cattle need salt and the new hand knows where to find it nearby. However, he doesn't want to go there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124220000 +0000" stop="20260124223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Hanging Of Roy Carter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Roy Carter is scheduled to be hanged. Another man confesses to the murder just before the execution is to take place. Paladin is hired to try to convince the warden to delay the hanging until the Governor can be reached."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124223000 +0000" stop="20260124230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Prison Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and Jason are escorting four prisoners to Levenworth prison when a stranger begins following along behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260124230000 +0000" stop="20260125010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Pain In The Pullman, A Ducking They Did Go, We Want Our Mummy, Commotion On The Ocean, Dopey Dicks, Sappy Bull Fighters</sub-title>
    <desc>"All aboard for non-stop hilarity! The Stooges and their pet monkey join a traveling vaudville troupe, making for a very bumpy ride. , After recruiting the police chief, governor and mayor into what turns out to be a sham duck hunting club, the Stooges cleverly find a way to avoid jail.  , Stranded in Mexico, the Stooges need a job and a pretty actress friend gets them an engagement at the Plaza de Toros.  When they accidentally switch suitcases with that of their friend, they must sneak into her house to retrieve their own and are confronted by her jealous husband who vows to kill them if he sees them again.  At the arena where they perform a comedy bullfight (Joe is the matador, Moe and Larry are in a bull costume) the husband bribes the attendants to let a real bull into the ring.  Joe knocks the bull out with a head butt and becomes a hero. , The stooges go to Egypt in search of the mummy of king Rootin-Tootin for which a museum will pay a $5000 prize., The Stooges are would-be reporters, who are tricked into becoming stowaways by "Borscht", a spy for an enemy country.  Stranded on a freighter on the high seas, they discover that Borscht has concealed some stolen microfilm in watermelons they brought aboard for him.  After a wild chase, they subdue Borscht and recover the microfilm. , It's mindless fun at its best when the Stooges meet a mad scientist in search of a human brain for his headless mechanical man.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125010000 +0000" stop="20260125033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Fiend Without A Face</sub-title>
    <desc>"Invisible atomic monsters attack a U.S. Armed Forces base and the local residents."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125033000 +0000" stop="20260125040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Impractical Joker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Joker steals the Jeweled Key Of Kaincardine with the aid of his new invention, a mysterious little spark-spewing box that renders the Dynamic Duo helpless.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125040000 +0000" stop="20260125050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>This Side Of Paradise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise crew is trapped in paradise when they come to rescue colonists who have fallen to pacifying alien spores and become infected themselves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125050000 +0000" stop="20260125053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Atomic Captive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois and Jimmy attempt to rescue Dr. Ladislav, a nuclear scientist, from foreign agents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125053000 +0000" stop="20260125060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Superman Silver Mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Mr. Pebble, a prospector, donates a silver mine to a children's fund. A crook impersonates him and captures Mr. Pebbles, Lois, and Jimmy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125060000 +0000" stop="20260125070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Forbidden World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On their next planetary stop, the Robinsons encounter a hermit who plans to attack the Jupiter 2 with his army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125070000 +0000" stop="20260125080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Mummy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A 3,000-year-old mummy puts a spell on Crane and terrorizes the Seaview.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125080000 +0000" stop="20260125090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Graveyard Of Fools</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Twin brothers plot to take over the planet, and send the Earthlings to the Graveyard of Fools, a place fraught with hallucinatory visions, to recover an alien servo-actuator for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260125090000 +0000" stop="20260125100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>End Of The World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>In a 1910 mining town, Tony and Doug try to rescue 200 miners trapped by a cave-in.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
