<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104033000 +0000" stop="20260104040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>Hizzoner The Penguin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After several heroic feats, the Penguin campaigns to be the Mayor of Gotham City. Batman realizes the only way to stop him is to run for mayor himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104040000 +0000" stop="20260104050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Archons</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise encounters a seemingly peaceful civilization run by a "benevolent" being named Landru.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104050000 +0000" stop="20260104053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Zero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A little man from Mars appears. He has the unwitting power to freeze people with his finger, and criminals trick him into helping them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104053000 +0000" stop="20260104060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Whatever Goes Up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jimmy accidentally discovers an anti-gravity fluid, but then he can't remember the formula.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104060000 +0000" stop="20260104070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Blast Off Into Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Smith and Will befriend an old miner named Nerim. After a series of earthquakes indicates that the planet is breaking up, Dr. Smith tries to convince them that it is merely the effects of mining, and no harm will come to the planet. John informs him that he is wrong and that the Robinson family will be departing within the day. It is a race against time to escape the crumbling planet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104070000 +0000" stop="20260104080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Heat Monster</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview battles alien heat monsters on the arctic ice cap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104080000 +0000" stop="20260104090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>A Small War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A sadistic child discovers the Earthlings and unleashes his mechanical toys against them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104090000 +0000" stop="20260104100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Town Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug are propelled into the future (1978) to fight invaders siphoning off the Earth's oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104100000 +0000" stop="20260104110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Mutation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>David meets a stripper who claims to have seen something strange in the desert, but a secret jeopardizes his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104110000 +0000" stop="20260104120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Seekers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Before the mountain's hit by a storm,a military man,Master Sargent Monahan arrives,whom Mad Jack mistakes for an infamous being of sorts. It's up to Adams to not only prepare all for the storm but to prove the identity of the Sgt. as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104120000 +0000" stop="20260104123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>To Rope A Grizzly</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan are invited to help capture one of the most feared animals on four legs, a livestock marauding grizzly.  They plan to use the only capture method suited to the animal and the country – roping the fierce and powerful bear."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104123000 +0000" stop="20260104130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Sea Lion Number Seven</sub-title>
    <desc>"Far out in the Pacific Ocean lies a tiny island.  Once every year, these barren rocks explode with life as Steller sea lions come ashore by the thousands to breed and give birth to their young. Marlin sails to the island to join a team of scientists to observe and take part in a tagging project."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104130000 +0000" stop="20260104133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Return Of The Salmon</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the chill, glacier-fed streams of Alaska sockeye salmon are born, and follow the current to the sea.  After two or three great annual circuits of the North Pacific, the call comes to return."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104133000 +0000" stop="20260104140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>In Search Of A Giant Armadillo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Stan journey to Guyana, South America in search of one of the world’s rarest wild animals, the giant armadillo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104140000 +0000" stop="20260104143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chase By Copter</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim take to the air in a helicopter for two thrilling hunts over Canada…one in search of a giant moose and then in the mountains of western Canada for a mountain goat roundup."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104143000 +0000" stop="20260104150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Lion Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Probably the greatest of the great cats is the king of beasts … the African lion.  Roaming the open savannas, its roar is a threat to all who live within its range.  Its amazing physical abilities make it the most feared hunter on the African continent."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104150000 +0000" stop="20260104153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Popularity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Jan competes in a popularity contest at school. With Peter as her campaign manager and the rest of the family pitching in, she's got a great chance of winning - if she can stop making promises to her classmates that she can't possibly keep.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104153000 +0000" stop="20260104160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Tell It Like It Is</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Carol has been acting mysteriously lately and Mike and Alice can't figure out what she's up to. It's discovered that Carol is writing an article about life with the Brady family for Tomorrow's Woman Magazine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104160000 +0000" stop="20260104163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Clampetts Go Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Jake and Opal Clampett are continuing to stay at the Clampett mansion, and Elly and Jethro are more than happy to serve them. But Granny isn’t impressed by Jake at all, and isn’t even sure if Jake is related to Jed. Jethro and Elly both decide they want to get into the movie business, and the two get help from Jake and Opal. Jethro turns into a Marlon Brando-type and Elly fancies herself a glamorous movie star, taking the name Venus Adore.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104163000 +0000" stop="20260104170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Garden Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale is having a garden party and tells the Clampetts not to attend. However, they misunderstand and think she wants them to come. Jane and Drysdale try to stop them, but when they say how they still want to go, Jane arranges for them to have society clothes. When they arrive at the party, Mrs. Drysdale sends them back next door to handle the overflow crowd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104170000 +0000" stop="20260104173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie Loves Helen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie develops a crush on his teacher, Helen Crump, at the school dance. He spends .74 cents to buy her a gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104173000 +0000" stop="20260104180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Lucy Gets A Paris Gown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucy decides to go on a hunger strike until Ricky agrees to buy her a designer dress. The plan works perfectly, even though Ethel has been smuggling food to Lucy. But when Ricky discovers what Lucy has been up to, he puts together a crazy outfit made of burlap and passes it off as a Paris original.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104180000 +0000" stop="20260104183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Glamour Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is shocked to learn that the glamorous Kitty Bannerman is visiting Mayfield and he's afraid that she will find out that he's not the rich hot shot that he told her he was in the letters that he had sent her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104183000 +0000" stop="20260104190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Chuckie's New Shoes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A neighbor gives Wally the responsibility of taking her son, Chuckie, down to the shoe store to pick out a pair of shoes. However, when Wally gives the job to Beaver, Beaver finds himself searching for Chuckie, who has gotten himself lost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104190000 +0000" stop="20260104200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>Hellride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Sabrina becomes a race driver while Kelly, Jill and Bosley assume unusual disguises to learn why a pretty woman driver lost control of her car and died in a flaming wreck. They discover a conspiracy that extends far beyond the track.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104200000 +0000" stop="20260104210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Hit Jennifer Hart</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Jonathan uncovers a scandal effecting dockworkers, a hit man posing as a long lost cousin is hired to kill Jennifer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104210000 +0000" stop="20260104220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Escape / Cinderella Girls</sub-title>
    <desc>"With the help of Ipsy Dauphin, Gregory Udall satisfies his ego and performs the "Ultimate Escape" on Fantasy Island."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104220000 +0000" stop="20260104230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Love Boat Musical (my Ex-mom / The Show Must Go On / The Pest / My Aunt, The Worrier) (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"The crew surprises Captain Stubing with the news that they are putting on a musical revue as entertainment for the passengers, with a script co-written by Gopher and Isaac. The Captain publicly declines to play the lead role in it, but privately fantasizes about being in it and even practices for it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104230000 +0000" stop="20260104233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Physical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney learns that in order to pass the mandatory physical for the deputy's office, he must weigh more and be taller. Andy and Aunt Bee try to stretch him and fatten him up, until Andy comes up with the solution.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260104233000 +0000" stop="20260105000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>David Meinz- Vintage Fitness Fads</sub-title>
    <desc>"Dietician and nutritionist David Meinz has collected a museum's worth of samples, advertising, and more showcasing America's decades-long love affair with quack cures and weird weight-loss schemes. Americana expert Henry Tankersley weighs in on the market value of David's wildest finds, from weight-loss cigarettes to a vitamin mixture made with alcohol, for the whole family!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105000000 +0000" stop="20260105003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Picture This</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter's attempts to assemble the crew for a family portrait are thwarted by a feud between bunkmates Pierce, Hunnicutt and Winchester. Things are not helped by the efforts of Margaret, Klinger and Mulcahy to bring the Swampmen back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105003000 +0000" stop="20260105010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That Darn Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger buys a goat, with the intention of getting rich by selling its milk. Then the goat eats the 4077th's $22,340 payroll, leaving paymaster Hawkeye holding the bag. Meanwhile, Charles also thinks he can make a killing when he sees an ancient vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105010000 +0000" stop="20260105013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's 50th Birthday (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Before Edith arrives home, Gloria and Mike teaches Archie the plan for Edith 50th birthday surprise party which will be taken at 6 o'clock at the Stivics house. Edith comes back home while Archie and the Stivics leave to decorate the house for the party. A sudden knock at the door reveals a cop. Edith welcomes the policeman inside the house who claims that there's a rapist in town but he slips out that it's him. Edith is held at
gunpoint and pushed on the couch. The rapist slowly strips Edith! Before it can go any longer, the phone rings. The rapist orders Edith to get rid of the caller as soon as possible. When she does, Archie knocks at the door, wondering why the hell the door is locked. The rapist hides himself in the closet and once again orders Edith to get rid of Archie. She does as quickly as possible. Still stranded in the house with the armed man, they suddenly smell something burning. It was the cake which Edith previously started to bake. They rush to the oven where the room is just smoke. When she it pulls, she tosses the hot cake in the rapist's face and rushes outside the kitchen door, but he stops her. She knees him in the groin and exits as soon as possible out of the front door and interupts the party, running into Archie's arms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105013000 +0000" stop="20260105020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's 50th Birthday (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith tells the story to the family in tears, Gloria and Mike believe she should report to the police while Archie fears Edith will be the one going to jail. Two weeks later, Edith is still ironing sheets for no reason and keeps running upstairs when someone knocks on the door. 
Gloria tells her dad to give her some TLC (Tender Loving Care). But while he does so, Gloria gets a call from the policemen asking her to identify the rapist. Edith is afraid, but with convincing, Archie takes Edith to the police station.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105020000 +0000" stop="20260105023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Unequal Partners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie must delay his weekend fishing trip with Barney when Edith announces that she has invited people from the SunShine Home to attend an elderly couple's wedding at 704 on the same day Archie planned to leave.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105023000 +0000" stop="20260105030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie's Grand Opening</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>On the eve of his grand opening, Harry quits Archie's bar when the bigot bosses Harry around. Helpless, Edith and the Stivics come on time and gladly decide to help out. With a great crowd, Archie faces more problems; Mike can't get the right mixes, Edith sings, the guys are after Gloria and not only that, Archie's boss at the loading docks arrive where Archie quits, upseting Edith.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105030000 +0000" stop="20260105033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Lucky Suit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert is ecstatic when he is recommended for the FBI job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105033000 +0000" stop="20260105040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Skit, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra do a dead-on impersonation of Frank and Marie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105040000 +0000" stop="20260105043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bad Old Days</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob yearns for the good 'ol days... until a dream takes him back to reality.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105043000 +0000" stop="20260105050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Sol And The Sponsor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob's old Army buddy visits and insults a big sponsor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105050000 +0000" stop="20260105053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Please Leave The Premises</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The Kramdens and the Nortons fight a rent increase, though Ralph is the only one who really wants to fight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105053000 +0000" stop="20260105060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Trouble With Templeton</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging actor longing for the good old days is given a sobering glimpse of the past he holds so dear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105060000 +0000" stop="20260105070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Beyond The Sea Of Death  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>After a failed marriage to a fortune hunter, heiress Grace Renford vows to never make the same blunder again.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105070000 +0000" stop="20260105080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Run For The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate members Trask and Mason control the Syndicate's illegal racing operations, with Trask ruthlessly dispatches the competition—the IMF must take them out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105080000 +0000" stop="20260105090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The End Of The Line</sub-title>
    <desc>"As Dr. Kimble attempts to return a wallet that he stole, he witnesses a murder and becomes the prime suspect himself."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105090000 +0000" stop="20260105100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Second Sight</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell is drawn into an extraordinary mystery when he follows a trail of murders forecast by a novelist suffering from hysterical blindness."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105100000 +0000" stop="20260105103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Cigarette Butt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A murder victim's smoking habits help Friday track down the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105103000 +0000" stop="20260105110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>D.h.q. - Missing Person</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A high school student is missing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105110000 +0000" stop="20260105113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 71 -- I Feel Like A Fool, Malloy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>It is a shift of conflicts forcing Malloy and Reed to use their wits to keep control and make the right decisions end on a low note.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105113000 +0000" stop="20260105120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 72 -- El Presidente</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy teases Reed about calculating the cost of a new house while their first baby is still six months away. In the meantime they settle a domestic dispute between arguing neighbors and help a taxi driver who was just robbed as well as a local man mistaken as the president by a group of rural Mexicans. Finally, they must arrest a psychotic shooter holed up in his house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105120000 +0000" stop="20260105130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' The Cornhusker State</sub-title>
    <desc>"Oh my, Omaha! Nebraska's splendor is savored by Toony and Bill."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105130000 +0000" stop="20260105133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Kenneth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While at a parent's meeting, June leans from Miss Landers that someone has been stealing in Beaver's class. So far a baseball glove, a lunch box and a baseball cap were heisted. Later, June makes a shocking discovery; she finds the stolen items under Beaver's bed. This leaves June and Ward wondering if they're raising a thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105133000 +0000" stop="20260105140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Accordian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An advertisement in the mail for a free tryout of an accordion has Beaver sneaking around behind Ward's back. After rescuing the flyer from the trash, Beaver sends it in and indeed gets an accordion that he quickly finds hard to hide from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105140000 +0000" stop="20260105150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Willard Nesbitt faked his drowning death in a boating accident so his wife could collect the double indemnity life insurance money.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105150000 +0000" stop="20260105160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Thoroughbred  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When the manager of a thoroughbred farm is murdered, her father begs Matlock to represent the mentally handicapped man accused of the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105160000 +0000" stop="20260105170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Samurai</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>McGarrett protects suspected gangster Tokura from Japanese assassins, even as he and Five-O try to find evidence linking Tokura to organized crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105170000 +0000" stop="20260105180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Sinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A young preacher, Matthew Fordwick (John Ritter), comes to Walton's Mountain fresh from seminary, where he has learned the currently-popular fire and brimstone style of preaching.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105180000 +0000" stop="20260105190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Winner Take All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt intervenes when an intense feud between the Renner brothers reaches its breaking point.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105190000 +0000" stop="20260105200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Bank Run</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Hoss get in some trouble when they "rob" the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105200000 +0000" stop="20260105203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Retired Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Wes Carney and his wife, Clair, want to settle down and they figure North Fork might do fine. Wes is a well known gunfighter, who has promised Clair that he would hang up his guns for good. The Carney's want to live a simple, honest life and the Feed and Grain Store, which is up for sale, seems like it might work for them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105203000 +0000" stop="20260105210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Photographer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Abel Goss, the photographer who took Lucas' wedding photograph, is in North Fork doing a portrait of Mark standing in the street. When Goss sees Col. Whiteside and his sidekick, Jamison, he recognizes them as the butchers who tortured him and others while he was captive in a Civil War prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105210000 +0000" stop="20260105220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Hector Heatherton Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>"Charlie has finally found someone else who shares his dream of man being able to fly, henpecked inventor Hector Heatherton, who has been working on an idea for building a flying machine so Charlie volunteers to build a machine for Hector."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105220000 +0000" stop="20260105230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Fix It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's husband is trapped under their house, where a natural oil well has erupted. John tries to fix a boy's bike. A boy who wants to become a doctor is admitted to Rampart. The firemen rescue a child stuck in a pipe. Roy and John remove a ring from a young man’s finger. Roy and Capt. Stanley struggle with a shutoff valve at a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105230000 +0000" stop="20260105233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and her nursing staff are about to be inspected by Col. Bucholz. Meanwhile, Kellye is offended that Hawkeye is attracted to nurses besides her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260105233000 +0000" stop="20260106000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Affairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Army tries to get a North Korean pilot to defect, and Charles gets a rude shock when he falls for a French nurse with a Bohemian past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106000000 +0000" stop="20260106003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Is Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of reminders about Trapper John's skill as a practical joker, B.J. bets Hawkeye he can prank everyone present.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106003000 +0000" stop="20260106010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Who Knew?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye volunteers to deliver the eulogy for a dead nurse that he briefly dated, and belatedly discovers her deep feelings for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106010000 +0000" stop="20260106013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Family Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Taylors quickly realize why they haven't invited Bee's sister and her husband, Ollie, for a visit in more than a decade. When Uncle Ollie borrows Andy's squad car to go fishing, it's the final straw.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106013000 +0000" stop="20260106020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Education Of Ernest T. Bass</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. is back in Mayberry to get his diploma. He is so determined that Andy convinces Helen to allow him to attend class, but Ernest T. isn't exactly classroom material.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106020000 +0000" stop="20260106023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Breakup Tape, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra wants to know why Ray saved a gift for his college girlfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106023000 +0000" stop="20260106030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Talk To Your Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is totally unprepared for Ally's line of questions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106030000 +0000" stop="20260106033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happiness Is A Warm Sergeant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Klink finds Sergeant Schultz drunk he gets a tough new replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106033000 +0000" stop="20260106040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Scientist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau pretends to be a famous French scientist who is visiting camp while Hogan smuggles the real one out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106040000 +0000" stop="20260106043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Steve Lawrence And Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In TV Commercials, Carol and the gang parody classic kitchen products. Then, in The Oldest Man, a fast-changing actor hires the Oldest Man. Finally, in Day Shift-Night Shift, Carol and Tim pantomime as a married couple on opposite shifts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106043000 +0000" stop="20260106053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Haunted Husband</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hitchhiking because her purse was stolen, Claire Olger is picked up by Michael Greeley. Intoxicated, he loses control of the car and collides with an oncoming truck. Arriving at the scene of the accident, the police find Claire alone in the car and the truck driver dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106053500 +0000" stop="20260106060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Most Unusual Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Small-time crooks end up with a camera that takes photos of events five minutes into the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106060500 +0000" stop="20260106070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Night Caller  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A mystifying young man and intimidating phone calls put Marcia Fowler on the edge of madness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106070500 +0000" stop="20260106080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Eight To Five, Its A Miracle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate an alleged miracle that has been occurring on the land of a crime boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106080500 +0000" stop="20260106090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Gordon Bell gets involved in a fight. When his opponent dies, Gordon is arrested and charged with murder. Cannon has to bring the truth to light . The corpulent detective soon discovers that Gordon is only a pawn in a devilish scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106090500 +0000" stop="20260106100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Jeopardy For Two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby follows a double agent who's stolen a porcelain collection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106100000 +0000" stop="20260106103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Courtroom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>The policeman's role in court is highlighted in this episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106103000 +0000" stop="20260106110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Parolee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon retrace a 14-year-old investigation to determine whether charges can be brought against a man up for parole.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106110000 +0000" stop="20260106113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 101: Someone Stole My Lawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed wants an early dinner when his wife puts him on a low-cal diet. However, one after another events prevents them from going code 7 all night long. Events include the theft of a man's sod, stolen credit cards and a suspected car theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106113000 +0000" stop="20260106120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 132 -- Producer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed tries to pawn off his new litter of puppies to co-workers, strangers and even victims. The officers work a silent alarm, rescue a boy with his head stuck in a fence and track down a prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106120000 +0000" stop="20260106130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Pepe!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate the debut of Pepé Le Pew."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106130000 +0000" stop="20260106133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward's Uncle Billy arrives in Mayfield for a visit and begins telling Wally and Beaver exaggerated stories. Not realizing this, Beaver expects Billy to come through after promising Beaver a fishing reel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106133000 +0000" stop="20260106140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher's Daughter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's latest girlfriend is Julie Foster, who just happens to be the daughter of a Mr. Foster, who teaches English. Meanwhile, at school, a new semester lands Wally in Mr. Foster's class and he quickly finds himself feeling uncomfortable—especially after Eddie tells him that his relationship with Julie will determine his grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106140000 +0000" stop="20260106150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Blind Man's Bluff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Crooked jewelry store owner Karl Addison learns that he needs an operation that will temporarily blind him. Addison makes plans to rob his own store knowing that his sightlessness will provide him with a perfect alibi.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106150000 +0000" stop="20260106160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Model  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock has finally had a breakthrough in the case he was struggling with, but after being hit by a car, he needs to put the case together from scratch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106160000 +0000" stop="20260106170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>...and They Painted Daisies On His Coffin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>While off-duty, Danno chases down a young teenager who was trying to break into a car. Danno is stunned when he accidentally kills the boy. When investigators can't locate the boy's gun, Danno is indicted for first-degree murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106170000 +0000" stop="20260106180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Boy From The C.c.c.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A troubled teenager from Manhattan runs away from the Civilian Conservation Corps to Walton's Mountain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106180000 +0000" stop="20260106190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Eliab's Aim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Festus' nephew Eliab comes gunning for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106190000 +0000" stop="20260106200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam takes a trip to Mexico to collect the body of the son of a former Ponderosa foreman who is too old to make the trip. Believing it to be a simple task, Adam arrives only to find that there is a lot more going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106200000 +0000" stop="20260106203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shivaree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Aaron Pelser's wagon train comes across a pair of young boys on a buck board heading west, so he invites them to join the train. When he finds out that one of the boys is actually a girl and the two claim to be headed to Yuma to get married, Pelser and his crowd force them to be married in North Fork.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106203000 +0000" stop="20260106210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadeye Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>McCain befriends Donnel O'Mahoney, a tough kid from Brooklyn, and arranges with two men for the young man to continue his travels on their wagon. Things go wrong, however, when one of them is murdered, and the other accuses the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106210000 +0000" stop="20260106220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Echo Pass Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>"While out looking for water Coop and Charlie are stopped by a gang of five, including two women, who are on the run after robbing a bank and killing three lawmen. The leader of the gang shoots Charlie after tying him up, and they take Coop to lead them through a mountain pass to get to California."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106220000 +0000" stop="20260106230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Gossip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy encourages John to represent the station in the Fireman's Olympics track events. An armored car sideswipes a motorist and Station 51 must break into the van. A nurse spreads the rumor that Dr. Morton is having financial problems. Doctors treat a child with cyanide poisoning from peach pits. Dr. Brackett treats a bigamist with a skull fracture. The firemen rescue an electrocution victim hanging in mid-air and a man trapped in a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106230000 +0000" stop="20260106233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombshells</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing the theory that people will believe in anything, Charles and Hawkeye start a rumor that Marilyn Monroe plans to visit the 4077th, which gets everyone excited. Meanwhile, B.J. feels responsible when he's unable to rescue a wounded soldier, and is less than impressed when he is presented with a Bronze Star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260106233000 +0000" stop="20260107000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Settling Debts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and the crew surprise Colonel Potter with a party to commemorate Mildred's final payment on the couple's mortgage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107000000 +0000" stop="20260107003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moon Is Not Blue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>With the camp facing prohibition and a severe medical supply shortage during another heat wave, Hawkeye resolves to lift morale by importing a racy new movie.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107003000 +0000" stop="20260107010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Run For The Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>When an Olympic runner assigned to the 4077th fails to materialize, Father Mulcahy must save the camp's honor in a high-stakes footrace against the 8063rd.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107010000 +0000" stop="20260107013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee's Romance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An old beau of Aunt Bee comes to town to court her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107013000 +0000" stop="20260107020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Bloodhound</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney's attempts to train an old mutt named Blue as a police dog coincide with a manhunt for an escaped criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107020000 +0000" stop="20260107023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Vote For Debra, A</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray votes against Debra for school president.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107023000 +0000" stop="20260107030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Call Me Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray wants Debra to start calling Marie "mom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107030000 +0000" stop="20260107033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan's Hofbrau</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan visits a local Hofbrau to get the plans to a German army division that is camping out nearby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107033000 +0000" stop="20260107040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Oil For The Lamps Of Hogan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that there is oil underneath the camp in order to discourage the Germans from building a synthetic fuel plant there.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107040000 +0000" stop="20260107043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Joel Grey And Vincent Price</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol meets Vicki's mama's-boy boyfriend. Then, in The Switchboard, Carol plays a nosey operator who eavesdrops on the romantic entanglements of the hotel guests.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107043000 +0000" stop="20260107053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lonely Heiress</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Heiress Marilyn Cartright places an ad in a magazine in order to find love and companionship. In reality, Marilyn is looking for the con artist who swindled and drove her sister to suicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107053500 +0000" stop="20260107060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Dust</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>After selling the rope for a hanging, a conscienceless peddler tries to sell the condemned man's father a bag of "magic dust."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107060500 +0000" stop="20260107070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Evil Of Adelaide Winters  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A woman runs a psychic scam, making people believe she can contact their dead love ones. One of her victims, however, becomes dangerously obsessed when he believes she is able to contact his dead son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107070500 +0000" stop="20260107080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Delayed Reaction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix discovers that a 20-year-old crime is attached to a mysterious hit-and-run accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107080500 +0000" stop="20260107090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Seventh Grave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon investigates a kidnapping case. The lawyer David Rackham has been abducted. Because he is diabetic and needs a certain drug, Cannon questions the pharmacists of the surroundings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107090500 +0000" stop="20260107100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Bond Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby is hired to reinvestigate a case in which a woman is found innocent of murder by a jury, but found guilty by the townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107100000 +0000" stop="20260107103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary Auto - Juvenile Genius</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday tracks down thieves responsible for a series of Los Angeles robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107103000 +0000" stop="20260107110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Bunco - $9,000</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The search is on for a swindler who conned an old vaudevillian out of $9,000 he found on a sidewalk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107110000 +0000" stop="20260107113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 111: Snake In The Trunk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A ditzy young woman reports her 1958 Ford convertible stolen while she went into a liquor store. She left the keys in the car, has no paperwork, doesn't know the license number or other details but she needs it by 6 PM for a date. She finally tells the officers that her eight-foot boa constrictor is in the trunk as she was coming from the vet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107113000 +0000" stop="20260107120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 61: The Runaway</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Walters and Brinkman are on a roll lately and like to brag, much to the irritation of Reed. He and Malloy help them out by finishing one of their calls, then rescue a sick teenage girl and arrest the young man who took her in. Back on patrol, they meet an informant who gives them a tip on a big drug buy scheduled for 11 PM. They give the info to Sgt. Miller who asks them to help in the bust.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107120000 +0000" stop="20260107130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Toon In's Wellness Wednesday: Money Matters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony try to improve their finances in the new year with consumer advocate and special guest Jeff Rossen from Rossen Reports."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107130000 +0000" stop="20260107133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Ward's Millions</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Wanting Ward to become a millionaire, Beaver buys him a book called "I Became a Millionaire in Twelve Months." Ward thanks him for it but Beaver quickly learns that Ward is just being polite as to spare his feelings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107133000 +0000" stop="20260107140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Secret Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After revealing that he wants to be a writer when he grows up, Ward buys Beaver a diary to practice writing and Beaver begins keeping a record of his daily activities. However, June and Ward pick the lock and sneak a peek at his diary after Beaver neglects to come home on time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107140000 +0000" stop="20260107150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Barefaced Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>In a small California town throwing a festival during which all men wear beards, Paul Drake tries to locate missing money embezzled by a former bank president.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107150000 +0000" stop="20260107160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Temptation  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A thug tries to make Leanne fall in love with him by using her journal that he stole from her house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107160000 +0000" stop="20260107170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Twenty-four Karat Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman buys fish from a monger, and is followed home and murdered. McGarrett and the team must discover who killed her and stop smugglers from completing their operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107170000 +0000" stop="20260107180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ceremony</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A Jewish Nazi-refugee family moves to Walton's Mountain from Germany</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107180000 +0000" stop="20260107190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Thursday's Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Doc falls for a woman who seems to be haunted by her past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107190000 +0000" stop="20260107200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Tax Collector</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>At the behest of a local bureaucrat, good-for-nothing Jock Henry becomes Virginia City's tax collector. Jock also becomes drunk with power, levying huge, unfair assessments against everybody in the vicinity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107200000 +0000" stop="20260107203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Indian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart arrives in North Fork in search of renegade indians suspected of the brutal killing of a Texas Ranger and his family. The townspeople are suspicious of him, however, when they discover that he, too, is an indian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107203000 +0000" stop="20260107210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarding House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Reformed card shark Julia Massini now runs a respectable boarding house in North Fork, but Sid Fallon is threatening to reveal her sordid past unless she lets him turn the establishment into a saloon and gambling hall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107210000 +0000" stop="20260107220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Chottsie Gubenheimer Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale finds his old flame Chottsie Gubenheimer (played by John McIntire's real-life wife Jeanette Nolan) working in a gambling house and in an argument with the owner, so he asks her to come with him and join the wagon train. He comes to realize that he's getting more problems than he bargained for."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107220000 +0000" stop="20260107230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nagging Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy picks winning horses from the newspaper and Johnny wants to know how he does it. The paramedics rescue a woman who has fallen into a lion’s cage, a dancer in a bar and an adult skateboarder who landed in a cactus patch. They also save a bleeding policeman from a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107230000 +0000" stop="20260107233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>U.n., The Night And The Music</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A United Nations delegation tours the 4077th—a Swede, a Hindu and a British officer— and each leaves a lasting effect on the men and women of the camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260107233000 +0000" stop="20260108000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Bedfellows</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th faces a sleepless night as Charles's snoring keeps B.J. and Hawkeye from counting sheep. Meanwhile, Colonel Potter discovers that his son-in-law, Bob Wilson, has had an affair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108000000 +0000" stop="20260108003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Say No More</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A military strategist refuses to accept responsibility for the war games that have mortally wounded his own son. And Margaret develops laryngitis, as she is about to meet her hero, Dr. Chesler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108003000 +0000" stop="20260108010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Friends And Enemies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter must deal with an old Army friend who is getting his own soldiers killed through his incompetency.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108010000 +0000" stop="20260108013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In The Middle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Thelma Lou have an argument. They reconcile quickly, but it leads to other arguments between Andy and Barney, Thelma Lou and Helen, Andy and Helen, and another between Barney and Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108013000 +0000" stop="20260108020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Uniform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred the grocery store clerk repeatedly sweeps trash into the street, even after Barney writes him a citation. Fred threatens that if he ever sees Barney out of uniform, he'll pound him, causing Barney to leave his uniform on at all times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108020000 +0000" stop="20260108023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Mother's Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra takes offense when Marie accuses her of being rude.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108023000 +0000" stop="20260108030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Bigger Person, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra goes out of her way to ensure that Ray doesn't spend time with his mother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108030000 +0000" stop="20260108033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Reservations Are Required</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Hogan tries to arrange the unscheduled escape of 20 men, his mission is complicated when a captured sergeant jumps the gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108033000 +0000" stop="20260108040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Anchors Aweigh, Men Of Stalag 13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men are tasked with getting an escaped prisoner and smuggled German gun sight to England. To accomplish this Hogan convinces Klink that he is fatigued and should have an officer's club in which to relax.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108040000 +0000" stop="20260108043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Tim Conway And Bernadette Peters</sub-title>
    <desc>In As the Stomach Turns, Carol's sweet niece visits, only to discover she's possessed, in this parody of "The Exorcist". Then, in Two-Man Sub, two sailors must complete their mission: sink Cleveland.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108043000 +0000" stop="20260108053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Green-eyed Sister</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Arthur West, a disreputable private investigator, has found J. J. Stanley in a cheap motel. He knows Stanley and his partner, Ned Bain, were involved in the embezzlement of the Texas National Bank. He wants to blackmail Bain into giving him money to keep quiet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108053500 +0000" stop="20260108060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Back There</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>While discussing time travel among friends in 1961, a man suddenly finds himself in 1865—on the date of Lincoln's assassination.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108060500 +0000" stop="20260108070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Jar  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A man buys a jar containing a mystifying "thing" in this tale adapted from a short story by Ray Bradbury.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108070500 +0000" stop="20260108080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill A Writer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>When Mannix is hired to prevent a murder of a mystery writer, the intended victim wants no help in solving the crime himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108080500 +0000" stop="20260108090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Catch Me If You Can</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl turns up dead at the yacht party thrown by two jet set brothers, Edgar and Norman Bruce. Her father, George Able, wants to exact revenge, but before he can even get close to the siblings he is beaten up by his henchmen. Cannon is hired by Abel's second daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108090500 +0000" stop="20260108100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Theater Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A former actress believes that someone is trying to foil her comeback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108100000 +0000" stop="20260108103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narco - Missing Hype</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>This episode focuses on drugs, paying particular attention to addiction symptoms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108103000 +0000" stop="20260108110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - Helpful Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Police track down a thief who specializes in elderly people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108110000 +0000" stop="20260108113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 81: The Long Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>After roll call, Reed and Malloy provide backup at a robbery, help a lost man return home, handle a call about a prowler and respond to a silent alarm. Malloy demonstrates for Reed the importance of "officer presence."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108113000 +0000" stop="20260108120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 36 -- Jimmy Eisley's Dealing Smack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed and Malloy spot TJ, an informant, who tells them about a possible drug house. They spot a woman and girl at the same bus stop an hour apart. When they stop to talk to her, she tries to run.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108120000 +0000" stop="20260108130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday 1949</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore the year 1949!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108130000 +0000" stop="20260108133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Track Meet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is all set to compete in a track meet but after the coach catches him "horsing around" in the locker room, he's ousted from the meet, even though Lumpy and Eddie were egging him on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108133000 +0000" stop="20260108140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Old Buddy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Beaver's spends the weekend at the Cleavers and Beaver is all ready to have a great time like they used to. However, Beaver quickly discovers that people change and in this case Beaver's old buddy has indeed changed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108140000 +0000" stop="20260108150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Difficult Detour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Contactor Pete Mallory is charged with the murder of a vacation resort developer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108150000 +0000" stop="20260108160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Crook  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Wally McDaniels, a fellow choir member, after he is arrested for killing the man who had turned him in to the police for stealing rare books.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108160000 +0000" stop="20260108170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The Ways Of Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>After a girl dies during a high-speed car chase, the trail of clues leads to a Los Angeles prison. McGarrett goes undercover as convict Steve Crowley and aids in a prison escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108170000 +0000" stop="20260108180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Legend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>John's World War I buddy (Jim Antonio) visits,</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108180000 +0000" stop="20260108190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Breckinridge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawyer from the east questions Matt's every move.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108190000 +0000" stop="20260108200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Vengeance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>After accidentally killing Willie Twilight, a guilt-stricken Hoss is inconsolable. Meanwhile, Willie's brother, Red, arrives in town intent on exacting revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108200000 +0000" stop="20260108203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas puts his life in jeopardy when he agrees to testify in a murder case involving a witness killed before he could testify and a killer still at large.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108203000 +0000" stop="20260108210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Outlaw Sam Morley falls in love with a young woman who has a serious illness. He asks Lucas to turn him in for the reward and then use the money to pay for her medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108210000 +0000" stop="20260108220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Wanda Snow Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>"Wanda Snow has several times seen events before they have happened, causing several people on the wagon train to accuse her of being a witch. A medicine show peddler/magician gets the idea to use her in his act, but this creates friction between him and his devious partner."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108220000 +0000" stop="20260108230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Gaffe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and Joanne go on a TV quiz show. Roy and John respond to a holdup where both a policeman and a suspect have been shot, and another officer gives them a hard time over treating the suspect. A woman brings in her abused son for treatment. A man inhales too much nitrous oxide. The paramedics treat a boy suffering an allergic reaction to a bee sting. A pickup carrying kerosene collides with a station wagon and starts a brushfire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108230000 +0000" stop="20260108233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Give And Take</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A wounded GI learns a painful lesson when he forms a recovery room friendship with the enemy soldier he's critically wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260108233000 +0000" stop="20260109000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>As Time Goes By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and Hawkeye work on a time capsule to commemorate their time in Korea; Rizzo and B.J. goof around with a fake hand grenade; Klinger becomes smitten with a young, pretty Korean war criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109000000 +0000" stop="20260109003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pilot Episode</sub-title>
    <desc>"At the 4077th Mobile Army Surgical Hospital (M.A.S.H) unit in Korea, two army doctors by the names of Hawkeye Pierce and Trapper John McIntyre receive some exciting news in the mail. Their Korean house boy, Ho-John got accepted into Hawkeye's old college. Hawkeye and Trapper decide to hold a party filled with music, dancing, and alcohol to raise money for Ho-John's plane trip to the U.S. They achieve this by raffling off a weekend pass with a nurse, Lieutenant Dish for R&amp;R in Tokyo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109003000 +0000" stop="20260109010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>To Market, To Market</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>After black marketers hijack the 4077th's supply of hydrocortisone, Hawkeye and Trapper concoct a deal with local black marketer, Charlie Lee, to get some more. The catch: Henry's antique oak desk, which they must trade in order to get the medicine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109010000 +0000" stop="20260109013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie finds a lost wallet containing $50, and just as he's waited the seven-day period to claim the money as his own, the owner steps forward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109013000 +0000" stop="20260109020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Sheriff Taylor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers moving to Raleigh for another job. An upset Barney tries to demonstrate to Andy just how bad Mayberry would be without him, creating more harm than good in his effort to get Andy to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109020000 +0000" stop="20260109023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>First Time, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and Debra fondly recall the first night they spent together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109023000 +0000" stop="20260109030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Cult, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert decides to join a support group.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109030000 +0000" stop="20260109033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Happy Birthday, Adolf</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys plan to destroy a gun emplacement so the Allies can attack on Hitler's birthday.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109033000 +0000" stop="20260109040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gold Rush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>French gold has been stolen by the Nazis. Hogan convinces Klink to have it brought to Stalag 13 so the prisoners can steal it back.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109040000 +0000" stop="20260109043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Vic Voyeur Show, Carol discovers her husband is cheating on her while listening to a radio program. Then, in The Thin Man, a parody on the hit series,  the husband-wife detective duo search for a murder among dinner guests. Finally, in The Interrogator, a captured American solider meets the toughest interrogator yet -- a Hitler puppet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109043000 +0000" stop="20260109053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fugitive Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Janet Norris is charged with poisoning her doctor husband just before he flew to his death in his private plane. Further investigation reveals that Dr. Norris did not die in the plane crash and that he is in Mexico with his nurse mistress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109053500 +0000" stop="20260109060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Invaders</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman in an isolated farmhouse is troubled by the appearance of tiny aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109060500 +0000" stop="20260109070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Final Escape  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A prisoner bent on breaking out of a maximum-security prison matches wits with his custodian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109070500 +0000" stop="20260109080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl In The Frame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is hired to investigate a possible forgery of a Renoir when the collector sees the model who posed for the painting in person.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109080500 +0000" stop="20260109090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Press Pass To The Slammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109090500 +0000" stop="20260109100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Orchid Killer, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As soon as a man is released from a mental institute for the criminally insane, he's accused of killing one of the nurses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109100000 +0000" stop="20260109103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Who Killed Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A shooting case exemplifies how the police gather—and why they must sometimes withhold—evidence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109103000 +0000" stop="20260109110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Burglary - The Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday investigates a woman's claim that her husband is an armed robber.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109110000 +0000" stop="20260109113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 62 -- Grand Theft Horse?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The officers have to put with a mystery noise in the car while handling grand theft horse, a naive girl and a robbery suspect who makes fake calls to distract the police</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109113000 +0000" stop="20260109120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 33 -- It All Happened So Fast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>In a behind-the-scenes look at police investigations into deadly force incidents, Reed endures a night of intensive questioning by the station's lieutenant after he kills a man in self-defense.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109120000 +0000" stop="20260109130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Panic At The Museum</sub-title>
    <desc>"What begins as a relaxing day trip to a local history museum turns into a overnight fiasco."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109130000 +0000" stop="20260109133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tonsils</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>When Beaver becomes sick, the doctor thinks Beaver may need to have his tonsils taken out. Ward quickly puts Beaver's fears to rest by telling him everyone will bring him presents when they visit him in the hospital. This leads Beaver to tell everyone that he's going to have surgery, but then he finds out he may not need the operation after all.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109133000 +0000" stop="20260109140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Fish Count</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie makes it known to everyone that he's just gotten a job down at Parker's Pet Store, which happens to be holding a contest in which you guess the number of fish in a tank. After hours of counting and re-counting, Gilbert suggests to Beaver that they ought to just ask Eddie for the count, but Beaver is a bit hesitant about cheating.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109140000 +0000" stop="20260109150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Cowardly Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hilde Fursten and Tony Osgood work at the San Diego Zoo. When a baby monkey goes missing, Fursten is blamed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109150000 +0000" stop="20260109160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Murder Game  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to spend the weekend as part of a murder mystery with Cliff, Leanne and three people who each paid $10,000 for the privilege of matching wits with the famous Ben Matlock. When the pretend victim turns up dead, Matlock and his team must determine which of the three paying customers is the guilty party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109160000 +0000" stop="20260109170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>No Blue Skies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a singer, Joey Rand, finds that his career doesn't pay well enough, he turns to cat burglary. However he doesn't reckon on Hawaii Five-O.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109170000 +0000" stop="20260109180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Literary Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A well-read man claiming to be a writer, comes to Walton's Mountain and befriends John-Boy, helping him with his writing</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109180000 +0000" stop="20260109190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Bank Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Bert Clum plots to rob pilgrim families in nearby camps.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109190000 +0000" stop="20260109200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The boys decide that Ben is getting too old and advise him to take it easy while they go on search for cattle rustlers. Ben reluctantly agrees, but when his sons fail to return he goes out after them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109200000 +0000" stop="20260109203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>One Went To Denver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas welcomes his old friend, Tom Birch, who once saved his life, unaware that the man is now a bank robber who is on the run with his gang.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109203000 +0000" stop="20260109210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Wait</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Maury, released from Yuma prison, arrives in North Fork intent on getting even with Marshal Torrance, who helped send him to jail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109210000 +0000" stop="20260109220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Miss Mary Lee Mcintosh Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>"Coop and Charlie ride into a small village for supplies finding it deserted. There is an Indian who stays hidden and later three men and a woman ride into town. They have been looking for the woman's father in a cave filled with bats."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109220000 +0000" stop="20260109230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Surprise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman is thrown from a motorcycle into a cactus patch. A surprise birthday party is planned for Dixie, who breaks her ankle while shopping, and the ER falls apart without her. Gage and DeSoto rescue two workers trapped on the side of a building next to a 1,000-pound sign. A man is trapped in his new sauna. When an old woman refuses to leave her apartment during a gas leak, the building explodes with John inside.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109230000 +0000" stop="20260109233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Requiem For A Lightweight</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Trapper and Hawkeye seek to keep a new nurse from being transferred by Hot Lips, and they vie for her affection. Henry Blake, challenged by another commander to a boxing tournament, makes Trapper fight a big, intimidating soldier in exchange for keeping the nurse at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260109233000 +0000" stop="20260110000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Chief Surgeon Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Burns complains about Hawkeye Pierce's disrespect, and when Henry appoints Hawkeye chief surgeon, it's to Burns' shock. The rest of the 4077th "coronates" Hawk while Frank and Hot Lips complain to General Barker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110000000 +0000" stop="20260110003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Moose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Sergeant Baker arrives at the camp with his "moose." Hawkeye decides to find a way of getting her away from Baker. He tries ordering him to release her, tries buying her and then resorts to cheating at cards. He releases her but she won't go, so he tries to teach her how to be independent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110003000 +0000" stop="20260110010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yankee Doodle Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is designated as the setting for the making of an army film on Mobile Army Surgical Hospital units. Hawkeye is chosen as the star while Margaret and Frank compose a screenplay. Hawkeye objects to the piece of propaganda that filmmaker Lt. Bricker is producing and, having exposed the original film, reshoots a new one his way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110010000 +0000" stop="20260110013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pageant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets the lead role in the Centennial Pageant as Lady Mayberry. She is, however, not up to the challenge, and Andy must find a way to tell her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110013000 +0000" stop="20260110020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darling Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Darlings come to Mayberry looking for a boy whom they could engage to Charlene's new baby. Opie becomes the prime target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110020000 +0000" stop="20260110023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Counseling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra and Ray see a marriage counselor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110023000 +0000" stop="20260110030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Homework</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Raymond is invited to address the curriculum review board.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110030000 +0000" stop="20260110033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Zolle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to detain a German general at camp for 24 hours to allow the Allies to amass troops. Things get complicated when a Gestapo officer comes in search of the reason for Klink's perfect record.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110033000 +0000" stop="20260110040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It Takes A Thief... Sometimes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of underground operatives that Hogan and his team begin working with is actually a group lead by a Gestapo captain who's set on capturing them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110040000 +0000" stop="20260110043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hit, Carol puts a "hit" on her husband, then worries she's in danger being around him. Then, in P.T.A. Auditions, a Russian director must cope with a bad leading lady. Finally, in Daughter of Houdini, a fake magician finds herself trapped in a sinking box.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110043000 +0000" stop="20260110053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The One-eyed Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Della and Mason's dinner at a fancy French restaurant is interrupted by a phone call and an envelope containing $500 from a mysterious woman named Marian Fargo. She wants him to make an exchange: the money for some documents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110053500 +0000" stop="20260110060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Penny For Your Thoughts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Gaining telepathic abilities when his coin lands on its edge, a mild-mannered bank clerk learns about the difference between other people's plans and fantasies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110060500 +0000" stop="20260110070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Murder Case  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A struggling actor auditioning in London learns that his ex-girlfriend is now married to the play's wealthy backer. They soon rekindle their romance and plan to murder her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110070500 +0000" stop="20260110080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Cry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix discovers evidence of a crime from an unlikely source: a deaf girl who "heard" the plot by reading the lips of a criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110080500 +0000" stop="20260110090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Publisher Quigley asks Cannon for help. He believes that hotel proprietor Rawdon has killed six girls. When the seventh victim is found, however, it's Quigley himself who becomes the prime suspect. A lab assistant manipulates the samples used in the framework of the murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110090500 +0000" stop="20260110100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Price Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the murder of a reporter who was investigating a Vietnam veteran's past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260110100000 +0000" stop="20260110103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Only Boy In The Class</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Bobbie Jo takes pity on the only boy in her home economics class and induces her mother to help him win a passing grade.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
