<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213150000 +0000" stop="20251213160000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Janus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A melody holds the clue West needs to trap a departmental traitor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213160000 +0000" stop="20251213170000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tom O'neal Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E31</episode-num>
    <desc>"Tom O'Neal and Ellen Howard want to get married, but their parents object, so Tom takes money from his father's savings and runs away with Ellen. They soon realize that that was an unwise decision."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213170000 +0000" stop="20251213180000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Plunder!</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Heath is sent to a town endangered by a possible dam break. The town has been abandoned except for a few men who are there to guard against looters. Temptation gets the better of them, and they turn on Heath.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213180000 +0000" stop="20251213190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Old Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt searches for the real killer of Joe Silva when an old man is framed for the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213190000 +0000" stop="20251213200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Death At Dawn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When a local merchant is gunned down for refusing to pay off thugs who've taken over town, Farmer Perkins is charged with the crime and sentenced to hang. Ben is taken hostage by Perkins' employer, with threats to hang Ben if Perkins is not released.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213200000 +0000" stop="20251213203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Quiet Night, Deadly Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Townspeople brace for the worst when a new girl arrives—with symptoms of smallpox.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213203000 +0000" stop="20251213210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Never Rides Alone</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger rides into North Fork for a meeting with Lucas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213210000 +0000" stop="20251213220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Quivira</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Monty Fox comes stumbling up to the night camp playing the concertina, saying he's found the promised land. He says he's found Quivera, Coronado's golden city. He says he'll share with those who help him against those who chased him out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213220000 +0000" stop="20251213223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Silver Convoy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>Paladin is hired to find James Becker. He trails him to Monterey and discovers he has been arrested and is sentenced to work in a silver mine. Paladin finds that Becker has died in a cave-in or so he is told. The owner of the mine hires Paladin to guard a silver convoy, but first Paladin wants to find out a little more about the mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213223000 +0000" stop="20251213230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Triple Vise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and Jason go to Mexico searching for Al Hemp's brother, Billy. Al took the blame for Billy's crime and ends up waiting for his brother—a no show.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251213230000 +0000" stop="20251214010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Little Beers, Dizzy Doctors, Tassels In The Air, Sing A Song Of Six Pants, Fiddlers Three, Rusty Romeos</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Stooges are inept deliverymen at a brewery.   , Larry, Curly and Moe make a grand mess of things when they mistake the medicine they're selling for auto polish.  , The Stooges don't know it, but they are all engaged to the same girl, a gold-digger who plans to get an engagement ring from each of them and then abandon them.  When all three show up at her house at the same time, a wild fight ensues, as each stooge accuses the others of making time with "his" girl.  The gold-digger gets it in the end (literally) with tacks shot from a repeating rifle.  [A remake of "Corny Casanovas".] , Moe pretends to be trendy interior designer. , "The stooges are tailors, and are heavily in debt to the Skin &amp; Flint finance company. When the boys read about the big reward for a fugitive robber, they think it could be the answer to their problems. The bank robber conveniently ducks into their shop and leaves a suit with a safe combination. After his girl friend fails to retrieve it, the robber returns with gang and a wild fight ensues. The boys miss out on the reward but wind up with the crook's bankroll and can pay their creditors. 
" , The Stooges are musicians at the court of King Cole.  When they ask the king's permission to marry their sweethearts, the King agrees, but only after Princess Alicia has married Prince Valiant.  This news upsets Mergatroyd, an evil magician who plans to marry the Princess himself and rule the Kingdom.  Mergatroyd abducts the Princess, and it's up to the Stooges to foil his plans and expose his evil doings. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214010000 +0000" stop="20251214033000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>Duel</sub-title>
    <desc>"A business commuter is pursued and terrorized by the malevolent driver of a massive tractor-trailer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214033000 +0000" stop="20251214040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Wail Of The Siren</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Using her hypnotic voice, the Siren sends Commissioner Gordon on a mission to find the location of the Batcave and Batman's secret identity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214040000 +0000" stop="20251214050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Is Yesterday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Enterprise collides with a black hole and is thrown back to Earth in the 20th century, where they must find a way back to their timeline while erasing any trace of their presence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214050000 +0000" stop="20251214053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Close Shave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After being convinced to go straight, notorious gangster Rick Sable tips Jimmy off to a robbery his gang will commit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214053000 +0000" stop="20251214060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Alibi</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A professor invents a machine to transport people by telephone wire, and crooks use the machine to send Lois and Jimmy to Alaska.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214060000 +0000" stop="20251214070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Civilization</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Robinson men discover an underground civilization while exploring the planet. Will wakes a sleeping princess who wants him to remain and rule with her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214070000 +0000" stop="20251214080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Brand Of The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Exposure to radiation causes Nelson to be afflicted by the werewolf virus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214080000 +0000" stop="20251214090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Panic</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A friendly Giant scientist tries to help the Earthlings with his teleporter, but the SID find out about his sympathies and set a trap.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214090000 +0000" stop="20251214100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Merlin The Magician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>In England, the time travelers try to help Merlin the magician secure the throne for young King Arthur.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214100000 +0000" stop="20251214110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>Inquisition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A bombing and a suspicious man leads Vincent to question an official with possible alien connections.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214110000 +0000" stop="20251214120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Spoilers</sub-title>
    <desc>"Fish in Hoot Owl Creek are dying off and animals are falling ill as well. Adams,Jack and Nakoma decide it could be something in the water...but what and possibly who is caused it?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214120000 +0000" stop="20251214123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Swamp Water Safari</sub-title>
    <desc>"Death stalks the Florida Everglades.  Not swift death by predators but a slow, agonizing death caused by drought and floods.  Marlin and Jim visit the Everglades to investigate this problem first hand."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214123000 +0000" stop="20251214130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Exploring Jaguar Country</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to the high country of northern Mexico to explore the hills where the jaguar roams."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214130000 +0000" stop="20251214133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>To Catch A Giraffe</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to Rhodesia to join in a game relocation project with the rangers of Wankie National Park … a game preserve where all kinds of wild animals make their home.  Two animals are on their list:  a zebra and a giraffe."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214133000 +0000" stop="20251214140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Giants Of Dadanawa</sub-title>
    <desc>"Because of its inaccessibility to man and its climate, the South American jungles encourage the growth of its animal life.  Marlin and Stan Brock go on an expedition to capture the largest of their kind and to see just why these jungle giants grow to such proportions."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214140000 +0000" stop="20251214143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Strange Partnership</sub-title>
    <desc>"Throughout the wild kingdom there are many examples of animal cooperation, and one of the most remarkable takes place in a picturesque little valley in southern Utah …  home for families of badgers, bobcats, coyotes and golden eagles."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214143000 +0000" stop="20251214150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tuskers Below</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey to Kruger National Park in the Republic of South Africa to join the rangers there in an exciting wild elephant capture."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214150000 +0000" stop="20251214153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Coming-out Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike's boss, Mr. Phillips, invites the Brady family on a fishing trip. However, when Cindy comes down with tonsillitis, the trip is postponed, to everyone's dismay. They try to keep an epidemic at bay in the Brady house.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214153000 +0000" stop="20251214160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Our Son, The Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg, tired of the antics of his younger siblings, thinks he should have his own room. Mike allows Greg to turn his den into his own room. This also leads to Greg dressing a whole new way and talking a whole new way, including calling his parents by their first names.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214160000 +0000" stop="20251214163000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Fonzie receives a Christmas gift from his father but is reluctant to accept and open it. Meanwhile, Richie and Lori Beth argue about what they've spent on each other's gifts, and Joanie is upset at Howard for getting an artificial tree.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214163000 +0000" stop="20251214170000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Angels Of Mercy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Laverne and Shirley become hospital volunteers, or "candy stripers," and have a hard time as newbie nurses.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214170000 +0000" stop="20251214180000 +0000">
    <title>A Very Merry Bugs Bunny Christmas</title>
    <sub-title>Bugs Bunny's Christmas Carol, Gift Wrapped, Abominable Snow Rabbit, Freeze Frame, Weasel While You Work, The Fright Before Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"When Sam lacks the Christmas spirit, Bugs Bunny makes a plan to change his mind., It's Christmas time and Sylvester tries to switch his present with Granny's present which is Tweety in a birdcage., Bugs and Daffy decide to tunnel underground over to Palm Springs. Wrong directions end them up in the Himalayas where they run into trouble with the Abominable Snowman... , The coyote orders a blizzard machine to cover the entire desert with snow after he finds out that Road Runners are easy to catch in the cold. , During a snow-covered winter, Foghorn Leghorn uses the weasel against the barn's guard dog. , Taz breaks free of his a plane shipping crate and falls from the sky into Santa's laundry. He hijacks Santa's sleigh and ends up in Bugs' house tearing down everything, but Bugs gets wise to the Devil. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214180000 +0000" stop="20251214183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Pet Fair</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A pet fair at school has Beaver feeling left out because he doesn't have a pet, but he tells everyone he does, a parrot. Meanwhile, Ward tries to find a pet for Beaver and buys him a hamster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214183000 +0000" stop="20251214190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Test</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>An upcoming test in history, Wally's weakest subject, has Wally studying all weekend and has Larry and Eddie coming up with a plan that will give them good grades on the test.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214190000 +0000" stop="20251214193000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Christmas Present</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts are preparing for Christmas, but are lacking in one thing: Christmas spirit. Jed thinks it is because they aren’t doing anything special for anyone this Christmas. He thinks they should do something special for Mrs. Drysdale, unaware she is still trying to get rid of them. They try to get jobs to raise money for her gift, so she doesn’t find out.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214193000 +0000" stop="20251214200000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Week Before Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a letter from Sam Drucker in Hooterville, but Elly's bear eats it. So after Granny finds very little success knowing if she is engaged or not, Jed, Granny and Elly all decide to spend Christmas in Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214200000 +0000" stop="20251214220000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>A Very Brady Christmas</sub-title>
    <desc>"The entire Brady family manages to overcome personal obstacles to spend a happy holiday together."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214220000 +0000" stop="20251214230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Presence, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mickey Rooney plays a mystical Christmas presence among a motley group of passengers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214230000 +0000" stop="20251214233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mountain Wedding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney visit the Darlings to rid them of Ernest T. Bass, who has his mind set on marrying daughter Charlene.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251214233000 +0000" stop="20251215000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Star Wars- Gus Lopez</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gus Lopez's out-of-this-world, Star Wars collection includes Han Solo's screen-used jacket, C-3PO's body parts, and the screen-used DEATH STAR! Expert Rob Klein attempts to make a trade with Gus, by bringing him a special Star Wars collectible that may not be familiar to every Star Wars fan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215000000 +0000" stop="20251215003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Death Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester fulfills a family Christmas tradition but has trouble maintaining the anonymity required to keep it a truly charitable act. Even Klinger lends a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215003000 +0000" stop="20251215010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215010000 +0000" stop="20251215013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Crisis Of Faith (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith's religious faith is shaken after her friend, female impersonator Beverly LaSalle, is brutally murdered by street thugs at Christmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215013000 +0000" stop="20251215020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Edith's Crisis Of Faith (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Mike is put in the hospital and Beverly LaSalle is murdered by a thug at Chistmas.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215020000 +0000" stop="20251215023000 +0000">
    <title>Good Times</title>
    <sub-title>Penny's Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Christmas season has the Evans family in the spirit and planning a Christmas Eve party. Meanwhile, while Christmas shopping for her mother, Penny gets her wallet stolen, and later steals a necklace from a department store in a desperate attempt to try</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215023000 +0000" stop="20251215030000 +0000">
    <title>Good Times</title>
    <sub-title>The Traveling Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When Keith's Scrooge-like boss at the taxi-cab company won't give him Christmas off, the Evans family brings their Christmas party to Keith and holds at the company. J.J. hosts the festivities and it features Michael singing, Bookman (dressed as Santa) da</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215030000 +0000" stop="20251215033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Walk To The Door, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is mortified when he meets a girl he dated 25 years earlier.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215033000 +0000" stop="20251215040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Young Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>All hell breaks loose when Robert starts dating a girl half his age.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215040000 +0000" stop="20251215043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Boarder Incident</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Buddy's stay at the Petries causes endless problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215043000 +0000" stop="20251215050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Father Of The Week</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie isn't happy when Rob is awarded "Father of the Week".</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215050000 +0000" stop="20251215053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>A Dog's Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph feeds his boss dog food, thinking that it is an appetizer that Alice made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215053000 +0000" stop="20251215060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Nice Place To Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After being shot to death, a gangster finds himself in a place where he gets everything his heart desires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215060000 +0000" stop="20251215070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle George  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A neighbor's letter about an unfaithful wife disturbs an advice columnist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215070000 +0000" stop="20251215080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Blues (aka Hard Rock)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF plots to bring down a corrupt music producer who murdered a singer he had under contract through manipulating his equally unscrupulous partner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215080000 +0000" stop="20251215090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Set Fire To A Straw Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble reluctantly becomes involved with Stella Savano, the sister of George Savano, a mobster who runs the trucking company where Kimble works. Stella is an emotionally disturbed woman with a dangerous attraction to Johnny, the adopted eight-year-old son</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215090000 +0000" stop="20251215100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Eyewitness</sub-title>
    <desc>"A slaying in a black ghetto finds Harry Orwell relying on a blind "eyewitness" to zero in on the killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215100000 +0000" stop="20251215103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Police Commission - Dr-13</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives crack down on wildcatters—freelance tow-truck drivers who victimize motorists.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215103000 +0000" stop="20251215110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215110000 +0000" stop="20251215113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Team Work</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>As part of a trial program, Malloy and Reed team with Motor Officer Grant to better combat crime. Out on patrol, they make a safety check at a residence, investigate a suspicious witness at the scene of a traffic accident, deal with a young member of a neighborhood watch, respond to an annoying complaint about illegally parked cars and perform a daylight stakeout to catch a serial burglar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215113000 +0000" stop="20251215120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Roll Call</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>An anonymous call of shots fired over the radio leads to an 'Emergency!' roll call and frantic search for Motor Officer Grant. Meanwhile, Malloy and Reed respond to a citizen report of an armed robbery in progress at a bar, and Reed goes undercover as a pizza delivery driver to bust a dangerous scam.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215120000 +0000" stop="20251215130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Catch The Connection: Holiday Edition</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer is back again with a holiday edition of his new game show, "Catch The Connection." Bill, Toony and viewers will have to guess what all five of the cartoons have in common."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215130000 +0000" stop="20251215133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Library Book</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward allows Beaver to check out a book on his library card but when Beaver loses the book he becomes convinced that Ward will be put in jail, thanks to Eddie Haskell's wiseguy comments.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215133000 +0000" stop="20251215140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Election</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie nominates Wally for class president but Wally has no interest in the position; that is until Ward gives him some encouragement. Wally quickly gets wrapped up in the election and his friends see a change in him—a change that prompts them to vote against him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215140000 +0000" stop="20251215150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ill-fated Faker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Jim Ferris is having an affair with his uncle's bored young wife. They concoct a scheme to finagle $80,000 from the man by faking a kidnapping. It doesn't take long before things go horribly wrong.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215150000 +0000" stop="20251215160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Play  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When an actress is murdered, Matlock represents her director in a community theatre play—on the grounds that Matlock won't be cut from his role in the production!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215160000 +0000" stop="20251215170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>By Means Most Foul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A restaurateur and her mechanic boyfriend plot to eliminate her husband, but their scheme backfires. Gillespie takes heat over a string of mailbox bashings. And Virgil soon regrets ignoring Parker's theory regarding where the vandals would strike next.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215170000 +0000" stop="20251215180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Indiscretion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Corabeth finds a romantic letter in Ike's belongings and wants a divorce</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215180000 +0000" stop="20251215190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Violators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E04</episode-num>
    <desc>When someone is scalped in Dodge, the townsfolk are eager to blame the Indians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215190000 +0000" stop="20251215200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Showdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>After taking part in robbing the Virginia City bank, Sam Kirby gets hired at the Ponderosa, moonlighting as a farm hand while waiting to hear when the townsfolk have given up searching for the thieves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215200000 +0000" stop="20251215203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>I Take This Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lou looks for a way out when the man her dying father promised her to arrives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215203000 +0000" stop="20251215210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Assailants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An assassination plot unfolds as four gunmen disguised as cavalrymen enter North Fork. Their target: Sen. Jim Borden. Their weapon: a Gatling gun.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215210000 +0000" stop="20251215220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Mullins Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E32</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke and Charlie leave the train for supplies and to see Duke's old friends at a fort. One is a minister who was cashiered out of the Army who is trying to create peace with the Modocs despite a Major who only wants to kill all Indians."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215220000 +0000" stop="20251215230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Inheritance Tax</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A child is trapped in a car under downed power lines. A stockbroker with heart problems is reluctant to be treated. An elderly woman that Roy and John treated the previous year dies and remembers them in her will. Dr. Early administers first aid to two young boys. A teenager loses a hamburger eating contest. The Paramedics treat a burn victim at an explosive fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215230000 +0000" stop="20251215233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251215233000 +0000" stop="20251216000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Are You Now, Margaret?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A Congressional aide, Williamson, visits the 4077th on a supposedly routine fact-finding tour, but it's discovered that his motives are far deeper—too uncover Margaret as a communist sympathizer. His case is full of innuendo, so the gang set out to help Margaret.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216000000 +0000" stop="20251216003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216003000 +0000" stop="20251216010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216010000 +0000" stop="20251216013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Big House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>When the state police leave two captured bank robbers in the custody of the Mayberry police department overnight, Barney is determined to show the prisoners that the Mayberry jail is as good as any other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216013000 +0000" stop="20251216020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie The Birdman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie accidentally kills a mother bird with his new slingshot and takes it upon himself to raise the orphaned baby birds. After adopting them, Opie faces the difficult task of setting them free.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216020000 +0000" stop="20251216023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Sneeze, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray fears that he is going to come down with something dreadful.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216023000 +0000" stop="20251216030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>What Good Are You?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray questions his manliness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216030000 +0000" stop="20251216033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Masterpiece</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan convinces Klink that the kommandant is a great painter so the prisoners can meet an underground contact at an art gallery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216033000 +0000" stop="20251216040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gestapo Takeover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>The Gestapo takes over Stalag 13, planning to send Klink and Schultz to the Russian Front.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216040000 +0000" stop="20251216043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Paul Sand And Eydie Gorme</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Parolee, an just released parole tries to calm his girlfriend down before she makes a scene and gets him thrown back in jail. Then, in Salute to the Movie Series, the gang parodies classic entertainment, including "Young Dr. Kildaire", "The Cisco Kid", and "The Latin Bombshell". Finally, in The Wolfman, Carol and friends poke fun at horror movie cliches with a haunted castle, gypsy, and a wolfman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216043000 +0000" stop="20251216053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Drowning Duck</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Donald Briggs is an unscrupulous private investigator hired by Clyde Waters to uncover information about Marv Adams, his daughter's fiance. Briggs learns that Marv Adams' father was Ben Devereaux, who was convicted of murder 18 years ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216053500 +0000" stop="20251216060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare As A Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolteacher finds a strange and very serious little girl on the stairs outside her apartment. The girl seems to know her, and tries to jog her memory about a man she saw earlier that day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216060500 +0000" stop="20251216070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Run For Doom  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A doctor plans to marry a good-looking soloist despite warnings that her three ex-husbands all experienced brutal deaths.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216070500 +0000" stop="20251216080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Cost Of A Vacation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E02</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating the location of a missing person, Joe uncovers the death of a colleague who appears to have committed suicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216080500 +0000" stop="20251216090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Tomorrow Ends At Noon</sub-title>
    <desc>Cannon is hired by a Cuban exile to investigate the death of the man's brother at the hands of law enforcement officials.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216090500 +0000" stop="20251216100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Mystery Clycle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>An insurance settlement hangs on the result of an investigation of a motorcycle manufacturer's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216100000 +0000" stop="20251216103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216103000 +0000" stop="20251216110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216110000 +0000" stop="20251216113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspect Number One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy tries to find a way to help a 60-year-old career criminal he arrested 10 years ago, who was recently released and begs to be re-arrested so he can spend his retirement years in the federal penitentiary. Meanwhile, he and Reed become suspicious while investigating an apparent home burglary, and later respond to a bank robbery in progress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216113000 +0000" stop="20251216120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. MacDonald is suffering a marital crisis and turns to Malloy for advice. On today's patrol, a female cashier is taken hostage inside a grocery store by a couple of trigger-happy robbers who attempt to escape on the roof, and an elderly woman turns up missing from her retirement home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216120000 +0000" stop="20251216130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Rival Of The Ages: Holiday Edition</sub-title>
    <desc>"We're pitting Boomer versus Zoomer to see which generation reigns supreme with holiday challenges."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216130000 +0000" stop="20251216133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver And Andy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An old acquaintance of Ward's stops by and offers to paint the trim on the house. However, June and Ward are both apprehensive about the prospect of an alcoholic coming in contact with Wally and Beaver, despite the fact that he says he's cleaned himself up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216133000 +0000" stop="20251216140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Dance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Both Beaver and Larry are forced into attending dancing school by their parents and after one lesson, they find that they absolutely detest it, like they knew they would. This prompts them to skip class next time and they hide out behind a barn until it's time to go home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216140000 +0000" stop="20251216150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Singular Double</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason is accused of obstructing justice when he defends a woman who had faked her own suicide by running an empty car off a cliff. It seems as though the police found the body of another woman in the wreckage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216150000 +0000" stop="20251216160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Fisherman  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a Vietnamese fisherman and his son when they are accused of murdering a racist fisherman. And It isn't just the fishermen that Matlock ends up defending, as he, too, becomes a target of the racist townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216160000 +0000" stop="20251216170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Trundel's Will Be Done</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>V.J. Trundel's widow takes Harriet to court to gain custody of Eric. But Harriet is determined that her nephew will not be raised in the home of the man who ordered the murder of her sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216170000 +0000" stop="20251216180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heartache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rose and Stanley plan to get married.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216180000 +0000" stop="20251216190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Doctor's Wife</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E05</episode-num>
    <desc>When a new doctor arrives in Dodge, his wife starts a smear campaign against Doc Adams.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216190000 +0000" stop="20251216200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Mission</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss befriends an old drunk named Charlie Trent, who at one time had been the best scout the Army had. When the Army's current scout, Lewt Cutter, refuses to obey Captain Pender's orders, he is fired and replaced by Charlie, whom the captain knew from his earlier days.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216200000 +0000" stop="20251216203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Mark's Rifle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Sharpshooter Marty Blair tries to persuade Lucas to buy Mark a rifle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216203000 +0000" stop="20251216210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Most Amazing Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Fast-draw artist Wade Randall is less than anxious to display his prowess.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216210000 +0000" stop="20251216220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The David Garner Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E33</episode-num>
    <desc>"Hale is entrusted to deliver $8,000 to a bank. Young David Garner is determined to steal it and he stows along on the wagon train, along with a girl who's in love with him. Following them is a shady man who seems to have a hold over David."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216220000 +0000" stop="20251216230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Zero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman screams for therapeutic reasons. When the paramedics are interviewed on a TV program, Johnny freezes in front of the camera and Roy must bail him out. A young boy attempts suicide by leaping off an apartment ledge at the hospital; the doctors suspect he may be an abused child. The paramedics rescue a man trapped in a doughnut machine and a child from a fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216230000 +0000" stop="20251216233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251216233000 +0000" stop="20251217000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217000000 +0000" stop="20251217003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217003000 +0000" stop="20251217010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217010000 +0000" stop="20251217013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ernest T. Bass Joins The Army</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ernest T. wants to join the Army to impress a girl with the uniform. When he is refused induction, he goes on a window-breaking rampage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217013000 +0000" stop="20251217020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Sermon For Today</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A visiting preacher gives a sermon about taking time to relax. In trying to create an atmosphere of relaxation on a Sunday afternoon, the townsfolk all end up running themselves ragged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217020000 +0000" stop="20251217023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Super Bowl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray must choose who will accompany him to the Super Bowl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217023000 +0000" stop="20251217030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ray's Journal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is mortified when he realizes that Marie used to read his journal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217030000 +0000" stop="20251217033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Kommandant Schultz</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Schultz lets his new power as camp kommandant go to his head.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217033000 +0000" stop="20251217040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Eight O'clock And All Is Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan finds that a new prisoner is a German spy right after he tells the man all about their secret operations.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217040000 +0000" stop="20251217043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jack Weston</sub-title>
    <desc>In Computer Date, Carol meets a blind date who knows as many fun facts as she does. Then, in Tacky Song, Carol plays a dowdy librarian singing "The Lady Is a Tramp". Finally, in Dr. Jekyll and Ms. Hyde, a doctor's experiment goes horribly wrong when he continually turns into his female alter ego.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217043000 +0000" stop="20251217053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Sulky Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>An impetuous niece who demands her trust fund be released comes to Mason for help. But it's her boyfriend who needs defending when he is charged with murdering her controlling uncle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217053500 +0000" stop="20251217060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Stop At Willoughby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Riding home from work on a train, a stressed-out man falls asleep and dreams it is 1880 and he is entering a small town called Willoughby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217060500 +0000" stop="20251217070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Death Of A Cop  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A police officer concocts a grim preparation to punish the killer of his son, a recruit cop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217070500 +0000" stop="20251217080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Harvest Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E01</episode-num>
    <desc>When two crop-dusting pilots disappear, Mannix is hired to find them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217080500 +0000" stop="20251217090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Predators</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon believes that this time he has accepted a peaceful job. He must protect the bar of a friend, Millie Carroll, against robberies. However, suddenly he finds himself amid a complex love story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217090500 +0000" stop="20251217100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby must find out what happened to a woman who disappeared after dating a country singer's ex.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217100000 +0000" stop="20251217103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217103000 +0000" stop="20251217110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217110000 +0000" stop="20251217113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Lady Beware  (s7, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed join forces with Sgt. Gloria Tyler to search for a rapist who attacks teen girls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217113000 +0000" stop="20251217120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>X-force</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed lead a house-to-house search for a missing six-year-old girl, and what Malloy does after discovering the horrible things that have happened to her could short-circuit his career ambitions. Meanwhile, they come to the aid of a man who's gotten stuck in a storm sewer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217120000 +0000" stop="20251217130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Quizzer's Trivia Hour: Holiday Edition</sub-title>
    <desc>"Mr. Quizzer presents an hour of holiday trivia along with festive cartoons."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217130000 +0000" stop="20251217133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Larry's Club</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry is furious when Beaver leaves him out when he joins a club called the Bloody Five. To get revenge, Larry makes up a story that he is starting his own club and that people are waiting in line to join. This prompts Beaver to resign from the Bloody Five and he tries to join Larry's bogus club.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217133000 +0000" stop="20251217140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally lends his school sweater to Frances and quickly finds getting it back is going to be difficult because the girl keeps making up excuses. Things reach a boiling point when Ward and June overhear Frances bragging to her friends how Wally is chasing after her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217140000 +0000" stop="20251217150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lavender Lipstick</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A heiress to a cosmetics company is charged with the murder of the company's owner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217150000 +0000" stop="20251217160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Heiress  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a troubled young woman is accused of murder, her late father's former business partner hires Matlock to prove her innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217160000 +0000" stop="20251217170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Moseley's Lot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gillespie learns that the son of an old friend is a compulsive gambler. The young man wants his father to pay off his losses. But when two gangsters show up from New Orleans to collect, his jealous sibling sees the perfect opportunity to get rid of his troubled brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217170000 +0000" stop="20251217180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Lumberjack</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A new company starts in the area and wants to sell wood to the Waltons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217180000 +0000" stop="20251217190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Take Her, She's Cheap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A grateful family wants Matt to marry their daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217190000 +0000" stop="20251217200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Badge Without Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Adam is rescued from an ambush by Gerald Eskith, a lawman who is on a mission to Virginia City. Eskith is looking for a man who happens to be married to a close friend of the Cartwrights. By the time Adam realizes Eskith's real agenda, it may be too late to save someone's life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217200000 +0000" stop="20251217203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Squeeze Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A speculator will stop at nothing to grab Lucas's land.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217203000 +0000" stop="20251217210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Gun Shy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark blames himself for a friend's accidental death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217210000 +0000" stop="20251217220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>Alias Bill Hawks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Hawks travels to a desert town to visit an old friend, an indian who has a ranch there. However, upon arriving on his friend's property, he discovers that it is under the control of the local townspeople, who are drilling for water, and that his friend is nowhere to be seen. The townspeople are unwilling to give him any information, and in fact display outright hostility towards him, leading Hawks to suspect that his friend may be in danger or even dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217220000 +0000" stop="20251217230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Promise</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Responding to a vehicle fire, the firemen discover a catatonic mechanic; at Rampart the doctors are mystified by his condition. Roy lectures a woman who keeps calling the paramedics because she is lonely. A woman mixes ammonia with bleach and inhales poisonous gas. An elderly couple is trapped in their house by a bunch of tumbleweeds.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217230000 +0000" stop="20251217233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. And Mrs. Who?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles returns to the 4077th after a trip to Tokyo with an uncharacteristic hangover and the uneasy feeling of a romantic entanglement. Meanwhile, the hospital struggles to find a cure for an outbreak of deadly hemorrhagic fever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251217233000 +0000" stop="20251218000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Life Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. race against the clock to save a soldier from paralysis. B.J.'s harvesting an aorta from a dead soldier doesn't sit well with the soldier's friend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218000000 +0000" stop="20251218003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Uncle Abdul</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger discovers that his duties as company clerk include catering to the eccentric whims of the 4077th officers. Consequently, the unusual demands by Klinger's superiors leave little time to write a letter home to Toledo.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218003000 +0000" stop="20251218010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Captain's Outrageous</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A brawl at Rosie's Bar puts Rosie in the hospital, and the 4077th doctors are pressed into service as temporary saloon-keepers. Meanwhile, Father Mulcahy is apprehensive that his long-pending promotion to captain will again be denied.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218010000 +0000" stop="20251218013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Briscoe Declares For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Briscoe Darling becomes obsessed with Aunt Bee after hearing her recite a poem, going as far as to kidnap her and bring her back to his shack in the hills.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218013000 +0000" stop="20251218020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gomer The House Guest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy takes Gomer in after Wally fires him for not doing his job right. Gomer proceeds to drive Andy, Aunt Bee and Opie crazy with all of the noise he makes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218020000 +0000" stop="20251218023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Silent Partners</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra realizes that her and Ray, no longer have anything to say to one another.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218023000 +0000" stop="20251218030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Fairies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is upset when he discovers that his twins, are playing fairies in the school play.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218030000 +0000" stop="20251218033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Tanks For The Memory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered to photograph and destroy a model for a radio-controlled tank that is being tested at camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218033000 +0000" stop="20251218040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>It's Dynamite</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A dynamite truck, which Hogan plans on hi-jacking, deviates from its planned route.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218040000 +0000" stop="20251218043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest John Byner</sub-title>
    <desc>In Carol and Sis, Carol and Harvey fight in front of an encounter group. Then, in Fun in a Saloon, a western bad guy starts a dancing brawl. Finally, in Court Stenographer, Carol plays a recorder who can't help but interfere with the court case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218043000 +0000" stop="20251218053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Partner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Harry Bright and Chuck Clark were once best friends and business partners, until Margaret entered the picture. Margaret, a young woman on the make, entranced Chuck into marrying her. When Margaret is found shot to death, Harry is arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218053500 +0000" stop="20251218060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Chaser</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A man, desperate to win the affection of a beautiful woman, slips her a love potion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218060500 +0000" stop="20251218070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>A Home Away From Home  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a mental institution patient imprisons the staff, he reverses the roles of doctors and patients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218070500 +0000" stop="20251218080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Beyond The Shadow Of A Dream</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A mentally unstable woman is having trouble grasping the difference between nightmare and reality. Mannix is hired to figure which of her companions is creating her confusion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218080500 +0000" stop="20251218090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Long Way Down</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An illegal immigrant from Mexico has died in a coyote's case. Sheep grower Rita McBain is accused of the deed. Cannon must prove Rita's innocence and deal with a human smuggler ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218090500 +0000" stop="20251218100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Time To Kill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When a dinner guest falls asleep, his host steals his diamond.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218100000 +0000" stop="20251218103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218103000 +0000" stop="20251218110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218110000 +0000" stop="20251218113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol</sub-title>
    <desc>"A drunk's antics appear harmless at first; a stakeout uncovers a cash stash."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218113000 +0000" stop="20251218120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Credit Risk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After his wife's credit card is turned down attempting to buy a washing machine, an irate Reed begins a long and painful process with his bank to get his credit rating corrected. Out on patrol, he and Malloy investigate a parking lot hit-and-run accident based on the victim's recollection of the perpetrator's license plate number, search for two runaways who steal camping gear from a store's basement and make a rare mistake after responding to a liquor store robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218120000 +0000" stop="20251218130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: Holiday Edition</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony enjoy the holiday splendor of the 1960s with nostalgic party food, vintage crafting and more!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218130000 +0000" stop="20251218133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Hypnotist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>After seeing someone being hypnotized in a movie, Beaver sets out to do the same. He tries hypnotism on Eddie—who pretends Beaver has hypnotized him—and Beaver gets scared when Eddie won't snap out of the trance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218133000 +0000" stop="20251218140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally And Alma</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>After drawing Alma's name for a school picnic, Wally finds himself meeting her parents and her mother takes an immediate liking to Wally, setting him and Alma up on numerous dates, but then turns around and accuses Wally of monopolizing Alma's time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218140000 +0000" stop="20251218150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wandering Widow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man accused of a murder is freed from prison upon newly discovered eyewitness testimony, it starts a chain reaction of blackmail and murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218150000 +0000" stop="20251218160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lemon  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's new neighbor, Les "Ace" Calhoun (Don Knotts), is charged with murdering the used car salesman who sold him a lemon, Matlock takes the case to prove that more than one person had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218160000 +0000" stop="20251218170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Family Reunion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-convict attempts to retrieve his loot from his wife and her new husband in this tongue-in-cheek episode.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218170000 +0000" stop="20251218180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E21</episode-num>
    <desc>One of Mary Ellen's mountain patient dies, leaving his young teen to the helping hand</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218180000 +0000" stop="20251218190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Help Me Kitty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Kitty and an unmarried expectant mother end up stranded in the desert when bandits attack their stagecoach.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218190000 +0000" stop="20251218200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Mill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben's neighbor, Joyce, comes to the Ponderosa asking Ben to help her disabled husband build a mill. She thinks the project will help her husband break free from his depression and the grip of a man named Ezekiel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218200000 +0000" stop="20251218203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Anvil Chorus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Nils Swenson, North Fork's blacksmith, volunteers to take the marshal's place for a few days while Micah attends a wedding in another town. To help maintain peace, Nils institutes a policy that anyone coming into town must turn in their weapons, getting them back when they leave. This plan backfires on Nils when some dishonest men come to town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218203000 +0000" stop="20251218210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Conflict</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas's self-confidence begins to slip away when he misses an easy shot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218210000 +0000" stop="20251218220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Antone Rose Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E35</episode-num>
    <desc>"Invalid rancher Henry Ludlow is so determined that daughter Judy not marry Basque sheepherder Antone Rose that he sells his land and joins the wagon train to head west. When Antone learns of this, he joins the train as well to marry her."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218220000 +0000" stop="20251218230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Body Language</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A crop-duster makes a rough landing in a field; the pilot suffers a punctured lung, and a bystander is poisoned with pesticide. A patient reports to Rampart with an ear infection caused by mothballs. A couple overdoses on daffodil bulbs. A weekend cowboy refuses treatment after falling from his horse. Two victims of a traffic accident get friendly. The lead singer of a rock band goes into cardiac arrest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218230000 +0000" stop="20251218233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Stars And Stripes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friction arises between B.J. and Winchester when they are asked to write an article for a prestigious medical journal on how they saved a soldier's life with a daring operation. Meanwhile, Hot Lips receives an eventful visit from Scully.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251218233000 +0000" stop="20251219000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Yessir, That's Our Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby born to a Korean woman and an American GI is abandoned at the 4077th. Knowing that Amer-Asian children are often mistreated in Korean society, the troop sets about the frustrating task of finding a new home for the infant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219000000 +0000" stop="20251219003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bottle Fatigue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Horrified by the gigantic size of his monthly bar tab at the officer's club, Hawkeye vows to give up booze for a week. Meanwhile, Winchester desperately tries to halt his sister's impending marriage to a man he considers unworthy of the Winchester heritage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219003000 +0000" stop="20251219010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heal Thyself</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter turns crotchety when he catches the mumps, and his condition is worsened when Winchester gets the same disease and has to be quarantined with him. A temporary replacement surgeon, Newsome, is quickly brought into the 4077th and seems to be a gem in terms of both personality and ability.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219010000 +0000" stop="20251219013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Black Day For Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney are to protect a shipment of gold passing through Mayberry. It's critical that they keep it a secret, but Barney spills the beans immediately and soon all the town knows.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219013000 +0000" stop="20251219020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Ill-gotten Gain</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie is given a bike after bringing home a report card filled with straight As. He soon discovers that the high marks were a mistake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219020000 +0000" stop="20251219023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Stefania Arrives</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Robert gets a surprise visit from Stefania.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219023000 +0000" stop="20251219030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Humm Vac</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray purchases a new state-of-the-art vacuum cleaner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219030000 +0000" stop="20251219033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Tiger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and his men try to rescue an underground leader on route to Berlin to be executed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219033000 +0000" stop="20251219040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Broadcast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses Klink's car radio to sneak a message to London when a pair of radio detection trucks enters the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219040000 +0000" stop="20251219043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Steve Lawrence</sub-title>
    <desc>In Double Calamity, the gang parodies the film-noir classic "Double Indemnity", with Carol as Barbara Stanwyck and Steve as Fred McMurray.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219043000 +0000" stop="20251219053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Mourner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Carla Adrian is having trouble fending off amorous neighbor Mark Cushing. When another neighbor hears a shot and a woman's scream in Mark Cushing's cabin, it's not long before the police discover Cushing's dead body and arrest Mrs. Belle Adrian.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219053500 +0000" stop="20251219060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Passage For Trumpet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Convinced he'll never amount to anything, a trumpet player attempts suicide and then finds himself in a world where no one can hear or see him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219060500 +0000" stop="20251219070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>A Nice Touch  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An adulterous partner is caught between a drunken husband and a determined lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219070500 +0000" stop="20251219080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Huntdown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is stuck in a farm town with an injured foot, and a group of citizens who seem to be keeping a deadly secret from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219080500 +0000" stop="20251219090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Rip-off</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Simeon is accused by orderly Duran of stealing drugs in the Metropolitan Hospital . Cannon has to find out whether this is right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219090500 +0000" stop="20251219100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Death On Deposit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A cattleman is murdered in his own corral on the day he was to withdraw his money from the bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219100000 +0000" stop="20251219103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219103000 +0000" stop="20251219110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219110000 +0000" stop="20251219113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pot Shot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>While paying a visit to the laundromat before going into work, Malloy encounters a man using the facilities to dry something much different from clothing. On patrol, he and Reed deal with a minister-in-training who uses a very unorthodox method to get his message across, try to reunite a Finnish-speaking child with her family, mediate a strange dispute between feuding neighbors and engage in a high-speed chase with a well known drug dealer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219113000 +0000" stop="20251219120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>G.t.a.</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed investigate a large car theft operation that targets older cars, then stages them around the city as abandoned vehicles so they can be towed and scrapped. Meanwhile, they try to figure out why the son of Malloy's girlfriend is getting bad grades, search for a suspect who robbed an elderly woman and attempt to rescue two foolish teenagers who enter a house that is being fumigated.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219120000 +0000" stop="20251219130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' All 50: Holiday Edition</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony explore regional holiday eats, treats, and traditions around America!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219130000 +0000" stop="20251219133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Bike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver asks his parents if he could ride his new bike to school instead of the bus, and after some hesitating they finally agree to it. However, on the first day, a naive Beaver gets his bike stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219133000 +0000" stop="20251219140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Orchid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally asks out a rich girl who drops hints that she would like an orchid for her corsage. Wally quickly discovers that getting one is going to be more difficult then he originally thought.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219140000 +0000" stop="20251219150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Clumsy Clown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Two owners of a circus are trying to buy out each other. Both also are after a clown in the circus for the funds. The second owner is blackmailing him regarding his wife's second marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219150000 +0000" stop="20251219160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Mistress  (s8, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Laura McCord after she's charged with murdering her husband, David, in a jealous rage. Matlock and Julie soon realize that David's lover is the key to the case, but she seems to have disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219160000 +0000" stop="20251219170000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Sanctuary: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A political prisoner who entered the country illegally, seeks sanctuary in a monastery. Gillespie and Tibbs find themselves at odds with Sheriff McComb when they try to help the man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219170000 +0000" stop="20251219180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Revel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E22</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy returns to New York with a new book - that is not good</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219180000 +0000" stop="20251219190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Hung High</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A lawman-hater causes trouble for Matt and a retired marshal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219190000 +0000" stop="20251219200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Hopefuls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While in Virginia City on ranch business, Adam meets up with Sam Board. As they are leaving town, they come across a wagon train and decide to help the settlers out. Adam finds himself falling for the daughter of the group's leader, but soon finds that love doesn't always overcome morals and beliefs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219200000 +0000" stop="20251219203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Line Shack Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad gang boss John Gangling kills one of his crew to rob him of his savings. To cover his tracks, Gangling puts the blame on Johnny Wing, an Apache worker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219203000 +0000" stop="20251219210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>On the road Lucas and Mark come upon Winslow Quince, a peddler whose wagon has broken down, and help him get his wagon into North Fork for repair. While in North Fork Quince barters several items that implicate him in a series of murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219210000 +0000" stop="20251219220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Jim Whitlow Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E36</episode-num>
    <desc>"Duke Shannon returns to check on his small ranch he split evenly with a childhood friend. When he arrives he finds tenant farmers being bull-whipped and a ruthless foreman his partner does not want to fire claiming he is needed."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219220000 +0000" stop="20251219230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Understanding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>At an explosive fire, a girl's horse is trapped in a burning barn. Dr. Brackett and Nurse McCall lecture a man who keeps forgetting his insulin shots. A girl calls the hospital, threatening suicide; firemen stand by while hospital workers attempt to trace the call. A hostage in a bank robbery has heart problems; the paramedics must treat him at gunpoint.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219230000 +0000" stop="20251219233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Old Soldiers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is appointed temporary commander of the 4077th when Colonel Potter rushes off to Tokyo on a mysterious mission. While in command, Hawkeye's main problem is housing a large group of Korean refugees comprised mainly of rambunctious children who need medical care.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251219233000 +0000" stop="20251220000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Morale Victory</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of their constant complaints about the quality of recreational activities at the 4077th, Colonel Potter appoints Hawkeye and B.J. as the new morale officers. Winchester's morale has already reached a new peak: He's ecstatic about his operation on a wounded soldier, Sheridan, which saved the boy's leg, leaving only "negligible" side effects—less use of his right hand. However, the soldier was a concert pianist before the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220000000 +0000" stop="20251220003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lend A Hand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Irritated that the 4077th is planning a "surprise" party for him, Hawkeye volunteers to go to the aid of a wounded surgeon at the front. An additional irritant to Hawkeye is the arrival of Dr. Borelli, a wisecracking medical advisor with whom he habitually disagrees.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220003000 +0000" stop="20251220010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Cruel World</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger redecorates his quarters, but the resultant ridicule he receives drives him to new heights in his efforts to get out of the Army. Meanwhile, the doctors are perplexed by the reaction of an Asian-American war hero who tries to kill himself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220010000 +0000" stop="20251220013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Date For Gomer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Gomer is asked by Andy and Barney to take Thelma Lou's cousin, Mary Grace Gossage, to the Chamber of Commerce dance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220013000 +0000" stop="20251220020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Barney's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>After being kicked out of Mrs. Mendlebright's boardinghouse, Barney becomes suspicious of the man who takes his room.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220020000 +0000" stop="20251220023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Canister, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Tempers flare when Marie accuses Debra of not returning a canister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220023000 +0000" stop="20251220030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Net Worth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra becomes angry when Ray contributes $1,000 to his friends' scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220030000 +0000" stop="20251220033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Gypsy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>In an effort to transport a German anti-radar to London, Hogan passes LeBeau off as a fortune teller after convincing Klink he was struck by lightning.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220033000 +0000" stop="20251220040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Dropouts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan helps three German scientists escape to England.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220040000 +0000" stop="20251220043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Tim Conway</sub-title>
    <desc>In Opening Talk on Plane, passengers discuss their plans in Australia. Then, Carol and friends perform "Waltzing Matilda" and "It's Today". Next, in The Oldest Man, the Sydney orchestra is led by the Oldest Man. Finally, in The Ham Actor, an ailing Carol tries to perform, despite already being replaced by Vicki.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220043000 +0000" stop="20251220053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Crimson Kiss</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fay Allison is getting married in a few days to Dane Grover. Her roommate, Anita Bonsal, is having a clandestine affair with a married man, Carver Clement. When Aunt Louise arrives early one morning to see Fay, she finds Fay and Anita both unconscious.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220053500 +0000" stop="20251220060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Bevis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>An eccentric loser gets a new life from his guardian angel, but there is a price to keeping it.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220060500 +0000" stop="20251220070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Terror At Northfield  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A pious extremist embarks on a killing spree to retaliate for the death of his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220070500 +0000" stop="20251220080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Coffin For A Clown</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is on the middle of a fence when it comes to an intense child custody case, in which he is working for the mother while seeing the father dash attempts on his life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220080500 +0000" stop="20251220090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Paul Stubber taps the computer of the railroad company to be able to rob cars with valuable goods. However, nothing can be proved against him. Cannon finds Stubber's weak spot: The crook fights for the right to keep his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220090500 +0000" stop="20251220100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Web Of Deceit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A newsman takes pictures of evidence showing that an industrialist is involved with the mob.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20251220100000 +0000" stop="20251220103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Steve's Uncle George</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Steve's Uncle George visits the Shady Rest hotel and lives up to his reputation as a troublemaker.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
