<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221203000 +0000" stop="20260221210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Treasure Of Canyon Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>In a ghost town, Lucas, Mark and Micah tangle with the Newman family and learn the secret of the town's 20-year-old mystery of a lost gold mine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221210000 +0000" stop="20260221220000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident Of Judgement Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Rowdy's ex-commanding officer, Captain Cabot, convenes a makeshift court-martial for him in a ghost town. He and some of Rowdy's old Army buddies believe that Rowdy betrayed their attempted escape from a Union prison camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221220000 +0000" stop="20260221223000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>A Sense Of Justice</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The sheriff of a small town needs help to prevent the lynching of simple-minded Andy Dawes. The townspeople are sure he is a murderer. Paladin offers to help</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221223000 +0000" stop="20260221230000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Journey For Josh</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh and the beautiful female prisoner he is transporting to trial fall in love, but tragedy awaits when the woman's partner follows.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260221230000 +0000" stop="20260222010000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Dumb Clucks, In The Sweet Pie And Pie, G.i. Wanna Go Home, Scrambled Brains, Muscle Up A Little Closer, Stone Age Romeos</sub-title>
    <desc>"Their father's plan to marry prompts the Stooges to break out of jail to save him from himself and, it turns out, from this intended dangerous posse. , The Stooges are convicts about to be executed for some murders they didn't commit.  The day before the execution they are tricked into marrying three rich girls who need husbands to collect a legacy.  At the last minute the real murderers confess and the Stooges are pardoned.  The girls are now stuck with the Stooges so they plot to get rid of them by making them become gentlemen.  The girl's lawyer convinces them to throw a big party in the hope that the Stooges will humiliate them and they can get a divorce.  The boys do just that as the party degenerates into a wild pie fight.  But the girls decide to keep the Stooges and give their lawyer the boot. [Dance teacher footage from "Hoi Polloi"] , The Stooges hope to collect a reward by proving to a museum that cavemen still exist.  They return from their expedition with a film purporting to show some stone age Stooges defending their women from other cavemen.  The museum curators are about to pay they reward, until they overhear the Stooges talking about how they faked the film, with themselves playing the cavemen. , The Stooges are discharged from the army and go to see their fiancées, but find they have been dispossessed and the wedding is off until they find a home.  The boys have trouble finding a vacant apartment so they set up housekeeping in a vacant lot.  Their housing problems seem to be solved until a farmer destroys their new home with a tractor.  The Stooges then build a house of their own, but the girls aren't impressed with the one room mansion and walk out on them. , Shemp is a sick man, suffering from hallucinations.  His worst vision is that his ugly nurse Nora is actually beautiful.  When Moe and Larry come to take him home from the sanitarium, they discover he's become engaged to Nora.  On the way to Nora's apartment for the wedding, the boys get in a fight with a stranger who promises to get even with them if he ever sees them again.  They arrive to finding Nora waiting for her father, who, when he arrives, turns out to be the man they just fought with. , Joe is engaged but can't get married until he recovers the engagement ring which has disappeared.  The Stooges suspect the ring was stolen by Elmo, a beefy bully, who works at the same factory they do.  They confront Elmo in the company gym, but he's too tough for them.  Fortunately Joe's girl is even tougher, and she gets Elmo to confess and return the ring. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222010000 +0000" stop="20260222033000 +0000">
    <title>House of Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Mist</sub-title>
    <desc>"After a strange storm, a small town community is terrorized by dangers emerging from the mist."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222033000 +0000" stop="20260222040000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Penguin's Nest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>The Penguin opens an exclusive restaurant, the Penguin's Nest, and creates a catalog of Gotham's richest signatures to use in a forging scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222040000 +0000" stop="20260222050000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Alternative Factor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Kirk and Spock encounter an alien named Lazarus who claims to be from an anti-matter universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222050000 +0000" stop="20260222053000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Brainy Burro</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Lois and Jimmy investigate a Mexican story of a burro who can read minds. Crooks use the burro to rob a bank.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222053000 +0000" stop="20260222060000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Perils Of Superman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A master criminal plans terrible traps for each of Superman's friends: Lois, Jimmy, Perry White and Clark Kent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222060000 +0000" stop="20260222070000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>The Deadly Games Of Gamma 6</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The future of Earth hangs in the balance when Dr. Smith agrees to do battle with a group of galactic gladiators.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222070000 +0000" stop="20260222080000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Wax Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hostile wax figures of the crew take over the Seaview.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222080000 +0000" stop="20260222090000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Underground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings help out giants who are resisting the tyrannical Giant government.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222090000 +0000" stop="20260222100000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Revenge Of The Gods</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Tony and Doug materialize near ancient Troy just before the last battle between the Trojans and Greeks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222100000 +0000" stop="20260222110000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Innocent</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Aliens abduct David but with the intention of proving they mean no harm to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222110000 +0000" stop="20260222120000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Skyrider</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams and Mad Jack find an unusual man. Mr. Milton Wright's trying to achieve human flight in his bird-like "glider" invention. S close watch is kept on him. He keeps crashing but also needs to find the answer to realizing his dream."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222120000 +0000" stop="20260222123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bayou Backwaters</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim journey by flat-bottomed boat into the uncharted, moss-covered silence of the Louisiana bayou country on an animal collecting trip."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222123000 +0000" stop="20260222130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Tale Of The Fox</sub-title>
    <desc>"This is the tale of the fox cub as it explores the wild kingdom for the first time in the North Woods of Wisconsin."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222130000 +0000" stop="20260222133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Bobcat Kingdom</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim observe a family of bobcats in the Zion Canyon area in the Utah wilderness."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222133000 +0000" stop="20260222140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Mysteries Of The Wild</sub-title>
    <desc>"Many mysteries of the wild present a challenge to seek the answer. In this episode Jim Fowler brings to the viewer some of the most memorable scenes ever captured on film."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222140000 +0000" stop="20260222143000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part I</sub-title>
    <desc>"Marlin and Jim visit South Africa to study and photograph the chacma baboons in their natural environment and to conduct some fascinating experiments."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222143000 +0000" stop="20260222150000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Chacma Country Part Ii</sub-title>
    <desc>"The chacma baboon has many homes.  Marlin and Jim explore all of ‘chacma country’ from the lush coastal areas to the semi-desert interiors of South Africa."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222150000 +0000" stop="20260222153000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Click</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Greg wants to be on the football team, but Carol is against it, fearing that he's going to get hurt - which of course he does. Can he and his camera still find a way to help out the team?</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222153000 +0000" stop="20260222160000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Father Of The Year</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Marcia enters Mike in a "Father of the Year" contest through the newspaper, but in order to mail her entry before the deadline she breaks curfew. Mike catches her but she's unable to explain, and he grounds her from the family ski trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222160000 +0000" stop="20260222163000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Because Mammoth Pictures is losing money, Drysdale decides to tear down the studio and turn it into Clampett City. The Clampetts are excited about getting a town and streets named after them, and when they go to explore their town, they come to a Western set, which they fall in love with.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222163000 +0000" stop="20260222170000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Clampett City General Store</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts move into the Western street on their movie studio, but Drysdale tries to stop them. He gets the Clampetts a role in a new picture about Cleopatra and Nero, with Jethro as Caesar, Elly as a martyr who gets thrown to the lions and Granny as Cleopatra. However, Elly makes friends with the lion and Granny gets Nero drunk on elderberry wine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222170000 +0000" stop="20260222173000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Merchant Of Mayberry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Traveling salesman Bert Miller is getting tired of traveling, so Andy and Barney plan to help him set up a small general goods shop on a vacant lot.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222173000 +0000" stop="20260222180000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Ethel's Home Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The Ricardos and the Mertzes stop at Ethel's hometown: Albuquerque, NM. Under the impression that Ethel has been called to Hollywood and not Ricky, the townsfolk accord her a monumental ovation. When Ethel refuses to disillusion them—and even goes so far as to put on a "celebrity act"—Lucy takes matters into her own hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222180000 +0000" stop="20260222183000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Mustache</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally's on-again off-again girlfriend, Julie Foster, seems to have thrown him over for a new guy in school who just happens to have a mustache. Wally's ego is bruised when Eddie tells him that Julie thinks he's naive and immature. This is the last straw and Wally decides to grow a mustache, much to the dismay of his family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222183000 +0000" stop="20260222190000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Parking Attendants</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The social event of the season, according to Fred Rutherford, is a big party that a wealthy family is throwing and he rubs it in due to the fact that June and Ward didn't get an invitation. However, Wally and Eddie will be there after they get jobs parking the guest's cars. However, trouble ensues when Eddie parks Fred's car in a no parking spot and the car gets towed away by the city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222190000 +0000" stop="20260222200000 +0000">
    <title>Charlie's Angels</title>
    <sub-title>To Kill An Angel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Angel Kelly takes Skip, a little boy in the children's ward at a local sanitarium, on an outing to an amusement park. There, in a moment of confusion, she loses sight of the child.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222200000 +0000" stop="20260222210000 +0000">
    <title>Hart to Hart</title>
    <sub-title>Cop Out</sub-title>
    <desc>"The Harts pursue a serial killer that preys on prostitutes, unaware that it's really a vice squad detective."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222210000 +0000" stop="20260222220000 +0000">
    <title>Fantasy Island</title>
    <sub-title>Salem / Superstar</sub-title>
    <desc>"Richard Delaney's fantasy to become a "Superstar" is experienced on Fantasy Island just in time to give him the courage he needed to gain respect from his boss. Martha and Walter Tate's fantasy is fulfilled. when they arrive in "Salem" to experience morality only to find it begins at home."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222220000 +0000" stop="20260222230000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>Pal-i-mony-o-mine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A companion befriends a doctor's ex-girlfriend; Gopher falls for a former teacher; a father learns a lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222230000 +0000" stop="20260222233000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Aunt Bee The Warden</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Mayberry jail is filled to capacity with a group of moonshiners who blame Otis for their capture, Andy takes Otis home to serve his term.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260222233000 +0000" stop="20260223000000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Meet Fred</sub-title>
    <desc>"Fred likes toys, cars and other TV and pop culture memorabilia; but what he really likes is having those items signed and authenticated by the celebrity they “belong to.” His sizable collection ranges from a signed broken fender from racing legend Dale Earnhardt Jr. to a ping-pong ball from TV’s Captain Kangaroo. Fred Jr. who often goes on these signing missions with his Dad, joins him, while our expert appraiser Michael Osacky will put a value amount on the collection –and also bring a surprise trade offer that Fred will have a hard time refusing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223000000 +0000" stop="20260223003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Your Hit Parade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>With the arrival of a shipment of records, Radar plays the part of a disc jockey and helps to get everyone through the incredibly long deluge of wounded.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223003000 +0000" stop="20260223010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>What's Up, Doc?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hot Lips, believing herself to be pregnant, asks Hawkeye to test her. The only rabbit available to use for the test is Radar's pet, Fluffy. Meanwhile, Martinson, a patient, holds Charles at gunpoint, demanding he be sent back to Ohio.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223010000 +0000" stop="20260223013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>The Bunker's Go West</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mike and Gloria cancel their trip home for Christmas, the Bunkers decide to travel west for the holidays.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223013000 +0000" stop="20260223020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 1)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Bunkers head out to California for Christmas to find out that Mike and Gloria are having marital problems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223020000 +0000" stop="20260223023000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>California, Here We Come (part 2)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Separation is Archie's reaction when he discovers that Gloria has been unfaithful to her husband. For the first time in nine years, he turns his back on his daughter and sides with Michael.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223023000 +0000" stop="20260223030000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At The Pta</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When Edith develops laryngitis on the eve of her singing debut at Stephanie's PTA recital, Archie steps in to understudy the duet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223030000 +0000" stop="20260223033000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Car, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gets upset when she discovers that she's driving Ray's old "make out mobile."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223033000 +0000" stop="20260223040000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Diamonds</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray discovers the diamond in Debra's wedding ring is fake.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223040000 +0000" stop="20260223043000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Gesundheit, Darling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob worries that he's allergic to his own wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223043000 +0000" stop="20260223050000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Man's Teeth Are Not His Own</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob worries that Jerry will find out he went to a different dentist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223050000 +0000" stop="20260223053000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223053000 +0000" stop="20260223060000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Little People</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>An astronaut declares himself a god when his ship lands on a planet populated by people smaller than ants.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223060000 +0000" stop="20260223070000 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Power Of Attorney  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>A smooth con man uses his appeal to rip off rich women.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223070000 +0000" stop="20260223080000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>Double Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Shanks and Blake are Syndicate men who run the loan shark racket in Hawaii and are preparing to transfer $10 million to the mainland, leading to the Syndicate expanding their operations there. The IMF must stop the Syndicate's expansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223080000 +0000" stop="20260223090000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of The Swan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>At a carnival, Kimble meets Tina Anderson, an attractive young woman whom helps him get a job and introduces him to her uncle Harry, whom is a retired police detective. But Harry soon recognizes Kimble and tries to arrest him. Tina helps Kimble get away a</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223090000 +0000" stop="20260223100000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>The Confetti People</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell is hard pressed to protect a former jazz great from a knife-wielding killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223100000 +0000" stop="20260223103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-06</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday's apartment party provides insight into the nature of an officer's private life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223103000 +0000" stop="20260223110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Robbery - Dr-15</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives tackle cases for the department's robbery division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223110000 +0000" stop="20260223113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Log 125 -- Safe Job</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>There's been a rash of cracked safes in the area, and Malloy thinks the suspect is someone who lives in the neighborhood who now claims to be a reformed family man. In the meantime, he and Reed track down a female robbery suspect, who turns out to be a victim herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223113000 +0000" stop="20260223120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Extortion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy stares down the barrel of a rifle during the search for gloved robbers who are able to make off with $500 from a tavern in a stolen car. He and Reed also try to apprehend a group of anti-semites before their repeated shakedown attempts cause further damage to a defiant Holocaust survivor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223120000 +0000" stop="20260223130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Digital Detox</sub-title>
    <desc>"Toony's forced to unplug on a digital detox retreat."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223130000 +0000" stop="20260223133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>More Blessed To Give</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Gilbert go to a carnival and Beaver surprisingly wins a fourteen caret gold locket in one of the carnival games. Beaver thinks about giving it to June but, thanks to Gilbert, decides to give it to a girl whom he has a crush on. However, soon it becomes apparent that this was a mistake when the girl's parents discover Beaver's gift.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223133000 +0000" stop="20260223140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Good Deed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver seems to be on a selfish streak after backing out of a babysitting and later not wanting to do a simple favor for Wally. Ward gives Beaver a stern lecture and he soon takes Ward's advice when a tramp comes to the door wanting some kindness. However, the tramp quickly takes advantage and helps himself to more than a glass of water.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223140000 +0000" stop="20260223150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Angry Astronaut</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Astronaut Matthew Heller is suspected of killing his old service rival, General Addison Brand, after Brand is put in charge of the astronaut program.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223150000 +0000" stop="20260223160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Sisters  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When he is accused of murdering his wealthy wife, an old acquaintance hires Matlock to defend him. The more digging Matlock does, the more he begins to suspect other family members.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223160000 +0000" stop="20260223170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Killer Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A psychiatric worker is trying to drive a fellow Vietnam veteran crazy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223170000 +0000" stop="20260223180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Honeymoon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Olvia and John finally get a chance to take their postponed honeymoon to Virginia Beach</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223180000 +0000" stop="20260223190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>By Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Despite his illiteracy, Festus becomes a reporter for Dodge's new paper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223190000 +0000" stop="20260223200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Crucible</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After being robbed in the desert, Adam stumbles onto a seemingly chivalrous prospector named Peter Kane, who offers him a mule and supplies for three days work. However, Kane is a demented madman who is interested in psychological torture, hoping to drive a seemingly rational man like Adam to murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223200000 +0000" stop="20260223203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Dark Day At North Fork</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Blinded in an explosion, Lucas fights despair as he prepares for a meeting with a gun-toting enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223203000 +0000" stop="20260223210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Two ex-Confederate officers seek revenge on Lucas. McCain was a lieutenant in the 8th Indiana, which defeated the 12th Cavalry 15 years earlier at the Battle of Fort Donaldson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223210000 +0000" stop="20260223220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Daniel Barrister Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Faith is tested when a man's wife is injured and he refuses to let her receive medical aid. When Flint rides to the nearest town to get a doctor, he finds they have their own problems: a smallpox epidemic.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223220000 +0000" stop="20260223230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Right At Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Dr. Brackett rides along with a fire department helicopter crew. A boy causes trouble for the paramedics when he and his father are rescued after their camper has overturned in a canyon. Dr. Early treats a boy with spinal meningitis. The firemen rescue a man from a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223230000 +0000" stop="20260223233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Mail Call Three</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After a delay of three weeks, five sacks of mail arrive, and everyone in camp reacts to good and bad news from home. Hawkeye receives love letters addressed to another Benjamin Pierce, another man has approached B.J.'s wife, and Radar's mom has found a boyfriend.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260223233000 +0000" stop="20260224000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Temporary Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>With a temporary transfer of personnel between the 4077th and the 8063rd, Captain Roy Dupree replaces Hawkeye, while Lorraine Anderson makes eyes at Charles. Fearing this to be permanent, Charles and B.J. successfully conspire to have Dupree permanently removed from the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224000000 +0000" stop="20260224003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Potter's Retirement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter is upset when General Waldo Kent informs him that people in the 4077th are complaining about his leadership. Potter returns to camp and discovers that the complaints are coming from a Corporal (actually Lieutenant) Benson, who had been sent by a disturbed Colonel Frank Webster.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224003000 +0000" stop="20260224010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dr. Winchester And Mr. Hyde</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles takes amphetamines to keep up his energy level, and even drugs Radar's mouse, "Daisy," so that it will win a race against a Marine's mouse, "Sluggo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224010000 +0000" stop="20260224013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The County Nurse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mary Simpson, the county nurse, wants to get all of the farmers in the county to take their innoculations. Figuring everyone will follow suit if she can just get Rafe Hollister to do it, she enlists the help of Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224013000 +0000" stop="20260224020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Barney In The Big City</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>While staying in Raleigh, Barney believes he is witnessing a man casing the hotel clientelle. Barney is right in believing a crime about to be committed, but he is tailing the house detective and has hooked up with the real crook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224020000 +0000" stop="20260224023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Game, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray and his family find themselves arguing about honesty.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224023000 +0000" stop="20260224030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Recovering Pessimist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray agrees to become more upbeat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224030000 +0000" stop="20260224033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered home and Colonel Crittendon is sent to replace him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224033000 +0000" stop="20260224040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket Newkirk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk unknowingly sneaks a beautiful Gestapo agent he has fallen for into camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224040000 +0000" stop="20260224043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Jim Nabors</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hollow Hero, the Queen and King try to give their Hollow solider a blue pony. Then, in The Family, Eunice finds out her husband went into a massage parlor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224043000 +0000" stop="20260224053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Foot-loose Doll</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When Millie Crest assumes another woman's identity after an embezzlement scheme, she ends up stabbing an intruder in self-defense—but, of course, things are not what they seem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224053500 +0000" stop="20260224060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Four O'clock</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A bitter, self-righteous man believes that he can will every evil person in the world to shrink to two-feet tall at four o'clock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224060500 +0000" stop="20260224070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The World's Oldest Motive  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Married Alex Morrow wants to wed his girlfriend, and sees his opportunity when an outsider offers to murder his wife for a price.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224070500 +0000" stop="20260224080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Quartet For A Blunt Instrument</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix agrees to help a mechanic accused of beating an inventor to death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224080500 +0000" stop="20260224090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Exchange</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Private eyes so rarely get a vacation free of peril, and Cannon is no exception. He goes fishing, little knowing that someone from his police past is hunting him: a murderer determined on revenge for the time he spent in prison.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224090500 +0000" stop="20260224100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Fraternity Of Thieves</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A pair of amateur thieves attempt to cover up the death of their cohort during a holdup - at the risk of the diamonds they've stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224100000 +0000" stop="20260224103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-12</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Police and Secret Service undertake maximum security for a Presidential visit to Los Angeles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224103000 +0000" stop="20260224110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Training - Dr-18</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday clashes with a woman writer gathering research material for an article on policewomen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224110000 +0000" stop="20260224113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Million Dollar Buff</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a run-in with a suspected professional jewel thief and fear she will walk due to lack of evidence. They also find themselves in competition with a millionaire vigilante, who provides assistance with apprehending a drunk driver and ending a shootout, but seems destined to soon overstep the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224113000 +0000" stop="20260224120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Grandmothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for a hype who robbed a hand-made craft store run by elderly women, only to later return the money after robbing an antique store. In the meantime, they engage in a high-speed pursuit, and pull over a priest in possession of marijuana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224120000 +0000" stop="20260224130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Trekkin' Series Finale: Land Of Lincoln</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224130000 +0000" stop="20260224133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Credit Card</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie brags about getting a credit card to his high school friends. When Wally's battery dies on his car, Eddie comes to the rescue by getting him a brand new battery. Everything is fine until Mr. Haskell finds out that Eddie charged it on their charge account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224133000 +0000" stop="20260224140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Uncle Billy's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E26</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward go away for a couple of days and leave Uncle Billy to stay with Wally and Beaver. Beaver quickly realizes Billy runs a much looser ship than Ward and June and feels as if he can get away with more things. However, he's soon in for a rude awakening when he helps Gilbert sneak into the movies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224140000 +0000" stop="20260224150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Borrowed Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A baby mysteriously appears in Mason's office along with a rare St. Christopher medal, which could help identify the baby's parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224150000 +0000" stop="20260224160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Cop  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Detective Joe Peters has been accused of taking bribes and murdering a fence; he also is suspected in the death of a fellow cop. Matlock takes the case and finds himself investigating the police force.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224160000 +0000" stop="20260224170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>The One With The Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Peter Corman is murdered during a game of poker, and his brother, Lorenzo, arrives in Hawaii for revenge. McGarrett must work out what happened and prevent Lorenzo from carrying out his intentions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224170000 +0000" stop="20260224180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An offer to buy their land makes the Waltons think about what it would be like to have more money than they need</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224180000 +0000" stop="20260224190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Treasure Of John Walking Fox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A hunter and his companion are taunted by the bigoted townspeople of Dodge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224190000 +0000" stop="20260224200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Blessed Are They</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben Cartwright and Virginia City's enigmatic new minister work together to decide which set of feuding grandparents, the Mahans or the Clarkes, will have custody of their recently orphaned twin grandchildren.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224200000 +0000" stop="20260224203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Assault</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>A salesman can't talk his way out of an assault charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224203000 +0000" stop="20260224210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Short Rope For A Tall Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Mark are in another town to sell a bull to Joe Lovering. While there, Mark buys two horses from Mr. Schneider. Neither Mark nor his father knows that the horses have been illegally bought and resold to them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224210000 +0000" stop="20260224220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Major Adams Story: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>During the Civil War, Charlie Wooster joins Bill Hawks under the command of Major Seth Adams. When Adams is seriously wounded saving Hawks's life he must struggle to survive, while dreaming of the girl he left behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224220000 +0000" stop="20260224230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Girl On The Balance Beam</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl is in a rush to go to the Olympics. The firemen rescue an actress trapped on a high wire at a studio, extricate a drunk driver from his car and attend to a burning train carrying ammonium nitrate.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224230000 +0000" stop="20260224233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Topper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>With the possibility of contaminated morphine, the doctors at the 4077th administer placebos to the patients, which seems to work. Meanwhile, a new soldier, "Boots" Miller, is released on a Section Eight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260224233000 +0000" stop="20260225000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Commander Pierce</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye undergoes a drastic change when he becomes temporary commander of the 4077th, and learns about the tedious bureaucracy and accompanying headaches that Colonel Potter deals with daily.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225000000 +0000" stop="20260225003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Peace On Us</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye becomes so disgusted with the stalled Panmunjon peace talks that he impulsively takes matters into his own hands, and goes to the meetings to lend a hand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225003000 +0000" stop="20260225010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Lil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Colonel Potter meets a female soldier of the same age and interests as himself named Lil. The others in the camp think that he might be cheating on Mildred, even though his friendship with Lil is completely platonic. Meanwhile, Hawkeye tries to find out what B.J.'s initials stand for. As it turns out, he was named after his parents, Bea and Jay Hunnicutt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225010000 +0000" stop="20260225013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Bells For Aunt Bee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Clara convinces Aunt Bee that Andy won't be able to find a wife as long as she's around, Aunt Bee begins searching for a man whom she can marry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225013000 +0000" stop="20260225020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three's A Crowd</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Every time Andy tries to be alone with Mary, Barney shows up. After Andy explains that he wants to be alone with her, Barney believes that Andy is planning to propose.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225020000 +0000" stop="20260225023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Dog, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray brings home a stray bulldog.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225023000 +0000" stop="20260225030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Neighbors</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank's sawing and Marie's meddling bother the neighborhood.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225030000 +0000" stop="20260225033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>War Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to get the Gestapo to release its prisoners, Hogan tricks Klink and Hochstetter into thinking the war is over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225033000 +0000" stop="20260225040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan prepares Klink to flee to Argentina with information for the Allies after Klink is challenged to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225040000 +0000" stop="20260225043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Pail, The / Stella Toddler</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Pail, a woman discovers her psychiatrist is her old school bully. Then, in Stella Toddler, Carol plays an accident-prone woman trying to report that she's been mugged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225043000 +0000" stop="20260225053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fraudulent Photo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E16</episode-num>
    <desc>While investigating corruption in a Northport Hospital project, District Attorney Brander Harris is the victim of a setup, resulting in an incriminating photo. When one of the men who may be trying to besmirch Harris's name ends up dead, Harris is charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225053500 +0000" stop="20260225060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Hocus-pocus And Frisby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A loud-mouthed braggart's boasts attract the attention of aliens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225060500 +0000" stop="20260225070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Monkey's Paw: A Retelling  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>In a retelling of classic chiller "The Monkey's Paw," a man realizes too late the evil powers of a monkey's paw that grants its owner three wishes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225070500 +0000" stop="20260225080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Memory: Zero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Maggie escapes from a deadly accident by a hair. The felon is a militant taxi driver. Mannix has the suspicion that he has already committed murder once, that of his colleague, Maggie's boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225080500 +0000" stop="20260225090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Avenger</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon takes on a missing person's case which leads to the death of a policeman."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225090500 +0000" stop="20260225100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Sister Of Death</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A nun is accused of taking her terminally ill sister off life support.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225100000 +0000" stop="20260225103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Public Affairs - Dr-14</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to get citizens to take part in a crime-prevention campaign.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225103000 +0000" stop="20260225110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Narcotics - Dr-16</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A businessman's war against drug addiction results in a new group whose motto is "freaking out isn't in."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225110000 +0000" stop="20260225113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Radical</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>At roll call, Malloy and Reed are asked to look out for a suspected militant and, after spotting him, attempt to follow him to his stash of weapons. Malloy also is asked by a security guard to investigate a possible shakedown and smuggling operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225113000 +0000" stop="20260225120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Search</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed report to a robbery at a grocery store, where Malloy is required to engage in a high-speed pursuit with one of the suspects while Reed apprehends the other on foot. When Malloy is seriously injured in a rollover accident at a remote location and loses two-way radio communication, Reed and others from the department race against the clock to locate him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225120000 +0000" stop="20260225130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>On This Day... February 25th</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony take a look at some of the biggest events that happened on February 25th."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225130000 +0000" stop="20260225133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver comes home with the news that he applied to appear on a local television show called 'Teen Forum' and has been accepted. Beaver gets out of classes for the taping and all his classmates are treated to being able to watch him on TV during class. However, what Beaver, his friends and family don't know is that the show tapes each episode a week in advance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225133000 +0000" stop="20260225140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Box Office Attraction</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E23</episode-num>
    <desc>June and Ward have noticed the Wally has been spending quite a bit of his time at the movie theater but it's not to see the movies. He's been eyeing the pretty young lady who works in the box office. Thanks to Eddie, Wally works up enough courage to ask her out but quickly sees another side to the young lady that is a bit too mature for Wally's taste.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225140000 +0000" stop="20260225150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Counterfeit Crank</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A crazy man, his dead nephew and a military base are tangled up in a confusing case for Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225150000 +0000" stop="20260225160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Angel  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock reluctantly agrees to take the case of free-spirited rock star Angel. The musician has been accused of killing her manager, and due to an alcohol-induced blackout can't even offer an alibi for the night of the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225160000 +0000" stop="20260225170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Cry, Lie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Chin Ho is accused of bribery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225170000 +0000" stop="20260225180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Jason and John Boy's friend Seth is diagnosed with leukemia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225180000 +0000" stop="20260225190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>My Father, My Son</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A gunslinger kills a young man out to gain a reputation, and then faces the wrath of the dead man's family.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225190000 +0000" stop="20260225200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Dowry</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>After recovering a stolen dowery, the Cartwright boys begin to grow suspicious when more attempts are made on the loot and the fiancé takes everything in stride.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225200000 +0000" stop="20260225203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarence Bibs Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A janitor-turned-gunfighter's reputation hangs on one lucky shot—and a lot of gall.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225203000 +0000" stop="20260225210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Score Is Even</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas looks for help when he is shot after witnessing a murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225210000 +0000" stop="20260225220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Major Adams Story: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Years after the Civil War, Major Adams gets a second chance with his lost love, Ranie, who had married in his absence. But happiness doesn't always come easy, as a sinister rival and a dark secret attest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225220000 +0000" stop="20260225230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Involvement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Rampart's former Emergency! department head nurse tries to commit suicide; she is brought to Rampart, where she befriends a paraplegic child who almost drowned in a swimming pool. Also: a woman wrapped in plastic, a family suffering from carbon monoxide poisoning and a man pinned under a tank truck containing volatile fuel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225230000 +0000" stop="20260225233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260225233000 +0000" stop="20260226000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Our Finest Hour</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Newscaster Clete Roberts, reprising an earlier interview appearance, returns to update Korean War conditions, when he conducts a series of television talks with the leading characters of the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226000000 +0000" stop="20260226003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Billfold Syndrome</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles becomes so irate when he is turned down for a future medical position at home that he refuses to talk to anyone in the unit, until Hawkeye and B.J. send him a false telegram from home. Meanwhile, a young soldier, Jerry Wilson, can't remember his own identity, so Sidney Freedman is called for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226003000 +0000" stop="20260226010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>None Like It Hot</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>As the temperatures reach triple digits, Hawkeye and B.J. receive their new rubber bathtub from Abercrombie &amp; Fitch. However, soon the whole camp is hot under the collar as word leaks out about the tub and everyone wants a dip, except for Klinger, who is trying to get his Section 8 by wearing a fur coat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226010000 +0000" stop="20260226013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Bookie Barber</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>A bookie from Raleigh sets himself up in Floyd's barbershop as an extra barber, trying to avoid the heat. Andy gets suspicious when the new barber has the same three clients.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226013000 +0000" stop="20260226020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy On Trial</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A news mogul swears revenge on Andy after he is arrested for what he deems a minor infraction. In retaliation, he sends a reporter to Mayberry to dig up whatever dirt she can on Andy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226020000 +0000" stop="20260226023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Fascinatin' Debra</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra is being interviewed by a psychotherapist for a book.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226023000 +0000" stop="20260226030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Why Are We Here?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Debra gets fed up with Ray's family intruding in her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226030000 +0000" stop="20260226033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Axis Annie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use a propaganda radio announcer to get information to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226033000 +0000" stop="20260226040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>What Time Does The Balloon Go Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A basket-weaving and a kite-flying contest are part of Hogan's plan to transport an agent to England in a balloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226040000 +0000" stop="20260226043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Family, The / Take My Drink</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Family, Mama and Eunice battle it out over charades. Then, in Take My Drink, Carol spills her guts to a wise-cracking bartender.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226043000 +0000" stop="20260226053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Romantic Rogue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>After con man Stacey Chandler and Helen Harvey are married in Vegas, Chandler's former associate and scheming con woman, Irene Wallace, is found murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226053500 +0000" stop="20260226060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Trade-ins</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly couple visits the New Life Corporation, hoping to transport their personalities into youthful artificial bodies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226060500 +0000" stop="20260226070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>The Second Wife  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Newlywed Martha Hunter compulsively believes that her husband killed his former wife and plans the same fate for her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226070500 +0000" stop="20260226080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Nowhere Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>When investigating a case of hit-and-run, Mannix gets caught amid the fronts of a mafia war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226080500 +0000" stop="20260226090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>A Killing In The Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A former prostitute aids Cannon in an investigation involving mobsters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226090500 +0000" stop="20260226100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Charade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty falls for a playboy who's planning a murder to gain an inheritance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226100000 +0000" stop="20260226103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Internal Affairs - Dr-20</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Martin Milner and Kent McCord appear as Officers Malloy and Reed to portray the policeman's role in society.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226103000 +0000" stop="20260226110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Community Relations - Dr-17</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A conference provokes old-line policemen to reassess their attitudes, particularly toward minority groups.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226110000 +0000" stop="20260226113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferret</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are on the lookout for an environmentalist known as "The Ferret" who has been posing as an employee to infiltrate and sabotage industrial complexes he feels are creating too much pollution. In the meantime, they respond to a woman who is nearly comatose and ultimately gives birth to a stillborn baby. They then investigate the witchdoctor who has been convincing her and other women that eating clay will ensure a successful pregnancy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226113000 +0000" stop="20260226120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Truant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After apprehending a couple of juvenile delinquents who are ransacking a house, Reed is inspired to submit an idea on how to deal with truants, which ultimately gets implemented on a trial basis by the captain, but draws the ire of Officer Wells. Back on patrol, they apprehend a couple of high-level drug dealers who run into bad luck, and nearly get run over by two men using stolen automobile parts to build a high-powered go cart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226120000 +0000" stop="20260226130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Black History - Sitcoms, Spin-offs &amp; Stars</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226130000 +0000" stop="20260226133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver, The Caddie</sub-title>
    <desc>"Beaver has gotten a job as a caddy and is quickly running around the golf course chasing balls. However, all innocence is broken when one of the guys, Beaver is caddying for cheats in order to win a bet. Soon, Beaver begins wrestling with his conscience over whether or not to tell anyone."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226133000 +0000" stop="20260226140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Lumpy's Scholarship</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally is let down when he learns that he didn't get the sports scholarship from State University. However, he does learn that Lumpy did get one and this leads him to throw a party in Lumpy's honor. However, half way through the party, Fred calls with some unfortunate news for Lumpy, the scholarship is no longer available due to Lumpy's grades.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226140000 +0000" stop="20260226150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Ancient Romeo</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della go out for a night at the theatre to see 'Romeo and Juliet.' After the theatre suddenly goes dark during a dueling scene, the audience is horrified to discover that one of the actors has been killed with a sword when the lights are restored.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226150000 +0000" stop="20260226160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Professor  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Professor Erskine Tate wakes from a drunken stupor behind the wheel of his car. He doesn't know how he got there or what happened. When he's accused of having hit a mailman during a drunken joyride, he goes to a former student, Matlock, for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226160000 +0000" stop="20260226170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Most Likely To Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Police officer Lew Morgan and his wife are long-time friends of Danno. When she is murdered, Morgan sets out to find the culprit. He uncovers secrets that may have led to her death, putting a strain on his friendship with Danno.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226170000 +0000" stop="20260226180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Cradle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Olivia is happy to learn that she is pregnant again, but John worries that having another baby will be hard for her</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226180000 +0000" stop="20260226190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Parson Comes To Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A stranger wearing a murdered preacher's coat causes tension in Dodge when he announces his intention to watch someone die.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226190000 +0000" stop="20260226200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Inger, My Love</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben indulges in a nostalgic reverie about Hoss's deceased mother. Having worked his way west to Galesburg, Illinois, Ben is befriended by a girl named Inger, the fiancee of the tavern owner who gave him a job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226200000 +0000" stop="20260226203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Mescalaro Curse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is marked for death: he was foreman of a jury that convicted an Apache.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226203000 +0000" stop="20260226210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stopover</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Trouble brews at Lucas' when a whisky salesman and a gunfighter fall for the same woman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226210000 +0000" stop="20260226220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Charles Maury Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Adams becomes suspicious of a soldier who's supposedly providing protection for the wagon train from bandits.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226220000 +0000" stop="20260226230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Above And Beyond... Nearly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and John receive commendations for bravery, but they can't remember the incident. A 94-year-old man breaks his ankle while dancing. Dr. Brackett treats a man who passed out in a dentist's chair. An injured mountaineer is stranded on a cliff.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226230000 +0000" stop="20260226233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>They Call The Wind Korea</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A strong windstorm affects the M*A*S*H personnel in varying ways: Hawkeye and most of the unit busy themselves securing items that could blow away; Radar prepares his animal hutch for the worst; a disgusted Charles switches his Tokyo-leave transportation from air to ground and runs into a difficult medical situation en route to Seoul.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260226233000 +0000" stop="20260227000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Major Ego</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Captain Tom Greenleigh of "Stars and Stripes" comes to the 4077th to write an article about Charles, which makes him act even more egotistical than usual.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227000000 +0000" stop="20260227003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Baby, It's Cold Outside</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>While everyone is complaining about the record cold snap, Charles becomes the most unpopular man in camp, when his parents send him a winterized polar suit that he insists on flaunting in front of everyone.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227003000 +0000" stop="20260227010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Point Of View</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In this unique episode, the camera becomes the eyes of a young wounded soldier. It records his sensory responses to being wounded, flown by helicopter to the 4077th, examined, operated on and treated in post-operation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227010000 +0000" stop="20260227013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Cousin Virgil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney tries to help out his visiting cousin, Virgil. When Virgil makes one too many mistakes, Barney rails against him and storms out. Leave it to Andy to put things right.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227013000 +0000" stop="20260227020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Deputy Otis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Otis has been writing letters to his brother and sister-in-law for some time on courthouse stationary. Because of this, they have come to believe that he is a deputy, something they expect to see on their upcoming visit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227020000 +0000" stop="20260227023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Ray's On Tv</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray is devastated when he discovers his family lied to him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227023000 +0000" stop="20260227030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Father Knows Least</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray gets to use the "active technique" he and Debra learned in parenting class.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227030000 +0000" stop="20260227033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Lebeau And The Little Old Lady</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>LeBeau tells the others he is taking messages to a little old lady, when really she is a beautiful lady he has fallen for.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227033000 +0000" stop="20260227040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>How To Escape From Prison Camp Without Really Trying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan hides 30 prisoners in order to keep the SS busy while the Allies build reinforcements.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227040000 +0000" stop="20260227043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Maggie Smith</sub-title>
    <desc>In Kitchen Crumbles, Carol tests her newly remodeled kitchen, and everything goes wrong. Then, in The Family, Eunice meets with her son's teacher, who thinks the problem may start at home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227043000 +0000" stop="20260227053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Careless Kitten</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>When a woman receives a phone call from a man claiming to be her wealthy uncle who disappeared 10 years prior, Mason is called in to investigate. A proposed encounter with the man leads to the discovery of a corpse and soon the niece of the phantom uncle is poisoned.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227053500 +0000" stop="20260227060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An alien crash-lands in a remote mountain village, stirring up fear and animosity among the villagers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227060500 +0000" stop="20260227070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Night Fever  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>An injured criminal uses a compassionate nurse to run away from a hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227070500 +0000" stop="20260227080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Sound Of Darkness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E13</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mannix tracks down an assassin, he is shot and seriously injured. Having a breakdown, Mannix is diagnosed with psychosomatic blindness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227080500 +0000" stop="20260227090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Flashpoint</sub-title>
    <desc>"Cannon is on the case when a psychiatric patient is accused of rape and murder after falling in with some unsavory companions. CANNON attempts to clear a young man accused of rape-murder while the real villain's mother accuses her son of the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227090500 +0000" stop="20260227100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Testament Of Power</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>The executors of a millionaire's estate attempt to get rid of a new will putting them out of their jobs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227100000 +0000" stop="20260227103000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>Homicide - Dr-22</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A 91-year-old apartment-house manager gets involved in a murder investigation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227103000 +0000" stop="20260227110000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>B.o.d. - Dr-27</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>The detectives go to work on several cases connected with the department's business-office division.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227110000 +0000" stop="20260227113000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are ambushed by two men who want to silence the prisoner they are transporting from Malibu to Los Angeles. Their problems are compounded by the lack of radio communication in Malibu Canyon, which ultimately results in Reed being taken hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227113000 +0000" stop="20260227120000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed brainstorm what to get Sgt. MacDonald for his anniversary, subdue an understandably belligerent wrestler in a bar and get followed by a man with a recent streak of bad luck. Afterward, they investigate an unethical used car salesman and liquor store robbery and also thwart an attempted camper theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227120000 +0000" stop="20260227130000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Combine Time</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227130000 +0000" stop="20260227133000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Silent Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver is all set to go with Eddie and Wally to hook up a AM/FM car radio in Eddie's car but June stops him and insists he go to the grocery store to pick up the items he had promised. This leads Beaver to give June the cold shoulder treatment while playing up to Ward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227133000 +0000" stop="20260227140000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Eddie's Sweater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Eddie has been seeing one particular girl, Cindy Andrews, and she wants to give Eddie a birthday gift, so she decides to knit a sweater. She uses Wally as a model and he begins spending so much time at Cindy's he arrouses the suspicions of Julie, Eddie, Lumpy, Beaver and his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227140000 +0000" stop="20260227150000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Promoter's Pillbox</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Aspiring screenwriter Herbert Simms submits a teleplay to unscrupulous producer Charlie Corby, who passes the manuscript off as his own. Corby's scheme dies with him, however, when he is fatally whacked over the head with a whiskey bottle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227150000 +0000" stop="20260227160000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Claus  (s1, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a down-on-his luck Santa Claus (Tom McCabe) is accused of killing his avaricious landlord, Matlock finds himself defending the very unlikeable man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227160000 +0000" stop="20260227170000 +0000">
    <title>Hawaii Five-O</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A research scientist, Dr. Royce, is set up by revolutionaries to be transported away from the islands in a submarine. McGarrett must stop this from happening and also has to contend with the interference of federal agents in the case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227170000 +0000" stop="20260227180000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fulfillment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Curtis and Ann are unhappy to learn that they are unable to have children of their own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227180000 +0000" stop="20260227190000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Prime Of Life</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Kyle Stoner is involved with a pair of thieves who beat up Festus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227190000 +0000" stop="20260227200000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Mountain Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Raised in the hills by her reclusive grandfather, Trudy is left in Joe's care when he dies. Honoring a promise to the girl's late grandfather, Joe is determined to transform the hoydenish Trudy into a "lady."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227200000 +0000" stop="20260227203000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lonesome Bride</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Two pranksters write away for a mail-order bride, using Lucas's name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227203000 +0000" stop="20260227210000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Death Trap</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas recognizes Dr. Simon Battle as an ex-gunslinger with whom he once traded shots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227210000 +0000" stop="20260227220000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Dan Hogan Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>In a growing town, Seth meets a friend from his distant past. He remembers how they met and the circumstances bringing them west. When his friend's home is threatened, he learns that removing his firearm may be the key to resolving the situation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227220000 +0000" stop="20260227230000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Grateful</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a couple is rescued from under a car, they hang about the stationhouse, helping out. An elderly man tries to perform CPR on his friend, but does more harm than good. A child is struck in the eye with a BB gun. While returning from a false alarm on Copter 10, Roy and John rescue the victims of a boat fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227230000 +0000" stop="20260227233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Comrade</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and B.J. discover that Charles is living the "life of Riley," thanks to the attentions of his menially paid Korean servant, Comrade Park, a man of unusual skills. He has an important contribution to make—a native remedy for a seemingly insoluble medical problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260227233000 +0000" stop="20260228000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228000000 +0000" stop="20260228003000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228003000 +0000" stop="20260228010000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228010000 +0000" stop="20260228013000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mr. Mcbeevee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>While walking through the woods, Opie meets Mr. McBeevee, a man who, Opie claims, "lives in the trees" and "jingles when he walks." Andy eventually learns that Opie's new friend works for the telephone company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228013000 +0000" stop="20260228020000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy's Rich Girlfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy has begun seeing Peggy McMillan and he discovers she is from a wealthy family. The differences in their upbringings and education unsettle Andy, and he begins to doubt the ability of the relationship to endure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228020000 +0000" stop="20260228023000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Brother</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray takes his brother, Robert, out for a night on the town.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228023000 +0000" stop="20260228030000 +0000">
    <title>Everybody Loves Raymond</title>
    <sub-title>Mozart</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Ray tries to teach Ally an important lesson about not quitting.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228030000 +0000" stop="20260228033000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Collector General</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E27</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan tries to keep a fortune in paintings from winding up in the collection of a general.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228033000 +0000" stop="20260228040000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Ultimate Weapon</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to send German defenses to the wrong target by "giving" Schultz ESP so that the Allies can bomb an important target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228040000 +0000" stop="20260228043000 +0000">
    <title>Carol Burnett and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Guest Maggie Smith</sub-title>
    <desc>In The Hollow Hero, Tim is given the honor of christening a ship, only the Queen can't pronounce the name correctly. Then, in Jowls, Carol and the gang parody the classic thriller "Jaws", with a shark that can get into any bathtub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228043000 +0000" stop="20260228053500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Caretaker's Cat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Wealthy Peter Baxter decides to test the loyalty of his heirs. He pretends to change his will cutting them all out and leaving his entire estate to groundskeeper James Hing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228053500 +0000" stop="20260228060500 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Dummy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E33</episode-num>
    <desc>A ventriloquist is convinced that his dummy is not only alive but also evil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228060500 +0000" stop="20260228070500 +0000">
    <title>The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <sub-title>Off Season  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Fired from the law enforcement, a trigger-happy ex-policeman takes a job in a small-town sheriff's office.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228070500 +0000" stop="20260228080500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Who Killed Me?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Bradley Everett crashes his small plane into the sea. After an intensive search turns up no sign of the man, he suddenly appears at Mannix's door, babbling about a murder attempt.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228080500 +0000" stop="20260228090500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Man Who Couldn't Forget</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon is in a full blown jam when he gets mistaken for the assassin of a bishop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228090500 +0000" stop="20260228100000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Copy-cat Killing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband kills his wife's lover.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20260228100000 +0000" stop="20260228103000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo's Bike</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Working toward earning money for a motorbike, Betty Jo takes up babysitting, turning the Shady Rest into one giant nursery.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
