<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630023000 +0000" stop="20250630030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Imogene Coca And Robert Goulet (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Imogene Coca and Robert Goulet. Originally aired on 04/07/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630030000 +0000" stop="20250630033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Go Tell The Birds And The Bees</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Richie has been giving his classmates lectures on the facts of life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630033000 +0000" stop="20250630040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>Body And Sol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob remembers when he was a boxer in the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630040000 +0000" stop="20250630043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Loudspeaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph writes a speech because he thinks he's going to be Raccoon of the Year—but it turns out Norton receives the honor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630043000 +0000" stop="20250630053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Mute</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A 12-year-old girl who lost her parents in a fire doesn't speak because she has grown up in a secret telepathic community. The couple who take her in, and her teacher, are determined to help her adapt to their society, no matter the cost.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630053000 +0000" stop="20250630060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Number Twenty-two</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A petty crook clashes with a hardened criminal in a jail cell.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630060000 +0000" stop="20250630070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Rebel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF must rescue three scientists in a dictatorial country and destroy their notes. They rescue two but the third one, Khora, refuses to leave and is executed. Jim and Dana meet with his son, Alex, (a rebel leader) to get his notes and Dana is captured.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630070000 +0000" stop="20250630080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>The End Is But The Beginning</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Kimble takes advantage of a deadly car accident as a way to try and convince Gerard that he is now dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630080000 +0000" stop="20250630090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Shades</sub-title>
    <desc>"Harry Orwell confronts race hatred and blackmail in his attempt to clear a businessman's housekeeper of murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630090000 +0000" stop="20250630093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Masked Bandits</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Four bandits wearing red masks commit a series of robberies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630093000 +0000" stop="20250630100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Bank Examiner Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Two con men, posing as bank examiners, are bilking the elderly out of their life savings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630100000 +0000" stop="20250630103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Truant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>After apprehending a couple of juvenile delinquents who are ransacking a house, Reed is inspired to submit an idea on how to deal with truants, which ultimately gets implemented on a trial basis by the captain, but draws the ire of Officer Wells. Back on patrol, they apprehend a couple of high-level drug dealers who run into bad luck, and nearly get run over by two men using stolen automobile parts to build a high-powered go cart.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630103000 +0000" stop="20250630110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Ambush</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are ambushed by two men who want to silence the prisoner they are transporting from Malibu to Los Angeles. Their problems are compounded by the lack of radio communication in Malibu Canyon, which ultimately results in Reed being taken hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630110000 +0000" stop="20250630120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Cosplay Show</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony run into a few almost identical faces at a cartoon curation fan convention."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630120000 +0000" stop="20250630123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Watch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>While watching Wally and his friends play baseball, Beaver is put in charge of looking after everyone's coats and watches. However, after the game is over Lumpy comes to claim his watch, but Beaver has no watch to give him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630123000 +0000" stop="20250630130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Her Idol</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver becomes good friends with a classmate, Linda Dennison. However, their relationship is blown out of proportion by Beaver's classmates who begin to tease him and goad him into insulting Linda to prove that she isn't his girl.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630130000 +0000" stop="20250630140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The 12th Wildcat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Burt Payne coaches and owns 10% of a professional football team. His rich wife, Ellen, owns the remainder. Knowing that he's washed up and needing some quick cash, Burt tries to sell his share of the team to a group of investors.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630140000 +0000" stop="20250630150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Best Friend  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Vanessa Douglas when she's accused of murdering Stephen Cassidy, an author who destroyed a political family's ambitions with a tell-all book. When Matlock realizes his client is indeed guilty, he sets up an ingenious plan to draw out a confession.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630150000 +0000" stop="20250630160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Falsely Accused</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Sweet is the target of false accusations by two corrupt and racist car salesmen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630160000 +0000" stop="20250630170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An old abandoned home is condemned</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630170000 +0000" stop="20250630173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Blacksmith</sub-title>
    <desc>"German immigrant and town blacksmith, Emil Wolhter and his German mail order bride, Gretchen Mueller, are to be married. Matt, Doc and Chester along with Emil meet Gretchen at the stage station. Emil and Gretchen throw a big wedding party for all their friends in Dodge;however, not everyone in Dodge is friendly to Emil and Gretchen."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630173000 +0000" stop="20250630180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Small Water</sub-title>
    <desc>"Matt &amp; Chester are bringing in Leroy Finn to face murder charges. Leroy gets the drop on Chester during the night and Matt kills him. Matt &amp; Chester go to Leroy's home to tell his father about what happened and to tell him to keep the rest of his sons out of Dodge."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630180000 +0000" stop="20250630190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Erin</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When Ben allows the Paiutes to camp on Ponderosa land, a neighbor threatens Hoss' fiancée, Erin, a beautiful young woman who was raised by Indians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630190000 +0000" stop="20250630193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Challenge</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>When escaped convicts hold up the general store in North Fork and take Marshal Torrance hostage, Lucas comes to the rescue.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630193000 +0000" stop="20250630200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Hawk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Young Mark manages to capture a hawk, but then falls into danger from a rattlesnake. When a stranger comes to his rescue, the grateful Mark invites the man home, unaware that he is on the run from the law.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630200000 +0000" stop="20250630210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The C.l. Harding Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A reporter has joined the wagon train. When the Major finds out he is a she, he has his hands full, especially when curiosity jeopardizes everyone's safety and their right to vote.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630210000 +0000" stop="20250630220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Screenwriter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A screenwriter spends a day observing Squad 51 at work, including a motorcycle accident, a worker suffering from exposure to chemicals, the delivery of a baby and a fire at a toy factory.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630220000 +0000" stop="20250630223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Out Of Gas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Heavy casualties are arriving, creating severe problems for the M*A*S*H unit because they are nearly out of Pentothal. Mulcahy takes up a collection from everyone—including a case of wine from Charles' private supply—and he and Charles take the jeep to make a trade with the black marketers for Pentothal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630223000 +0000" stop="20250630230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>An Eye For A Tooth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy takes being passed over for promotion philosophically until he hears of the rapid advancement made by a heroic helicopter pilot. Then his uncharacteristically bold actions stun Colonel Potter and the entire company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630230000 +0000" stop="20250630233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Dear Sis</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Father Mulcahy writes a pre-Christmas letter to his sister, who is a nun. He recounts his frustrations at not being more effective at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250630233000 +0000" stop="20250701000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>B.j. Papa San</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E15</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. almost becomes the surrogate father to a Korean family. Finding them a substitute for his own absent family, B.J. spends so much time with them that his medical efficiency begins to suffer, and Hawkeye worries about his health.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701000000 +0000" stop="20250701003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Man In The Middle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney and Thelma Lou have an argument. They reconcile quickly, but it leads to other arguments between Andy and Barney, Thelma Lou and Helen, Andy and Helen, and another between Barney and Thelma Lou.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701003000 +0000" stop="20250701010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney's Uniform</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Fred the grocery store clerk repeatedly sweeps trash into the street, even after Barney writes him a citation. Fred threatens that if he ever sees Barney out of uniform, he'll pound him, causing Barney to leave his uniform on at all times.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701010000 +0000" stop="20250701013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Trotting Horse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny needs to get around Beverly Hills and is having no luck with a driving lesson. When she hears that the Drysdale are looking at the horses, Granny decides she needs a trotter and buggy. Drysdale learns that the Clampetts want a horse, and after he learns of its potential winnings, the Clampetts acquire Ladybelle, a racehorse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701013000 +0000" stop="20250701020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>On Stage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E31</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, Alice and Ed are in a Raccoon play, and Ralph expects to be a big star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701020000 +0000" stop="20250701023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plays a waiting game with a German general. The scheming general has planted a rocket-fuel depot right outside Stalag 13 in hopes of trapping the area's resident saboteur, whom he suspects is Hogan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701023000 +0000" stop="20250701030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Carter Turns Traitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Carter pretends to be a traitor so he can learn the location of a chemical plant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701030000 +0000" stop="20250701033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Execution</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Just before being hanged for murder, a man in 1880 is transported to the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701033000 +0000" stop="20250701043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Playboy Pugilist</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Boxing trainer Jimmy West thinks he's finally found a championship contender in Davey Carroll. Unfortunately, Davey's tangled love life leads to Jimmy being charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701043500 +0000" stop="20250701050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Ad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con named Steve Deal contacts Friday and Gannon when a classified ad that he placed, offering to do "anything" for money, results in an offer to commit murder. Friday goes undercover as Deal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701050500 +0000" stop="20250701053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The End Of Indian Summer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>An old woman is investigation by her insurance company when she plans to get married for a third time, her previous husbands having died mysteriously.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701053500 +0000" stop="20250701060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One For The Road</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Marsha discovers that her husband has a lover and decides to poison him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701060500 +0000" stop="20250701070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Lost Art Of Dying</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix is forced into proving death row inmate Carl Danzig is innocent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701070500 +0000" stop="20250701080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Child Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Paul Stubber taps the computer of the railroad company to be able to rob cars with valuable goods. However, nothing can be proved against him. Cannon finds Stubber's weak spot: The crook fights for the right to keep his son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701080500 +0000" stop="20250701090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Circle Of Treachery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>As a thief awaits trial, his accomplice puts out a contract on the only witness to the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701090000 +0000" stop="20250701093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly apartment manager is found to have been beaten to death with a hammer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701093000 +0000" stop="20250701100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Candy Store Robberies</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon try to figure out a pattern to a series of candy store hold-ups. The solution comes when they discover that there are two suspects.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701100000 +0000" stop="20250701103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anniversary</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed brainstorm what to get Sgt. MacDonald for his anniversary, subdue an understandably belligerent wrestler in a bar and get followed by a man with a recent streak of bad luck. Afterward, they investigate an unethical used car salesman and liquor store robbery and also thwart an attempted camper theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701103000 +0000" stop="20250701110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Assassination</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed become the repeated targets of an unidentified sniper who has them called to fake disturbances and follows them to some of their real calls, which include a special deliver, a suicide threat at a gas station and a reported prowler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701110000 +0000" stop="20250701120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Waterpark It!</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony visit a waterpark. Bill gets stuck on the past... and stuck in a slide!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701120000 +0000" stop="20250701123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Ring</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Being Beaver's godmother, Aunt Martha sends him a gift of a ring that had once belonged to an uncle who was also named Theodore. June cautions Beaver that she doesn't want him taking it to school, but he sneaks off to school with it anyway. This leads to a confrontation between his peers that ends with him getting the ring stuck on his finger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701123000 +0000" stop="20250701130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Shave</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>When Eddie and some of his other friends brag about shaving, Wally decides it's time he try. After nicking his face, Ward tries to discourage him but this just leads Wally to continue to shave. When Ward catches him again, he scolds him right in front of Eddie which leads to Wally being made fun of.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701130000 +0000" stop="20250701140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Wrathful Wraith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Louise Self finds herself in the unfortunate position of having to stand trial for the murder of her husband twice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701140000 +0000" stop="20250701150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Debt  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Leanne's ex-husband is charged with a murder, the possible motive makes Matlock despise his former son-in-law more than ever.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701150000 +0000" stop="20250701160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Step Removed</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Parker's stepfather Roy threatens his former employer after an altercation. When the boss is murdered Roy is arrested.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701160000 +0000" stop="20250701170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Fledgling</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy wants to buy a printing press to start his own newspaper</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701170000 +0000" stop="20250701173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Say Uncle</sub-title>
    <desc>"Martin Nagel is a hard working store owner that has plans to build up his business and eventually leave the business to his son, Lee Nagel. When Martin Nagel is killed in a freak accident, Lee Nagel thinks that his Uncle (Hutch) did the killing."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701173000 +0000" stop="20250701180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Shooting Stopover</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Matt and Chester are transporting a prisoner on a stage coach to Wichita, Matt learns that the stage is also carrying gold. Matt fears that outlaws might attack the stage for the gold. While at a stagecoach stopover, the outlaws attack the station."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701180000 +0000" stop="20250701190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Company Of Forgotten Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A retired Army sergeant, bitter that he never received his pension from the government, kidnaps one-time friend Candy, forcing him to help in a plan to blow up the U.S. mint in Carson City and hold the gold and silver for ransom.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701190000 +0000" stop="20250701193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Three-legged Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rambunctious teenager wrecks a schoolroom, Lucas McCain, as a member of the North Fork school board, asks the boy's reluctant uncle to pay for the damages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701193000 +0000" stop="20250701200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Angry Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E31</episode-num>
    <desc>The McCains try to be tolerant of their embittered neighbor, Abel MacDonald, who tells Lucas to keep off his land and won't allow his son to become friends with Mark. However, McCain decides he's gone too far when he won't allow his injured boy to get medical treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701200000 +0000" stop="20250701210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Estaban Zamora Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint finds a young man bleeding to death and a knife nearby. He takes the body to the sheriff who identifies the man as the youngest Zamora brother. He feels duty-bound to kill the murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701210000 +0000" stop="20250701220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>I'll Fix It</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman's husband is trapped under their house, where a natural oil well has erupted. John tries to fix a boy's bike. A boy who wants to become a doctor is admitted to Rampart. The firemen rescue a child stuck in a pipe. Roy and John remove a ring from a young man’s finger. Roy and Capt. Stanley struggle with a shutoff valve at a burning building.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701220000 +0000" stop="20250701223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Inga</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E16</episode-num>
    <desc>It's instant attraction for Hawkeye when a beautiful Swedish doctor, called Inga, arrives to observe combat surgery. That is, until she upstages him in the operating room with a superior technique, and his ego is bruised.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701223000 +0000" stop="20250701230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Price</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E17</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th is confronted by two crises: Colonel Potter's mare, Sophie, mysteriously disappears from her corral, and Hawkeye and B.J. find themselves with a young Korean boy on their hands, who is trying to avoid conscription into the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701230000 +0000" stop="20250701233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Young And The Restless</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A lecture on the latest techniques by a young surgeon from Tokyo, and a later demonstration of his surgical skill, turns Winchester into a drunk and Potter into an invalid, whilst bringing home to Hawkeye and B.J. that they are out of touch with new medical practices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250701233000 +0000" stop="20250702000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>C*a*v*e</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E20</episode-num>
    <desc>The 4077th evacuation to a nearby cave to avoid US artillery fire on a Chinese target poses problems for Hawkeye, who has a claustrophobia problem of which Colonel Potter is not aware.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702000000 +0000" stop="20250702003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Opie finds a lost wallet containing $50, and just as he's waited the seven-day period to claim the money as his own, the owner steps forward.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702003000 +0000" stop="20250702010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Goodbye, Sheriff Taylor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy considers moving to Raleigh for another job. An upset Barney tries to demonstrate to Andy just how bad Mayberry would be without him, creating more harm than good in his effort to get Andy to stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702010000 +0000" stop="20250702013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Buggy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny gets a buggy for her horse Ladybelle and gets the same thing for Mrs. Drysdale so they can have buggy races. But the horse she buys for her neighbor is known around the stables as "Old Gluepot." She tries to cheat to win, but ends up with Lightening, the poor horse, after Jed tries to teach her a lesson.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702013000 +0000" stop="20250702020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Opportunity Knock But</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Ed play pool with Ralph's boss and Ed gets a job at the bus company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702020000 +0000" stop="20250702023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Two Nazis For The Price Of One</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A Gestapo agent knows about Hogan's operation and tries to leverage this knowledge to find out information about the Manhattan Project.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702023000 +0000" stop="20250702030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Is There A Doctor In The House?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Klink's illness causes problems for one of Hogan's plots.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702030000 +0000" stop="20250702033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Tall Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E27</episode-num>
    <desc>A boy who believes in magic thinks he is helping a boxer win with his "big, tall wish."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702033000 +0000" stop="20250702043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Double-entry Mind</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Timid bookkeeper Clem Sandover is irate when his longterm embezzlement scheme is discovered by a fellow employee. When that co-worker turns up dead, however, it's Sandover's wife who's charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702043500 +0000" stop="20250702050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman real estate agent is missing and turns up dead in a vacant home. The detectives' one suspect, the woman's ex-boyfriend, is cleared; then credit card bills for purchases made after the woman's death start appearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702050500 +0000" stop="20250702053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Cream Of The Jest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>An unemployed actor plays his last role.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702053500 +0000" stop="20250702060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Killed The Count (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Count Mattoni is brutally murdered and Scotland Yard Inspector Davidson must wade the through a myriad of suspects."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702060500 +0000" stop="20250702070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Walk On The Blind Side</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Syndicate thugs have kidnapped an informer—or so they believe. Their victim is actually Peggy Fair, Mannix's secretary, which puts the detective on their trail.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702070500 +0000" stop="20250702080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Shadow Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank Cannon is hired to search missing rancher Dale Lucas following his wife's order. He notes that the guard service of the ranch has been replaced.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702080500 +0000" stop="20250702090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>A rapist threatens to get more violent with Betty's friend if she tells the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702090000 +0000" stop="20250702093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Fur Job</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gannon goes undercover as a buyer in order to trap fur thieves"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702093000 +0000" stop="20250702100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Jade Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $200,000 worth of imperial jade is reported stolen. Friday and Gannon determine the burglary was an inside job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702100000 +0000" stop="20250702103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Dinosaur</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Eight years after an act of heroism put him out of commission, an officer returns to active duty, only to find that the changes made to the job that limit an officer's power and increase suspects' rights are too much to handle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702103000 +0000" stop="20250702110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Pick-up</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed actively search for a serial rapist/murderer who hasn't left behind any solid clues, which causes Malloy to vent about what he perceives to be over-reliance on computers at the expense of old-fashioned police logic. In the meantime, they deal with a kid who crashes his friend's dirt bike, engage in a futile high-speed pursuit of a porsche and search for an armed suspect of a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702110000 +0000" stop="20250702120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Too Close Encounters</sub-title>
    <desc>"It's World UFO Day, and Toony is convinced that Bill was abducted by Aliens!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702120000 +0000" stop="20250702123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Pipe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward receives an antique pipe as a gift from Fred Rutherford and a curious Larry and Beaver decide to try it out. First they use coffee but then they try tobacco. When Ward discovers someone has used the pipe, he jumps to the conclusion that Wally is the culprit.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702123000 +0000" stop="20250702130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's New Suit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally needs a new suit for an upcoming dance and he convinces his parents that he's old enough to pick out his own clothes. So he and Beaver go down to the shop and pick out the loudest, cheapest plaid suit in the entire shop.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702130000 +0000" stop="20250702140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Runaway Racer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Test driver Pete Griston cracks up a vehicle owned by Pappy Ryan. Pappy accuses Havey Rettig of tampering with the car and files charges against Rettig and Griston. Then Rettig is killed and Griston is found standing groggily over the body.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702140000 +0000" stop="20250702150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Gift (aka The Christmas Show)  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a Santa accused of murder at a party populated by Saint Nicks, and plays Father Christmas to the defendant's daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702150000 +0000" stop="20250702160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Affection</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman asks Harriet to help her get an eviction order rescinded. The chief gives Parker a new radar gun - and soon comes to regret it. Sheriff McComb requests that Gillespie and Bubba help investigate a murder. Meanwhile Lonnie and Luann search for the boy who reported the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702160000 +0000" stop="20250702170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Collision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Selena Linville returns and talks to John-Boy about the rebellion in Spain</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702170000 +0000" stop="20250702173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Peace Officer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Stella (played by Susan Cummings) leaves Tascosa to escape her bad boyfriend Clegg Rawlins. Stella is shot when she tries to help Matt. Matt takes her to a rancher's cabin and takes care of her wound. Then brings her back to Dodge."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702173000 +0000" stop="20250702180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Don Matteo</sub-title>
    <desc>"Garth Tabor makes threats after Bill Pence throws him out of the Long Branch for being rough with the ladies. Estaban Garcia (Matt’s old friend comes into Dodge looking for Matt and Tabor. Estaban wants to kill a man."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702180000 +0000" stop="20250702190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Clarion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben helps an old friend having trouble keeping her newspaper business afloat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702190000 +0000" stop="20250702193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Woman</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E32</episode-num>
    <desc>An unfounded rumor causes North Fork's outspoken feminist schoolteacher to be attacked by a mob of angry townspeople.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702193000 +0000" stop="20250702200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Money Gun</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When his employer begins to suspect him of embezzlement, bookkeeper Asa Manning decides to hire a professional gunman to take care of the problem.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702200000 +0000" stop="20250702210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Elizabeth Mcqueeny Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth McQueeny is traveling with her girls, heading to a finishing school in the west. When her real purpose becomes known, all the females want her gone but her worth shows itself before that can happen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702210000 +0000" stop="20250702220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Gossip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy encourages John to represent the station in the Fireman's Olympics track events. An armored car sideswipes a motorist and Station 51 must break into the van. A nurse spreads the rumor that Dr. Morton is having financial problems. Doctors treat a child with cyanide poisoning from peach pits. Dr. Brackett treats a bigamist with a skull fracture. The firemen rescue an electrocution victim hanging in mid-air and a man trapped in a warehouse fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702220000 +0000" stop="20250702223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Rally Round The Flagg, Boys</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The sinister Colonel Flagg pops up at the 4077th again, playing his usual spy games, convinced that Hawkeye is a communist sympathizer after he saves the life of a North Korean soldier. Also, an American soldier is less than impressed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702223000 +0000" stop="20250702230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Preventive Medicine</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E22</episode-num>
    <desc>On a sub-note, Klinger plays the part of a voodoo practitioner to try and get out of the Army.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702230000 +0000" stop="20250702233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Night At Rosie's</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A typical day in the life of Rosie's bar, complete with AWOL problem drinkers, a bound and gagged Winchester and a gambling scheme.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250702233000 +0000" stop="20250703000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Ain't Love Grand</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E24</episode-num>
    <desc>The impossible happens for the snobbish Charles when he shares an emotional experience with Klinger, who discovers a US nurse, Debbie, finds him and his bizarre attire attractive, while Charles succumbs to the exotic charms of a Korean girl, called Sooni, who he meets at Rosie's Bar.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703000000 +0000" stop="20250703003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Pageant</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Aunt Bee gets the lead role in the Centennial Pageant as Lady Mayberry. She is, however, not up to the challenge, and Andy must find a way to tell her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703003000 +0000" stop="20250703010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Darling Baby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Darlings come to Mayberry looking for a boy whom they could engage to Charlene's new baby. Opie becomes the prime target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703010000 +0000" stop="20250703013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Cat Burglar</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The city of Beverly Hills is on alert because a cat burglar is on the loose. Elly is worried that this person will steal her cats and kittens, since he is a "cat" burglar. And Jane and Drysdale are worried that the Clampetts will get robbed, since they are prime targets. The cat burglar shows up at the Clampett mansion, posing as a detective to check the place out. Elly shows him the traps she has set. Mike and Bernie, the burglars, decide the caper here will be easy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703013000 +0000" stop="20250703020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Unconventional Behavior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E33</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed handcuffs himself to Ralph on their way to the Raccoon convention.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703020000 +0000" stop="20250703023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Hogan, Go Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan is ordered home and Colonel Crittendon is sent to replace him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703023000 +0000" stop="20250703030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Sticky Wicket Newkirk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Newkirk unknowingly sneaks a beautiful Gestapo agent he has fallen for into camp.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703030000 +0000" stop="20250703033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Nice Place To Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E28</episode-num>
    <desc>After being shot to death, a gangster finds himself in a place where he gets everything his heart desires.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703033000 +0000" stop="20250703043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Hateful Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Young cop Jimmy Anderson and his veteran partner come across a robbery at the Wilson Plastics Company while on patrol one night. His partner killed in the ensuing shootout, evidence then points to Jimmy as having been an accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703043500 +0000" stop="20250703050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dog</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A purse-snatching dog? This is the case Friday and Gannon must solve. Making things more difficult, victims give different descriptions of the four-legged thief.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703050500 +0000" stop="20250703053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Killed The Count (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Scotland Yard Inspector Davidson continues in his investigation of the murder of Count Mattoni. As he continues to wade trough the suspects, Davidson discovers that each not only appears guilty, but also that many readily admit to having committed the crime."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703053500 +0000" stop="20250703060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>I Killed The Count (part 3)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Scotland Yard Inspector Davidson discovers who killed Count Mattoni. Due to a legal loophole, however, the killer cannot be tried."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703060500 +0000" stop="20250703070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The World Between</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Peggy is a patient in the same hospital as the African premier, who was admitted under disguise for unknown reasons.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703070500 +0000" stop="20250703080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hear No Evil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Reporter Molly Stoner needs the help of her friend Frank Cannon. The police wants to take her in coercive detention. Molly affirms that infamous gangster Benje Canto has been murdered. Yet her source cannot be revealed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703080500 +0000" stop="20250703090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Killer On Campus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby probes the supposed suicide of a college professor who had been the victim of his student's pranks.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703090000 +0000" stop="20250703093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Shooting</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A police officer is shot while making a routine check on a pair of paroled convicts parked near a liquor store.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703093000 +0000" stop="20250703100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Hit And Run Driver</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon use newspapers, radio and TV to publicize their clues to the identity of a hit-and-run driver.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703100000 +0000" stop="20250703103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizens All</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed deal with a surly victim of a purse snatching and search for her assailant, who is driving a vehicle that should be easy to spot. In the meantime, they surveil a disabled vehicle with a suspicious driver, respond to a loud music call at a residence that's been transformed into a hippie party house by its recently widowed owner, and break up a fist fight at a lunch stand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703103000 +0000" stop="20250703110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Princess And The Pig</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and reed report to a disturbance at a night club caused by a young folk singer whose career has been derailed by drug addiction and contends that she is being threatened with death by the manager who is a member of a large drug ring. Reed agrees to</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703110000 +0000" stop="20250703120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Throwback Thursday: 1972</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony revisit the year 1972."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703120000 +0000" stop="20250703123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>School Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A school play has Beaver and his classmates assigned parts and Beaver is assigned the role of a canary. However, he doesn't seem to be graceful enough to fly around like a bird. To make matters worse, on the night of the play, Ward's words of encouragement lead to Beaver coming down with a case of stage fright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703123000 +0000" stop="20250703130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Visiting Aunts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally are all excited about going to the carnival; however, Aunt Martha throws a wrench into their plans when she makes an unexpected visit with a friend of hers, forcing Wally and Beaver to count the hours away, hoping she will leave soon enough so they can still go to the carnival.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703130000 +0000" stop="20250703140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Silent Six</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Police Sergeant Dave Wolfe warns Joe Oliver to stay away from his kid sister, Susan. Now Susan's been beaten up in her apartment, Oliver has been shot to death and Dave is being charged with murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703140000 +0000" stop="20250703150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Obsession  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Even from his hospital bed Matlock can't get the case of a TV star accused of killing a therapist out of his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703150000 +0000" stop="20250703160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Leftover Man: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A white supremacist politician plans to have his wife's lover murdered and blame it on black radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703160000 +0000" stop="20250703170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The First Edition</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>John-Boy publishes his first newspaper</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703170000 +0000" stop="20250703173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Worm</sub-title>
    <desc>"A buffalo hunter (Spadden) and his partner Ritchie come to Dodge City causing trouble. Spadden has the reputation for bullying other people and bullying his buffalo skinner, Ritchie. When Jim Cornet's friend is killed in a fight by Spadden, Spadden and Cornet have angry words."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703173000 +0000" stop="20250703180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Badge</sub-title>
    <desc>"While Marshall Matt Dillon is riding alone on a prairie road, he is shot and taken captive by two outlaws who at first wanted his horse."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703180000 +0000" stop="20250703190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady And The Mountain Lion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A shady magician and his identical twin daughters create confusion in Virginia City.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703190000 +0000" stop="20250703193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Matter Of Faith</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Although a drought has forced local cowhands to seek work on a railroad construction project, railroad executives are afraid that their workers will desert them if they believe an old man's claim that he has found a way to make rain.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703193000 +0000" stop="20250703200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Blood Brothers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas McCain gives blood to save a dying man and is surprised by Marshal Torrance's odd behavior toward the man. Then three men arrive from a nearby town and demand custody of the stranger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703200000 +0000" stop="20250703210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Martha Barham Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Flint and a longtime Sioux Indian friend reunite, but trouble is brewing as the Cheyenne are on the warpath and in their way is Fort Hastings, an old flame of Flint's and her new Army captain fiancé.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703210000 +0000" stop="20250703220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Nagging Suspicion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy picks winning horses from the newspaper and Johnny wants to know how he does it. The paramedics rescue a woman who has fallen into a lion’s cage, a dancer in a bar and an adult skateboarder who landed in a cactus patch. They also save a bleeding policeman from a sniper.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703220000 +0000" stop="20250703223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Party</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Talk of a post-war reunion gives B.J. an idea—planning a present-day stateside gathering of 4077th families. He continues to obsess with the idea even under the duress of bug-out instigated by a Chinese breakthrough. Also, Klinger fears that the party will blow his cover, as his mother doesn't know he's stationed in Korea.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703223000 +0000" stop="20250703230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Too Many Cooks</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E01</episode-num>
    <desc>A clumsy foot soldier, "Look Out Below" Conway, finds the quickest way to the crew's heart, boosting morale at the 4077th by cooking gourmet delights. Only Colonel Potter, burdened with a personal crisis, is immune from the high spirits enveloping the hospital.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703230000 +0000" stop="20250703233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Guerilla My Dreams</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The arrival of a wounded Korean woman sparks a conflict at the 4077th: Hawkeye wants to heal her, but a steely ROK officer, Lt. Park, is more anxious to "question" her about alleged guerilla activities.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250703233000 +0000" stop="20250704000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>On leave in Tokyo, Radar is desperately needed back at the crisis-stricken 4077th, but his return is delayed by outside events. While casualties continue to pour in from the front, the 4077th's generator conks out, and the backup has been stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704000000 +0000" stop="20250704003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy And Helen Have Their Day</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Helen are having a hard time finding quality time together, so Barney volunteers to take over for a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704003000 +0000" stop="20250704010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Three Wishes For Opie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Barney acquires some fortune-telling cards and a secret box. The cards promise magical occurrences, and when his wish is granted, he becomes convinced that the box has mystical powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704010000 +0000" stop="20250704013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Chicken</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>After Granny mistakes an ostrich that Drysdale owns for a giant chicken, which she believes she caused by means of her "growing tonic" made for tomatoes, she tries to shrink it down to size and keep it a secret. She never does succeed in shrinking it back down to normal, so in the end Granny decides to enter this giant bird in the county fair.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704013000 +0000" stop="20250704020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Safety Award</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E34</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph has an accident on his way to receiving his Safest Bus Driver Award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704020000 +0000" stop="20250704023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>War Takes A Holiday</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>In order to get the Gestapo to release its prisoners, Hogan tricks Klink and Hochstetter into thinking the war is over.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704023000 +0000" stop="20250704030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Duel Of Honor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan prepares Klink to flee to Argentina with information for the Allies after Klink is challenged to a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704030000 +0000" stop="20250704033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nightmare As A Child</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A schoolteacher finds a strange and very serious little girl on the stairs outside her apartment. The girl seems to know her, and tries to jog her memory about a man she saw earlier that day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704033000 +0000" stop="20250704043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dodging Domino</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Phil Schuyler is a two-bit songwriter who comes to a bad end on Halloween night. Someone enters his bungalow while Phil is taking a bath and tosses an electric heater into his tub.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704043500 +0000" stop="20250704050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Pyramid Swindle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>A female con-artist uses an evangelistic approach to lure buyers into her pyramid scheme. The Bunco division can't charge her with false advertising, so they prosecute her for operating a lottery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704050500 +0000" stop="20250704053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>One More Mile To Go</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>With the dead body of his wife in the trunk of his car, a man is hassled by police for a burnt-out taillight.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704053500 +0000" stop="20250704060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Vicious Circle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>A hit man has to choose between his childhood sweetheart and obeying his boss.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704060500 +0000" stop="20250704070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Sunburst</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix searches for the identity of the murdering punks who held him hostage in a desert diner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704070500 +0000" stop="20250704080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>The Endangered Species</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill Coates, Cannon's old friend, a boat builder, finds himself charged in his son's hunting-accident death. Unbeknown to Coates his lawyer is the man behind the homicide.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704080500 +0000" stop="20250704090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Valentine, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>A murderer is sending valentines to his victims before killing them - and Betty may be the next target.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704090000 +0000" stop="20250704093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Bookie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday goes undercover with the department's chaplain in order to bust a gambling ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704093000 +0000" stop="20250704100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Subscription Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday learns about a scam artist with a novel twist: he uses an authentic Congressional Medal of Honor to solicit magazine subscriptions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704100000 +0000" stop="20250704103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Tip</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bandits using tear gas and a unique escape route rob an armored truck at a savings and loan."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704103000 +0000" stop="20250704110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Parole Violator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy is told that the best player on the recreational league basketball team he coaches has begun using narcotics again, which he flatly denies despite evidence to the contrary. He and Reed also search for a hit-and-run driver who struck a child, and pull over a driver with a seemingly disrespectful and wanted passenger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704110000 +0000" stop="20250704120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The T.i.w.m.</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill auditions for the newest teen drama."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704120000 +0000" stop="20250704123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Wally's Present</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally decides that he is going to have a birthday party, and Beaver jumps to the conclusion that he won't be invited. While shopping for Wally's present, Larry talks Beaver into spending his money on a bow and arrow set for himself and buying a cheap gift for Wally.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704123000 +0000" stop="20250704130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>The Grass Is Always Greener</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver and Wally make friends with the garbage man's kids, Chris and Pete. They quickly learn that they take for granted what they have. Simple things like just having a yard to play in leave Chris and Pete in awe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704130000 +0000" stop="20250704140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fugitive Fraulein</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason and Della travel behind the Iron Curtain and get involved in a murder case, which ends up being tried in an East German court.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704140000 +0000" stop="20250704150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Body  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a woman after she's accused of murdering an aerobics instructor who slept with her husband.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704150000 +0000" stop="20250704160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>The Leftover Man: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E17</episode-num>
    <desc>A white supremacist politician plans to have his wife's lover murdered and blame it on black radicals.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704160000 +0000" stop="20250704170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Vigil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Grandma is sick and Mary Ellen misdiagnosis the ailment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704170000 +0000" stop="20250704173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Distant Drummer</sub-title>
    <desc>"Raffie Bligh comes to Dodge with his drum. Grade makes Raffie play his drum. Sloate &amp; Grade corner Raffie in the stable and make him crawl on a rafter to get his drum. When Grade is found dead everyone thinks Raffie did it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704173000 +0000" stop="20250704180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Ben Tolliver's Stud</sub-title>
    <desc>"Ben Tolliver quits working Jake Creed. Ben’s in love with Jake’s daughter Nancy. Jake accuses Ben of stealing one of his stud horses."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704180000 +0000" stop="20250704190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Five Candles</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Ben and three others are trapped when the floor of the courthouse collapses—and one of the men may be a murderer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704190000 +0000" stop="20250704193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger At Night</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E36</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark's finding the body of a murder victim starts Lucas, his friend, Artemus, and Marshal Torrance on a search for the killer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704193000 +0000" stop="20250704200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Raid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E37</episode-num>
    <desc>When renegade Apaches wound Lucas and kidnap Mark, Marshal Torrance joins with U.S. Marshal Sam Buckhart to form a rescue posse.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704200000 +0000" stop="20250704210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Cappy Darrin Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Old salt Cappy Darrin is on the train with his orphaned grandson, Tuck. Cappy's daughter granted custody of Tuck to his uncle, but as their parting nears Cappy finds he is reluctant to let Tuck go.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704210000 +0000" stop="20250704220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Communication Gaffe</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Roy and Joanne go on a TV quiz show. Roy and John respond to a holdup where both a policeman and a suspect have been shot, and another officer gives them a hard time over treating the suspect. A woman brings in her abused son for treatment. A man inhales too much nitrous oxide. The paramedics treat a boy suffering an allergic reaction to a bee sting. A pickup carrying kerosene collides with a station wagon and starts a brushfire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704220000 +0000" stop="20250704223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Good-bye Radar: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>As company clerk Radar O'Reilly reluctantly prepares to depart the 4077th, the unit is still without electricity due to a broken generator, and the operating room continues to fill up with war wounded as night falls.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704223000 +0000" stop="20250704230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Period Of Adjustment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger and B.J. both have Radar-related woes, causing them to go on a drinking binge. A drunken B.J. becomes violent with Hawkeye.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704230000 +0000" stop="20250704233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Nurse Doctor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful and ambitious young nurse, Harris, who plans to become a doctor when she leaves the Army, finds herself in a misunderstanding with Father Mulcahy. Meanwhile, the camp's water supply is depleted, and the rest of the 4077th is more concerned about where their next shower will come from.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250704233000 +0000" stop="20250705000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Private Finance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A South Korean woman misinterprets Klinger's motives when he tries to help her daughter financially. Meanwhile, Hawkeye wrestles with his conscience over a promise made to a dying soldier, Eddie Hastings.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705000000 +0000" stop="20250705003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Otis Sues The County</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Otis slips and falls in the Mayberry jail, he meets an opportunistic lawyer who convinces him to sue the county.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705003000 +0000" stop="20250705010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Barney Fife, Realtor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy lectures Opie about the importance of informing a potential buyer of the true condition of the item being sold. Meanwhile, Barney decides to dabble in the real estate field.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705010000 +0000" stop="20250705013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Sonny Drysdale Returns</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny predicts that Elly will get married, but Jed doesn’t believe her. However, when Jethro tells them Sonny Drysdale is returning, Granny believes that this will be Jed’s future son-in-law. Drysdale believes the same thing, and has Sonny and Elly set up to be married. Drysdale makes Sonny get a job, selling beauty products door-to-door.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705013000 +0000" stop="20250705020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Mind Your Own Business</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E35</episode-num>
    <desc>Ed sells irons after Ralph's advice got him fired from the sewer. When Ed lies about how much money he's making so that the Kramdens don't feel bad, Ralph considers selling irons, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705020000 +0000" stop="20250705023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Axis Annie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to use a propaganda radio announcer to get information to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705023000 +0000" stop="20250705030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>What Time Does The Balloon Go Up?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A basket-weaving and a kite-flying contest are part of Hogan's plan to transport an agent to England in a balloon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705030000 +0000" stop="20250705033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Stop At Willoughby</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E30</episode-num>
    <desc>Riding home from work on a train, a stressed-out man falls asleep and dreams it is 1880 and he is entering a small town called Willoughby.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705033000 +0000" stop="20250705043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unsuitable Uncle</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E07</episode-num>
    <desc>An unscrupulous uncle, who is in reality the father of his niece, returns home from the sea seeking money from the sale of oil leases on his land. When the man is found murdered, his shipmate is charged with the crime.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705043500 +0000" stop="20250705050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Phony Police Racket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon investigate a scam involving a phony LAPD newsletter, which comes with a card for subscribers entitling the bearer to preferential treatment from the police.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705050500 +0000" stop="20250705053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Three Dreams Of Findlater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A husband dreams constantly of a beautiful woman who prompts him to kill his wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705053500 +0000" stop="20250705060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Night The World Ended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>A group of newspapermen plays a joke on a man who in return decides to get payback.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705060500 +0000" stop="20250705070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>To Cage A Sea Gull</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The site of a helicopter accident uncovers the body of a member of the Nazi party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705070500 +0000" stop="20250705080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Nobody Beats The House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E13</episode-num>
    <desc>Cannon faces a mob kingpin threatening the life of a gambler's wife. Toby Hauser has accumulated 200,000 dollars in game debts. When he hides away his wife asks Cannon for help. Toby wants to put everything on a map. This game should be his last. Either he wins, or he dies.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705080500 +0000" stop="20250705090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Duet For Danger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>The two amateur singers that Barnaby put in jail escape and head for Nashville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705090000 +0000" stop="20250705093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>The Umquaw Strip</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Railroad executive Homer Bedloe believes he has found a loophole in getting the Cannonball shut down: a Native American tribe may have a land claim to an area in which the tracks cross.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705093000 +0000" stop="20250705100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>As Hooterville Goes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A new automatic voting machine in Crabtree Corners may end Hooterville's record as the first community in the state to file election returns.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705100000 +0000" stop="20250705103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Ballet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Mrs. Drysdale gets Jed to back the Beverly Hills Ballet Company, and Jed figures that ballet is the perfect way to keep Granny, who is tired of getting “butler sassed,” among other things, in Beverly Hills. Jed gets her interested in the dance just as Mrs. Drysdale gets the money she needs to save the ballet company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705103000 +0000" stop="20250705110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Sam Drucker's Visit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts return from giving up J.C. Enterprises, and Granny gets a telegram saying that Sam Drucker, who won a trip to Hollywood, is going to visit, thinking he is coming to propose. When he arrives, she tries to get him to believe she is the goddess of the handsome Hollywood actors, as does Jethro, who doesn’t want Granny to move to Hooterville.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705110000 +0000" stop="20250705113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>Popeye For President, Weight For Me, Matinee Idol Popeye, Barbecue For Two</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye and Bluto run for President against each other., Popeye and Brutus return from six months at sea to find a very different Olive., Brutus is an egotistical French director making a film about Antony and Cleopatra, starring Popeye and Olive Oyl., Popeye's BBQ for two with  is interrupted by everyone else."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705113000 +0000" stop="20250705120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Brothers Carry-mouse-off, Goldilocks And The Three Bears, Jerry-go-round</sub-title>
    <desc>"Jerry uses radar to avoid any traps Tom has set up for him using food. Eventually Tom tries to dress up like a female mouse to trap Jerry but he is foiled when other cats chase him., Papa bear is a bit accident prone and somewhat cowardly in this version of the classic tale., Jerry helps out an injured elephant at the circus and the two work together to stop Tom from bothering them."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705120000 +0000" stop="20250705130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Wrestling Wrecks, Ski-napper, Witty Kitty, Private Eye Pooch, Case Of The Cold Storage Yegg, Three Lazy Mice, Hot Noon Or 12 O'clock For Sure</sub-title>
    <desc>"Woody heckles at a wrestling match and ends up in the ring with the champ., Chilly tries to borrow coal from a ski resort where Smedley is working. When Smedley refuses, Chilly uses skis for tinder instead., Doc tries to claim a turkey he won in a raffle, only to discover the raffle was a con, and the prize is guarded by a watchdog named Cecil., After escaping a taxidermists' office, Woody is pursued by Strongnose the Bloodhound, who is supposed to bring him back to be stuffed., Inspector Willoughby follows bank robber Yeggs Benedict around the world in an attempt to capture him., Three lazy mice try to get out of working by claiming to be blind., Woody is a piano player in the Old West. When Buzz Buzzard comes into town to kill the sheriff, the sheriffs ask Woody to take over and catch him."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705130000 +0000" stop="20250705140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Hare We Go, Old Glory, Buckaroo Bugs, By Word Of Mouse, The Cat's Bah, Yankee Doodle Bugs</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs accompanies Christopher Columbus to search for America. , Porky learns about the importance of the Pledge of Allegiance from the spirit of Uncle Sam and gets a complete history lesson., The masked marauder strikes again! A local dopey-hero is hired to catch the villain. Bugs gives the hero a hard time until he realizes that the masked marauder is Bugs! , A foreigner mouse comes to America and is amazed by its economic system. He goes to a mouse professor who explains how it works while they are being chased by Sylvester. , Pepe is in search of a female, American tourist skunk to take back to the Casbah. The, unfortunate, object of his desire is a female cat who accidentally had paint make a stripe on her back., Bugs gives his nephew pointers on early American history, writing himself into about half of the events. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705140000 +0000" stop="20250705150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Undead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>The guys become involved with a voodoo ceremony and the walking dead as they try to track down a missing scientist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705150000 +0000" stop="20250705160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Felizia Kingdom Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Tough as nails Felizia Kingdom controls an enormous amount of land by force, and no one is good enough to inherit the responsibility. When Flint handles her henchmen with ease, she decides he's the man for the job.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705160000 +0000" stop="20250705170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>The Great Safe Robbery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Three comically inept brothers try hard to crack a railroad safe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705170000 +0000" stop="20250705173000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>No Chip</sub-title>
    <desc>"Hutch Dolan and his brothers cause trouble by putting their cattle on Jeff Mossman’s land. They cause more trouble but pouring flour onto Pete, Jeff’s son. When Jeff confronts the Dolan’s with a gun, Hutch shoots him. With Jeff in town at Doc's the Dolan's ride back to Mossman's ranch."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705173000 +0000" stop="20250705180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Wave</sub-title>
    <desc>"Gus Mather comes into Dodge and throws a big wake for a man named Orson Boggs Doc and Chester are suspicious of this whole wake situation, but Chester and Doc attend the wake nonetheless and partake of the free drinks. When Matt comes back to Dodge from his business trip, Chester informs Matt on what has been going on . Matt also thinks something strange is going on as well."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705180000 +0000" stop="20250705190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Wish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hoss gets a taste of racism when he helps a black family get their farm in working order.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705190000 +0000" stop="20250705193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Outlaw's Inheritance</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E38</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas is the town's representative to the railroad commission until an infamous train robber dies and leaves his ill-gotten wealth to him. Lucas must clear his name and stop the reckless ambition of his replacement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705193000 +0000" stop="20250705200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Boomerang</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E39</episode-num>
    <desc>When a rancher dies after the bank forecloses the mortgage on his property, his son blames the banker for his father's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705200000 +0000" stop="20250705210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Deadhorse: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Town boss Jud Hammerklein remains confident that he will never be executed, despite the feverish activity of the hangman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705210000 +0000" stop="20250705213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>Helen Of Abajinian</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>An Armenian winemaker hires Paladin to find his runaway daughter and break up her ill-considered romance with a cowhand.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705213000 +0000" stop="20250705220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>Breakout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Josh in a federal prison plotting the great escape? The government employs Randall to portray an escaped prisoner in order to trick his cellmate into leading authorities to the $50,000 he stole and stashed away in a secret location.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250705220000 +0000" stop="20250706000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>Three Missing Links, Rockin Through The Rockies, G.i. Wanna Go Home, Merry Mavericks, Corny Casanovas, Uncivil War Birds</sub-title>
    <desc>"Larry, Moe and Curly go on a location to Africa when Curly is cast as a gorilla, and there they come face to face with danger when they encounter a real gorilla on the set.  , The Stooges are frontier guides leading a minstrel show west.  When hostile Indians run the horses run off they are stranded.  They must contend with a snowstorm and a marauding bear as well the Indians.  After almost killing each other ice fishing they solve their problems by rigging up a sail on the wagon and sailing west. , The Stooges are civil war soldiers who are constantly changing uniforms to avoid the opposing armies.  Eventually they decide to be loyal to the south, but remain disguised as Union soldiers.  Curly is detected as a spy, but Moe and Larry prevent his execution.  The boys escape with a secret map and marry their three southern belles. , The Stooges are discharged from the army and go to see their fiancées, but find they have been dispossessed and the wedding is off until they find a home.  The boys have trouble finding a vacant apartment so they set up housekeeping in a vacant lot.  Their housing problems seem to be solved until a farmer destroys their new home with a tractor.  The Stooges then build a house of their own, but the girls aren't impressed with the one room mansion and walk out on them. , Set in the old west, the Stooges are mistaken for lawmen and manage to capture a gang of crooks.  The boys then get the job of guarding some money in an old house reputed to be haunted by the ghost of an Indian Chief.  The crooks escape and go after the money disguised as ghosts, but Shemp, disguised as the Indian Chief, manages to knock them out. , Love is in the air for these laughable Lotharios. The Stooges all romance the same gold-digging gal with hilarious results.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706000000 +0000" stop="20250706023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Vampire</sub-title>
    <desc>"When an errant bomb unearths the coffin of a vampire during the London Blitz, a gravedigger unknowingly reanimates the monster by removing the stake from his heart."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706023000 +0000" stop="20250706030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>When The Rat's Away, The Mice Will Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>The Riddler blackmails Commissioner Gordon: unless he's paid $1 million dollars, he'll destroy The Queen of Freedom Monument along with King Boris.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706030000 +0000" stop="20250706040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>Where No Man Has Gone Before</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>While exploring the edge of the galaxy, the Enterprise encounters an energy barrier that gives two crewmen godlike powers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706040000 +0000" stop="20250706043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Through The Time Barrier</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Twiddle invents a time machine which takes Jimmy, Lois, Clark and a thug back 50,000 years.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706043000 +0000" stop="20250706050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>The Talking Clue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Inspector's son is collecting sounds with a tape machine and records a safe being opened. When two crooks use the tape to their advantage, the son becomes an unwitting accomplice.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706050000 +0000" stop="20250706060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>There Were Giants In The Earth</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Professor Robinson discovers that the planet they are on will travel further from the sun. In an attempt to survive the Robinsons pack up and head south. Dr Smith stays at the Jupiter 2 while the Robinson family encounters a terrifying cyclops and an ancient deserted city.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706060000 +0000" stop="20250706070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>The Phantom Strikes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Havoc is wrought aboard the Seaview, as it is nearly destroyed by a phantom sub and its ghostly captain who seeks to reincarnate himself through Commander Crane.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706070000 +0000" stop="20250706080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Rescue</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The Earthlings inadvertently cause a cave-in that traps two giant children, and Steve and Dan volunteer their services to Kobick to help rescue the children.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250706080000 +0000" stop="20250706090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Massacre</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>The time travelers try to save themselves from the massacre of Custer's Seventh Cavalry.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
