<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd"><tv generator-info-name="www.matthuisman.nz">
  <channel id="metv">
    <display-name>MeTV</display-name>
    <icon src="https://new.mjh.nz/.images/metv.png"/>
  </channel>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719070500 +0000" stop="20250719080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Press Pass To The Slammer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Tim Jardine was persuaded by his friends Amy and Claude to blackmail his father for 50,000 dollars. Nevertheless, Jardine's father is facing bankruptcy and Claude loses his patience and becomes a criminal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719080500 +0000" stop="20250719090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Captives, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E08</episode-num>
    <desc>A runaway housewife gets involved with a gang of thieves plotting an armored-car heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719090000 +0000" stop="20250719093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Betty Jo's Pen Pal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Betty Jo's Japanese pen pal, Nobuko, comes for a visit to the U.S. and stays at the Shady Rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719093000 +0000" stop="20250719100000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Bedloe's Nightmare</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>A psychiatrist suggests that Homer Bedloe learns to love the Cannonball in order to stop the recent nightmares he has been experiencing about the engine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719100000 +0000" stop="20250719103000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Hills Of Home</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E02</episode-num>
    <desc>The Clampetts head home to the Ozarks with the goal of getting Elly May married before Elverna Bradshaw's daughter does. And with the Silver Dollar Fair about to start, they believe they'll be able to meet a lot of young, single men. Granny has something else going on besides getting Elly a husband: she is fighting with her enemy, Elverna Bradshaw, and betting her granddaughter will marry before Elverna’s daughter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719103000 +0000" stop="20250719110000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jane Finds Elly A Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny continues her search to get a man for Elly, though fears her mission might be harder with Elly having entered the cake-baking contest. Back at the mansion, Jethro becomes restless in Beverly Hills and decides to join his family in the hills, especially after hearing about the fair going on. Miss Jane comes along, being told by Drysdale to keep her watch on the family and not to let Elly get serious about a man.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719110000 +0000" stop="20250719113000 +0000">
    <title>Popeye and Pals</title>
    <sub-title>My Pop, My Pop, Pre-hysterical Man, I Eats My Spinach</sub-title>
    <desc>"Popeye is building a boat when his daddy, Poopdeck Pappy, insists on helping., Olive Oyl discovers a caveman and dinosaur in Yellowstone Park., At the rodeo, Bluto sets his sights on Olive."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719113000 +0000" stop="20250719120000 +0000">
    <title>The Tom and Jerry Show</title>
    <sub-title>Advance And Be Mechanized, The Lost Chick, Haunted Mouse</sub-title>
    <desc>"Tom is a space security guard and he uses his cat robot to chase Jerry's mouse robot as it attempts to sneak some cheese out of the Mining Facility., Two squirrels find an egg that rolled away from the mother hen's nest and when it hatches they do their best to try and take care of the chick., Jerry’s Uncle comes to visit him and, along with freeing some animals Tom has eaten, causes all kinds of havoc for the cat."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719120000 +0000" stop="20250719130000 +0000">
    <title>The Woody Woodpecker Show</title>
    <sub-title>Tragic Magic, Tricky Trout, Broadway Bow Wows, Fair Weather Fiends, Kiddie Koncert, Kittens' Mittens, Kiddie League</sub-title>
    <desc>"A magician tries to get revenge on Woody for heckling his act by asking him to assist with some tricks. However, Woody turns the table on the magician by casting his own magic spell on him., Chilly tries to steal trout from a trout hatchery run by Wally Walrus., John the showbiz dog leaves his fiancee and their double act for another woman only to return to her when her solo act is more successful than his., A storm strands Woody and Wolfie on a deserted island, and they battle each other to find food., Wally conducts a whimsical animal band., Three kittens blame their lost mittens on a vagabond cat, who will bear the punishment if they don't tell the truth., Woody's Kiddle League Baseball team is in the championships and antic ensue."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719130000 +0000" stop="20250719140000 +0000">
    <title>Bugs Bunny and Friends</title>
    <sub-title>Rabbit Transit, A Tale Of Two Mice, Daffy Duck Hunt, Falling Hare, The Crackpot Quail, Hare-way To The Stars</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bugs and Cecil Turtle decide to have their own "tortoise and the hare" race. , Babbit and Catstello try to steal some cheese from under the nose of the house cat. , Porky goes hunting with his dog. They encounter a completely wacky Daffy, who dodges all Porky's bullets and breaks into a can-can dance. , A gremlin hijacks a WWII bomber and Bugs must stop him before the gremlin does some serious damage. , A goofy dog decides to go off hunting for quails. He runs into a wise-guy quail similar to Bugs Bunny -- who gives him similar trouble. , Suffering from a rabbit-hangover, Bugs accidentally climbs onto a rocket ship and is taken to Marvin the Martian's home. "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719140000 +0000" stop="20250719150000 +0000">
    <title>The Wild Wild West</title>
    <sub-title>The Night Of The Simian Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A visit to the plantation of a U.S. Senator reveals a mysterious family past that intersects with a doctor infamous for his experiments with apes. The agents are lucky enough to arrive just as the Senator's forgotten giant son and his friend, a giant ape, are rampaging through the plantation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719150000 +0000" stop="20250719160000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Ricky And Laura Bell Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Laurie and Ricky Bell uproot and go west, leaving their comforts in Baltimore. When Laurie announces she is pregnant, Ricky is less than happy as he feels she has just made their lives more complicated, especially where it concerns his needs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719160000 +0000" stop="20250719170000 +0000">
    <title>The Big Valley</title>
    <sub-title>Last Stage To Salt Flats</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Stage passengers, including Victoria, Jarrod and Heath, are abandoned in the middle of the desert by robbers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719170000 +0000" stop="20250719180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>All That</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher tries to save his property from foreclosure.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719180000 +0000" stop="20250719190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of A Lynching</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Will Griner is acquitted of a murder after two key witnesses disappear before the trial. When a bloodthirsty lynch mob comes after him, thinking that he silenced the witnesses, Griner goes to the Cartwrights for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719190000 +0000" stop="20250719193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Heller</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>After foiling a girl's attempt to rob the general store, Lucas finds that she and her brother are plotting the murder of their abusive stepfather.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719193000 +0000" stop="20250719200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Grasshopper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A condemned killer being transported by train murders a marshal and takes Mark hostage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719200000 +0000" stop="20250719210000 +0000">
    <title>Rawhide</title>
    <sub-title>Incident At Seven Fingers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E30</episode-num>
    <desc>A black Army sergeant, being pursued by the Army on cowardice and desertion charges, joins Favor's trail drive. The troopers finally catch up to him, but Favor wonders how such a decent and competent person could be guilty of those charges.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719210000 +0000" stop="20250719213000 +0000">
    <title>Have Gun, Will Travel</title>
    <sub-title>The Reasonable Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher having a dispute with his foster son hires Paladin to keep one of them from killing the other in a duel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719213000 +0000" stop="20250719220000 +0000">
    <title>Wanted Dead or Alive</title>
    <sub-title>The Hostage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Who needs enemies with friends like the residents of Rogue City? The townsfolk celebrate Randall for bringing in notorious killer Jumbo Kane, but just as quickly turn on him when Kane breaks loose and demands a hostage to ensure his escape.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250719220000 +0000" stop="20250720000000 +0000">
    <title>The Three Stooges</title>
    <sub-title>A Ducking They Did Go, A Plumbing We Will Go, Scrambled Brains, Rip, Sew, And Stitch, Horses' Collars, I'll Never Heil Again</sub-title>
    <desc>"After recruiting the police chief, governor and mayor into what turns out to be a sham duck hunting club, the Stooges cleverly find a way to avoid jail.  , To escape the police, the Stooges pose as plumbers and are hired to fix a leak in a fancy mansion.  They wind up crossing the electrical system with the plumbing and generally ruin the place.  One memorable scene has the lady of the house tuning into a television broadcast from Niagara Falls as a torrent of water pours from the set.  To escape the wrath of the homeowners the Stooges escape through a magician's trap door. , A follow up to "You Natzy Spy", the Stooges have taken over the country of Moronica.  Moe is Hailstone the Dictator, Curly is a Field Marshall and Larry is Minister of Propaganda.  The Stooges are planning with their allies to conquer the world, which mainly consists of fighting over a globe.  The former king's daughter gets into their headquarters and plants a bomb, which Curly detonates.  All ends well as the king regains control of the country and the Stooges wind up as trophies on the wall. , Shemp is a sick man, suffering from hallucinations.  His worst vision is that his ugly nurse Nora is actually beautiful.  When Moe and Larry come to take him home from the sanitarium, they discover he's become engaged to Nora.  On the way to Nora's apartment for the wedding, the boys get in a fight with a stranger who promises to get even with them if he ever sees them again.  They arrive to finding Nora waiting for her father, who, when he arrives, turns out to be the man they just fought with. , The Stooges run a tailor shop and need money to pay their creditors.  A bank robber leaves his coat in the shop with a combination to a safe.  When the crook comes back to retrieve the coat, the Stooges capture him and get his bankroll. , The Stooges are private detectives in the old West trying to help a girl recover an IOU from a bad guy.   "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720000000 +0000" stop="20250720023000 +0000">
    <title>Svengoolie</title>
    <sub-title>The Black Cat ('34)</sub-title>
    <desc>"Honeymooning in Hungary, Joan and Peter Allison share their train compartment with Dr. Vitus Verdegast, a courtly but tragic man who is returning to the remains of the town he defended before becoming a prisoner of war for fifteen years. When their hotel-bound bus crashes in a mountain storm and Joan is injured, the travellers seek refuge in the home, built fortress-like upon the site of a bloody battlefield, of famed architect Hjalmar Poelzig. There, cat-phobic Verdegast learns his wife's fate, grieves for his lost daughter, and must play a game of chess for Allison's life."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720023000 +0000" stop="20250720030000 +0000">
    <title>Batman</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Goes To School</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Joker attempts to recruit high school dropouts for his gang, it's up to Batman and Dick Grayson to teach the students to make better choices.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720030000 +0000" stop="20250720040000 +0000">
    <title>Star Trek</title>
    <sub-title>The Enemy Within</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A transporter malfunction causes Captain Kirk to split into his "good" and "evil" selves, and a landing party will freezes to death if they don't merge the two back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720040000 +0000" stop="20250720043000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Great Caesar's Ghost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Perry White is a key witness in a gangster trial. But on the eve of his testimony, he believes he hears a ghost. Superman must restore the editor's credibility.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720043000 +0000" stop="20250720050000 +0000">
    <title>Adventures of Superman</title>
    <sub-title>Test Of A Warrior</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Superman helps an Indian leader through superhuman ordeals to win the chief's bonnet of the tribe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720050000 +0000" stop="20250720060000 +0000">
    <title>Lost in Space</title>
    <sub-title>Welcome Stranger</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Jimmy Hapgood lands on the planet and the Robinsons befriend him. After helping him fix his spaceship, the Robinsons try and convince him to take Will and Penny back to Earth with him. But Dr. Smith tries to get aboard the ship back to Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720060000 +0000" stop="20250720070000 +0000">
    <title>Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea</title>
    <sub-title>Graveyard Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>The Seaview is nearly destroyed by a giant Portuguese man o' war when a scientist tries to force Nelson and Crane to retrieve youth serum data from his sunken research ship.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720070000 +0000" stop="20250720080000 +0000">
    <title>Land of the Giants</title>
    <sub-title>Shell Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E25</episode-num>
    <desc>A deaf boy tracks Fitzhugh to the Spindrift and takes it home to the seafront community where he lives. The Earthlings must recover it, and their only bargaining chip is their advanced knowledge with which they can build a hearing aid for the boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720080000 +0000" stop="20250720090000 +0000">
    <title>The Time Tunnel</title>
    <sub-title>Reign Of Terror</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>In Paris during the French Revolution, the time travelers agree to aid Marie Antoinette in exchange for safe-conduct passes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720090000 +0000" stop="20250720100000 +0000">
    <title>The Invaders</title>
    <sub-title>The Enemy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman discovers an injured alien.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720100000 +0000" stop="20250720110000 +0000">
    <title>The Life and Times of Grizzly Adams</title>
    <sub-title>The Fugitive</sub-title>
    <desc>"Adams saves a man, Will Boker, from drowning. Will states he lost his possessions by the river. Adams goes back but finds a lot of money in a carpetbag. He questions Will, who says he came by it accidentally - or did he really?"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720110000 +0000" stop="20250720113000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>King Of Beasts</sub-title>
    <desc>"Comparisons and contrasts are drawn as Marlin and Jim analyze the behavior of the lion in his natural habitat in Africa and in the zoo."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720113000 +0000" stop="20250720120000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Crater Of Gold</sub-title>
    <desc>"Rivers of fire and erupting volcanoes in British East Africa have created a crater called Ngora Ngora, which shields the great herds of African wildlife from the advances of man.  By plane to the top of the crater and by jeep into the crater, we study one of the truly last strongholds of the wild kingdom."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720120000 +0000" stop="20250720123000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Vanishing With The Wilderness</sub-title>
    <desc>"What happens to the creatures living in the wilderness when their natural habitat is destroyed? Some die out…others move to a new home, and some like the coyote and opossum have journeyed far beyond their original range.  Others move in, attracted by food or by the elimination of their natural enemies.  Camped in a wilderness area on the fringe of civilization, Marlin Perkins explores the why and hows of this cross-migration."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720123000 +0000" stop="20250720130000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Land Of Quaking Earth</sub-title>
    <desc>"In the southeastern coastal plain of the United States in Georgia, there exists one of the world’s truly unique jingle swamps named by the Indians OKEEFENOKEE (land of floating islands).  Here in this intricate maze of river-ways with its ferns, grasses and cane growths, Marlin Perkins and Jim Fowler explore a fairytale jungle that is one of the last strongholds of the alligator.  The jungle suddenly becomes marshland, also called wet prairies, with water 1 to 4 feet deep.  Here in profusion fly hundreds of American egrets, the swamp fisherman.  Jim uses the Indian soap plant to wash his hands, and Marlin tries to balance on one of the floating hammocks or floating islands of “quaking earth.”  We witness the lassoing, from a boat, of a bear that has moved in too close to civilization.  After being caged, he is moved into the interior on an island that can support him, and we follow his encounters with an alligator, a skunk, and an alligator snapping turtle."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720130000 +0000" stop="20250720133000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Trailing The Midnight Sun</sub-title>
    <desc>"Winter is night, summer is day, and you need your wits to survive in the forbidding land north of the Arctic Circle.  In this story you go by walrus skin boat, dogsled, airplane and helicopter.  You hunt seal with Eskimos, find polar bear and beluga whale.  You round up a large herd of reindeer and tag them for conservation officials. And you watch Jim Fowler discover a far-north version of a popular rodeo event:  bulldogging moose from a helicopter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720133000 +0000" stop="20250720140000 +0000">
    <title>Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom</title>
    <sub-title>Winter Comes To Yellowstone</sub-title>
    <desc>"All roads are closed, but by helicopter and snow plane Marlin and Jim travel though the park to uncover a fascinating story of animal life in winter."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720140000 +0000" stop="20250720143000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Eenie, Meenie, Mommy, Daddy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E03</episode-num>
    <desc>Cindy has been cast as in the school play, but learns she can only invite one parent to the show. Torn between whom she should choose, Cindy fakes an injury to get out of being in the play altogether.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720143000 +0000" stop="20250720150000 +0000">
    <title>The Brady Bunch</title>
    <sub-title>Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E04</episode-num>
    <desc>No longer feeling needed around the Brady household, Alice makes up a story about an ailing aunt in Seattle in order to leave. Later the family finds out the truth and launches "Operation Alice" in an attempt to make her stay.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720150000 +0000" stop="20250720153000 +0000">
    <title>Happy Days</title>
    <sub-title>The Cunningham Caper</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E14</episode-num>
    <desc>An ill Richie is home alone while the rest of the family go to see Cinerama. Hearing noises downstairs, he investigates and finds a burglar!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720153000 +0000" stop="20250720160000 +0000">
    <title>Laverne &amp; Shirley</title>
    <sub-title>Dog Day Blind Dates</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E06</episode-num>
    <desc>When Laverne and Shirley unwittingly double-date with two criminals intent on robbing the bank next to the Pizza Bowl, the girls find themselves being held as hostages.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720160000 +0000" stop="20250720163000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy The Matchmaker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy, trying to lift Barney's spirits, stages a minor robbery and tries to match his deputy with a shy seamstress.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720163000 +0000" stop="20250720170000 +0000">
    <title>I Love Lucy</title>
    <sub-title>Visitor From Italy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Mario, the Ricardos and Mertzes' gondolier in Venice, comes to New York to surprise his brother, Dominic, but turns up at the Ricardos' apartment when he can't find him. Lucy is sure Dominic is in San Francisco and sets out to help Mario raise the bus fare. Her earnest efforts pay off in a surprising way.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720170000 +0000" stop="20250720173000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Most Interesting Character</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E39</episode-num>
    <desc>Miss Landers assigns Beaver's class to write a short essay about the most interesting character they know. While Judy writes about her dad, Beaver debates over whom he should write about. Beaver finally decides to write about Ward, but Beaver isn't sure if Ward is interesting enough.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720173000 +0000" stop="20250720180000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Blind Date Committee</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Wally becomes the chairman of the blind date committee for an upcoming dance. However, Wally quickly wants to resign from the position when he can't find anyone to go with the new girl, Jill Bartlett.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720180000 +0000" stop="20250720183000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Wedding Plans</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E05</episode-num>
    <desc>After Matthew Templeton says he’d be proud to marry Elly, the Clampetts begin to plan and rehearse Elly's wedding. Meanwhile, Drysdale tries to stop this wedding from happening, or at least from losing his largest account. He goes to Silver Dollar City and decides to buy the Bank of Bugtussle so he can still handle his favorite account.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720183000 +0000" stop="20250720190000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Buys Central Park</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S08E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Elly are preparing for the wedding, but a big blow comes when Matthew mentions that he has a wife, and Granny learns he is really a preacher, saying he’d marry Elly because he marries people every day. Meanwhile, con man Shifty Shafer, a.k.a. Honest John, comes to Silver Dollar City and, after hearing how much money they have, he persuades the hillbillies to go to New York with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720190000 +0000" stop="20250720193000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>The Little Dictator</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The exiled president of a revolution-torn country visits the island.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720193000 +0000" stop="20250720200000 +0000">
    <title>Gilligan's Island</title>
    <sub-title>Smile, You're On Mars Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A NASA satellite with a TV camera, accidentally lands on the island instead of the intended target: Mars.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720200000 +0000" stop="20250720203000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>Mama's Layaway Plan  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama is one of only two people at cousin Ludie's funeral, she decides to spend funds meant for a family vacation and bowling competition to ensure a suitable funeral for herself.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720203000 +0000" stop="20250720210000 +0000">
    <title>Mama's Family</title>
    <sub-title>My Phony Valentine  (s5, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Mama claims to have a date for Valentine's Day, Iola hires an escort—and it's painfully obvious that he's an escort.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720210000 +0000" stop="20250720220000 +0000">
    <title>The Love Boat</title>
    <sub-title>The Lady From Laramie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman falls for a paid escort; Gopher learns about a ghost aboard; Vicki aims for sophistication to attract a boy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720220000 +0000" stop="20250720223000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Opie's Charity</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy becomes upset when Opie contributes a measly three cents to the Underprivileged Children's drive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720223000 +0000" stop="20250720230000 +0000">
    <title>Collector's Call</title>
    <sub-title>Andrew Somer- Smurfs</sub-title>
    <desc>"Andrew Somer shares his smurf-tastic Smurf collection, including original Smurf toy prototypes, sentimental pieces from a lifetime of collecting, rare vintage store displays, and more. Expert appraiser John Ragusa attempts to make a “smurfy” trade with Andrew by bringing him something that’s a perfect match for his love of both store displays and Smurf."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720230000 +0000" stop="20250720233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snap Judgment: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E07</episode-num>
    <desc>The military police think they've solved a rash of thefts at the 4077th when they apprehend Klinger with Hawkeye's stolen camera.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250720233000 +0000" stop="20250721000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Snappier Judgment: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E08</episode-num>
    <desc>B.J. and Hawkeye resolve to clear Klinger's name after he chooses Winchester to defend him at his military court-martial.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721000000 +0000" stop="20250721003000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Et Tu, Archie</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie is all excited when an old friend whom he used to work with, Joe Tucker, stops by for a visit. Archie soon discovers that Joe, who has been unemployed for quite some time, is trying to get a job at Archie's plant. Archie soon tries to sabotage Joe's efforts to land a job at the loading dock because he's afraid the man might be in line for his position.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721003000 +0000" stop="20250721010000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Gloria's Boyfriend</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Gloria befriends the box boy, George, who works at the local supermarket and happens to be mentally handicapped. When Archie discovers this, all of his misconceptions come pouring out and he encourages Gloria not to lead him on. Meanwhile, Archie encourages George to take a break at the Bunker's while George is still on the clock. George's father storms over to the Bunker's home with the bad news that George has been fired.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721010000 +0000" stop="20250721013000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Lionel's Engagement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Edith, Mike and Gloria are each extended a special invitation to attend Lionel's engagement party. However, Archie isn't invited, that is until a big argument between Louise and George results in Louise deciding to invite him. Later, during the party, George is in for a big shock when it turns out that Lionel's fiancée, Jennie has interracial parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721013000 +0000" stop="20250721020000 +0000">
    <title>All in the Family</title>
    <sub-title>Archie Eats And Runs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Archie comes home for a nice dinner that Edith has prepared: beef and mushroom stew. Later, when Mike comes to the table for dinner, he finds Archie has completely finished his meal and then breaks the news that there has been a recall at the supermarkets of a certain brand of mushroom. Convinced that he has food poisoning, Archie rushes down to the hospital for treatment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721020000 +0000" stop="20250721023000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Nanette Fabray And Ken Berry</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Nanette Fabray and Ken Berry. Originally aired on 10/12/70."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721023000 +0000" stop="20250721030000 +0000">
    <title>The Carol Burnett Show</title>
    <sub-title>Guests Gwen Verdon And Pat Boone</sub-title>
    <desc>"Guests Gwen Verdon and Pat Boone. Originally aired on 11/03/69."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721030000 +0000" stop="20250721033000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>I Do Not Choose To Run: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Rob is asked to run for city councilman.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721033000 +0000" stop="20250721040000 +0000">
    <title>The Dick Van Dyke Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Making Of A Councilman: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>While running for New Rochelle city councilman, Rob realizes his opponent is much more knowledgeable.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721040000 +0000" stop="20250721043000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Brother Ralph</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph, after making a suggestion at work, is laid off. Alice decides to take a job as a secretary, but tells her boss that Ralph is her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721043000 +0000" stop="20250721053000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Printer's Devil</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E09</episode-num>
    <desc>His newspaper in financial trouble, a man agrees when a stranger appears and offers to pay off the debts and run the linotype machine.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721053000 +0000" stop="20250721060000 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Together</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E15</episode-num>
    <desc>A man is trapped in an office with the body of the woman he just murdered.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721060000 +0000" stop="20250721070000 +0000">
    <title>Mission: Impossible</title>
    <sub-title>The Missile (aka Torpedo)</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The IMF dupe two foreign agents into gathering intelligence on a bogus missile guidance system. However, the mission is interrupted when a psychotic kidnaps Dana.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721070000 +0000" stop="20250721080000 +0000">
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <sub-title>Scapegoat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A man who knew Kimble during one of his disguises, meets him again. He tells him that on one of his hurried, silent departures from a town, he left behind evidence which indicated he was dead and an innocent man is being held for his murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721080000 +0000" stop="20250721090000 +0000">
    <title>Harry O</title>
    <sub-title>Mayday</sub-title>
    <desc>"The fact that Senator John Elton miraculously survived the plane crash and Ellen Nevin's husband (pilot of the plane) was killed, leaves no doubt in her mind: it's murder. She hires private investigator Harry O to prove it."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721090000 +0000" stop="20250721093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Prophet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are convinced that "Brother" William Bentley's Temple of the Expanded Mind is just a sham—a front for Bentley to sell LSD to the students of a nearby elementary school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721093000 +0000" stop="20250721100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Amateur Cop</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Citizens are full of praise for Officer Gideon C. Dengle, wanting to bestow him with awards, honors and home-baked cookies. There's only one problem: there's no such officer in the LAPD.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721100000 +0000" stop="20250721103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 1</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed starts a flu epidemic that decimates the city's police force, forcing him and Malloy to work a double shift. During day watch, he and Malloy encounter a bookmaker being held at gunpoint, mediate a dispute over a cantaloupe, investigate a possible robbery in progress, engage in a foot chase with an athletic young man and pull over a motorist who turns out to be a VIP.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721103000 +0000" stop="20250721110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Clear With A Civilian: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Newly appointed Police Commissioner Edna Dixon accompanies Malloy and Reed on night watch, where they deal with a naked elderly wino at a bar, try to diffuse a possible riot situation following a gang-related stabbing and pursue a deaf teenager in a stolen car.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721110000 +0000" stop="20250721120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Southern Trek</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate the Christmas in July traditions of the Southern Hemisphere... and meet South Pole Santa!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721120000 +0000" stop="20250721123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Bath</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward and June allow Wally to babysit Beaver one evening while they attend a party. However, things go awry when Beaver gets ready to take a bath. He accidentally lets the bathtub overflow, causing the water to leak onto the bathroom floor and into the downstairs ceiling.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721123000 +0000" stop="20250721130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Prize</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>After leaving the cap off the ink, Beaver is grounded to the house for a whole day after spilled ink ruins some of Ward's papers. However, Larry and Beaver sneak out to the movies and when Beaver wins a bike, he must find a way to keep it a secret from his parents.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721130000 +0000" stop="20250721140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Tsarina's Tiara</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E23</episode-num>
    <desc>When a jeweler and gem expert is pulled over for speeding, the corpse of an international jewel thief is found in the trunk.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721140000 +0000" stop="20250721150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Heiress  (s2, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When a troubled young woman is accused of murder, her late father's former business partner hires Matlock to prove her innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721150000 +0000" stop="20250721160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Love Lost</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Lana's ex-boyfriend comes to see her and brings a load of stolen rifles with him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721160000 +0000" stop="20250721170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Rebellion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Another woman begins to play the church organ instead of Grandma which upsets Grandma</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721170000 +0000" stop="20250721180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Long, Long Trail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt accompanies a young woman on a treacherous journey across the desert, where the pair must brave sandstorms, thirst and Indians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721180000 +0000" stop="20250721190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>To Stop A War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Dan Logan is hired as a range detective to stop a cattle rustling outbreak, but when he is framed for murder he needs the help his old friends, the Cartwrights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721190000 +0000" stop="20250721193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>A Time For Singing</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Mark discovers that the new preacher and his wife are impostors planning a robbery.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721193000 +0000" stop="20250721200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Deserter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Lucas and Marshal Torrance get into trouble with the Army when they try to help a wounded young soldier who deserted.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721200000 +0000" stop="20250721210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tom Tuckett Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Ever since he was young, Tom Tuckett has been sent to good schools and looked after by an unknown benefactor. When he joins the wagon train, Tuckett sets out to discover who the mysterious benefactor is—and is shocked when the individual's identity is reveal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721210000 +0000" stop="20250721220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Eater</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>A temporary captain from "the old school" doesn't feel Gage and DeSoto should be practicing "medicine." An elderly man sets his chair on fire. Dr. Early keeps coming up with oranges when all he wants is an apple. The paramedics struggle to save a heart attack victim. A boy with asthma gets trapped in a storm drain. Dr. Brackett uses an old-fashioned sedative on a biker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721220000 +0000" stop="20250721223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>'twas The Day After Christmas</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E09</episode-num>
    <desc>To boost post-yuletide morale on Dec 26, Potter has the officers and enlisted men change places for the day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721223000 +0000" stop="20250721230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Follies Of The Living - Concerns Of The Dead</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While suffering a fever, Klinger communicates with the spirit of a dead soldier, Private Weston, who stays on to witness his own last rites.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721230000 +0000" stop="20250721233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Birthday Girls</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret's birthday plans are spoiled when she and Klinger get stranded on a desolate roadside. Meanwhile, Charles gives a lecture for Margaret, and the surgeons assist in the delivery of a calf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250721233000 +0000" stop="20250722000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Blood And Guts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is outraged when a sensationalistic war correspondent, Clayton Kibbee, reports irresponsible G.I. stunts as tales of military valor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722000000 +0000" stop="20250722003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>A Feud Is A Feud</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy strives to end a long-running feud between two neighboring families.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722003000 +0000" stop="20250722010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Ellie For Council</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Ellie's decision to run for town council sparks a battle of the sexes.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722010000 +0000" stop="20250722013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Party Line</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny and Jethro return to Elly and Jed after visiting Pearl back home. Granny returns with presents and a new device, a telephone. For Granny, this phone is high tech. She gets Jethro to install it, but he installs wrong, connecting wires to a light pole instead of a telephone pole, electrocuting himself, causing it to blow up and making Granny go temporarily deaf.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722013000 +0000" stop="20250722020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Hello, Mom</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E10</episode-num>
    <desc>"Ralph sleeps at the Nortons' to avoid his visiting mother-in-law.  "</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722020000 +0000" stop="20250722023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Missing Klink</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to kidnap Burkhalter to trade him for an underground agent but ends up with Klink.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722023000 +0000" stop="20250722030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Who Stole My Copy Of Mein Kampf?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan plans to eliminate a beautiful allied defector who is giving Klink an award.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722030000 +0000" stop="20250722033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Howling Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E05</episode-num>
    <desc>A man on a walking trip of post-World War I Europe gets caught in a storm. He takes shelter in a remote monastery and finds a mysterious prisoner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722033000 +0000" stop="20250722043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Two-faced Turnabout</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E18</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Balkan dictator with ties to an American businessman dies, the race is on to destroy papers belonging to him that may implicate the businessman in corruption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722043500 +0000" stop="20250722050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722050500 +0000" stop="20250722053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Sylvia</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Sylvia will do anything to get her ex-husband back into her life.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722053500 +0000" stop="20250722060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Motive</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Tommy Greer is a crime buff who decides to commit a motiveless murder in order to confuse the police, selecting his victim from a phone book at random.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722060500 +0000" stop="20250722070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Voices In The Dark</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A former championship diver, now disabled, believes she is going to be murdered after receiving death threats.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722070500 +0000" stop="20250722080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Heritage</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Publisher Quigley asks Cannon for help. He believes that hotel proprietor Rawdon has killed six girls. When the seventh victim is found, however, it's Quigley himself who becomes the prime suspect. A lab assistant manipulates the samples used in the framework of the murders.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722080500 +0000" stop="20250722090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Reincarnation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby looks into a 20-year-old case hoping to find clues to an elderly doctor's death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722090000 +0000" stop="20250722093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Starlet</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A teenage runaway, intent on becoming a star, has instead wound up in pornographic films. Acting on behalf of the girl's aunt, Friday and Gannon try to find the young "starlet."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722093000 +0000" stop="20250722100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Clan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Sgt. Friday is offered a bribe to assist a gypsy family trying to gain control of the gypsy community.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722100000 +0000" stop="20250722103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Citizen's Arrest - 484</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed search for a suspected child stealer who has escaped custody with the baby after being arrested for shoplifting baby formula. Meanwhile, Reed has to think quickly when he is held at gunpoint while responding to a burglary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722103000 +0000" stop="20250722110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>The Beast</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed have a difficult night ahead of them when they get stuck with an old patrol car that it is riddled with problems. On patrol, they deal with a female car thief, chase down a prowler with a sympathetic story, pull over a motorist who points out an ironic detail, investigate suspicious activity at a warehouse and pursue an armed robbery suspect.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722110000 +0000" stop="20250722120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Santa Cruise</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony enjoy some fun in the sun aboard a Santa Cruise!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722120000 +0000" stop="20250722123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Baby Picture</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver's class holds a "Most Beautiful Baby" contest in which each student is supposed to bring in a baby picture. To make the deadline, June picks out a cute picture of Beaver at the last minute and sends it to Miss Landers, not realizing that the cute picture may cause Beaver embarrassment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722123000 +0000" stop="20250722130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Takes A Walk</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward saves an old pedometer from being thrown out and gives it to Beaver, but not before telling him a story about when he was a kid he would walk 20 miles a day. Taking the story literally, Beaver makes a bet with Whitey that he, too, can walk 20 miles in a day.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722130000 +0000" stop="20250722140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Fanciful Frail</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Things keep going from awful to good grief for poor Ethel Andrews. First she's left at the altar by her fiancee, Bruce Strickland, who also lets her take the blame for a $50,000 securities theft.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722140000 +0000" stop="20250722150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Lemon  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>When Matlock's new neighbor, Les "Ace" Calhoun (Don Knotts), is charged with murdering the used car salesman who sold him a lemon, Matlock takes the case to prove that more than one person had a motive.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722150000 +0000" stop="20250722160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Singin' The Blues</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Luann moonlights as a singer at a nightclub and finds romance with the clubs owner. Her happiness is short-lived when she realizes that the bartender is dealing drugs.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722160000 +0000" stop="20250722170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Ferris Wheel</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Elizabeth has nightmares about being trapped on a Ferris wheel.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722170000 +0000" stop="20250722180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>The Squaw</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A young man is unwelcoming toward the young Indian bride his father brings home.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722180000 +0000" stop="20250722190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Medal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>When Matthew Rush runs afoul the embittered Nagle clan, he and his love, Susan, the Nagle's daughter, fear for their lives and turn to the Cartwrights for help.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722190000 +0000" stop="20250722193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Vision</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>After Mark contracts typhoid fever and has a vision of his dead mother, he no longer seems interested in getting well.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722193000 +0000" stop="20250722200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Lariat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>An old friend of Lucas's returns to town in the company of a shady gambler and is accused of cheating at cards.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722200000 +0000" stop="20250722210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Tracy Sadler Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>David Forest always believed his father to be as he claimed. When Tracy Sadler joins the wagon train his beliefs are altered when he slowly and painfully learns the truth about his father's past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722210000 +0000" stop="20250722220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Kidding</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny is assigned to conduct a school tour of Rampart hospital; the youngsters are highly inquisitive. A veteran mentally reliving a battle is subdued by the paramedics; he turns out to have a brain tumor. A woman gets stuck in a dog door. A famous novelist attempts suicide. A cargo plane crashes in a residential area, hitting a school bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722220000 +0000" stop="20250722223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>A Holy Mess</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E13</episode-num>
    <desc>An AWOL soldier, Nick Gillis, seeks sanctuary in the mess tent, after Father Mulcahy's service. At the same time, a special Sunday brunch is due to be served, following the donation of some eggs to the camp by a grateful farmer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722223000 +0000" stop="20250722230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Tooth Shall Set You Free</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Charles has a serious toothache, but hates the thought of having anything done about it. The doctors suspect prejudice when an inordinate number of black casualties are brought in from a single unit, led by Major Weems.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722230000 +0000" stop="20250722233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Pressure Points</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E15</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter sends for Sidney Freedman when he loses confidence in his surgical abilities, and Winchester loses patience with his bunkmates' sloppiness.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250722233000 +0000" stop="20250723000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Where There's A Will, There's A War</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye goes to help at an aid station, and under heavy shelling he draws up a will, leaving various items to his friends at the 4077th.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723000000 +0000" stop="20250723003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Christmas Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A modern-day Scrooge (businessman Ben Weaver) causes trouble on Christmas Eve.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723003000 +0000" stop="20250723010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Stranger In Town</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E12</episode-num>
    <desc>When a stranger comes to town, Barney and the people of Mayberry grow suspicious when he seems to know too much about them.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723010000 +0000" stop="20250723013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Soup Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E02</episode-num>
    <desc>Granny enters Elly in a soup-making contest, with her own Snider Surprise soup. When Jed finds out Granny cheated, he demands that she pull Elly May out of the contest. But Granny refuses to because this is a way to get Elly a husband. She tricks Jed into believing she got Elly out of the contest and gets him to go hunting, just in time. The men from Savory Soup visit the mansion and are amazed by the beautiful Elly, thinking she’d be a beetle.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723013000 +0000" stop="20250723020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Deciding Vote</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph is busy buying Alice a vacuum while Norton is the deciding vote in the Raccoon election for convention manager.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723020000 +0000" stop="20250723023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Operation Hannibal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and the daughter of a German general try to photograph her father's plans designed to prolong the war.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723023000 +0000" stop="20250723030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>My Favorite Prisoner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>A baroness is asked by Klink to get secrets out of Hogan, and he complies by giving her a British agent with phony invasion plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723030000 +0000" stop="20250723033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Eye Of The Beholder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E06</episode-num>
    <desc>A bandaged young woman awaits the outcome of an experimental treatment that has been administered to her in a last-ditch effort to make her appear normal.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723033000 +0000" stop="20250723043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Surplus Suitor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After a wealthy heiress' uncle is found dead, she is charged with the murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723043500 +0000" stop="20250723050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723050500 +0000" stop="20250723053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Miss Bracegirdle Does Her Duty</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E18</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly maid leaves the parsonage in search of her sister.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723053500 +0000" stop="20250723060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Equalizer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Eldon Marsh sets out to confront the man who stole his wife from him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723060500 +0000" stop="20250723070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>The Color Of Murder</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A witness against a crime boss is murdered just before he can reveal the syndicate's plans.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723070500 +0000" stop="20250723080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave (part 1)</sub-title>
    <desc>"A serial murder targets Cannon as his next victim. At first the homicide wanted to be finally released from his compulsion to kill. Cannon accepted to help him. But Cannon got too involved in the killer's demands."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723080500 +0000" stop="20250723090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Of Fear</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E10</episode-num>
    <desc>While on vacation, Betty meets a doctor who's being stalked by a trio of bikers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723090000 +0000" stop="20250723093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Little Victim</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E22</episode-num>
    <desc>When a nine-month old child is beaten, Friday and Gannon investigate the parents, who are more concerned about their failing relationship than their baby son.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723093000 +0000" stop="20250723100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Squeeze</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E23</episode-num>
    <desc>An ex-con accused of extortion is interrogated. He calmly and smugly insists that he is innocent, but Friday and Gannon have a surprise for him: taped conversations and a voice analysis device.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723100000 +0000" stop="20250723103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Killing Ground</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>During a seemingly routine traffic stop, Malloy and Reed are ambushed and kidnapped by two men who are on the run after a foiled robbery attempt. Their only hope is a young woman who is led to believe that Malloy and Reed killed her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723103000 +0000" stop="20250723110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Nightwatch</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Reed thinks he can haggle another $12.50 off a used car, but malloy warns him that he's pushing his luck. On patrol, they test a suspected drunk driver who hit a light pole, investigate a home invasion that results in a man fatally shooting his ex-son-in-</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723110000 +0000" stop="20250723120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>The Elves And Flip-flop Maker</sub-title>
    <desc>"The classic tale of "The Elves and the Shoemaker" is given a summer Toony twist!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723120000 +0000" stop="20250723123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Borrowed Boat</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Larry and Beaver spend the day at the lake, which is where they encounter two kids who let them borrow their boat. However, little do Larry and Beaver know, the boat is stolen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723123000 +0000" stop="20250723130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Tree</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E08</episode-num>
    <desc>While his class is reciting a poem about trees, Beaver remembers a tree that Ward had given him for his birthday when they lived at their old house. Wanting "his" tree back, Beaver and Larry go to Beaver's old home and promptly dig it up.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723130000 +0000" stop="20250723140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Unwelcome Well</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Powerful and avaricious businessman Jerome Klee has made a fortune in oil and intends to make a lot more. But after crossing a business associate and his wife, he turns up dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723140000 +0000" stop="20250723150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Ambassador: Part 1  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Anthony Stewart is charged with murdering Michael Russell, the husband of the woman with whom he has been sleeping. Although Stewart, a visiting British ambassador, has diplomatic immunity, he refuses to use it and wants to clean his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723150000 +0000" stop="20250723160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Virgil Tibbs: Attorney At Law</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Attorney Virgil Tibbs returns to Sparta and is soon assigned his first case as a defense attorney.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723160000 +0000" stop="20250723170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Elopement</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E16</episode-num>
    <desc>The forestry student who previously visited Waltons Mountain (in "The Competition"") now returns</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723170000 +0000" stop="20250723180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Chesterland</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E08</episode-num>
    <desc>Chester purchases a piece of land when he gets engaged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723180000 +0000" stop="20250723190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>The Stalker</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E08</episode-num>
    <desc>After he shoots and kills an armed robber, Candy helps the man's widow and young son run their farm—while the widow plans her revenge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723190000 +0000" stop="20250723193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Smoke Screen</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Several men are vying for a rancher's daughter's affections. When she is found dead, one of them becomes the prime suspect in her murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723193000 +0000" stop="20250723200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Shotgun Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E29</episode-num>
    <desc>Shotgun man John Beaumont, who Lucas sent to prison, returns with vengeance on his mind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723200000 +0000" stop="20250723210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Alexander Portlass Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Kidnapped, Flint is forced to scout and find a lost Aztec treasure. As some of the men were previously thrown off the wagon train, their unfriendliness is certain unless he can help them find the lost treasure of Montezuma.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723210000 +0000" stop="20250723220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>Prestidigitation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Johnny is assigned to conduct a school tour of Rampart hospital. A veteran mentally reliving a battle is subdued by the paramedics. A woman gets stuck in a dog door. A famous novelist attempts suicide. A cargo plane crashes in a residential area, hitting a school bus.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723220000 +0000" stop="20250723223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Promotion Commotion</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Winchester, Pierce and Hunnicutt find themselves in the sticky position of having to decide which enlisted men to recommend for promotion. For Winchester it could be a matter of life and death.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723223000 +0000" stop="20250723230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Heroes</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye is the golden boy of the world press when he treats a celebrity prizefighter, "Gentleman" Joe Cavanaugh, who has a stroke at the 4077th. Father Mulcahy finds the news hard to take, as Cavanaugh was a hero of his.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723230000 +0000" stop="20250723233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Sons And Bowlers</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E19</episode-num>
    <desc>After losing to the Marines once again, Colonel Potter wishes there was one sport the 4077th were any good at. When Klinger mentions he can bowl, the Colonel decides to have a bowling competition. Unfortunately, he and Klinger are the only two good bowlers in the camp, so BJ and Father Mulcahy are "recruited" to the team.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250723233000 +0000" stop="20250724000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Picture This</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Potter's attempts to assemble the crew for a family portrait are thwarted by a feud between bunkmates Pierce, Hunnicutt and Winchester. Things are not helped by the efforts of Margaret, Klinger and Mulcahy to bring the Swampmen back together.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724000000 +0000" stop="20250724003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Mayberry Goes Hollywood</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E13</episode-num>
    <desc>When a Hollywood film crew decides to use Mayberry as a backdrop for a movie, everyone in town begins to put on airs, risking the small-town charm that attracted the crew in the first place.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724003000 +0000" stop="20250724010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Horse Trader</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E14</episode-num>
    <desc>Ignoring his own advice to Opie, Andy plays fast and loose with the facts when trying to sell the old town cannon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724010000 +0000" stop="20250724013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>Jed Gets The Misery</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Jed is feeling poorly, and the family is worried about him. To make Elly feel better, Jed reveals that he is faking an illness to please Granny. When Drysdale hears of this, he decides to help out, too, and fakes illness as well. When Drysdale’s doctor, Dr. Clyburn, hears of this, he rushes over to the Clampett mansion. Granny mistakes Clyburn as a patient and puts him in bed with Jed and Drysdale.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724013000 +0000" stop="20250724020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Something Fishy</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Norton don't want to take their wives on a Raccoon fishing trip.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724020000 +0000" stop="20250724023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Watch The Trains Go By</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan arranges for Burkhalter's sister to keep Klink occupied, so he can leave camp and blow up a train.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724023000 +0000" stop="20250724030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Klink's Old Flame</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan uses the car of an SS man who's just married Klink's old girlfriend and is honeymooning in Paris, where Hogan needs to pass radios to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724030000 +0000" stop="20250724033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>Nick Of Time</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E07</episode-num>
    <desc>A superstitious newlywed becomes obsessed by a penny fortune-telling machine when he and his new wife are stranded with car trouble.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724033000 +0000" stop="20250724043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Golden Oranges</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E20</episode-num>
    <desc>Mason goes to the dogs when his defense of a murder suspect hinges on a surprise witness—a dog named Hard Tack. It seems as though Hard Tack holds the key to the murder of a developer who planned to bulldoze orange groves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724043500 +0000" stop="20250724050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724050500 +0000" stop="20250724053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>On The Nose</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E20</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman has problems staying away from the race track and it threatens her marriage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724053500 +0000" stop="20250724060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Guest For Breakfast</sub-title>
    <desc>"A marriage about to be broken is saved by a killer."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724060500 +0000" stop="20250724070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Shadow Play</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>The wife of a money man for the mob is killed during a hit-and-run accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724070500 +0000" stop="20250724080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>He Who Digs A Grave: Part 2</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E02</episode-num>
    <desc>A lady journalist is forced to reveal her sources in a murder news or she will go to jail on a contempt charge. She enlist Cannon's service to unravel the murder of a missing excursionist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724080500 +0000" stop="20250724090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Devil's Handmaiden, The</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E11</episode-num>
    <desc>A girl begins to see future fatal accidents while exploring the occult.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724090000 +0000" stop="20250724093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Suicide Attempt</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon learn that a young man has called his mother from Hollywood "to say goodbye." With the help of the man's sister, the two detectives trace the impending suicide to a hotel with more than 1,200 rooms.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724093000 +0000" stop="20250724100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Departure</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Petty theft from drug and hardware stores leads to a group of four teens who are determined to start their own nation on a remote island off the California coast.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724100000 +0000" stop="20250724103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Suspended</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E20</episode-num>
    <desc>While off duty following shooting re-qualification, Reed fires his weapon at a would-be unarmed mugger whose armed accomplish drives off. When the would-be suspect later dies, the unfortunate circumstances leave Reed facing a possible suspension and murder charge.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724103000 +0000" stop="20250724110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>A Fool And His Money</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy wins $10,000 in a contest to name a new woman's shampoo, resulting in a lot of unwanted advice on how to use the money. On patrol, he and reed deal with a loud music complaint that has a romantic sub-context, encounter a sniper perched atop a parki</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724110000 +0000" stop="20250724120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Oh What A Chocolatey Surprise!</sub-title>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724120000 +0000" stop="20250724123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Teacher Comes To Dinner</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver gets a surprise when June invites Miss Landers over for dinner and Larry convinces him that something bad might happen. This leads Beaver to become a nervous wreck as he tries to make sure his parents don't do anything to embarrass him. Meanwhile, Larry charges a quarter to anyone who wants to spy on Miss Landers eating dinner at the Cleavers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724123000 +0000" stop="20250724130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver's Fortune</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver has his fortune read by a machine and becomes convinced nothing but good luck is headed his way. However, he doesn't feel that way when Larry sets it up so that Beaver will have to fight a 5th grader, Sonny Cartwright.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724130000 +0000" stop="20250724140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Dead Ringer</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E26</episode-num>
    <desc>While Mason is representing Barbara Kramer, who accuses Otis Swanson of stealing her father's intellectual property, Swanson hatches a nefarious scheme to discredit Mason and distract him from the case. Mason loses the case; however, Swanson soon turns up dead and Mason now defends Kramer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724140000 +0000" stop="20250724150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>Ambassador, The (part 2)</sub-title>
    <desc>"After Anthony Stewart is nearly killed in a hit and run, Matlock realises that the only way to clear him is to find Shelby Russell, the supposed witness whose claim put Stewart in the hot seat in the first place. He tracks her down via her mother, and tells her that if she doesn't take the stand, her lover will go down for Michael Russell's murder."</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724150000 +0000" stop="20250724160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>Every Man's Family</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Bubba travels to Atlanta to help his nephew after the boy overdoses on drugs. He soon teams up with a street wise cop to take down the drug ring.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724160000 +0000" stop="20250724170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>John's Crossroad</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E17</episode-num>
    <desc>John takes a job away from home to make more money</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724170000 +0000" stop="20250724180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Milly</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Milly Glover decides to marry the first available man in order to support herself and her brother.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724180000 +0000" stop="20250724190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>Meena</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E09</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe and Candy help a timid young woman stand up to her domineering father.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724190000 +0000" stop="20250724193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>Sins Of The Father</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E30</episode-num>
    <desc>After shooting a man in self-defense, Andy Moon turns to Lucas for protection from his vengeful brothers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724193000 +0000" stop="20250724200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Prodigal</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E31</episode-num>
    <desc>To keep his invalid mother happy, an outlaw forces Lucas and Mark to go along with a masquerade that he is the owner of Lucas' ranch.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724200000 +0000" stop="20250724210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Christine Elliot Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Her father on his deathbed, Christine Elliot decides to fulfill his dream of a boys school and joins the wagon train. However, one man is determined to stop her unless he collects his pound of flesh.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724210000 +0000" stop="20250724220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>It's How You Play The Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E19</episode-num>
    <desc>John agrees that the losing baseball team at the fireman's picnic will pay for the picnic. Chet becomes Station 51's only hope when their pitcher breaks his arm. A drunk driver becomes violent after crashing his car; another man is trapped in a car with a tiger. A man with a back problem must be extricated from his waterbed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724220000 +0000" stop="20250724223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>That Darn Kid</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S10E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Klinger buys a goat, with the intention of getting rich by selling its milk. Then the goat eats the 4077th's $22,340 payroll, leaving paymaster Hawkeye holding the bag. Meanwhile, Charles also thinks he can make a killing when he sees an ancient vase.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724223000 +0000" stop="20250724230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Hey, Look Me Over</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Margaret and her nursing staff are about to be inspected by Col. Bucholz. Meanwhile, Kellye is offended that Hawkeye is attracted to nurses besides her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724230000 +0000" stop="20250724233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Trick Or Treatment</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E02</episode-num>
    <desc>It's Halloween at the 4077th, and the staff dons costumes and trades ghost stories. Father Mulcahy discovers a soldier alive that had been pronounced dead.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250724233000 +0000" stop="20250725000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Foreign Affairs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E03</episode-num>
    <desc>The Army tries to get a North Korean pilot to defect, and Charles gets a rude shock when he falls for a French nurse with a Bohemian past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725000000 +0000" stop="20250725003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Those Gossipin' Men</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E15</episode-num>
    <desc>After Andy teases the fairer sex about gossiping, Aunt Bee pulls a prank to prove that men are gossips, too.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725003000 +0000" stop="20250725010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>The Beauty Contest</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E16</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy is chosen to be the sole judge of a local beauty pageant. The entrants include Floyd's niece, the mayor's daughter and Ellie Walker.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725010000 +0000" stop="20250725013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Badger Game</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E04</episode-num>
    <desc>A young girl shows up at the Clampett mansion, claiming she is a friend from back home, Emaline Fetty. The Clampetts welcome her into their house. But it turns out that Emaline is working with someone to blackmail the Clampetts. She takes pictures of her and Jed in a compromising position. Colonel Foxhall, the man who is in control of the caper, and Emaline develop the photos and show them to Jane and Drysdale, who believe something else is going on.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725013000 +0000" stop="20250725020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>Opportunity Knock But</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E32</episode-num>
    <desc>Ralph and Ed play pool with Ralph's boss and Ed gets a job at the bus company.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725020000 +0000" stop="20250725023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>Up In Klink's Room</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E21</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan gets himself sent to the hospital so he can get information from a wounded agent.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725023000 +0000" stop="20250725030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Purchasing Plan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan and crew are ordered to deliver airdropped ammo to the underground.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725030000 +0000" stop="20250725033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>The Trouble With Templeton</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E09</episode-num>
    <desc>An aging actor longing for the good old days is given a sobering glimpse of the past he holds so dear.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725033000 +0000" stop="20250725043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Lawful Lazarus</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E21</episode-num>
    <desc>When a man declared legally dead suddenly re-appears and tries to get a hold of his dying wife's money in order to protect their children's interests, her entire family rallies against him until one of them turns up murdered. "Lazarus" is naturally charged.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725043500 +0000" stop="20250725050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725050500 +0000" stop="20250725053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Return Of The Hero</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A war hero must choose between a new love and the girl he left behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725053500 +0000" stop="20250725060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Right Kind Of A House</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E23</episode-num>
    <desc>A woman schemes to avenge her son's death with a unique plan.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725060500 +0000" stop="20250725070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Overkill</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix gets involved with the case of a serial killer after his friend becomes the latest victim. But not all is as it seems when he discovers the killer may not be responsible for every murder.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725070500 +0000" stop="20250725080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Memo From A Dead Man</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E03</episode-num>
    <desc>A rich lady, Cecilia Lasher, hires Cannon to locate the son her husband abandoned years before. She turns to Cannon after being blackmailed and terrorized.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725080500 +0000" stop="20250725090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Prisoner Of Deceit</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates the death of a reporter who was about to break a huge story.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725090000 +0000" stop="20250725093000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Investigation</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E26</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are screening applicants for the Police Academy. One seems to have all the right qualifications, except that six months are missing from his application.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725093000 +0000" stop="20250725100000 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Gambler</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E27</episode-num>
    <desc>More than $100,000 has been embezzled from an industrial company. An investigation of the employees leads Friday and Gannon to a habitual gambler.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725100000 +0000" stop="20250725103000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Anatomy Of A 415</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E22</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed return a young runaway to his home while responding to a domestic disturbance call at the same address, discovering a dysfunctional situation that appears to be escalating toward a tragic conclusion. In the meantime, they search for a female drug pusher who mistakes a stranger for a fellow pusher, investigate a man attempting to force his way into a truck and encounter a wino riding a stolen bike at night.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725103000 +0000" stop="20250725110000 +0000">
    <title>Adam-12</title>
    <sub-title>Keeping Tabs</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Malloy and Reed are stunned to discover that the driver who led them on a high-speed chase is the son of Sgt. MacDonald, and Malloy takes it upon himself to help his boss figure out why the young man is acting out. In the meantime, they investigate a possible burglary in progress at an apartment building, mediate a dispute at a park over an elderly woman feeding ducks, respond to a call of two armed men fighting over a woman and deal with a wino who is attempting to direct traffic at a busy intersection.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725110000 +0000" stop="20250725120000 +0000">
    <title>Toon In With Me</title>
    <sub-title>Joyful Jolly July</sub-title>
    <desc>"Bill and Toony celebrate Jolly July!"</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725120000 +0000" stop="20250725123000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver Makes A Loan</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E11</episode-num>
    <desc>Ward loans Beaver 25 cents but gives him a dollar, expecting 75 cents as change. However, Larry manages to convince Beaver to loan him the 75 cents. When Larry doesn't pay him back when he said he was going to, a feud erupts.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725123000 +0000" stop="20250725130000 +0000">
    <title>Leave It to Beaver</title>
    <sub-title>Beaver The Magician</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E12</episode-num>
    <desc>Beaver buys a common magic trick but is disappointed by everyone's "that's nice" reaction. He gets a totally different reaction out of Bengie, however, when Larry and Beaver convince him that Beaver has been turned into a rock.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725130000 +0000" stop="20250725140000 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Misguided Model</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S09E27</episode-num>
    <desc>After he accidentally kills his friend's attacker—and she has him dispose of the body without alerting the authorities—a guilt-stricken ex-boxer decides to report the incident to Mason.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725140000 +0000" stop="20250725150000 +0000">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <sub-title>The Mistress  (s3, ep)</sub-title>
    <desc>Matlock agrees to defend Laura McCord after she's charged with murdering her husband, David, in a jealous rage. Matlock and Julie soon realize that David's lover is the key to the case, but she seems to have disappeared.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725150000 +0000" stop="20250725160000 +0000">
    <title>In the Heat of the Night</title>
    <sub-title>A Baby Called Rocket</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>A neglected baby stirs maternal feelings in Luann.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725160000 +0000" stop="20250725170000 +0000">
    <title>The Waltons</title>
    <sub-title>The Career Girl</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Erin graduates from high school still having no direction for her life</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725170000 +0000" stop="20250725180000 +0000">
    <title>Gunsmoke</title>
    <sub-title>Indian Ford</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S07E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Matt helps an Indian-hating officer find a white girl, hoping the search will not end in violence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725180000 +0000" stop="20250725190000 +0000">
    <title>Bonanza</title>
    <sub-title>A Darker Shadow</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Joe's friend, Wade Turner, is struck a devastating blow when he develops a brain tumor that afflicts him a paralyzing sensitivity to bright light and will soon render him blind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725190000 +0000" stop="20250725193000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Fourflusher</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E32</episode-num>
    <desc>A sharecropper enters his colt in a horse race, hoping to win enough money to buy his farm from the owner, who has bet on Mark McCain's entry.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725193000 +0000" stop="20250725200000 +0000">
    <title>The Rifleman</title>
    <sub-title>The Jailbird</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E33</episode-num>
    <desc>When Lucas hires an ex-con as a ranch hand, the man is the first one under suspicion when a robbery and murder occur in the area.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725200000 +0000" stop="20250725210000 +0000">
    <title>Wagon Train</title>
    <sub-title>The Joshua Gilliam Story</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E25</episode-num>
    <desc>Bill and the Major find a man lying hurt, and bring him into the wagon train. When he meets an innocent woman in the group who has an inheritance waiting for her, he shows other skills besides being just a schoolteacher—and her mother is wary.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725210000 +0000" stop="20250725220000 +0000">
    <title>Emergency!</title>
    <sub-title>The Mouse</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E20</episode-num>
    <desc>An elderly man is trapped in his burning house. Chet becomes obsessed with ridding the station of an uninvited guest. Paramedics and doctors treat a man who suffers repeated cardiac arrests. Dixie comforts the husband of an elderly patient. Roy and John help break up a fight. Several crises occur at an apartment house hit by a jet fighter.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725220000 +0000" stop="20250725223000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>The Joker Is Wild</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Tired of reminders about Trapper John's skill as a practical joker, B.J. bets Hawkeye he can prank everyone present.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725223000 +0000" stop="20250725230000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Who Knew?</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye volunteers to deliver the eulogy for a dead nurse that he briefly dated, and belatedly discovers her deep feelings for him.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725230000 +0000" stop="20250725233000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Bombshells</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E06</episode-num>
    <desc>Posing the theory that people will believe in anything, Charles and Hawkeye start a rumor that Marilyn Monroe plans to visit the 4077th, which gets everyone excited. Meanwhile, B.J. feels responsible when he's unable to rescue a wounded soldier, and is less than impressed when he is presented with a Bronze Star.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250725233000 +0000" stop="20250726000000 +0000">
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <sub-title>Settling Debts</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S11E07</episode-num>
    <desc>Hawkeye and the crew surprise Colonel Potter with a party to commemorate Mildred's final payment on the couple's mortgage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726000000 +0000" stop="20250726003000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Alcohol And Old Lace</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E17</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy and Barney, on a spree of destroying illegal stills, are surprised when a trail leads them to two spinster sisters.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726003000 +0000" stop="20250726010000 +0000">
    <title>The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <sub-title>Andy, The Marriage Counselor</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S01E18</episode-num>
    <desc>Andy counsels a Mayberry couple who are constantly bickering with each other.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726010000 +0000" stop="20250726013000 +0000">
    <title>The Beverly Hillbillies</title>
    <sub-title>The Badgers Return</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E05</episode-num>
    <desc>Drysdale is intent on getting the Clampetts to identify Colonel Foxhall and Emaline Fetty as dangerous criminals. Emaline is in hiding, but visits Jethro, tricking him into helping her hide from the police. The Clampetts mistake the officer that brought Foxhall as a criminal, and Foxhall gets away from the man holding him and hides in the Clampett mansion.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726013000 +0000" stop="20250726020000 +0000">
    <title>The Honeymooners</title>
    <sub-title>The Man From Space</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E14</episode-num>
    <desc>When the Kramdens and Nortons enter a Raccoon costume contest a feud arises between Ralph and Ed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726020000 +0000" stop="20250726023000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Witness</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E23</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan faces a startling development: His captors are sending him to America to demand surrender—with a super weapon supposedly supplied by the Russians.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726023000 +0000" stop="20250726030000 +0000">
    <title>Hogan's Heroes</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Dish</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S04E24</episode-num>
    <desc>Hogan must destroy an anti-aircraft defense system designed by a beautiful English woman who may have defected to Germany.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726030000 +0000" stop="20250726033000 +0000">
    <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
    <sub-title>A Most Unusual Camera</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>Small-time crooks end up with a camera that takes photos of events five minutes into the future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726033000 +0000" stop="20250726043500 +0000">
    <title>Perry Mason</title>
    <sub-title>The Case Of The Velvet Claws</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E22</episode-num>
    <desc>A photographer snaps a picture of politico Harrison Burke and a married woman, Eva Belter, as they leave a local gambling establishment. Eva goes to Mason for help and tells him that a scandal sheet called "Spicy Bits" is blackmailing her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726043500 +0000" stop="20250726050500 +0000">
    <title>Dragnet</title>
    <sub-title>The Big Problem</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E28</episode-num>
    <desc>Friday and Gannon are on a mission to bolster community relations when a young and slightly militant black man barricades himself in his apartment rather than submit to a traffic warrant.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726050500 +0000" stop="20250726053500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>The Foghorn</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E24</episode-num>
    <desc>A beautiful woman meets and falls in love with a stranger at her engagement party.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726053500 +0000" stop="20250726060500 +0000">
    <title>Alfred Hitchcock Presents</title>
    <sub-title>Flight To The East</sub-title>
    <desc>"A reporter goes from star to villain and then back to "star.""</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726060500 +0000" stop="20250726070500 +0000">
    <title>Mannix</title>
    <sub-title>Dark So Early, Dark So Long</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S05E01</episode-num>
    <desc>Mannix sets out to clear an old school friend of murder. The problem is that she, being an alcoholic, can't remember what she was doing when the murder occurred.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726070500 +0000" stop="20250726080500 +0000">
    <title>Cannon</title>
    <sub-title>Hounds Of Hell</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S03E04</episode-num>
    <desc>Frank travels to a small ranching town to help out a writer friend charged with a double murder. Frank's only clue is a cryptic note left by the man's wife.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726080500 +0000" stop="20250726090000 +0000">
    <title>Barnaby Jones</title>
    <sub-title>Deadly Homecoming</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S06E13</episode-num>
    <desc>A rancher believes his son's death was not an accident.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="metv" start="20250726090000 +0000" stop="20250726093000 +0000">
    <title>Petticoat Junction</title>
    <sub-title>Kate's Bachelor Butter</sub-title>
    <episode-num system="onscreen">S02E10</episode-num>
    <desc>When Charley and Floyd stop the Cannonball to pick apples for Kate's bachelor butter recipe, a passenger and food salesman, Jack Crandall, is shocked.</desc>
  </programme>
</tv>
